Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Get back here!
Give that chart back,
you damn woman thief!
W-What?!
A person fell from the sky!
Now I'm safe!
That was a pretty neat experience I had!
"A Terrifying, Mysterious Power!
Captain Buggy, the Clown Pirate!"
I'm starving...
B-Boss! You came to save me!
Wha--?
Who're you?
Sorry, but they're all yours now!
Hey! The girl got away!
That's okay!
Her boss is still here!
Ah! Tryin' to cover
for your crony, huh?!
Say, is there any place to eat around here?
Quit screwin' around, kid!
Don't touch my treasure!
--Bastard!
Wonder if they killed that guy...
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Wow!
You're really strong!
You beat people with sabers barehanded!
Hey! You're that... who?
I'm a thief who steals from pirates!
The name's Nami!
Hey, wanna team up with me?!
No. I don't feel like
teaming up with you.
H-Hold on!
Wait, I said!
Oh. I just remembered!
I'm starving...
Shall I treat you to some food?
Really?!
Y-Yeah...
They still haven't caught the thief?!
T-They should be pursuing her
as we speak, Captain Buggy! Yes!
How did the map get stolen
so easily in the first place?! Huh?!
Just when we're about to enter
the Grand Line and go on a rampage!
A-Actually, the shack was unlocked,
so it was easy to take for foes...
What did you say?!
As I said, it was easy to take for foes...
Who has a fake nose?!
Do you find this nose funny?!
Just like a fake nose?!
You have it all wrong!
It's huge and all red?!
Help!
--H-Here it comes...
--T-The Devil Fruit power...
Who am I?
C-Captain Buggy...
What happens if someone defies me?
A flashy death awaits them...
Please forgive me!
I'll never say it again!
I'll overlook your verbal slip-up
and forgive you just this once.
Now get that map back! Screw up...
and you know what happens.
Yes, Captain Buggy!
Yum!
Do you live alone in this house?
I don't live in this town.
Everyone here ran away because of Buggy.
--Then you're a sneak thief.
--How rude!
I'm a thief who only
steals from pirates!
Don't compare me
to scumbag sneak thieves!
But a thief's a thief.
My goal is to earn 100 million Berries,
no matter what it takes.
What do you need that much for?
It's a secret!
But with a map of the Grand Line,
100 million is a real possibility!
A map? Are you a navigator?!
Much more skilled than
your average navigator!
Oh, that's perfect!
Do you wanna be our navigator?!
Really?
Yeah! Our new pirate crew member!
No!
So you're a pirate?
Yeah. I swore to the person
who gave me this straw hat...
that I'd gather a crew
and become a pirate!
There's nothing I hate more
in this world than pirates!
I only like money and tangerines!
Hey. Be our navigator.
I said no.
No?
--Hey! You find her?!
--Can't find her anywhere!
Where'd that girl thief go?!
We're in trouble if
we don't get that chart back!
I gotta do something about them...
Well, I might consider it
if you agree to certain conditions!
Really?! I'll do anything!
I want you to come with
me to see Buggy the pirate.
But!
Why am I tied up?
It's just rope.
Is there a problem?
Oh well! I was hoping to
meet other pirates! Let's go!
Hold on, now!
What?!
The thief got away?!
Please forgive us, Captain!
All three of you are pathetic!
Die flashily!
Captain Buggy!
What is it?!
That thief from earlier
came back on her own!
What?!
That's them!
She's the one who stole the chart!
Ow!
I've captured the thief,
Captain Buggy the Clown!
Here's your chart back!
I appreciate it.
But why the change of heart?
My boss and I had a fight!
I'm fed up with him!
Please let me join your crew!
C-Captain Buggy is angry!
He's gonna use his Devil Fruit power!
Devil?
Fed up, huh?
You're a flashily amusing girl!
I like you!
You can join my crew!
Infiltration successful!
Pirates are so dumb
and easy to manipulate!
Why am I in a cage?
I feel great today!
Girl! What name do you go by?
Nami!
Alright! Let's hold a
welcome party for Nami here!
Celebrate flashily!
What's wrong?!
This party's in your honor!
Eat up!
Yes! Thank you!
I'll just keep my eyes peeled for
a chance to take the chart back.
And maybe I'll swipe all of
Buggy's treasure too, while I'm at it!
I... wanna eat, too!
Dammit!
This is flashily great!
Men! Prepare
a Special Buggy Ball!
All set, sir!
W-What's about to happen?
Observe the might of the Buggy Ball!
Light it.
What's that explosion?
One of Buggy-sama's
beloved Buggy Balls!
Buggy Balls?!
Truly flashy!
With Buggy Balls and Devil Fruit powers,
I can conquer the Grand Line!
Right, Nami?!
Y-Yes! Of course!
Eh?!
I'm the one who's
gonna rule the Grand Line!
What?
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
You idiot!
I see why you're sick of him, Nami!
Yeah! He takes the world too lightly...
and misunderstands everything!
I couldn't put up with it anymore...
Naturally!
In that case, I'll give you a
Buggy Ball to blow away your old boss!
It'll also serve to prove
your loyalty to me. Do it!
No, that's okay!
C'mon, this is a welcoming party!
Let's have fun!
Do it.
This is my style of welcoming party.
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
If I don't shoot, I'll be killed!
But if I do shoot, I'll wind
up no better than pirates!
Alright! Light it flashily!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Nami! Don't wimp out on me now!
What's the matter?
Your hands are shaking!
That's what happens when you take
on pirates with half-assed resolve.
Resolve to do what?!
To kill people like it's nothing?!
Is that a pirate's resolve?!
No!
The resolve to put your own life on the line!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Hey, new chick!
Quit bein' a tease!
This is how you light it!
What the--?! What the--?!
Crap! I didn't mean to--
Nami! What is the meaning of this?!
I'm sorry!
What?! Apologizing won't fix things!
Huh? Now you're saving me?
Don't be stupid!
I only did it because of the situation!
I just didn't want to wind up
like these inhuman pirates!
Oh, the situation!
Pirates took the life
of a person dear to me!
As if I'd ever be one!
Oh, so that's why... Huh?
It's lit!
Keep your ridicule to a minimum, girl!
Kill her flashily!
Yahoo!
Water! Water! Water! Water!
Not good!
You're...
Behind you!
Die flashily!
Hey, now...
How many of you are
taking on one girl at once?
Zoro!
You hurt?
Are you hurt?
N-No, I'm fine...
Whew, what a relief!
How'd you find us?
Hurry and get me outta here!
What do you keep playing around for?
First some bird runs off with you,
and now you're inside a cage?
It's pretty interesting, actually.
"Zoro"?
T-That's what he just called him, right?
The crew member he mentioned...
was Pirate Hunter Zoro?
What's going on?!
So you're Zoro?
What do you want? Are you here
to take my head or something?
Nope. Not interested.
I gave up pirate-hunting.
I'm interested, though!
Killing you will increase my name.
I wouldn't try it. You'll die.
Oh? That so?
Guess words aren't enough for you...
--Get 'im, Captain!
--Captain Buggy!
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Die flashily!
He had no resistance to him at all...
Whoa! He's weak!
No way...
What's with them?
H-Huh? Their captain's been killed...
But they're laughing!
Hey! What's so damn funny?!
Zoro!
What's that arm?!
What... the hell?!
The Chop-Chop Fruit...
That's the name of
the Devil Fruit I ate!
I'm a chop-chop person who can't be cut!
His body reattached itself!
I thought the
Devil Fruits were only a rumor!
A chop-chop guy?!
You mean he's a monster?!
"Rubber Person"
I didn't hit any vital spots,
but that's a pretty
serious wound! I win!
You're too much, Captain!
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Crap! The tables have turned!
If we don't do something quick,
me and these two guys are dead!
That one hurt a bit...
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Stabbing him from behind is unfair,
Big Nose!
Y-You idiot!
Don't call him that!
Who's... got a big nose?!
Luffy!
Buggy!
I will kick your ass!
Kick my ass? You're a real riot!
All three of you are
gonna die here, you know!
How should I have my ass
kicked in this situation?!
It's no use... It's all over...
I refuse to die!
Run! Zoro!
What?!
Wait! He came here to save you!
What're you gonna do?!
Understood.
Nothing makes sense anymore!
This is why I hate pirates!
Impudent fool!
As if I'd let you escape!
Fool!
Your Three-Sword Style has no effect on--
Hey! Listen when
people are talking!
Oh, crap!
The cannon's pointed this way!
--Hey! Light it!
--Eh?!
--Hurry!
--R-right!
Wait, wait, wait! There's still
a Special Buggy Ball in there!
You lit it!
Wait! No! Stop! Stop!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Hey, Zoro! Are you okay?!
Yeah, don't worry. I'm better now.
Great!
What're you talking about?!
You can't possibly be better!
Really?
Oh no! What's that?!
--What an unfriendly dog!
--I'm not referring to that!
Oh!
There's a polar bear on top of a lion!
They followed you guys here!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Desperate Situation!
Beast Tamer Mohji vs. Luffy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!