Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Crunch his head for sure this time!
Gum-Gum...
...Hammer!
Join our crew, Nami! Okay?!
How about we team up
for our common goal?
Alright! Fire!
"Epic Showdown!
Swordsman Zoro vs. Acrobat Cabaji!"
I'm here to kick your ass,
just like I promised!
Straw Hat?!
How dare you just come waltzing
back here, to Captain Buggy!
Listen! All I want is the
map and the treasure!
Yeah, I know.
Young'uns... Why are you here?!
Stay out of this. You're outsiders!
This is my fight! I will protect my town!
I don't need your meddling!
What the hell?!
Why did you attack the mayor?!
He was in the way!
Good thinking.
No doubt this old man
plans to die otherwise.
This is for the best.
Don't be crazy!
There were plenty of other
ways you could've done it!
Alright, here goes...
Big Nose!
That's the one thing you shouldn't say!
Damn you, you flashy idiot!
How dare you...
Flashily fire the Buggy Ball!
Why'd you say that?! You idiot!
Hey, Luffy! Run!
That...
Time to blow up!
...won't work on me!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
What is he?!
Don't tell me the Buggy Ball...
He bounced it back!
Say something beforehand, geez!
It's coming this way!
Alright! Now there's fewer enemies!
What the heck are you?!
You really know how
to freak people out...
I knew something was weird from
the time you fought that lion!
No human can do that! Explain yourself!
What was that balloon-inflatey
thing you just did?!
The Gum-Gum Balloon!
I'm asking what that is!
What are you, a monster?!
How dare you flashily try to do me in...
He used his henchmen as shields!
What happened here?!
You!
Heya!
The Straw Hat guy!
C-C-Captain Buggy! Be careful!
He has Devil Fruit powers too!
He's a rubber person!
What?!
Rubber person?!
Yeah! See!
A Devil Fruit...
That explains how he
bounced a Buggy Ball back.
This is the greatest insult we've
had since we hoisted our flag...
...Captain.
Oh, Cabaji! I'm so
angry I can't even fart...
Cabaji! What the hell
did you do to Richie?!
This cat? I used it as a shield,
to keep my clothes from getting dirty.
Richie!
Hey, Richie! Say something!
Are you all right?!
Richie!
Damn you, you bastard!
Out of the way!
No, you move!
Captain Buggy.
Yes, Cabaji?
Please leave this to me.
Alright! Show them your acrobat show!
I, Acrobat Cabaji, Chief of Staff,
take on Captain Buggy's anger!
I'll clash swords with you.
It's an honor, Roronoa Zoro...
To think I would get to slay you,
as a swordsman myself.
Hey, Zoro! You should
really rest! I'll handle this!
Stay out of this!
That's the stab wound the
captain gave him. The fool...
Acrobat Technique: Old Man Arsonist!
What's wrong? I'm sure I
didn't kick you that hard...
He fights dirty, going
after his injury like that!
Acrobat Technique:
Murder at the Steam Bath!
Acrobat technique, my ass!
That's just an ordinary cloud of dust!
He did it again!
What's wrong? A grown man
moaning is disgraceful!
Well? Now do you see
how foolish it was...
...to make an enemy
of the Buggy Pirates?
He's crazy to fight while
so seriously injured!
He's hurt so bad it's almost
mystifying that he's still alive!
Why're you just
standing there watching?!
He's gonna get killed!
Roronoa Zoro...
...is defeated!
Annoying bastard!
Is poking my wound...
...that much fun?!
Oww!
W-Why didn't you dodge that?!
Is that enough of a handicap for you?
Now I'll show you the difference
in level between you and me!
So cool!
So this is Roronoa Zoro, huh?
You think you can mock me...
My swords aim to be
the world's greatest!
I can't lose even once to anyone
who calls himself a swordsman!
I see...
A strong resolve keeps you going.
But never fear.
Wounds as bad as yours will be
more than enough of an excuse...
...for losing to me!
The hell with that...
If I lose to someone like
you with such light injuries,
I won't have much of
a bright future ahead of me!
Why, you--!
Do it, Zoro!
I can't go along with this!
You pirates can injure
yourselves for all I care!
It doesn't matter to me
whether you guys win or lose!
I'm gonna use this chance to swipe
their treasure and get outta here!
Let's team up again if
we ever get the chance!
See ya! Good luck with the fight!
Yeah! Thanks!
Taste my ultimate acrobatic move!
Acrobat Technique:
The Dance of 100 Kamikaze Tops!
Those aren't normal guys,
that Luffy and Zoro!
Nothing good'll come from
being involved with them!
Here we are!
Now to steal their treasure
and chart and get out of here!
Acrobat Technique:
A Hike in the Mountains!
Fireworks in the Cool Summer Breeze!
Whoa, he's high up!
Sting of the Unicycle!
Ground-hugging Chop-Chop Cannon!
Cabaji! I'll hold Zoro
down! Finish him off!
As you wish!
Damn you guys!
Luffy!
D-Damn you!
Stay out of Zoro's fight!
Wow! Look at all this!
And it's all mine!
What're you doin' with
our treasure, now?!
Crap! He woke up!
By Captain Buggy's orders,
anyone who gets near here is to be--
Huh? I'm all out?!
It hurts!
W-What?! What's wrong?
My chest suddenly started to hurt...
What?! Your chest?!
Hah!
Yes!
The chart of the Grand Line!
I can defeat you easily enough,
even without my captain's help!
Enough... I'm tired...
Finally given up, have you?
Though I must say, I'm impressed
you could fight with such injuries.
I meant I'm tired...
of your crappy-ass acrobatics!
Then I'll finish you off...
...with my real sword skills!
Die!
Oni...
...Giri!
Cabaji!
We, the Buggy Pirates,
beaten by mere sneak thieves...
We ain't sneak thieves...
We're pirates!
Luffy! I'm goin' to sleep now!
Right! I'll handle the rest!
I'd expect no less from the
notorious Buggy Pirates' treasure...
Hauling it is exhausting!
But with this much treasure--!
Anyways, I gotta get
off this island ASAP!
You guys are pirates?!
Yeah! We're going to the Grand Line!
That's no simple voyage nameless
bums like you can handle, dimwit!
What're you gonna do in
the Grand Line, anyway?!
Go on a sightseeing trip or something?
Become King of the Pirates!
Get real, you flashy idiot!
You, King of the Pirates?!
Would that make me God, then?!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates
and obtain this world's treasures!
Quit your dreaming!
You're annoying.
Just bring it on already!
Seeing that straw hat of yours
brings back memories of him...
...and irritates me!
Memories of that damn
cheeky red-haired man!
Red-haired?!
Red-haired... Does that
mean you know Shanks?!
Huh? Yeah, but why?
Where is he now?!
Dunno! Maybe I know where
he is, or maybe I don't!
What're you talking about?
Are you stupid or something?
Not as much as you!
I ain't nice enough of a guy to
just tell you what you wanna know!
Then I'll make you tell me!
I'll kill you before that ever happens!
I doubt rubber can
bounce back blades...
Nope, it can't!
Chop-Chop Rice Cracker!
Can't move in midair, can you?!
Can too!
Oh, quite interesting!
You, too!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Those are interesting abilities,
but they leave you wide open!
I'm gonna carve you up!
Gum-Gum...
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
...Sickle!
Not good enough, Gum-Gum!
Damn, you keep breaking into pieces!
W-What a fight...
It's almost like I'm dreaming...
H-Hey, you see that?!
You dumbass!
Keep pretending to be knocked out!
Get caught up in that, and you'd
never have enough lives to survive!
Chop-Chop Cannon!
Separate!
Well?! Now do you see, runt?!
You bastard!
Oh? Was I not supposed to
scratch your face or something?
How dare you...
How dare you damage this hat!
Huh?
This is my treasure!
Whoever damages this
hat absolutely must pay!
Yeah. I swore to the person
who gave me this straw hat...
...that I'd gather a crew
and become a pirate!
I thought there was nothing
that could faze him...
To think he could get this upset...
It would seem that
hat has a history to it.
That's right!
Is it that important of a hat?
If so...
...then protect it better!
Shanks!
Your arm!
I'll leave this hat with you.
It's dear to me.
Take good care of it!
Come bring it back to me someday!
Once you've become a great pirate!
That's our promise, Luffy!
How is this old,
tattered hat a treasure?
Treasure refers to sparkly gold,
silver, and jewels...
...that display their owner's grandeur!
You call this filthy
straw hat a treasure?
Cut the crap!
That's the hat Shanks
and I swore over!
What?!
Meaning this is Shanks' hat?!
No wonder it seemed familiar!
He always wore this by my side!
You and Shanks sailed
on the same ship?!
Yeah, back when we
were pirates-in-training.
We were comrades.
That damn detestable,
red-haired bastard!
Shanks is a great man!
You, his comrade?!
Don't compare yourself to him!
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
Hi, I'm Buggy!
Never say you and Shanks
are comrades ever again!
I can say whatever
I want about Shanks!
Tell me! What happened
between you and Shanks?
Damn it! How dare you
tear up my treasure!
Do you wanna know that badly?
He's the one person
I absolutely can't forgive!
I'll curse him for the rest of my life!
I'll never forgive him!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Get ready, Buggy!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Yeah! Beat him!
You'll pay for damaging the hat
me and Shanks swore over!
Okay, get going, Luffy!
Beat him up to protect my treasure!
Huh? That doesn't sound right...
It's basically the same thing!
Don't sweat it!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Who is the Victor?
Devil Fruit Power Showdown!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!