stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"The First Patient! The Untold
Story Of The Rumble Ball"
I... I can't breathe...
Stop it... Lashes...!
Everyone! Wake up! Wake up!
Good morning, Nami-san...
Give me your passionate morning kiss...
You bastard! Don't give me
that disgusting face!
That's what I wanna say!
--You bastard!
--It's an island! We can see an island!
Huh? An island?
An island!
Where's the island?
Look over there!
Whoa... Whoa!
Doesn't this island have monsters?
I prefer big and strong ones.
Don't step on it. Don't step on it.
Don't step on my life...
There doesn't seem to
be anything suspicious,
and it looks like this is a small island, too...
Look, Nami-san!
This is perfect for making
nonperishable food!
It looks like this island has tons of these!
I see... Seems like it'd be a good idea to
collect them and load them on the ship.
Looks like there're other plants
that can be used for food.
This island seems quite
enjoyable for a cook.
Okay. Then please go look for things
that can be used for food, Sanji-kun.
The remaining four of you will do this.
--Huh?
--What is it?
--Drawing lots?
The three who draw the shortest lots
will spend all day collecting these.
The one who draws the longest one
will stay here and watch the ship.
Why are you the one giving us orders?
Right. Normally the captain
would give orders, but...
Oh, hey... they're all short.
Hey, why'd you draw three of them?
Isn't the one who grabs
the most the winner?
Do you think this ship has a
captain who can give orders?
No, it doesn't.
Am I that great?
Obviously you aren't!
I drew the longest one.
So I'll be watching the ship?
Yes. Please look after the ship, Chopper.
Hurry up! Hurry up! Let's go already!
Let's go get fruits already!
You're coming too, right, Nami?
No, I'll spend all day today
measuring this island.
I'd like to put it on the sea chart.
I can't wait to put my skills in practice!
See you later! Be careful! Have fun!
Look after the ship, okay?!
The one who collects the most will win!
Hmm... what a pain...
Why do we have to take
orders from that woman?
Now, here I go! Measuring! Measuring!
Oh... How lively Nami-san is when she's
carrying measuring tools on her back!
Nami-san! You're lovely!
--Mellorine! Mellorine!
--Stop talking stupid and come already!
I'll be all by myself today.
When no one's around, the ship
looks really big somehow.
Listen, guys! I'll be the great
Captain Chopper from today!
Hey, everyone! Look this way!
Luffy! Don't eat others' food!
Usopp! Work harder!
Sanji! Prepare special dishes for me!
Hurray, Captain Chopper! Hurray!
How long have you been there?!
Being so quiet... How sneaky...!
L-Look! I still don't trust you!
You were a Baroque Works Officer Agent.
You were a rogue, and mean, and stupid!
I won't accept you! Even if
Luffy accepts you as a friend,
there's no way... I'd talk to you!
Her special skill is assassination,
right? I hear she's very smart, too.
I have to be careful.
Ah...
That's right, I went to bed after I
made ten Rumble Balls last night...
I'll spend all day making another ten!
Rumble Balls... I have to
make them when I can,
since you never know when
you'll run into enemies...
But...
...this brings back memories of the
time the Rumble Ball was created...
Doctorine won't notice if these get
reduced little by little, will she?
She always mixes this and this, right?
Hm? Was it this one?
She didn't put this one, did she?
Chopper! Do you know where
my medicine bottles are?
They have important medicine in them.
They're all rare and valuable medicines.
You wouldn't be playing
with them, would you?
Chopper!
I got a good scolding
from Doctorine then...
I wonder how Doctorine is doing now...
Maybe I'll write her a letter.
--Hm?
--They're called... Rumble Balls?
Are you trying to uncover
the secret of the Rumble Ball
and then assassinate me?!
Not a chance. I won't be taken
down by someone like you!
Rumble...!
Guard Point!
--Ow!
--Heavy Point!
Jumping Point!
Horn Point!
You see the power of the Rumble Ball?!
There's more where that came from!
I can see through your weak point!
Brain Point...! Scope!
Weak point...! Weak point...!
Where's her weak point?!
What's funny?
You don't have to look so fierce, right?
S... Stop it! Stop it! Stop tickling me!
--Stop it!
--How cute you are!
I like you.
C... Cute...?
Give me a break! Even if you like me,
that doesn't make me happy or anything!
There's no way I'm happy!
You jerk! You jerk! You jerk...!
--Well, then... shall we go?
--What?
--The water's gone, right?
--Ah...
I'd like to drink coffee... before I read.
What's the matter? You go draw
the water... since you spilt it.
Ah, yes.
Geez... How could I feel like
working on such a fine day?
Whoa! There sure are a lot of them!
Ahh!
He got me!
That time, I thought... "This is it...
This is the end of Captain Usopp...!"
I was attacked by a huge condor...
and I couldn't breathe...
Sorry... Because of that, I couldn't
get even a single fruit. I'm sorry.
That's okay. Don't worry about me...
Ugh...! I'm dead.
Why do I have to take orders from
that woman?! Seriously, how irritating!
Three-Sword Style...
...Dragon... Twister!
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
The contour line should be like this...
The right ridgeline is 42 degrees, maybe?
The love fever is also 42 degrees.
Please measure the height of
my feeling towards you, too!
--You're in my way! Move!
--Ow!
I'm the one who's going to draw
the water... Why is she coming, too?
What a fine day!
What?!
S-So what?!
Nothing, really. It's a fine day. That's all.
I just... wanted to take a walk somehow.
I haven't felt this way for quite a long time.
I was constrained every day for a
long time, so... I never smiled, either...
--Ah!
--Hm?
Wow...
Water!
If I remember correctly, you said you've
always been alone since you were eight.
Yes... By following pirates,
I barely survived...
Tell me... about this Doctorine person...
What?
You were talking about that person earlier.
She's a doctor, right? Is she your teacher?
Y-Yeah, but Doctorine is someone
whom I'm deeply indebted to.
People call her Dr. Kureha.
Dr. Kureha... What kind of person is she?
She really loves alcohol. Although
she's a woman, she's like a pirate...
And she's like a pirate, but she is a doctor.
I studied to be a doctor
under Doctorine for six years.
"After mixing these three kinds
of herbs, grind them well"...
Chopper! Chopper!
Urk!
Did you read the medical book?
The 500 pages that I told you to read?
Humph! You were playing
with the medicine again?
I wasn't playing!
That's the same as playing.
B-But...
But what?
I... I've been studying for three years now.
I've also read 200 medical books.
Let me compound the medicine...
It's still 100 years too early!
I-I've memorized all 200
books that I read! It's true!
I even memorized "The Seventh
Principle" by Dr. Alexandra,
which you said was the most difficult!
The TaboTabo bacteria start
dividing on the 7th day of culturing.
After showing the sign of overreaction
mentioned on page 1,254,
chapter 7, section 2...
Humph... So... wha...
Doctorine!
Are you okay?
Looks like I got a febrile disease
from the patient I saw the other day...
This is a terrible fever!
Chopper, if you talk big like that,
try putting your medical skill to the test.
What?
I'll be your first patient.
I won't give you any advice.
If you fail, I'll die...
Learn by experience that
medicine is a serious challenge
where patients' lives are at stake.
Will the blue-nose reindeer be
able to win in a serious challenge?
There's no mistake! This is
the pathogen of the Mondolin.
What works for this
pathogen is... let's see...
This is it!
Doctorine...
Don't die... Please...
Let's see...
You're not gonna ask what
medicine I compounded?
You think there're patients out there
who'd have enough composure
to ask doctors questions about everything?
If patients don't trust their doctors,
they won't recover from the sickness.
How is it? Do you feel a little better?
You dummy. No medicine
would work that quick.
Let me sleep a little.
Chopper!
Not too bad, considering
your lack of experience...
It was the first time that
Doctorine praised me.
It was the only time during those six years.
Instead of acknowledging me,
she left her life in my hands.
That's Doctorine.
That's the kind of person she is.
I won't forget... Some day, I'll become
a doctor that'll surprise even her.
Oh, no... I said too much...
Huh?!
We'd better get going or the sun will set...
I wish I had someone that I could
write a letter to... like you do...
What...? Ah!
This is heavy...
Heavy...
So... why weren't you able
to get even a single fruit?!
That's a good question...
That time, I thought...
A huge king condor attacked me...!
Sorry, everyone... I tried
risking my life to get fruits,
but I couldn't... I'm dead.
On the contrary, Zoro did a great job!
Keep up that momentum and stay
up all night tonight to get more!
Oh... How lovely Nami-san is, even
when she efficiently gives orders...!
Shut up! You lecher cook!
Wanna fight?! Moss Head!
I was just kidding.
But hey, today was the first
peaceful day in a while!
What about you? What did you
do all day today on the ship?
Me? Nothing special...
But it was a pretty good day.
Which direction should I run towards
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
I took the helm and opened the
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
I aimed for the sky and sought out
my dreams, though at times I got lost
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
I discovered the wonderful person in me
With just a bit of courage,
I gained something grand
Now's the time for my "wish"
to become my "pledge"
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
I'll put all my feelings
in a brand new wind now
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
I'll chase after you
wherever you go, Shining ray
Say, Sanji-kun... Please! There's
something I want you to buy for me.
Anything for you... Uhm...
these papers cost 4.8 million Berries!
Well, I wouldn't have that
much money, though...
--Don't be so cold.
--That's right. We do have money.
Oh, yeah. In exchange for this
guy with a bounty on his head...
What?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Uprising of the Navigator!
For the Unyielding Dream!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!