stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
What are you doing?!
Hurry and pick that up!
All right!
Pipe down, would you?
Hey, what's all the commotion?
They're coming for us.
We can go back to Luluka.
They're coming?! J-Just a minute! Hold on!
Let me out of here!
--Hurry it up!
--Okay!
H-Hold on!
Let me go, too, together with you!
Are you planning to just
leave me here, all alone?
Are you going to let me starve
to death?! Come on, please...!
Bring me the key! Don't abandon me!
Okay, you got it.
Thank you! I owe you for this!
"An Inevitable Melee!
Wetton's Schemes and the Rainbow Tower"
Gum-Gum... Rocket!!
Let me go, damn it! Let me go!
Stop it, Rapa Nui!
There must be some mistake!
Henzo would never become
one of Wetton's men.
This isn't something you can
just pass off as some mistake!
Our town was burned down by Wetton!
Burn! Burn to the ground!
If he has carried on, and not forgotten
that aggravation, and misery,
then he'd die before doing
anything Wetton told him to do!
Or have those feelings faded
over the last 50 years, too?!
What was 50 years ago for you
was not all that long ago for us!
Hold on, Rapa Nui!
You're only saying that because
you don't know anything!
Do you have any idea what
Pops here has had to live with
for the last 50 years?!
What...?
He's had the people in town
criticizing him, calling him Wetton's dog,
and yet he's put up with it, to continue
researching the Rainbow Mist!
Why?
Isn't it obvious? In order to save you!
It's all right. Rapa Nui, that had
nothing to do with you guys.
Hit me, Rapa Nui! I forsook
my shame and my pride,
to live under the protection of
Wetton! Hit me, with your fist!
Hit me, will you? Come on!
Damn it! Why did 50 years have to go by?!
As bad as I want to, I can't
hit you, at your age, can I?!
Man, these guys are awkward.
That's better. You're friends, after all.
Even though 50 years has gone by,
you still understand each other in the end.
Henzo...
Rapa Nui...
--Sorry!
--Luffy!
That idiot!
No problem. The inside of
the mist loops, after all.
They'll be back soon enough...
...or maybe not, huh?
Now what do we do?
Let's look for them. There's no telling
what will happen within this mist.
He's such a pain in the ass.
Rapa Nui...
Ow-w-w...
Where is this place?
--Hurry and pick me up!
--Right!
Y-You've gotta be kidding me!
Run, Nami!
Hey, do something! At this rate,
Nami-san will be devoured by--
Sanji!
What do I care? That's what you get
for trying to get the jump on us!
But Grandpa, we can't get
into Ape's Concert, either,
with that monster hanging around.
I know. But there's nothing
we can do about that monster.
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna die!
I know! Miss, use the safety gear!
The safety gear?
It's something that Professor Henzo invented!
He undoubtedly created it
for just this situation!
Professor Henzo? I don't know who you are,
but please, help me!
A lifeline?
Nami-san!
Nami!
No, stay away!
W-What?
What was that just now?
Chopper! If you please!
W-What do I do?!
Okay, I've caught it!
Here I go, into the mist.
When I give the signal, pull the rope back in!
You got it!
She's got guts, doesn't she?
Not a single person has ever
gone into the Rainbow Mist,
and then come back out of it.
She'll be back, that's for sure.
After all, Nami-san is the
best navigator in the world.
Chopper, we're not letting
anyone lay a finger on that rope
until Nami-san has returned.
Got it.
This should be interesting.
Let's let her do this.
We'll watch, to see if she
comes back out of there safely.
--What?
--The mayor will now change outfits!
What's this?
Flame Suit!
--Commencing element filling!
Internal tank pressure rising!
Safety mechanism released!
I'll burn you, right down to your bone marrow!
Hey, just a minute! Where are we going?!
Isn't that obvious? Back to our friends.
Really? Do you know a way to get
back to where our friends are?
Nope, I sure don't.
What's wrong?
Then, we're just running to wherever?
That's not true. I have a hunch.
That's called going wherever.
And it's your fault for knocking
me out here in the first place!
Sorry.
Apologizing won't fix this mess!
I'm finally reunited with Henzo,
and I didn't even get to
shake his hand, you know?
I'll never get back to Luluka now, either.
Damn it!
I'm going to die here in
this mist, just like my dad did.
Your dad?
My dad was an officer in the navy.
When I was still a little kid,
he left on a long journey to explore
some unknown area of the seas.
I'd been waiting, ever since,
for my dad to come back.
Even now, Dad was off having
adventures at sea somewhere.
That's what I believed. But then...
Dad! Dad!
I frantically searched the ship,
but I didn't find Dad anywhere.
We're not getting out of here alive, all right.
We're going to be shut up
inside this mist forever.
Hey, where are you going?
I told you, back to where our friends are.
But how?! We don't even know where we are!
And yet, you're still going to keep
moving forward through this mist?!
If we don't keep moving,
we'll never get back to
where everyone is, right?
How's your end?
No good. I didn't see them anywhere.
It's possible that both of them might
have been flung beyond the mist.
What do you mean?
Rapa Nui isn't here anymore?
Quite possibly.
Oh, no...
That is a galleon, from 200 years ago.
I've never seen that ship before.
It's possible that inside Ape's Concert,
the course of time itself is...
Hey! Guys!
Oh, it's you, Nami.
What do you mean, "oh, it's you"?!
And after I came all the way
here just to rescue you!
How rude of you!
You aren't the least bit convincing.
Pay no mind, pay no mind.
Huh? Who are these children?
Where did Luffy go?
What's the matter? You all look so glum.
Has something happened?
They're gone beyond the mist.
--Huh?
--Like I said, they're gone.
They're not here anymore.
What do you mean?
Just what he said.
You weren't here for it, so there's
no way to explain it to you.
Okay. We're withdrawing!
--Just a minute!
--What about Luffy?!
I'm not sure what happened,
but there's no way he's dead, is there?
Just leave him be, no problem.
Come on, we're heading back!
Is there a way to escape?
Of a sort.
That's just a rope, isn't it?!
You're the one who came from Luluka, are you?
Ian!
Who's this guy?
One of Wetton's buddies.
What is that guy doing in here?
Why don't you hand over that rope to me?
Why should I? If you want
to get out of the mist, too,
you can just come along with us, right?
Don't you care what happens to him?
--No, I don't.
--What?!
Who is that kid, anyway? I'm not
good-natured enough to help out
a kid I've never even seen before.
Yeah, can't argue with that.
What?! You jackass! I'll shoot him! I really will!
You murderer!
Do what he says!
Who, me? That's silly--
H-Hey, cut that out!
I don't want to lose any more of my friends!
Please, do what he says!
Nice, Isoka-chan! While you're at it,
attach that lifeline to the boat.
Isoka-chan, why don't you come with me?
With this much treasure,
we'll never have to work again.
Don't get me wrong!
Rapa Nui is the only leader we have!
I have no intention of following
a pantywaist like you!
What?!
Run, Isoka!
Damn you!
Rongo!
Mess with me, will you?!
Stop!
Damn it, let go! Let me go!
Hey, what's the matter?
Sea Prism Stone...
What?!
Damn it!
Hold it, you bastard!
Don't you dare miss!
--Hurry up and shoot! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
--W-Wait, let me aim, let me aim, let me aim!
I can't shoot, you know!
Burn! Burn!
It's no use! I can't get out of the way like this!
Rumble!!
Lake, there he goes!
Electroshock Suit! Maximum output!
You're not getting away!
Dragon Spark!!
Chopper!
You shouldn't take your
eyes off your opponent!
What is this?!
Silver Barbecue!!
B-Barbecue?!
Shoot your mouth off, will you?
You're an example of what we call
"not knowing your place."
Grandpa, it's pulling, it's pulling!
You mean, that girl is really
coming back from inside the mist?
Hey, pull her back here!
Right!
--Not yet.
--What?
I promised that until Nami came back,
no one was going to lay a finger on this rope!
Don't make me laugh!
To hell with your promise!
You're just being petty and stubborn!
Is that how badly you want the treasure?!
We don't want that.
Nami-san will be coming back,
you can count on it.
We're just guarding the spot
of her return with our lives.
Joue Shoot!!
This play at friendship disgusts me!
Mayor! There's a boat coming back!
All right, pull the rope. Lead it over here.
You kids are idiots! You can just
live inside this mist forever!
Oh, it sure feels good, being under a blue sky!
Oh, I see it, I see it! The town of Luluka!
I-Is that...?
That's not Nami...!
W-Who are you?
Sorry to be away so long! I am Ian!
Captain Wetton, you are
looking even better than ever!
M-Me?
I am doing very well, yes.
Ian? Ian, you say?
The same Ian that was under me?
Huh? Captain, who is this geezer?
Uh, well, see...
I'm the captain! I'm Wetton!
Eh? Then, who's this?
My grandson, Lake.
His son, Flip.
You're kidding! You're that
bed-wetting pipsqueak Flip?
You've even got a kid of your own now?!
That's absolutely astounding!
Stop laughing, I say! Stop laughing!
Tell me, Ian, what it's like inside the mist.
Y-Yes, sir.
Here, drink up.
Wow, thanks!
--Well?
--It's no use, I can't get through.
When the signal got through before,
it must have been a temporary thing.
Of all the bad luck.
To have a piece of jewelry with
a Sea Prism Stone in it there...
Sea Prism Stone?
It's a sea crystal. It has the power
to cancel out Devil Fruit abilities.
Aw, there's no point in
having this much treasure
if we can't even go outside of here with it.
You're a navigator, right? Do something.
Nothing I can do. This absurd
area of the sea is a first for me.
We've got no options, huh?
No, he'll be coming back.
What for?
Wetton's ultimate goal is the
treasure inside Ape's Concert.
Now that his man Ian has returned alive,
he'll be heading up a large
force and charging in here.
You've gotta be kidding me!
Let's fight! I won't hand over
this treasure to anyone!
Listen to you...
If only Rapa Nui were here for us...
Hey, buck up! Hey!
Damn!
It's no good! No matter how much we paddle,
we wind up back where we started!
It really is impossible.
We can't get out of this mist.
That's not so bad, is it?
We're the only ones in here.
We can sleep when we want,
and play when we want. It's our own paradise.
A land of freedom, a land of eternity!
Rapa Nui!
We don't have to go home.
Let's make our own land, all on our own.
I want to go home, back to our own town.
I want to go home to Luluka.
Dad?
Dad... Dad!
What's that light?
--Hey, isn't that...?
--An exit!
At last, my 50-year-old dream will come true.
The Rainbow Mist and this world
will be forever joined!
W-What's that?!
Everyone, grab onto something!
It's Rainbow Tower!
Whew, that was a close one!
Here's your hat.
Thank you. By the way, what is that?
They're planning to invade Ape's Concert.
Huh? They who?
In any case, let's hurry. Everyone's in danger!
So, Wetton, you've come after all.
Get going, men!
Take every last bit of Ape's Concert's treasures!
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
There are days where I almost lose to myself
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
This unique moment...
Wetton is here!
But this is the mayor we're facing, right?
He has a lot of men under him.
I've fought him all this time by myself,
and I haven't given my heart over to him.
Aren't you forgetting about us?
You're not alone.
I won't let you defile the
paradise of the Pumpkin Pirates!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"And So, the Legend Begins!
To the Other Side of the Rainbow"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!