Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
How the Black Cat Pirates have fallen...
Right?!
U-Us, feeble?!
Zoro!
Thanks!
Tiger Trap!
Get up!
Nami, you jerk!
Klahadore! Stop this!
Run away, Kaya!
I devoted myself to you...
For so long!
Yes, it was all so that
I could kill you today...
Damn you!
If you hate getting hit that much,
I got a hundred more punches for you!
"Beat Kuro! Usopp the Man's
Tearful Resolve!"
--What was that?!
--What did he do?!
It looked like his arm stretched!
--Get real!
--He sent Captain Kuro flying!
I leave the rest to you!
I'm gonna get me some treasure!
--The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
--You guys!
--Stay away!
Say your prayers, butt-ler!
It's punishment time!
Lousy pirate!
Disrupting this village's peace!
S-Stop!
--Darn you!
--Take this!
You brats! What are you doing?!
What're those runts doing?!
Stop that, you guys... Stop!
Alright! We'll let you off with just that!
Now Captain Kuro is really mad!
Those stupid brats!
Captain!
I knew it! You were fighting, Captain!
Why didn't you tell us?! That's unbare!
No! You mean "unfair"!
Who cares about that?! You guys
just gotta get out of here! Run!
--No!
--We're gonna fight, too!
The Usopp Pirates will
be shamed if we run!
You idiots! Get out of here, now!
Captain!
That hurt a bit...
That's quite a strange
technique you have there...
I take it you have Devil Fruit powers?!
Yep! I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit!
I'm a rubber person!
--What?! A Devil Fruit?!
--He's dangerous!
--They really do exist?!
--I thought he seemed strange!
I see. A rubber person. So I didn't
hallucinate his arm-stretching...
--Jango!
--Yeah?
I'll handle the boy.
You take care of Miss Kaya.
As we planned, have her write a will...
...then kill her!
And those three little ants...
They're an eyesore!
I'm on it.
Stop. I can't let you pass.
Butchie!
Cat...
...astrophe!
Not again!
He's on a completely
different level than before!
Crap!
Kaya!
Dammit...
I'm out of strength...
Dammit... Dammit! Dammit...
D-Damn...
Usopp Pirates!
--Y-Yes, sir?!
Listen to me!
We're not going to run!
Not after they did this to you!
We're going to avenge you!
Protect Kaya!
Listen closely!
I'm giving...
I'm giving you the most
important task there is now!
Take Kaya and get away from here!
Don't tell me you can't!
That was the reason we
formed our pirate group:
to become men who protect
what's important to us!
Usopp-san...
That's... a direct order...
--Yes, Captain!
Hurry, Kaya-san!
--This way! This way!
--This way!
He sure knows how to talk all big.
He basically just told 'em to run away...
The woods are like our backyard!
O-Okay...
--Jango!
--I wound up gawking!
The fools! They can't
possibly escape me--
--Howdya like that?!
--Damn you!
Go after them, you fool!
Y-Yeah, okay!
How pointless.
I know very well just
how weak Kaya is...
She'll never escape Jango.
If you want to help her,
go right ahead.
If you can get past this hill alive, that is.
Butchie!
You already lost to me once!
I told you not to get in my way!
Move!
W-What's that sound?!
Who knows? Ol' Jango is
probably tearing the place up.
Why not go and see for yourself?
Though it may already be too late...
Damn you...
Don't you even have a shred of pity?!
You lived with her for 3 years!
No. I already told you,
Kaya is nothing more
than a pawn in my plan.
Once she's dead, then I'll
express some gratitude.
Damn you...
What a helplessly evil guy!
I don't plan to help him, though!
Usopp!
Go to them!
We'll take over here!
Leave it to us!
Oh? You can still move?
How impressive.
Shut up...
I refuse to let you... have your way!
You went and betrayed the villagers'--
and Kaya's-- feelings...
I refuse to let you
have your way anymore!
Usopp!
D-Dammit...
I... can't... move...
You really are a riot!
I betrayed them, you say?!
Cut the crap! This was
all part of the plan!
A kiddie pirate captain like you
has no place to talk all-knowingly!
Just stay on the ground there.
Though, even if you did
catch up with Jango,
you'd be no match for him anyway.
This way is probably safest for you!
Even if I am no match...
Even if I am no match for him...
I will protect them!
I'm captain of the Usopp Pirates...
...and a brave warrior of the sea!
I won't let you lay a
finger on the village!
--What's with him?
--He's yellin' somethin'!
Check it out, he's cryin'!
What's so funny?!
Luffy!
Me and Usopp are gonna chase
that hypno-freak! That a problem?!
Nope! Hurry!
T-Thanks...
I'd actually be much faster by myself,
but they're inside some woods.
I'm gonna need your
directions to catch up to him.
Hold it, you two. Who gave you
permission to pass this hill?
I did!
Go! Zoro! Usopp!
And another!
Gum-Gum Spear!
Darn! He disappeared again!
Oh, well! They're past the hill, at least!
Before fighting, I have
one thing to ask you.
Why is an outsider like you butting
into this village's business?!
Because there's a man in this
village I don't wanna let die!
How simple. Are you okay
with that being why you die?!
Yep! I'm not gonna die, though!
I'll make sure you do!
Gum-Gum Whip!
...and Pistol!
You're making me yawn!
Why, you...
Damn... He cut my mouth...
That straw hat guy's
insanely strong, and yet...
T-That's Captain Kuro for ya!
--Get 'im!
--Hurray for Captain Kuro!
--Captain Kuro!
--You're awesome, Captain Kuro!
Don't call me that name!
Do you still not get it?!
This plan is so I can be completely
rid of the name "Captain Kuro"!
I'm tired...
Devising plans everyday for you
men who only care about mayhem...
Being relentlessly attacked by
government dogs and bounty hunters...
I was absolutely sick of it all!
The navy, huh?
This is the third time this week...
It can't be helped. We're doing
stuff that makes people chase us.
Plus you've made quite
a name for yourself...
Yes... That name is
what draws them to us.
That's why I'm giving
up being Captain Kuro.
That's pretty funny. But it's no use.
I think the navy'll keep
following you until you're dead.
I am going to die.
It would seem that
piracy just isn't for me...
B-But you're this ship's captain!
You can be captain!
I'm sick of this tumultuous lifestyle.
I'm... going to kill myself for all to see!
Captain Kuro!
--Captain!
How many vessels?
J-Just one!
What should we do, Captain?!
Should we blast 'em back?!
Lower a small boat.
--Huh?!
--A boat!
Vice-Captain Jango!
Captain Kuro just--
Yeah, I know.
"Yeah"?! It's way too reckless
for him to go there by himself!
Don't tell me he's turning himself in?!
--H-Huh?!
--The cannon fire stopped...
--What's goin' on?!
--This is creepy...
Dock with their ship.
B-But...
--Just do as I say, damn it!
--Y-Yes, sir!
--Hey, get ready to fight!
--I see... So that's why...
Hey, you.
Y-Yes?! What is it?
It was nice knowing you
for this short time...
--T-The marines...
--They've been wiped out!
Now, then...
Let's begin the plan...
Hey, now. Pull yourself together.
I was kind enough to
leave you alive, you know...
S-Shut up...
I-I'm not gonna beg for my life...
F-Finish me off, damn you...
That's a good look.
If you can howl that much with a
shattered jaw, then that's perfect!
I'm giving you, a nameless,
low-ranking soldier, a treat.
Accept it gratefully...
The head of Kuro,
Man of a Thousand Plans!
Your name is Captain Kuro.
This atrocity was your doing.
One, two, Jango!
My name is Captain Kuro.
This atrocity was my doing.
And you're the man
who caught Captain Kuro.
Return to base and execute this man.
One, two, Jango!
I'm the man who caught Captain Kuro!
You're doing it again, Vice-Captain!
Perfect...
With that fake gone, Captain Kuro
will disappear from the world.
And when my plan today succeeds,
my goal will be fully achieved...
Money and peace of mind will be mine.
Do you understand, boy?
I cannot allow this plan
of three years to fail!
My plan will not be disrupted!
Seems you can do
more than just stretch!
That's right! I've toughened
myself up, to be a pirate!
You're "tired"?!
You're not fit to be a pirate if having
a name on the seas scares you!
My ambition is much greater than yours!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Do you think Kaya-san and
the others managed to get away?
Those three are with her.
She should be fine.
Yeah, huh? She won't get lost
like someone else I know.
--Are you talking about me?!
--Who else is there?!
What're you talking about?!
You used to bounty-hunt while lost!
Don't put it like that!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Protect Kaya! The Usopp
Pirates' Great Efforts!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!