If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
It's not an exit... It's an entrance!!
It's a sky island!
Heso!
I'm sorry, I'm coming to a stop!
Is everyone all right?
You're the one who crashed!
It sure does require you to get the hang of it!
Nami-san!! You're the coolest!!
Whoa! This is incredible! I can't believe it!
Why is she able to ride that thing?!
Hey, where did Nami-san go?
Father, I wonder if she's all right.
Yes, Conis-san, I'm a bit concerned myself.
Why? What's the matter?
Here in Skypiea, there's a place that we're
never to step foot in no matter what.
Never to step foot in?
Why's that?
--It's sacred ground.
--Sacred ground?
We call that place...
...Upper Yard, the land where God lives.
"The Forbidden Sacred Ground! The Island
Where God Lives and Heaven's Judgment!"
There's a God?!
In a place where we're never to set foot in?!
--Yes.
--God... you mean that God?
God lives on the sky island?!
Yes. Since Skypiea is God's Land,
it's ruled by the Almighty God Eneru.
The Almighty God?
God Eneru knows everything in this world.
Everything?!
He's also watching us all the time.
--All the time?!
--Now, too?
Of course.
What?! He's watching us now?!
Humph. God, huh?
You don't believe in God?
I don't know. Whether or not
God exists doesn't matter to me.
I couldn't care less from the beginning.
But I don't intend to deny
those who want to believe.
So, have you seen that God who
lives in Upper Yard, Conis-chan?
No! God forbid!
We cannot step foot in Upper Yard. Never...
The sacred ground, Upper Yard, is forbidden.
So, the sky island has ground, too...
I see. A place that we're not
allowed to go no matter what, huh?
Ah! Your eyes...!
What're you thinking about right now?!
Listen good! "Never step foot in" means
you're absolutely not
supposed to go there, Luffy!
Oh, I see... So there's a place
that we're not supposed to go.
I see. A place that we're absolutely
not supposed to go, huh?
He's definitely planning to go there.
Hm? But if he's God, wouldn't he forgive you
even if you go someplace you're
not supposed to? He's nice, right?
Well... But breaking God's
rules is blasphemous, so...
I see. Well, I guess it doesn't matter either way.
That's because he intends to go
even if he won't be forgiven!
So, what happens if someone goes
into that forbidden Upper Yard?
Th-That's...
That's...?
The person cannot come back alive.
Everyone believes so.
Cannot come back alive?!
I-I'm worried about Nami-san.
I hope she isn't near Upper Yard.
--Nami-san!! Stay where you are
--In any case, let's go there, to find Nami!
--and don't go anywhere!!
--Is your reason for going really to find Nami?!
--Nami-san!!
--Isn't it really so you can
go to the forbidden land?!
Nami-san!!
What's with the huge trees?
I've never seen something this big before.
How old are these trees?
Several hundred years?
All these trees...
I can't see the top of them!
There's no doubt about it!
The treasure should definitely be here!
An extraordinary treasure is here.
We're very close, it's almost within our grasp!
There's someone there.
The treasure is close by! Hurry up!
The voice came from over here.
Hey, Luffy! Let's go!
Hm... Hold on a second.
We'll go after I finish these.
What're you gonna do if
something happens to Nami-san
while you're sitting around like it's nothing?!
Just leave them there,
since we're coming right back!
Hmmm... Hold on! This one, too.
Conis-chan, it'll be night if I wait for him!
Take me to that Upper Yard place!
What? B-But...
Hm?
...we don't know if she was really headed there.
And...
...if we incur God Eneru's wrath,
we'll really be in big trouble.
God Eneru seems to be pretty scary.
God Eneru... God, huh?
No one...
...seems to be on that boat.
Claw marks...! I wonder if it
was attacked by something.
There's no doubt about it!
The treasure should definitely be here!
An extraordinary treasure is here!
We're very close...
--Th-The seashell is talking!
--It's almost within our grasp!
--The treasure is close by!
Hurry up!
This is a seashell, right? There's no
way there's a human in here, right?
Listen! If we keep a record like this,
it may become useful later!
So this seashell can record voices!
I-I don't want to! I'm going back.
I-I'm scared! I can feel it!
I can feel God's anger!
What's that noise?!
C-Can't be...!
It's God!
They were killed?
By God?
I'm going back. It's creepy.
It seems better to leave this area.
Help!
Now, we're off!!
To the place we're not allowed to go!!
Ah! I'm sorry! There's a headwind right now.
With this wind, going to Upper Yard
will take quite long! I'm sorry!
--What?!
--Quite long?
If this ship moved using dial energy,
it wouldn't take that long.
I'm sorry.
How long do you mean by "quite long"?
I don't know. Only the wind knows.
--I see... Quite long, huh?
--Old guy! Isn't there any other way
--I'd very much like to go,
since I'm worried about Nami.
--Old guy! Isn't there any other way
--I'd very much like to go,
since I'm worried about Nami.
--to get there quicker?
--Even I, Usopp-sama, the hero...
--We'd better hurry, or Nami will be back!
...can't control the wind.
Hey, Luffy! So that was why, after all!!
--"That"? Which "that"?
--You liar.
Tsk! That son of a bitch! He took my prey.
What's going on? I can hear noises.
What on earth...?
Just give up!
You should, too. He's mine.
Stay out of my way!
Hoho! Same to you!
Hoho!
Wh-What on earth...?
What's going on... in this forest?!
There's finally a dangerous place we can go!
I can't sit around and wait
till the wind changes!
Hey Luffy! Could that be...
...the old broken waver?!
Here I come!!
That idiot!
This was obviously going to happen!
Help... me...
What're we gonna do? He sank again.
Just leave him!
Geez, you're such a pain!
So, this is your old waver.
This is really old.
We found it in the sea in the world below.
Would you like me to take a look?
If it can be fixed, I'll fix it for you.
You can fix it, old guy?
I'm a dial ship engineer.
Really?! Then, please fix it! Please...
...do it quickly!
Eneru...!
He's my prey!
Oh? So you want to compete, huh?
I don't mind fighting with you...
...to kill my boredom!
Ha! That's a joke.
Do you want me to put your
body in this guy's stomach?!
Hohoho! Small fries crushing each other?
That'll be a sight! Hoho!
You're the small fry!
Wh-What?! What?!
Hey! Help me!
Let me ride with you!
Err... Ride with me? But this
is a one-person boat, so...
I came here from another sky
island in search of treasure!
But I don't care about it any more.
Please!
Can another person ride on this? I don't know!
E-Even if I had to kill you...
Guerrilla!!
G-God...
Son of a bitch! Is this Eneru's doing?!
How dare you harm Vearth?!
Get some Water Dials now!
Put out the fire!
"Angel Island Lovely Street"
Together now, salute!
Heso!
"Captain McKinley
White Berets, Skypiea Police"
Heso, everyone!
That's the White Berets!
I wonder if something happened.
Everyone, please be careful!
Illegal entrants have infiltrated
Skypiea through Angel Beach today!
What?!
It was reported that there are
a total of seven infiltrators!
We, the White Berets,
are currently conducting a
full-scale search for these criminals!
Please watch out for suspicious individuals!
Please watch out!
It looked like that man
was talking to someone.
It was a guerrilla. He's just run away.
Hey, shut that dog up.
He was probably begging for his life.
But what is Eneru-sama thinking,
taking care of that man by himself?
Why were we...?
We probably ran out of time.
Ran out of time?
Another group of illegal entrants
has already infiltrated this land.
Hm? Again?
Old lady Amazon informed us that it's a
ship with seven Blue Sea people on board.
Seven Blue Sea people... Could he mean us?!
He said illegal entrants...
If you're going to the upper area,
pay the entrance fee of
one billion Extol per person.
That is the law.
Could it be because we
didn't pay the entrance fee?
No way!
The people who were riding that boat...
...and, that man, too...
Because they entered illegally, they were...
Then, will the same thing that
happened to that man happen to us?!
There's no challenge in taking
care of only seven people.
Seven heads... We can't divide them by four.
What just happened?
Who the hell are they?!
And what is this place?!
I have to tell everyone immediately!
This place is crazy!
Well? Usopp, look at this!
Mine's finished, too!
Check out that art!
Don't they look just like us?
That's amazing!
Just how does that look like us?!
This is what I think... of your art!
--While Nami-san could be in danger,
you're fooling around!!
--Stop it! How dare you?!
--Take this! And this!
--Don't take it out on my art!
--Can it be fixed?
--I've never seen these parts.
Please fix it one way or another.
I'm sorry, but I can't say much
until I investigate it more.
Anyhow, please try.
I'll try disassembling it.
Old guy, what's that?
You, suspicious ship over there, hold it!
Who're they?
Why the heck are they crawling?
I don't know.
They're probably... weirdos!
What?! So those are weirdos...
Everyone, halt!
--Heso!
Why, heso!
H-Hey, what're you guys saying?
Who're they?
Usopp said they're weirdos.
So you're the seven illegal entrants
who came from the Blue Sea?!
What?
I'll humbly bring Heaven's Judgment upon you!
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
There are days where I almost lose to myself
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
This unique moment...
Good! That's still only a 5th degree crime!
That's not good! When it's determined
to be a 5th degree crime,
in the name of God Eneru,
you'll be banished to the clouds.
Banished to the clouds?
What's that? Being banished to
the clouds sounds kinda nice.
No, it doesn't! It's the death penalty!
Death penalty?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Already Criminals?!
Skypiea's Upholders of the Law"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!