If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
Luffy and crew managed to avoid
the White Berets' demands,
"Upper Yard" "Lovely Street"
"Angel Beach"
but a divine messenger suddenly
dragged Nami and three others away.
So, they're saying that if we
want our friends and ship back,
we just have to come in from the front.
So that's our ordeal and... Heaven's Judgment?!
Yes. In Upper Yard, four priests
strong beyond imagination await you.
Oh, then it's easy.
To put it simply, all we have to do
is beat up those priests, right?
You're so simpleminded...
This is becoming fun!
"A Trap on Lovely Street! The Almighty Eneru"
--Hey! Luffy!
--W-Wait up!
What is it?
Where are you wandering
off to, all of a sudden?!
You heard Nami.
We'll only burden Conis and
the old guy if we stay here.
Yeah, but where are we going?
Isn't it obvious? The sacrificial altar.
How are you plannin' to get there?
Quit thinking!
We just need to swipe one of those
ships and take the Milky Road.
Do you see any ships we can swipe?!
I said quit thinking!
This isn't like the Blue Sea, you know!
This old map doesn't give us details
about Angel Island's geography,
and even how to get onto
the Milky Road is a mystery!
Man, what a pain...
Everyone...
Conis-chan! Did you come
all this way to see us off?!
My father asked me to help you on
your way to the sacrificial altar...
Oh? Pagaya-san did?
I'll accompany you to the Angel Island docks.
Once there, I'll prepare an
appropriate boat for you.
Wow! You're too perfect! Nothing
like a certain scatterbrain I know!
--That's for sure!
--I was referring to you!
We'd be delighted to have you
accompany us, Conis-chan!
Right, Luffy?!
Sure, we'll take you up on your offer!
G-Great!
I won't let you escape!
I'm going to send you to Upper Yard
to receive Heaven's Judgment!
What's that?!
That's Lovely Street. Once we're there,
we'll be right by the docks.
Aren't they already headed for Upper Yard?
Do we really need to be this secretive?
Fools!
All the Blue Sea people who've
come here have been the same!
At first, they talk all cool
about dreams and adventures,
but once they're in danger, they
suddenly cry and beg for their lives!
I'm so excited to go to Upper Yard!
Y-You could die, you know...
Yeah. Everyone dies sometime.
You're not concerned?
Nope! I'm excited!
--Eh?
--Quit laughin'!
Worry about Nami-san and Robin-chan, will ya?!
And the Going Merry and
Zoro and Chopper, too!
S-Sorry...
Wow! This place is great!
Lovely Street is the only
downtown area on Angel Island.
Check it out! The stores are floating!
They've been built using
the qualities of island cloud.
Wow! Any yakiniku shops?
They're here!
--Please, just go straight there...
--Just get outta here...!
Is it just me, or is everyone avoiding us?
Can't blame 'em.
Word's probably already
gotten out that we're criminals.
This feels great! All of downtown to ourselves!
All the angels are avoiding me...
Oh? There sure is a lot of weird stuff for sale!
Ooh! If only I had money!
Is a treasure payment plan okay?
No, no!
This must be a dial shop!
I wonder if the Going Merry
could speed along like a waver
if it had two of these big Breath Dials?!
Luffy! This ain't the time to be foolin' around!
Nami-san and the others
are gonna be sacrificed!
Are you even serious about saving 'em?!
Save them? They're gonna be fine!
Zoro was caught with them!
Like we can really count on him!
I just hope the ship isn't any more damaged,
but things've been so crazy lately...
Huh?! There's something
in the middle of the street!
Eh?
What a weird face! What is this? A seal?
Looks like a weird mud figure,
but it's probably a religious statue.
Morons! This is art! I can tell!
It's "Vearth." The people of
the sky have forever admired it.
Vearth?
Eh?! You guys admire this thing?
You must be crazy...
Yes, I'm sure it must be difficult
for Blue Sea people to understand.
Oh, the docks are this way!
Eh?! We're already leaving town?!
What're you talking about?!
This isn't our destination!
C'mon, can't we hang around a little more?
--Looks like it worked...
--They went straight to the docks...
We're saved!
Oh!
So many boats!
There are all kinds of boats anchored here.
From hotel ships where you can stay the night
to speed-oriented boats
loaded with giant dials.
There are many other kinds that--
Whoa! Check out this gondola!
It's so cool! Let's take it!
Look behind it! This one can
move on its own, like a waver!
This could turn into a fun gondola ride!
You idiot! We're rescuing Nami-san
and Robin-chan! Get serious!
Oh, your boat is over here.
--Right!
--Eh?!
Oh, boy! What kind of gondola is it?!
The Crow!
You can't be serious!
Crows... aren't even waterfowl.
I used it until just recently,
when I learned how to ride wavers.
It's not fast like a waver, but it does
have two Breath Dials on board!
Please feel free to use it!
No... I'm not going.
Just as I expected! He shows
his true colors at the last minute!
There's no one in this world
who doesn't value his life!
I prefer that one instead.
He was just being selfish?
Y-You don't like it? I'm sorry. But...
You damn ingrate! Apologize!
Apologize to Conis-chan from the
bottom of your heart! You scumbag!
Pay no attention to his selfishness!
--Sorry!
--N-No problem...
Your exit is Gate #2.
It will lead you to the giant Milky Road,
which connects to Upper Yard.
Y-You simply need to take that.
--Hey. Conis.
--Yes?
Why've you been shaking
ever since we left your house?
W-What the hell is he saying?!
D-Does it seem that way?
Yeah. It's like you're afraid of something...
No! She wouldn't!
Conis-chan! You're worried
about us! That's so touching!
Still, are you guys gonna be alright?!
Everyone in town is plainly avoiding us,
yet you're lending us your boat
and even giving us directions...
Doesn't that make you our accomplices?
Say, you're looking pale, too...
You should've told us if you were that scared.
We would've come on our own...
No. I'm...
It's not what you think!
She wouldn't!
Don't say anything you shouldn't!
It's strange, isn't it?
Explaining the route to your "ordeal,"
guiding you here myself...
It's like I want to lead you there,
despite saying how terrifying it is...
Stop it! Don't say anything foolish!
Huh? What was that?!
Don't tell me they're all...
Why?! There's no need for that!
They're different...
Why do I need to guide them?
They're already headed for Upper Yard...
Yes, if that were the case, I wouldn't
force this horrible job on you...
But most of the people we've
seen haven't been that way.
Once the initial excitement wears off,
everyone values their life more
than dreams and adventures...
We must lead them to the
very end... To Upper Yard...
Forgive me, Conis-san...
It is our citizens' duty. It is his will.
Could you run away?
I'm sorry!
--Stop!
--What are you saying?!
I was the one who called
the Super-Express Lobster!
The thing that took Nami-san
and the others?! You called it?!
While you weren't on board,
I lied to them about a current
that leads to Cloud End
and had them raise the anchor.
That was the signal for the
Super-Express Lobster...
Foolish girl! Do you want
to die?! This is our duty!
Once we know someone's a criminal,
we'll be killed if we don't lead
them to the place of judgment!
Stop it! Do you realize what you're saying?!
--You're blaspheming against God!
--Stop her!
This is our citizens' duty...
Are you serious?!
I'm sorry!
It's all so strange, isn't it?!
Don't be stupid! You didn't
have any choice, right?!
Then...
...why are you telling us?!
Your life is in danger!
--It's all over!
--We're too late!
--Stay away from the girl!
--The judgment is coming!
No good! It's too big!
What was that?!
What just happened?!
--Luffy!
--Conis-chan! Hey! Where'd you go?!
Luffy! Conis!
It's no use...
The almighty God Eneru sees all...!
They are both safe.
It's Gan Fall-san!
Oh! That weird old man!
"Weird"?
No, I am the Sky Knight!
This one is on the house!
Thank goodness! Conis-chan...!
Leave this girl with me. I will
not allow Eneru to harm her.
Right!
You now know this land's true nature,
as well as "God's" power.
What will you do now?
This land is none of our business.
Our friends are on "God's Island"!
I see... May luck be with you.
--What about them?
--They have chosen their course.
It is no fault of yours.
I know who you are.
I am the Sky Knight.
No, we all know. Please come back...
...God!
Get on! I'll give you a strong push out!
You're comin', too!
Alright, let's go to Upper Yard!
No...!
The bastards actually left...
With no hesitation or uncertainty at all...
Even if we're far apart
I don't want you to forget
That on those days when
you're brought to tears
You have a friend here to share the pain
That far-off feeling we refuse to concede
I won't let it just be a dream
The eternal brilliance that
everyone is searching for
We will surely embrace it with our own hands
Is Conis gonna be alright?
All we can do is count on the old man!
We gotta save Nami-san and Robin-chan now!
--There are two others.
--Huh? What's that?
--Aaah! Aieee!
--Is it "God's ordeal"? Shut up!
Just keep moving forward!
Please let me go home!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Onward, Crow! To the Sacrificial Altar"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!