Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
--Jango!
--Y-Yeah?
I'll handle the boy.
You take care of Miss Kaya.
As we planned, have her write a will...
...then kill her!
U-Usopp Pirates!
Protect Kaya!
Luffy!
Me and Usopp are gonna chase
that hypno-freak! That a problem?!
Nope! Hurry!
What?!
T-That's Captain Kuro for ya!
--Get 'im!
--Hurray for Captain Kuro!
--Captain Kuro!
--You're awesome, Captain Kuro!
Don't call me that name!
This plan is so I can be completely
rid of the name "Captain Kuro"!
I'm tired...
Devising plans everyday for you
men who only care about mayhem...
Being relentlessly attacked by
government dogs and bounty hunters...
W-What?!
You're "tired"?!
You're not fit to be a pirate if having
a name on the seas scares you!
My ambition is much greater than yours!
"Protect Kaya! The Usopp
Pirates' Great Efforts!"
Is that hypnotist still behind us?!
Nope, I don't see him!
Let's lose him for good!
Like he can really catch
us inside this forest!
Don't worry, Kaya-san!
We will keep you safe!
Yeah! In the name of the Usopp Pirates!
Thank you...
Not there...
Where are you, you runts?!
Don't think you can escape me!
I can shave this whole
forest bald, if you'd like!
Whoa! He seems really mad!
He's not just a hypnotist?!
Where did you run off to?
This way!
Where are you, you runts?!
Hey! East! East! I said east!
Like I know where that is!
Tell me left or right!
--Then turn right!
--That's the opposite way!
Kaya-san!
I'm sorry... You run on ahead...
What are you saying?!
Our mission is to protect you!
Oh, no! She's got a really bad fever!
Eh?! Hang in there, Kaya-san!
A doctor! Get a doctor!
You idiot! This is no time for that!
Someone's trying to kill her!
But it's dangerous for
her to run any more!
But...
Where are you, you runts?!
Thank you...
I'm happy that you helped me...
Just the thought is enough for me...
Run away, all three of you.
Where did you run off to?
It's no use running! Come on out!
If we leave Kaya-san and run now,
we'll probably survive, right?
Yeah, probably.
Plus our captain always said to run
with your tail between your legs
if you think you're gonna lose...
Damn brats think they can mock me!
Our captain is a liar!
Even he went and fought!
He tried so hard to protect us!
I won't let Kaya-san die!
Alright, then! Prepare
yourselves, Usopp Pirates!
--Alright!
--Let's fight him!
No! You're still just children!
You mustn't die for my sake!
We're not gonna die.
We're gonna fight to live!
As our captain always said.
--Yeah!
You brats...
T-That guy...
He broke Captain Kuro's "Cat Claw"!
That leaves only five more
of those weird swords!
It's okay! He can still fight plenty!
Yeah! He still has the other claw!
Scratch him up and
kill 'im, Captain Kuro!
Hey! That name is taboo now!
I think his name in this
village is Klaha... something.
Kla-san, then!
--Kla-san! Get 'im!
Be quiet, you!
I'll come exterminate
every one of you later...
Jango too, of course!
W-Why us?!
Please stop joking around, Captain Kuro!
It's still not too late for us
to attack the village, right?!
And if Captain Jango gets her to
write her will, the plan should work!
You need not worry about this plan;
your corpses will be enough for
me to place the blame on you...
I never intended to let you
leave this village from the start...
I can't have people who
know I exist stay alive...
You can't be serious!
Then you planned to kill
us from the very start?!
That's right...
Since three years ago, when I
was still known as Captain Kuro...
It was all...
...all part of my plan!
Man, you guys're dumb.
You're such an uncool pirate group!
"Uncool"?
Pirate groups are nothing more
than a collection of social outcasts!
Without plans, what
can they possibly do?!
Every last one should just
shut up and follow my plans!
Crew members are loyal
pawns of the captain!
Whether my men live or die is all
up to my orders as their leader!
No matter how powerful the obstacle,
they simply need to stand up
to it and die for my plan...
This is how pirates are!
Don't you talk down to me, traveler boy!
No matter how many hundreds
or thousands of men follow
you as their captain...
...you'll never be better than Usopp!
What?!
You're saying I'm inferior to a kid
pretending to be a pirate captain?
That's right!
You're hilarious!
Don't get cocky just because
you snapped one of my claws!
How exactly is he better
than me?! Let's hear it!
Character.
What?!
You don't know what a true pirate is!
H-He...
He kept up with the Pussy
Foot Maneuver's speed!
How insulting...
If you want to know about
real pirates that much,
then I'll show you that terror...
The terror of a pirate who's been
face-to-face with death many times!
Hey! That stance! Is he--
He's gonna use that technique?!
--But he's only fighting one guy!
--But that's definitely it!
He's planning to use the
Out of the Back Attack!
Isn't it bad for us to be
here?! He'll get us, too!
He plans to kill us, too!
He even said so earlier!
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
Anything but that technique!
We'll do anything you want!
Please, Captain Kuro!
What's the big deal?
He's only wobbling back and forth...
--Don't do it!
--Captain Kuro!
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
Out of the Back Attack!
What a small haul...
I thought they'd have a
little more treasure than that...
Let's see, is the fight over by now?
Huh? Everyone's stopped... Is it over?
T-There it is!
Why over there?!
Not again!
Now it's the wall!
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
It's no use! He attacks at random
using his Pussy Foot Maneuver!
Because of his speed, not even
he knows what he's cutting!
So many crew members
have fallen victim to--
Hey!
W-What's happening?!
People are suddenly being cut!
Show yourself, butler...
Who do you take your friends for?!
Luffy...
Found you!
Bastard! You should've let
yourself be cut like a good boy!
Look! Thanks to you, my adorable
men are left alive and in agony.
It would've been better for
them to die in that attack!
Now what? You look like
you have something to say...
Yeah...
I will never be...
...a man like you.
Not "will."
Someone like you can't be like me!
Especially since
you're going to die here,
while you writhe in agony as
I hack you up like raw fish...
I'm going to painstakingly
carve you up as a special treat!
Oh, no, you don't!
Out of the Back Attack!
Come out, you brats!
I know you're hiding there!
Give yourself up!
We surrender!
We'll give you Kaya-san!
Come over here!
We'll take you to her!
Like I'll really fall for that!
I can't trust what a bunch of brats say!
Huh?!
We got him! Now!
Take this! Pepper Attack!
I knew it! They were...
they were lying from the very start!
--Push...
--Hyaaah!
Oww! Oww! Oww!
End of the line, hypnotist!
Don't get cocky!
Darn it! We failed!
You made a mockery of me.
But I am a pirate...
--Onion!
You pretend pirates have
interfered a bit too much...
Where are you hiding, Miss?!
I'll start by executing these three.
You can reflect on your foolishness
to meddle in a real pirate fight
in the next life.
There you are.
--No!
--Run, Kaya-san!
Run!
--Hey!
--Yeah! That's them!
They're the other way?!
Please stop this!
Leave them alone! I'll write my will!
N-No!
You'll be killed if you write it, Kaya-san!
I'm sorry...
Fool. Don't try to make a deal with me.
Captain Kuro told me
to get rid of everyone.
You can't be serious!
If you don't do as I say,
then you won't get to kill me!
I won't write my will, either!
H-Hold on! Don't act hasty!
I absolutely must get
you to write that will!
K-Kaya-san!
Alright! I'll let the brats go!
Though they're really
in no condition to run...
Here!
Don't forget to sign your name!
I know...
D-Darn it...
"I leave my entire fortune
to Klahadore, my butler..."
Excellent! This is your will, all right!
That saved me the trouble
of hypnotizing you!
You promise not to kill them, right?
Don't worry.
I may not look like it, but I'm
known for being an honest man.
--Kaya-san!
There they are!
--There they are! There they are! Stop!
--Ouch, ouch! I've been cut there, you know!
Over there!
--Alright, I'll be back!
--Hey!
That's far enough, hypno-freak!
He followed me here?!
Looks like I better finish this quickly!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
All finished here! The rest is up to you!
I won't lose to someone who ditches
his name and runs from the sea!
Remember my name for
the rest of your life!
--What're you so mad about?
--I hate him! He's wrong!
That's how pirates are.
That's not what friends are like!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Anger Explosion!
Kuro vs. Luffy, How it Ends!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!