If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"Upper Yard" "Angel Island"
After the campfire ended...
Usopp had a mysterious experience late at night.
Meanwhile, Ohm, Gedatsu, and Shura
were called to God's shrine...
...where God Eneru made an appearance.
Tomorrow, I will let you enter
all areas of Upper Yard.
You can set up your ordeals wherever you like.
You can also ignore the rules
and go as wild as you want.
Tell me, Merry. Who was that?
--Let's get going!
--Yeah!
"A Giant Snake Bares Its Fangs!
The Survival Game Begins"
Hey! Where are you going, Zoro?!
That's the wrong way! West is this way!
Geez! Your horrible sense
of direction is such a pain!
West? That's east!
C'mon, Luffy! Why don't you
ever listen to anyone?!
It's the "skull's right eye," so we
gotta go right! Are you stupid?!
I think they both are...
We're heading south, so could
you tell them it's this way?
You got it!
Luffy! Zoro!
South, huh? Why didn't you say so sooner?!
Luffy! That's a nice stick!
Isn't it? You can't have it! Go find your own!
You're so lucky! Stick...! Stick...!
What about sticks?
I thought this forest would be a
scarier place, but it's not so bad!
Chopper! You're strong today?
That's right!
I feel so reassured when I'm with these three!
But it really is a let-down, to be honest.
There was nothing in the
forest yesterday, either.
We didn't run across a single priest.
I know how you feel, Chopper.
Right?!
What odd people. Do you want
an accident to happen that badly?
Huh? Those big roots have a weird pattern...
It's moving!
What's moving, Chopper?
O-Oh, nothing! It's nothing at all!
If I said I saw roots moving,
they'd all laugh at me for being afraid.
I'm supposed to be strong today!
I bet it was my imagination!
I sense something strange...
Chopper. Why do you keep
looking behind you?
N-No reason at all!
What are those big roots with a weird pattern?
You see it, too?! I knew it was strange!
Why are the roots moving?
You see it too?! Actually,
I noticed earlier, and...!
--W-What the...?!
--What the...?!
The wind's good! The helm's good!
Truly comfortable! What a perfect cruise!
But this thing sure is slow!
Hey, navigator! Do something!
I'm afraid I can't, Captain Usopp!
Say that again...
--I'm afraid I can't!
--No, not that part!
The Milky Road has intense ups and downs,
so our only choice is to rely
on the dial ship's power!
You can do it, Crow!
Oh, and Sanji. Be at my guard at all times!
The captain is afraid of this forest...
Shut up! Then quit acting
like a big-shot captain!
And just so you know, I'm only
going to protect Nami-san!
Oh, yeah! It's time for the
Weird Knight's medicine!
Where did Chopper say he put it again?
My name is Gan Fall. Gan Fall.
Oh, the medicine's on a
barrel next to the fridge.
Thanks, Nami-san!
Okay!
Looks like you've gotten a lot better, old man!
Yes. I thank you all.
If you're gonna thank anyone,
thank our ship's doctor!
Chopper's medicine works real wonders!
Oh, but you tried to save Chopper, right?
Then you're both even!
Old man?
Shall I talk a little about this land's history?
Until six years ago, I was God...
Did you hit your head, old man?
As you know, it is said that
Upper Yard appeared in Skypiea
some 400 years ago.
Until then, Skypiea had
been a peaceful sky island...
Items from the Blue Sea that
sporadically rode up the Knock-Up Stream
were rare and valuable to the sky people.
All the Vearth on the sky islands
came into the sky in this way.
But Vearth the size of Upper Yard
was an unimaginable miracle.
Naturally, the sky people were
overjoyed and worshipped it
as holy ground bestowed by Heaven.
However, indigenous people
lived on this Vearth,
and a battle over its ownership began.
Those people are the Shandians...
--You mean the guerrillas?!
--Yes.
So they originally lived on
Jaya in the world below?
Yes. They were sent into the sky
with the island, against their will.
Yet, you guys kicked them off the island?
Yes. The sky people stole their
homeland, due to their own greed...
Even after 400 years,
the war between the Shandians
and the sky people has not ended.
The Shandians are simply trying
to take back their homeland.
That's... kind of heartbreaking.
Then doesn't that make you the bad guys?!
Yes... You're right.
Oh, my medicine. Thank you.
What about Eneru?
Who is this "God Eneru"?
When I was God,
he suddenly appeared from
some sky island, leading soldiers.
He made a heavy blow to my
"Divine Squad" and to the Shandians,
then took control of Upper Yard.
This was six years ago.
Most of the Divine Squad is now
being forced to work hard by Eneru.
I do not know the details.
But to the Shandians, who God
is doesn't change the situation.
They simply want their homeland back.
If these Shandians just
want their homeland back,
why'd they attack us the
instant we came to the sky?
Members of the Divine Squad
sometimes escape via ship.
Naturally, the Shandians see them
as enemies and try to eliminate them.
Perhaps they mistook you for them.
We were almost killed because
of a mistake? That's too much!
One reason I became the Sky Knight
was so that I could help those
escapees flee to other islands safely.
As criminals, they can't stay here,
where Eneru can observe them.
From the sound of it, "God Eneru"
is almost like a king of terror...
Hey, now! Watch what you say!
The almighty God sees all!
Since when did you become
a native Skypiean?!
D-Didn't you hear what he just said?!
Terror, huh? No, it is worse than that.
Eneru establishes outsiders
like yourselves as criminals,
then has the denizens of Skypiea
lead them to their "judgment."
What this brings about is the
citizens' "awareness of sin."
A person becomes his weakest when
he senses sin in his own actions.
Eneru knows this.
He creates his own "lost sheep"
and controls them.
He is truly playing God. He's a powerful man...
We thought we found a paradise
when we arrived at Angel Beach...
Boy, were we wrong...
This is one hell of a place the
old city of gold flew up to...
Oh, that reminds me.
This "gold" you've been
fussing about since last night...
What exactly is it?
Eh?!
So you've appeared again...
Leave, old man!
Stop it, Wyper! Gan Fall is here to negotiate!
Negotiate, my ass!
Move aside, Chief!
Do you expect us to agree to a
compromise between two old men?!
Listen, Gan Fall!
We're not budging a single inch!
If you insist that fighting is
pointless, then give it all back!
Do you know what you've done
to us Shandians for generations?!
So why do you want "coexistence" now?!
I cannot return everything.
The power of Upper Yard's Vearth
is essential to Skypiea now.
They are all grateful for its blessings.
I cannot possibly take that
away from innocent people!
You're saying the sky people are innocent?!
Maybe so, if you live in peace and never fight!
Should we get people outside your
"Divine Squad" involved, too?!
Don't be foolish!
If you wanna undo your sins, take a risk!
Sacrifice 100 people who don't
wanna die, and bring their heads here!
I cannot do that!
Then our negotiations
have broken down! Leave!
Unless you want your head
removed where you stand!
Wait, Wyper!
Don't be saying my name so freely...
I...
...love pumpkin juice.
I'll kill you!
Wait, Wyper!
Men! Stop Wyper!
What are you doing?!
Kamakiri! Braham! Not you, too?!
Aisa certainly cries a lot, doesn't she?
Yes. She always cries when something
scary happens in the village.
Is it because of Wyper...?
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm not sure. Though he always is
in the center of any trouble there is.
Why do you think it's him?
I'm afraid of him, too...
After all, he's almost like a demon...
The Vearth!
Wyper!
I told you, that's Aisa's treasure!
Stop.
Braham!
Don't assume we'll get another chance!
I won't let this opportunity go!
Those who aren't prepared,
stay here. I won't blame you.
C'mon, Wyper! We're always prepared!
Are you prepared to abandon
anyone who falls during the fight?
Those who can step over comrades
and keep moving, come with me!
Today... Eneru's head will be mine!
Run! It's a giant snake!
What size! Is this also a result of
the sky island's environment?
You're like a catfish! I'll chop you into chunks!
How the hell can something
so big move so fast?!
Poison!
I think we should run away...
Definitely.
Yikes!
Don't touch the poison! You'll die instantly!
Hey! Poisonous snake! Over here! Follow me!
Your food's running away!
Robin! Look out!
Cinco Fleurs!
Too bad!
Robin! You're incredible...!
Alright! I should be behind its tail now...
Crap!
This way! Over here!
This isn't good...
I returned to our course,
but no one is coming...
Did I get separated? Should I
go ahead and wait for them?
Oh, no! I got separated! Huh?! Huh?!
H-Help! Where is everyone?!
Where are they? I look away for
a second and this happens...
Oh, well. I'm sure they'll manage somehow.
I got most of the map memorized,
anyway. It's to the right.
Yeesh...
Where'd they all go? Am I lost now?
Oh, well. Guess I'll go ahead
and wait at the ruins.
She said "straight south,"
and south is in a warm-ish direction!
This way!
It seems the Shandians have started to move...
And the Blue Sea people
have split into two groups...
And then split up even more... Solo, huh?
Today is going to be a lively day.
Just how many people will survive?
Well then, let the survival game begin!
We're now heading for God's shrine!
Don't stop, no matter what happens!
We're after only one thing... Eneru's head!
Yeah!
Even if we're far apart
I don't want you to forget
That on those days when
you're brought to tears
You have a friend here to share the pain
That far-off feeling we refuse to concede
I won't let it just be a dream
The eternal brilliance that
everyone is searching for
We will surely embrace it with our own hands
How many will survive?
Where is everyone?! Help me!
If you want a shoulder, you can have it!
They get lost so easily when I'm gone!
Eneru's head will be ours today!
Only five will be standing in three hours' time.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Deadly Reject!
War Demon Wyper's Resolve"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!