Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
T-There it is!
What the...?
Who do you take your friends for?!
There they are!
"Anger Explosion!
Kuro vs. Luffy, How it Ends!"
Tired?
The Out of the Back Attack does
have lots of unnecessary movement.
Don't get cocky.
Everything so far has been playtime.
You get the special treatment.
I'm going to let you taste plenty
of fear, then slowly cook you!
Out of the Back Attack!
Just try your foot technique now!
Damn you! Get away from me!
Now your plan of three
years is a complete failure!
What?!
He caught Captain Kuro!
Hey, if he wins, that means
we won't get killed, right?!
Now you die!
Oh, no, you don't!
You damn kids!
Looks like you're one
step too late, Haramaki!
I wouldn't say so!
Yes! That branch was in the way!
What?!
Usopp-san...
Get 'im, Rubber Guy!
Kick Captain Kuro's ass!
Get away!
You guys have no right to cheer me on!
Eat this, hypnotist!
Usopp-san!
--Captain!
Let go!
Gum-Gum...
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
--My plan will not be disrupted!
--...Bell...
H-He beat him...
H-He beat Captain Kuro!
Not even the navy was a match
for Kuro, Man of a Thousand Plans!
But he really beat him!
Just who are you?!
Monkey D. Luffy.
I'd never lose to a pirate who ditches
his name and runs from the sea.
The only time a pirate should
abandon his name is when he dies!
L-Luffy?! Yeah, I never
heard that name before!
Remember my name for
the rest of your lives!
I'm the man who's gonna
be King of the Pirates!
This guy's...
Take him and leave!
Never come here again!
Run!
Well done...
--Hurry!
--Raise the anchor!
I'd expect even you to collapse
after all you just went through...
Say.
What were you mad about earlier?
I hate them. They're wrong.
That's not how friends should act.
What're you talking about?
Of course it's not.
Pirates aren't the lovely things
you make them out to be.
I'd say Captain Kuro's
more standard than you.
I want some meat.
You're unbelievable!
Can you keep everything that's
just happened here a secret?
Eh?! A secret?! How come?!
Yeah! After we just fought
for the village's sake!
Everyone'll change their
opinion of you, too!
You could be the village hero!
--Yeah! Yeah!
Usopp-san. You need to clear up
everyone's misunderstanding...
Misunderstanding? I was only
called an exaggerator, like always.
There's no need to scare everyone
with something that's already over.
Aside from things like this,
no pirates will show up to attack
a remote village like this one.
I'm just going to pretend
that nothing ever happened.
It was all a lie.
I won't force you to, but...
No, I can do it! If it's for
the best of the village!
Me, too!
Me, too! I'll never say a word, ever!
Kaya...
Will it be hard for you?
No.
Where is Usopp-kun this morning?
It throws everything off for some
reason... I can't get motivated...
Mommy...
Is the liar guy not coming today?
That damn exaggeration-spewing kid...
Where is he today?!
Do you think maybe I was
too harsh yesterday?
He'll be back to his old tricks
come tomorrow! I'm sure of it...
Thanks!
I wouldn't have been able to protect
the village without you guys!
What're you talkin' about?
If you hadn't done anything,
I would've done nothing!
Me, too!
Who cares about that?
I got me some treasure!
This incident has helped me
finally come to a decision.
Captain Usopp! What did you
want to talk to us about?!
You guys fought well against
those Black Cat Pirates!
As captain, I feel very proud!
Y-You're too kind...
We're nothing compared to you...
You're embarrassing us!
No, you really did great!
You were scared to death,
but you managed to keep Kaya safe!
We overcame our biggest and
greatest battle since we formed
the Usopp Pirates five years ago,
when you guys were just four!
--Yes!
So, I know this is sudden, but I've
decided to set out to sea by myself!
I'm gonna be a real pirate!
I had always been unsure if I
wanted to stay here forever or not...
But, once I saw them,
I finally made up my mind!
I feel that, as a man, I must
set out onto the vast ocean!
So I'm leaving this village!
There's but one reason:
the pirate flag is calling me!
Captain! You're lying, right?!
You're lying again, right?!
It's way too hasty to do that!
Don't you love this village, Captain?!
What'll happen to the Usopp Pirates?!
You've been great to me, guys...
I plan to leave without telling
the villagers. Give them my regards.
--No...
--I don't want to!
Don't go, Captain!
Do you remember this place?
This is where we first met.
--All done!
--Liar guy!
Who're you guys?!
Don't treat me all buddy-like!
But you're famous!
Yeah, you're a famous person...
I see!
So, people've finally started to
respectfully call me Captain Usopp!
Everyone calls you Liar Usopp!
Alright! From this day forth,
you're members of the Usopp Pirates!
--Eh?!
Don't give me that!
A lot's happened, huh?
A Cerberus! Scare it away!
A dragon! Capture it!
Flour Star!
You're amazing, Captain!
But of course!
I am a brave warrior of the sea!
We don't wanna hear
about the old days!
Yeah! We don't wanna hear about that!
This isn't like you, Captain!
Why are you saying this stuff now?!
It's almost like you're...
You're so stupid, Captain! Stupid!
What are your ambitions in life?!
To run a pub!
To be a master carpenter!
To be a novel writer!
T-Then swear here that you'll
continue on each of your paths
and never let the fires
of your ambitions go out!
As of today...
...the Usopp Pirates...
...are disbanded!
"Food"
Well, we've eaten.
We should get going now.
Yeah...
--Here you are!
--Hey, Miss!
Are you alright, being out of bed?
Yes...
My sickness this past year
was caused by the mental dismay
from having lost my parents...
And Usopp-san really
cheered me up, too...
I can't stay coddled forever!
You've done so much for me. Thank you.
I've prepared a present for you
from the bottom of my heart!
Please accept it!
All packed...
Guess it's farewell to this house, too!
Alright...
What?!
What the...? I can't get out!
Darn it!
A caravel!
Can we really have this?!
Yes, please use it!
It's a slightly older model,
but I personally designed it!
A carvel-make caravel, with lateen
sails and a central stern rudder...
...the Going Merry!
Let me explain the running rigging!
First, about the Kruger
net yard adjustment--
No, no! You can explain
the ship stuff to me!
What a good ship! Especially
this front-- it's so cool!
We've loaded it with everything
you might need on a voyage.
Thanks! It leaves nothing to beat tired!
That's "leaves nothing
to be desired," you idiot.
Stop this thing!
Usopp-san!
What's he doing?
Let's just stop him for now.
He's on a collision course with the ship.
T-Thanks...
Sure thing.
So you are taking to
the ocean, Usopp-san?
Yeah. I've decided to get going
before I start to change my mind.
Don't stop me, now.
I won't. I could just tell somehow.
That's kind of sad, too!
The next time I come to this village,
I'll tell you adventure stories that
seem even more lie-like than lies!
Okay! I look forward to it!
You guys take care, too!
Let's meet again sometime!
--How come?
--Huh? "How come?"
Man, you're antisocial...
I'm gonna be a pirate too, so we'll
meet on the high seas eventually!
What're you talkin' about?
Get on already.
Eh?!
We're friends now, aren't we?
I...
I get to be captain, right?!
Don't be dumb! I'm the captain!
There goes the captain...
Yeah. But he's with those guys,
so I feel less worried now.
Yeah. I've never seen anyone
as strong as them before.
Guess it can't be helped.
He always talked about
how he wanted to be a pirate.
The villagers'll probably be
sad when we tell them, though...
It's all so sudden, plus he
livened things up all by himself...
I just had an idea!
--What is it?!
They were certainly pleasant people...
--Merry...
--Yes?
Lying hurts...
Are you referring to Klahadore?
No...
You mean how you really wanted
to stop Usopp-kun from going?
Miss, the villagers once told
me a story from his childhood.
Shortly after Usopp-kun's
father left the village,
his mother passed away.
Pirates are here!!
Pirates are here!
Dad's pirates are here!
H-Hold on, Usopp!
You mustn't shout!
Dad came back for us!
D-Don't be silly... Usopp...
But he said he'd take us with
him when you get better, Mom!
Your father won't be coming back...
But... I'm proud I married him...
T-There's a legendary medicine!
It can cure any sickness!
You're so silly... You dream too much...
I don't care if I'm silly!
I do dream! I am the son of a pirate!
Grow up to be a brave
man like your father...
Pirates are here!
Perhaps out of his loneliness,
he continued to shout it out
after his mother's death.
In the hopes that one day his father's
pirate ship would be at the shore,
in the hopes that one day
he would come back for him...
The villagers say that lie
of his also contains his wish.
Pirates!
As someone who lost his
own parents in this village,
he probably couldn't ignore you,
seeing as the same happened to you.
You will need to grow
stronger now, too!
To live up to everything
he's done until today!
Yes!
Cheers to our new ship and crewmate!
They said they were
fighting to live, not die.
Usopp-san's lies always
spoke about the joy of living.
They cheered me up
and told me to live!
Indeed.
Here we go!
Are we really gonna do this?!
You bet! We're following
in our captain's footsteps!
--Ready...
--Pirates are here!
You know what, Merry?
I'm going to be a doctor!
That's a wonderful goal to have!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Hey! This island gives me
the creeps! Let's go back!
Treasure-hunting, huh?!
That sounds exciting!
Watch out! There's something here!
What's with this guy?!
He's totally suspicious!
Says he's the protective
god of the island!
Neat! A scrub brush!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"You're the Weird Creature!
Gaimon and His Strange Friends"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!