Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
Don't tell me...
It's not that people fear God.
Fear itself is God.
Zoro!!
30 million volt...
The drum became...
...Hino!!
Why do you get up?
For the sake of our ancestors!
I-I'll come... with you!
No...?
Hey! Zoro! What're you doing?!
Wyper!
Skypiea will disappear...
It will be dropped to the ground...
Our village, too?!
Everything...
This is the Ark Maxim!
I know where they are.
It must be Nami and Eneru...!
Take me there!!
"They Finally Clash!
Pirate Luffy vs. God Eneru!!"
I can see Angel Island...!
Everyone, heso!
The unforgivably profane
Pagaya and his daughter,
along with their accomplice Gan Fall,
the former God, are on the run!
Please be careful!
If you see criminals,
please alert me immediately!
In the name of God Eneru, we,
the White Berets, protect Skypiea's peace!
Heso!
Oh, this is really reassuring.
But I'm scared. If those
criminals are hiding close to us,
won't we also get struck by God's judgment?
Report! Report!
What's the matter?
Yes, sir! Actually...
What?! You say that Pagaya's
daughter has appeared at the harbor?!
The blasphemer has entered Gate 1!
Why? Why is she acting like
she wants to be captured?
Don't let her get away! Capture her at any cost!
Come, criminal!
Please get out of my way!!
What're you doing?! Out of my way!
Why...?!
Captain!
N-No...
--It's the criminal!
--It's the woman who went against God!
--Don't come this way!
--God'll cast judgment!
What an enormous amount of gold...
That girl from Angel Island... Apparently,
she's causing a scene on Angel Beach.
Conis?! It can't be...! She should be on our ship!
There's a lot of commotion
going on outside, too.
Well... those are trifling matters, though...
Th-That Mantra ability you have...
You can even identify the person?!
I wouldn't say it's perfect.
But my case is special.
In addition to my strong Mantra ability,
I hear conversations by using my
lightning power to read radio waves.
If I hear a foolish conversation
somewhere, I cast my judgment.
As long as it's happening within
this nation, it's a simple matter.
That's why...
That certainly is an ability suitable for God.
Try as hard as you like to run
and escape, people of the sky.
This is the end of Skypiea!
A party with angels dancing in the sky!
Hey you, have you ever seen
the look on people's faces
when they lose their foothold?
What's with this guy?!
What's with this guy?! What's with
this guy?! What's with this guy?!
What am I gonna do?! If I don't escape now...
No... Even if I could escape okay,
if this sky island will be gone...
Isn't there anything I can do?!
U-Um...
Is something wrong, sir?!
Who is that?
No... it's nothing.
Please... Please listen to what I have to say!
Don't come! Don't get near us!!
Everyone, please listen!
There's no time to lose!
Please! Calm down and hear me out!
Shut up! Don't come!
Leave the island, you plague!
That's right! If you're here, we'll
also be struck by God's judgment!
You blasphemer!
No... I... came to...
Don't come near me!
This is a flame bazooka.
I'll shoot!
Everyone! Please go to the edge of
the clouds right away! To Cloud End!
Please escape to the Blue Sea!
This nation is about to disappear!
There is no time to waste!
Use every boat there is
and escape Angel Island!
What is this crazy talk...?!
God Eneru intends to eliminate this nation!
If you stay here, you'll all die!
Ha! Don't be ridiculous!
What're you trying to pull?!
Is this revenge?!
You're taking this nonsense too far!
Do you want us to be struck, too?!
Don't insult God Eneru!
Oh... I'm sorry...
What? She dropped her weapon?!
--Hey! Capture her!
--Yes, sir!
I... I do not accept Eneru as God!!
Father...
--How terrible!
--Get out of here, now!!
--Evacuate! Evacuate!
--Get away from that woman!
God's gonna cast judgment!
Oh?
This is strange. She hasn't
had judgment cast upon her.
--Why...?
--When she insulted God...
What's going on...?
It's because there's no longer any
point in eliminating just my life.
"Skypiea will be eliminated."
A member of the Divine Squad
escaped Upper Yard,
and this is the message that he
risked his life to let you all know.
He... He received God's judgment
together with my father.
What did she say about God? What?!
Doesn't God help us?
What's she saying?
There's no time to lose.
Everyone, please go to the edge of
the clouds immediately! To Cloud End!
Can't be...
--H-Hold on a second!
--Hm?
Don't be ridiculous!
We can't just up and go like that!
We were born and raised in
this sky! After all these years...
That's right! We've never
even been to the Blue Sea!
There's no way we can live there! Besides...
Then are you going to wait to be killed?!
You all have known for the past
six years what kind of man Eneru is.
Once he says he will do something,
he will definitely carry it out! If you still...
It may not happen! Maybe there'll
be a miracle or something,
and the sky island may not have to disappear.
Y-Yeah. God may change
his mind or something.
Yeah... if that happens...
What we know better than anything is
that he has power to cause us despair!
And that the time is imminent!
What's the point of waiting
for a miracle to happen?!
At least God doesn't exist
in this nation right now!
Before you pray... before you
turn a blind eye to reality...
...you have to do what you can!
The time where you could survive
if you lie low as a victim is over!
You have to take action!
You can't protect your own life
by blaming someone later!
Come on now! Make the
decision to leave this land!
Escape to the Blue Sea!!
--Hurry up and gather your things!!
--To Cloud End!
--To the edge of the clouds!
--Do what that girl says!
--Hurry up!
--There's no time to waste!
Excuse me!
Do you know what happened
to the Divine Squad?!
My husband is in the Squad.
I'd like to escape with him!
My son is in it, too! Are the
Divine Squad members okay?!
My son, too! My only son left for duty
--and hasn't come back yet!
--Um... well...
The Divine Squad is probably already...
I don't know...
What on earth has the Divine Squad
been forced to do up until now?!
Where are they?!
Isn't there something you could tell us?
We, the White Berets, will look into
the matter of the Divine Squad!
We'll have them catch up with you all later!
Please go on ahead! It'll be crowded!
Captain McKinley...
Please hurry up now!
Captain!
I can guess what will
happen to the Divine Squad.
Eneru is that kind of man... I know that.
However, having people on this island
quickly evacuate is our priority right now.
I won't let what happened
in Birka happen here.
--Birka...?
--A sky island in the far southeast
where Eneru was born and raised.
I heard that it disappeared
without a trace six years ago.
Six... don't tell me...
That's right. Eneru destroyed his
homeland and came to this nation.
I heard that there were strong
warriors in Birka as well,
but they were nothing before Eneru.
He's invincible, hence he's "God."
It may be true.
I think you know this,
but we also used to be members of the
Divine Squad that served Gan Fall-sama.
We believed that even if it appeared
that we betrayed the Divine Squad,
by obeying God Eneru and staying on this
island, there was a way to protect people.
However, that approach was pitiful after all!
We tried as much as possible to make
sure that no one would anger God,
or at least that no one would go against him.
That's all we did!
How shameful! How shameful! How shameful!
How shameful!!
I don't think so.
I'm glad to hear you say that.
I don't think you have to feel so bad.
You did it because you were
thinking of everyone's welfare,
so I'd rather want to say thank you.
Captain...
Um... can I ask you to
take care of the people here?
Of course, but where're you going?
Actually, there're people who
don't know the escape route.
Since they're my friends, I have to go back.
Thank you!
Oh, the Blue Sea people...
Heso!
It doesn't look like I can
carry them all at once...
At least, we need to...
somehow escape to the upper area.
Aisa!
You're sure that it's this way, right?!
Yeah! We're very close! I'm sure of it!
Okay!
That's it! Luffy! The hole on the
left-hand side! That's the place!
That's the place?! Alright!!
As I thought, it's apparently not
one of the five that survived...
Honestly... where on earth were they hiding?
Could it be...?
How aggravating... So my
prophecy did not come true.
"God"
Are you that Eneru guy?!
Luffy!!
What're you doing... to my friends?!
Which of that trash are you talking about?
Stay right there! I'm gonna
beat the crap outta you!
Watch your mouth! I am God!
What makes you God?!
He's picking a fight with Eneru big time.
Are you gonna be okay, Luffy?
H-Hey, Luffy! Be caref...
I can hear it now, the angels' party...
It seems that the residents
found out about Skypiea's fate.
I wonder how far they can get
before their foothold is lost.
Like I said... what makes you God?!
You'll know soon enough.
I see... Looks like you're not
an ordinary human, either.
However, you're only a Paramythia.
You haven't got a chance!
Before me, all is futile!
Hence I am God.
El... Thor!!
Luffy!!
Luffy...
Oh, no...
It seems that you dodged
it well... 60 Million Volt...
What?! Dodged it?!
...Jamboule!
100 Million Volt... Vaari!
That's right. It makes sense
when you think about it!
Lightning doesn't work on
Luffy because he's rubber!
Enough... already!!
Calm down! Physical attacks
won't work on my body!
Come to think of it, a monkey
from the Blue Sea like him is...
His lightning power is completely ineffective!
To think that a human that isn't
affected by lightning exists...
It must've been something that
even Eneru couldn't imagine.
It could be... that Luffy is Eneru's one
and only natural enemy in the world!
If you're feeling lonely, talk to me
You gaze at the heavens
as you wander about
Just like the moon,
you keep your gaze constant
And your deep reflection wanes
as you slowly disappear
Stay as you are, let those words guide you
Dream, you travelers who spend
countless nights drifting
Even if you may not be able to go back
you will surely start moving forward again
Look! This is a ship befitting to God!
I will create a world however I please.
Destroy Skypiea and lead me
to the Endless Vearth!
I won't let you have your way!
Now activate, Deathpiea, the circuit of despair!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Maxim Surfaces! Deathpiea Is Activated!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!