Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
Another warrior has perished...
And then there was that earthquake... Damn it!
You're the evil spirits!
--We're going to deal with you right now!
--T-This wasn't the agreement! Stop!
--Stop!
--Look out!
--Seto! Move aside!
--What's the meaning of this?!
The Shandoran warriors
I know and look up to...
...have much more pride than this!
Kid...
"Free from the Spell!
The Great Warrior Sheds Tears!!"
When this sun lowers in the
west and sinks once again...
...your men's lives will be offered to the gods!
Damn it!
The earth certainly swallowed you skillfully!
Truly an act of god! The fact that
you're alive is what's hardest to believe!
The entire ground?!
Prepare for the ceremony!
Take every last sacrifice to the altar!
Hey, wait a little longer!
The commodore'll be back!
Just two more hours! No, one! Please!
Why do we have to be burned at the stake?!
The sun is setting. The ceremony
should be starting soon.
How unsightly! Is this the wreck
of a man who defied the gods?
What are you so afraid of?
What?!
You tremble before intangible fears
and give up people's lives
for false consolation!
False consolation?!
Your sacrifices are nothing
but pointless deaths!
We have lived this way for centuries now!
That doesn't mean it's right!
Silence, outsider!
However great your gods may be,
people's lives are even more precious!
Take the sacrifices to the altar!
Burn them at the stake and
send them into the heavens!
--Commodore!
--We're gonna be set on fire!
You can send an innocent girl to her death...
...and have no qualms about it,
so I doubt you'd understand!
What you're doing is less than human!
No qualms, you say?!
The girl yesterday...
...was my daughter!
You would tell your own
daughter to end her life?!
It's you people who don't
understand how much power there is
in the words our priests hear from the gods!
Our village is commanded to obey!
We can't beg for our children's lives!
It's one size smaller... It must
be the Kashi God's child!
The gods' blood has come
to pass judgment on you!
Judgment, my ass!
Sixty years ago, my own land
lost hundreds of thousands of lives
to the Kinetsu plague that
is ravaging your village now!
But, in recent years, there've been
absolutely no deaths to this disease!
Do you know why?!
Because we discovered a cure for it!
What I'm holding in my right
hand is the bark of a Cona tree!
The Conine I can extract from it is the cure!
If I return with this, I can save the village!
Do you know how many man-hours
have been spent around the world,
and how many victims there have been?!
And you people are trampling
all over this great advancement!
That's why I say your "ceremonies"
are insults to those people!
Will I die in judgment, or in an accident?!
Will your village die by curse, or by disease?!
Are you that afraid of gods?!
I do know when a man is
speaking earnest words...
Answer me.
What did I just kill?!
--A snake.
--No!
I just broke our
commandments and killed a god!
But you call it a snake, and our
deadly curse a curable disease!
Will you really save my beloved village?!
Can you save it?!
I can!
A-A snake!
Is this...?
Hey, Calgara! Look at this!
What a shock! I didn't know
that snake had a grandchild...
"That snake"?
A snake, huh?
Those two make no sense...
They were trying to kill each
other until just recently...
Now, they're such good friends!
Calgara is never very friendly
with any of the villagers, either.
I've never seen him smile like that before...
Just follow me.
We climb down here.
Climb down?
This ringing...
Hey, Calgara! Where is this
beautiful ringing coming from?!
Follow me and you'll see.
They're here!
Lost for words?
This is Shandora, a city of gold.
We are its survivors!
A city of gold...
It's like I'm dreaming!
W-Whoa! It's gold everywhere!
It's a city of treasure!
Hey, guys! Stop!
It's fine.
Load your ship with all the treasure
you can, aside from the gold bell!
Seto! Show them where the treasure is!
--Right!
--Are you sure this is okay?
The villagers already agreed to it.
We owe you for saving our tribe
from that terrible disease.
This is nothing at all.
You're so generous, Great Warrior!
But haven't your people been
protecting the city all this time?
Yes. We've protected the city...
but not necessarily its treasure!
To be more specific...
...only this stone.
What is this? Writing?
Writings of history.
It's known as a "Poneglyph."
We can't read it, either.
You mean your ancestors didn't write this?
All we know for certain is
that this city of Shandora
fought and fell trying to protect this stone.
We must continue to protect it
with that amount of resolve.
As descendants, it is our
duty to protect the proof
that our ancestors fought and survived.
We revere our ancestors as if they were gods.
Still, I had no idea it was this
giant, gold bell I had heard...
This bell's ringing has words to it.
Words?
So that the spirits of our ancestors
who were greeted by the heavens
can return to this land at
any time without getting lost,
we continue to ring this bell,
as a way to say, "We are here!"
Its sound proclaims the
unquestionable glory Shandora once had,
and makes its existence
known to the ends of the sea!
We will never run or hide!
That's why we call this city's
grand bell the "fire of Shandora."
That explains why it has
such a majestic sound!
--Do you think so?!
--Yes!
This fire reached out to us
and helped us arrive here.
I heard this bell in a storm where
it shouldn't have been audible...
You like this bell's sound, too?
Are you going to grow up to be like
that other giant snake someday?
Probably not for a hundred more years!
Hey! Stay here as long as you like, Noland!
You're the first guests here in
the 400 years since Shandora fell!
I want to treat you with lavish hospitality!
I'd love that! I do want to
collect plants from the forest,
and I want to see this
plague all the way through.
Commodore! Commodore!
Hold on, now. What's with the clothes?
Look, look! An Eternal Pose!
And a map, Commodore! A map!
We took these from intruders.
Is that a map of this island?!
Yeah. This skull shape is definitely this island.
The name "Shandora"
means "the skull's right eye,"
which refers to this city's location.
Well, take care! Be sure she gets lots of rest!
Thank you, Doctor!
Hey! Come look, everyone!
Noland's giving us some weird crops!
I have a greenhouse on our ship,
with all kinds of plant samples.
I'll leave some seeds and sprouts
that are suited for your soil.
Is that any good?
Sure is! It's also full of nutrients!
All right! Let's work hard again today!
Work hard doing what?
Having a campfire party?!
Why?! Why would the doctor
and the others do this?!
Chief! Noland and the others are coming!
Listen! Do not speak of last night!
They said they are going
to set sail in a few days.
Do not do anything rash!
I guess we can't understand
each other after all!
No matter how good his
medicine is, he's still a god-killer!
Do they think they're great enough
to stomp all over our history?!
Endure it! Suppress your feelings,
and quietly wait for them to leave!
They're here!
Hey, guys! Is Calgara around?
Why is everyone acting so coldly
all of a sudden? Where's Calgara?
You guys are outsiders!
Calgara doesn't want to see you anymore!
Seto!
When are you gonna leave, anyway?!
Eh?!
They suddenly seem to hate us now...
Hey, hold on, you guys!
You can't just start acting like this!
Stop.
Let's continue our work.
We still have some forest to inspect.
Here you are, Calgara!
Noland was looking for you!
Yeah. I don't want to see his face anymore.
If I do, I think I might kill him!
The bell didn't ring today...
Yeah. It's the first time this's happened
in the month we've been here.
Commodore...
I'll be finished exploring
the forest in two days.
Y-Yes, sir...
Tell the crew we set sail again in three days,
so now's their last chance to
enjoy solid ground for a while.
Commodore... To be honest, I wanna
get off this awkward island...
Only after we've finished
our duties! Get some sleep.
Live here, Noland!
I know! Why don't you
make Mousse your wife?!
Don't be silly.
I have a family back home, with kids
about her age. I have to go back.
Calgara doesn't want to see you anymore!
When are you gonna leave, anyway?!
I know you're here, Calgara! Come out!
Don't you think this is too one-sided?!
Tell me why! I won't
understand unless you tell me!
We're going to set sail very soon!
I don't want to part ways like this!
Don't show your face around me!
Do you want your wife to end up a widow?!
Calgara!
If you're feeling lonely, talk to me
You gaze at the heavens
as you wander about
Just like the moon,
you keep your gaze constant
And your deep reflection wanes
as you slowly disappear
Stay as you are, let those words guide you
Dream, you travelers who spend
countless nights drifting
Even if you may not be able to go back
you will surely start moving forward again
The bell has lost all its meaning!
I only did what satisfied me!
If these were sacrifices
for your "advancements,"
we should never have accepted you!
They're right to be angry.
We have no reason to be forgiven!
We're returning to the Lvneel Kingdom!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Eternal Friends! The Vowed Bell
Echoes Across the Mighty Seas!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!