Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The Going Merry fell right into the
middle of a Naval base, Navarone.
Luffy and the others dispersed
under the cover of darkness.
Nami successfully disguised
herself as a cleaning person.
"On Duty"
Luffy and Sanji slipped into
the dining hall as cooks.
However, one of the crew,
Zoro, has been captured.
Welcome to Navarone.
"Captured Zoro and
Chopper's Emergency Operations!"
So six more, huh?
One of the Straw Hat Pirates, Roronoa Zoro...
Drake, shall we try questioning him?
But you told us to check
the dining hall, Commander.
Hm? I did?
You said that everyone gets hungry,
so they're likely to appear in the dining hall.
I'll go to the dining hall.
Jessica told me that new cooks from
headquarters are coming as well, so...
How should we proceed
with questioning Zoro?
"Justice"
I'll leave it to you.
Man... What the hell's with these guys?
Well, I guess I'll take it easy for a while.
Open the cell.
Yes, sir, Lt. Commander Drake!
But he's extremely dangerous.
By order of Vice Admiral Jonathan,
I'll question Roronoa Zoro.
Yes, sir! Please be careful.
Roronoa Zoro... You used
to be called a pirate hunter.
I would never have imagined that you'd
be a member of the Straw Hat Pirates.
What, you came all the
way here to tell me that?
Where did you come from?!
How many of you are there?!
What is your purpose
in invading this fortress?!
It was a good strategy to invade this
"hedgehog" fortress from the sky.
How did you do it?
Did you build a launch pad?!
Oh, we came from heaven.
Don't mock me!
I'm not mocking you or anything.
We really came from the sky.
I don't intend to go along with such a joke!
Like I said, we came from heaven
by riding a floating octopus balloon.
Got it?
So you insist on that, no matter what?
Don't make light of the Navy!
I'm gonna make you tell
us the truth at any cost!
"On Duty"
Next, you'll be in charge of
cleaning this exercise hall.
Okay, Boss!
"On Duty"
What is this...?
I have to clean this... by myself?!
Give the floor a good polish!
You'll enjoy lunch after your hard work!
This disguise may have been a mistake!
I heard that one of the
Straw Hat Pirates was captured!
What?! That wasn't a ghost ship, then?!
Yeah, in a sense, it's scarier than ghosts.
Don't be surprised when I tell you this.
It's Roronoa Zoro, the pirate hunter!
--Whoa!
--What?!
There should be other
crewmembers hiding, too.
If we could find even one
of them, we'd get noticed!
Y-Yeah!
To think that Zoro was caught...!
What am I gonna do?!
According to what they just said,
everyone else seems to be okay.
Darn! I wanna get out of here already!
But I don't know where they are,
and I don't know what to do...
What's that?!
If I continue to live like this,
I'll break down before I get caught!
Hold it!
Help!!
So it wasn't me...
But I have to come up with
a different disguise... Hm?
This is it!
Th-This isn't good! It's a dead end!
The raccoon dog went that way!
All right! The corner is raccoon dogged...
no, the raccoon dog is cornered!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
He's not here.
So he really was a raccoon dog.
He disappeared!
Hm?
He's in there.
It'll be a lot of work finding him in here!
--Ah!
--Shh!
Here we go!
What're these?!
Did he leave just his antlers?!
Who knows? But with just antlers,
we can't even make a pot dish.
Dammit! Did we lose him on our way here?!
I'm saved...
Where is the package?
It's probably that way.
Ah! This is it!
What're they doing with deer antlers?
I heard that they'll be used
as ingredients for medicine.
What?! What happened?!
They said that they ran into a storm.
Many were injured. Hurry it up!
Take them to the medical room quickly!
Let me see... Plunge the scalpel
vertically, and if it bleeds...
Blood, blood, blood...!
Honestly! Why did all the doctors
have to go on a business trip at once?
Oh, God, please don't
send any surgery patients!
--Medical Room Chief!
--Yes...
We brought the deer antlers,
the medicine ingredient.
Oh... Please leave them there.
Okay!
Where am I?
I look pretty good in this uniform,
if I do say so myself.
I'll be fine if I look like this!
Ugh! I'm sorry!
What're you apologizing for?!
Go to the medical room already!
What?! Hm? Huh?
There's an emergency!
All the nurses are being called in!
I knew it... I'm screwed no
matter what clothes I wear!
Dr. Kobato! It's an emergency!
I-Internal case? Pediatrics? Or...
There're quite a few seriously
injured marines on the Stan Marey!
S-Surgery?!
I-I'll leave them to you nurses,
since surgery isn't my field.
What're you saying?! You're the
only doctor in this base right now!
But...! I'm a pediatrician and,
um, surgery is outside my field!
Oh... This seems to be a medical room.
But I wonder if that doctor is gonna be okay...
One, two, three!
This is crazy! Did they run
into a cyclone or something?!
Here, treat their injuries!
Okay!
Darn! I don't have time for stuff like this!
We have to quickly find the Going Merry
and leave this place right away!
I-I'm sorry!
Stop daydreaming!
Doctor, what should we do?!
Right... right... Give him 50 mg of painkiller!
What about preparing the operation room?
Operation?! Operation...
Yeah, he needs an operation...
Doctor!
--Doctor! There's no time to lose!
--Please get a grip!
Please advise us on treating the patients!
--Doctor...
--I can't just stand back and watch!
I'll advise you all!
First, give this patient phenicol,
cardiotonic and tialcillin.
Respond if you got that!
Yes, doctor!
Perform cross-matching
with each patient's blood type!
Those who require an operation,
give them preoperative treatment!
Give that patient a tetanus
toxoid and 5 mg of morphine!
Yes, doctor!
Is the operation room ready?!
It's ready!
Then bring the patients in,
starting with seriously injured ones!
Yes, doctor!
Get a grip, doctor!
Chopper!
Nami! What are you doing in a place like this?!
What're you doing here?!
Excuse me... I don't know
what's going on, since I fainted...
You're... a doctor, right?
I don't know who you are, but you
saved us with your apt instructions.
--You're not saved yet!
--What?!
There're a number of soldiers whose lives
are in danger without an operation!
Yes...
Start the operations on seriously
injured patients as soon as possible!
Yes... Operations...
What's with you?!
I-I can't...
Can't do what?
I can't bear things like seeing
people in pain and bleeding at all.
When I'm really terrible even at giving shots,
to think of cutting a human body
or putting stitches on it...
I can't believe this! This is a naval base, right?!
How have you been giving treatments
until now if you're like this?!
My field is pediatrics. Since the other
doctors are all out on business trips,
I was asked to serve as a
deputy Medical Room Chief.
Deputy...?
Deputy or not, you're the
Medical Room Chief right now, right?!
Y-Yes, more or less...
More or less?!
Chopper! Let's get out of here already!
But...
We can get out! This place isn't
a lake! It's connected to the sea!
We can get out with the Going Merry!
--I can't go yet.
--What?!
You're a doctor, a person that
saves people's lives, aren't you?!
Yes... but even for a doctor,
there're things they can and can't do...
The person who taught me
medicine told me this story.
There was a man who was told by
his doctor that he was going to die.
He wandered in despair,
searching for a place to die.
But as he was passing over a mountain,
he saw vivid cherry blossoms
blooming all over the mountain.
He went to see a doctor again.
And the doctor said to him...
"You're completely healthy."
You're the only doctor to the patients here!
You're the only one who can save them!
You mustn't give up! There's no illness
in this world that can't be healed!
You mustn't say that
there're things you can't do!
There're no patients that
we doctors can't heal!
Doctors can make miracles happen!
At least, we have to believe that!
Say...
...will I be able to see
the cherry blossoms, too?
Or rather... can I show the cherry
blossoms to people who're suffering?
Yeah, of course! I'll help you!
H-Hey! We don't have time for that!
We don't, but people's lives have
priority over anything! I'm a doctor!
Are you serious?! You'll get left behind,
you know! Is that what you want?!
Doctor, preparations for
the operations are ready!
Okay! I'll be right over!
Chop... Dr. Chopper!
All right.
Chopper!
It's okay to leave me behind.
If I leave here now,
I'll be scolded by Doctorine!
Geez, you know we can't
just leave without you!
"Operating Room"
We had a doctor like that here?
We'll start the emergency operations.
There's a piece of iron in his chest.
We need to remove it.
The patient is already sleeping
soundly from the anesthesia.
--Scalpel!
--Yes, doctor!
Dr. Kobato! You'll be fine!
You're the one who can show
cherry blossoms to this patient!
Yes!
It's near an artery, so be careful.
Yes.
Nami, suction!
Yes, doctor!
The iron piece has been removed.
--I did it!
--This is no time to celebrate!
There're many other patients!
--Yes!
--Let's give it our best!
Yes!
What?! A doctor you've never
seen is performing an operation?
Yes, sir!
It might be one of the Straw Hats.
Chopper...
Pardon me!
We're in the middle of
an operation. Please leave!
It's an emergency! Dr. Kobato,
I wanna ask you something.
Dr. Kobato! His blood pressure is dropping!
Give him 6 units of red blood cell
suspension and 1 unit of platelets!
Yes, doctor!
It's all right. Continue the blood
transfusion! Also have dopamine ready!
--Dr. Kobato!
--We're in the middle of an
emergency operation! Please be quiet!
You're operating?! You fainted when
you saw blood flowing out of my arm!
A doctor we've never seen
before should be in there.
You're interrupting!
All you'll find in here are doctors and nurses
giving their all to save precious lives!
Let's go.
--Monitor them.
--Yes, sir.
Suture completed!
Doctor, that was the last patient.
Good work, Dr. Kobato!
Ch-Chopper!
You're a great doctor, Dr. Kobato.
Not at all... but you are a
great doctor, Mr. Raccoon Dog.
You dummy! I'm not a
raccoon dog! I'm a reindeer!
Shouldn't she be rather surprised
to see Chopper like that?
Honestly, what am I doing in a place like this?!
We don't even know if Nami-san
and Robin-chan are okay.
Ahh! But out of regard for Jessica-san,
I can't just abandon this task.
Yeah, exactly.
Hey, what're you doing?!
Well, I was watching this thing
and admiring how incredible it is.
Either help me out or come up
with a way to get us out of here.
Just do something!
But I wonder why we're not
getting out of this place?
It's come to this because you were dawdling!
--Say, Sanji...
--What?!
Octopuses can be eaten raw, right?
So what?!
How is it? Is your stuff ready?
If you take your time, the next
100 soldiers are gonna show up.
Oh, Jessica-san! I've just finished it!
Oh, yeah?! It's finally break time? I'm tired!
You didn't do anything!
Then I'd like you to chop up 300 more onions.
What?! Is she a devil?
Okay! I'm your servant, Jessica-san!
I get it! It's your fault it's come to this, Sanji!
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Rush forth, rush forth,
on the road opened before us
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
We won't give in, we won't give in,
even if the obstacle is big
It's nothing to be scared of,
we can overcome it
Dammit! That bastard! That hurt!
Anyway, are the others okay?
Oh, hey, Usopp! Is our ship all right?!
Robin, why're you dressed like that?
Captain and the idiot cook...
Never mind about them.
Looks like the situation is starting to change.
--On the next episode of One Piece!
--Don't read my line!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Navy's Dragnet Closes In!
The Second Member Captured!"
I'm gonna be a great swordsman!!
Hey!