Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
Run! Run! Run!!
W-Wait up!
Where's the Going Merry?!
"Enter the Hot-Blooded Special Forces!
Battle on the Bridge!"
S-Someone...
Hey! There's still one here!
Damn, I can't believe the Straw Hats
left one of their crew behind!
N-No! I'm Major Shepherd,
an inspector from the Navy!
--Give me a hand!
--Inspector?
I have to contact HQ...
...and let them know
Navarone let pirates escape...
You're a pathetic liar, Condoriano!
You may think you can fool us,
but you're wrong!
Take him away!
Condoriano?!
W-What is this?!
--Give it up, already!
--Let go! I am not Condoriano! I'm Shepherd!
Major Shepherd, an inspector from the Navy!!
W-What is it?!
Marines!
T-This way, too?!
This is bad! Very bad!
There's no way out of this!
Things are finally getting interesting!
The old fortress guy said there's
absolutely no escape from this place!
I can believe that. There are at least
1,000 marines stationed here...
And just how is that interesting?
There's absolutely no escape!
--Again, how is that interesting?!
--Just forget it, Usopp.
Once he says something, he doesn't stop...
Unit 37 has arrived!
Unit 44 has arrived!
Capture the Straw Hat crew!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Don't let them escape! After them!
Stop, Straw Hat!
Those are the Straw Hats!
--A dead-end?!
--No, we can run along the cliff...
So you've finally shown yourself, Straw Hat?
The commander of Navarone!
Jonathan, was it?
Old fortress guy! What're you doing there?
This is my room.
F-Fire cannons!
Huh? B-But firing at the central tower isn't--
I don't care! Fire!
L-Luffy! Luffy! Oh, yikes!
Whadya think?! I rescued my crew!
I told you, I'll leave when I wanna leave!
Indeed. So do you want to leave now?
Yeah! We're gonna leave now!
Think you can escape
from Navarone-- no, from me?
We won't get caught! We're pirates!
Run!
They got away!
Commander! Unit 21 is currently
in Block 7, ready to ambush them!
This is our chance to drive them
there and take them all out at once!
Have the men withdraw from Block 7.
It's a dead-end there! It's the perfect chance...
The Straw Hats don't play by the book.
Never underestimate someone
with a 100 million-Berry bounty.
A proper fight would result in
significant injuries to the soldiers.
There is no point in needless
casualties or destroying our own base.
Yes, sir!
They will, without fail, head for
the dock to retrieve their ship.
Let's have a counterattack waiting
for the seven pirates at Dock 88.
Stop, Straw Hats!
--Drake.
--Sir!
Rush ahead to the dock and lead
the capture of the Straw Hats.
Use of the weapon is granted.
Yes, sir!
But won't it take time for
Lt. Commander Drake to reach Dock 88?
Yes, that's true.
For them to proceed to Dock 88,
they will have to cross this bridge.
We simply need to defend it.
I suppose I'll lure them to the
Straw Gate on the upper deck...
However strong they may be,
it will take some work to break
through if we fortify the Straw Gate.
That should buy us some time.
I see.
Now, then. Which unit shall I have defend it?
I guess it would have to be them...
--# We are the Navarone Marines! #
--# We'll show you our fiery spirit! #
Of course!
Please leave Straw Bridge to us, Unit 55!
We will crush the Straw Hats, without fail!
# We'll show you our fiery spirit! #
# We are the Navarone Marines! #
I leave it to you...
Umm... Excuse me...
--What is it?
--Did something happen?
Pirates have escaped!
Vile ones called the
"Straw Hats," with bounties!
Apparently, a few are still
holed up inside the base.
Now what?! Luffy and the others
have already sprung into action!
They're probably headed for the
dock where the Going Merry is...
That means Luffy rescued Zoro!
What're you so happy about?!
We don't know the fortress' layout yet,
or even have an escape plan!
Why couldn't they have stayed still?!
B-But now we have no choice
but to go to the dock too...
In any case, we gotta get out of here
and meet up with the others...
The problem is them...
Kobato-san! We know that one of
the pirates is disguised as a doctor!
You're done operating! Let us look inside!
Kobato-san!
--Kobato-san! Open the door!
--T-This is bad! Very bad!
You two!
U-Uhh, Dr. Kobato...
I'm sorry I didn't say anything!
It's true! We're... pirates...
Please run! There are pirates
loose inside the base!
How terrifying! What's more,
they're pretending to be doctors!
You two could be in danger!
U-Uhh, well...
The truth is, those pirates... They're us.
We're pirates!
And I know this is shameless,
but you seem like a nice person,
so we have a favor to ask!
Could you tell us where the docks are?
We're in a really big hurry!
Pirates!!
--That scream!
--Kobato-san!
Kobato-san! What happened?!
Kobato-san!
--Something happened inside!
--Alright! Knock it down!
--Kobato-san!
--Are you all right?!
--W-What the--?
Are you alright?! Hey, say something!
What?! They escaped through the ducts?!
So they escaped through there?
Y-Yes! Hurry and catch them!
You're awake, Dr. Kobato--
Sorry! I understand why you want to shout,
but could you stay quiet for a bit?
Nami! Let's get out of here, quick!
C-Come to think of it, who are you?
Eh? Me?
Oh, it's me.
I, umm, ate a Devil Fruit, so I can transform.
She is such a ditz.
Oh, yeah. Dr. Kobato. I know
how hard it is to understand,
but there's no time to
explain the details right now.
It's all right. Nothing else
can surprise me now.
Well, we gotta go. There's no
telling when the marines'll be back.
Oh, wait! Mr. Deer!
Even if you are a pirate and a magical deer,
you taught me what it means to be a doctor!
I'd, uhh, like to thank you somehow...
I don't need thanks...
And I'm not a deer. I'm a reindeer!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, right! You're looking for the docks!
I could lead the way, if you'd like!
You'll take us there?!
B-But won't you get in
trouble for helping pirates?
Yes. But if things turn bad, I can just
pretend I've been taken hostage!
--Good thinking!
--So if I can be of help...
Looks like they can't see us here.
No, don't let your guard down.
The old fortress guy is tough.
You're the one who
shouldn't let his guard down!
Dock 88 is on the other side of that!
That's where the Going Merry's being kept!
But it looks like we'll run into lots of trouble...
How about up there?
It seems crossable!
But it's strange. There's no one there.
It's almost like they're inviting us up...
A trap, huh?
A trap?!
It's the same either way! Plus,
I've decided that we're leaving!
And worrying about
annoying crap is annoying.
Doesn't matter what traps come our way.
Hey, Luffy! Ahh, Sanji! Not you too, Zoro!
No, I don't wanna go!
If you get caught in a trap,
I'm not gonna come save you!
Without my help, you're gonna die!
Is that what you want?!
But save me if I get in trouble, okay?!
Where's my reply?!
Where is your ship?
There are actually many docks here...
Judging from where our ship landed,
it's probably in a dock on
the western side of the base.
The western side? Then I
suppose it could be Dock 88...
What makes you think that, Kobato-san?
Yes, well, because of budget cuts and all that,
our number of docks has been reduced.
But there's still equipment in that one,
and actually, that's where my father is!
It's right by where that warship is stopped.
What do we do, Nami? Are they headed there?
There's no way for us to know right now.
Now that they've already caused
trouble, we can't just sit around idly!
Let's rely on Dr. Kobato to lead the way!
There's no one here...
That's perfect, then! Let's get going!
--Hey!
--Wait, Luffy! You moron!
He never learns...
So high up! Yikes!
Oh! There they are!
See! W-What did I tell ya?!
So that's the score. Looks like
this'll be a good little workout...
I'm leaving, no matter what!
We, the Hot-Blooded Unit of Navarone,
will guard this bridge to the death!
We will never let the likes
of you pirates cross it!
Don't be so damn boastful.
Just sit there and wait while I have a smoke.
Don't underestimate us!
# We are the Navarone Marines! #
# We'll show you our fiery spirit! #
That's neat! Is this how it goes?
Charge!
Gatling!
Zoro!
--Outta the way!
--Okay!
Alright! Zoro! Fight bravely!
Prepare yourself, Straw Hat!
That's neat! Gum-Gum...
Now!
We studied your moves, Straw Hat!
W-What?! What?!
Don't be interruptin' my smoke break!
Bastards...
Your fates end here!
Damn crappy marine!
Hey, guys! What're you doing?!
Fight for real, will ya?!
I have you now!
H-Huh?!
I chopped with all my strength!
An Impact Dial!
There's... no end to 'em!
Listen up, you lousy pirates!
We're the "N" at the beginning of "Navarone"!
We'll risk our spirit to make sure
you pirates never cross this bridge!
Shut the hell up, you stone-head!
Oww!
Ugh. There's no end to this!
Those are neat things you have!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
Now! Grab his arms while
they're slowed down!
I'm not letting go this time!
You're so stubborn!
Gum-Gum...
Uh oh.
...Battle-Axe!
Geez. You never think
about the consequences!
I'm sorry...
Well, let's go. Which way is it?
Oh. That way.
Commander!
Part of the Straw Gate has been demolished,
and the Straw Hats have fallen into the bay.
Moreover, Unit 55 appears to have
no casualties or missing persons.
Whoa, now! That's clearly
far too much destruction!
Those guys...
But they did buy us 22 minutes.
You showed us your fiery spirit, Unit 55.
Commander! The special capture
operation at Dock 88 is ready!
We can now capture the Straw Hats!
Excellent. They've passed through Straw Gate,
so they're definitely headed for Dock 88.
Stay calm, and don't let your guard down!
You're sure it's this way, Usopp?!
Don't worry! This is it! Just keep moving!
Here they come!
Commence the capture operation!
Wha--?!
There's an urgent patient
at the dock! Let us through!
--Nami-san nurse!
--W-What is this?!
L-Luffy!
Yo...
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Rush forth, rush forth,
on the road opened before us
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
We won't give in, we won't give in,
even if the obstacle is big
It's nothing to be scared of,
we can overcome it
Flare bombs can't shut my eyes!
--Impressive, moss-head!
--Thanks, fancy-eyebrows!
--Bring it on, moss-head!
--You crappy cook!
This is no time to be arguing!
You will never reach your ship!
I'm out of strength again...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Breaking Through the Siege!
The Going Merry Is Recovered"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!