Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Gum-Gum...
What do you mean by that?
Please reduce it to a week.
Don't mess with me!
You could've eaten it if you
took that bug out, couldn't you?
It took three full days to
cook it, skimming the scum...
I'm a customer! I'm paying you!
Can money... satisfy your hunger?
What'd you say?!
I'm asking, "Can it...
satisfy your hunger?!"
"Unwelcome Customer!
Sanji's Food and Ghin's Debt"
I can't... hold it anymore...
Serving customers! That is "love"!
And "love" means "restaurant"!
The customer is king!!
Motto! Motto! Service motto!
Service is about pleasant greetings!
Welcome, ya damn crook.
Please never come back.
I'm terribly sorry.
Ten thousand berries coming in!
You look pathetic!
All right! I took a healthy dump, and
I'm in excellent shape again today!
Oh? Welcome, ya damn crook.
Motto! Motto! Service motto!
The customer is...
Ahh! Our customer!
You again, Sanji! What're you
doing to our customer?!
Of all people, he's a Navy Lieutenant!
What is it, you damn cook?!
Don't call my name as
if I were your friend!
A damn cook has no right
to call me "damn cook"!
Restaurants can't exist
without customers!
Hurting our precious customer...
What do you think you're doing?!
What's the big deal with customers?
He treated the food carelessly.
On top of that, he insulted cooks.
So I taught him a lesson.
What's with this restaurant...
No restaurant should treat
its customers like this...
I'll shut it down... I'll shut down
this restaurant! I'll shut it down!!
I'll contact the government
immediately and...
Then I'd better finish you off here...
Stop it, Sous Chef!
--A stuck up asshole like you
--What're you doing?!
If you keep going at him,
--A stuck up asshole like you
--What're you doing?!
If you keep going at him,
--who's too big for his britches
--we'll be in a big trouble!
Stop it, Sanji!! Stop it!
--who's too big for his britches
--we'll be in a big trouble!
Stop it, Sanji!! Stop it!
--just pisses me off!!
--You're going too far, Sanji!
So you think you're a big shot?! Huh?!
--What happened?
--Oh, boy...
--What now?
--What happened?
Boy... that startled me...
O-Owner! What the heck are you doing?!
Oh, dammit!! The ceiling
of my restaurant...
It's your fault, you brat!!
You broke it yourself!
What're you doing, Owner?!
You can do that later!
Please stop, Sanji!!
Hey, Sanji!
Are you going on a rampage in
the restaurant again, you idiot?!
Shut up, you damn geezer!
What'd you say?! Who do
you think you're talking to?!
Are you trying to put my
restaurant out of business?!
You brat!!
You, too! Get out of here already!
What's with this restaurant?
Even the owner is like a gangster...
It's as if... as if...
this were a pirate ship!
You listen! The customer is king!
Just those who eat your
damn crappy dishes.
Patty, Sanji! If you wanna
fight, do it in the kitchen!
Are these idiots really cooks?
L-Lieutenant! Lieutenant Fullbody!
W-We've got trouble!
Geez... what a wild restaurant...
Pirate Krieg's underling escaped!
What?!
After seven of us finally captured him
to get a lead on the Krieg Pirates...
Can't be! When we captured him three
days ago, he was close to starving!
And we haven't fed him at all since!
K-Krieg Pirates...
They're the ones who're said to be
the strongest pirates in the East Blue...
I'm very...
We have a new customer.
He'd better not be someone who'll
go on a rampage in my place.
A pirate, huh?
Anything's fine. Bring me food.
This is a restaurant, right?
Welcome, ya damn crook.
I'll say it only one more time,
so listen good. Bring me food.
That cook is gonna get killed...
Um, sir, I'm terribly sorry,
but do you have money for that?
--Would a bullet do?
--So you don't have money, right?
What?!
Patty, that dumb ass!
He broke the chair...
What power!
If you can't pay for the food,
you're not a customer.
Good job, Cook!
Beat that pirate up, Patty-san!
Oh... Your stomach is grumbling, pirate.
That was a fart, you stupid
racoon dog. Just bring me food.
If you're not a customer,
beat it already!!
I-I've had enough already!
I don't want anything
to do with this restaurant!
I-I'll never come back here!
Now, dumb customers,
please continue your meal!
Please never come back. Hmph!
Dammit! If I were in a normal
state, I wouldn't have been...
...mocked by someone like that...
Hey, are you hungry by any chance?
Shut up! I'm not hungry!
Eat it.
Shut up! Beat it!
Even when I'm down and out,
I won't take charity from others.
Take this food away now!
Stop whining and eat it already!
To me, anyone who's
hungry is a customer.
Sorry, but I'm not a customer.
How large and cruel the ocean is...
How scary it is to lose food
and water on the ocean...
How hard it is...
I can understand how a hungry
person feels more than anyone.
You can die for your pride if you want,
but if you eat and survive, don't you
think there's a future for you?
Sorry...
Sorry... Thank you... I thought I'd die.
I thought I was done...
Delicious... Delicious...
I've never eaten food so delicious.
It's damn delicious, isn't it?
I found a good cook!
Hey you, it's a good thing
that he gave you food!
You almost died!
Hey you, cook! Join my group!
Huh?
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
--Huh?!
Are you a pirate?
Yep!
Why the hell did you shoot
a cannonball into this restaurant?
That was an accident!
A self-defense, stray shot.
A what now?
In any event, don't do anything
stupid to this restaurant.
The owner of this place used to be
a cook in a famous pirate group.
I see... So pops was a pirate...
To that damn geezer, this
restaurant is like his treasure...
On top of that, those cooks, who
came here out of admiration for him,
are all hot-headed just like pirates.
Well, they're actually perfect for
this place since pirates come and go.
Yeah, this restaurant is really wild.
Yeah. This is how it is here every day.
There're even customers
who come to see
fights between cooks
and pirates these days.
Because of that, the waiters
all got scared and ran away.
Ah, I see... That's why pops
told me to work here for a year...
Hey, join our group.
I refuse. There's a reason that
I have to work in this restaurant.
No! I refuse!
Wh-What do you mean?!
I refuse your refusal!
You're a good cook,
so let's be pirates together.
Hey, listen to what I say.
So what's that reason?
I don't need to tell you.
Huh? You just told me
to listen to what you say!
I'm telling you
to accept what I say!
I'm gonna cut you into three
pieces, you damn straw hat!
What'd you say?!
I'm gonna beat you up
if you make fun of the
straw hat, you jerkwad!
Sorry to interrupt...
--What?!
I'm Ghin of the Krieg Pirates.
You're a pirate, too, right?
Do you have any goals?
I'm aiming for the One Piece.
I'm going to enter the Grand Line.
Given that you're looking for a cook,
it seems you have only a few members.
Yep. He's the fifth member.
Why are you counting me?!
Since you seem like
a nice guy, I'll warn you.
The Grand Line is the one
place you should avoid.
You're still young.
You don't need to rush.
The Grand Line is only a small
portion of the entire ocean.
If you wanna be a pirate,
there's an endless ocean out there.
I see... You know something
about the Grand Line?
No... I don't know anything...
I don't understand anything about it...
That's exactly why I fear it...
You're an underling of that Krieg,
and yet you talk so wimpy...
Hmm? Who's Krieg?
The hors d'oeuvre for
table three is ready!
Take it yourself.
We don't have any waiters.
Is it really okay, though, Patty?
Is what okay?
I hear the guy you beat up
earlier in the restaurant
is one of the Krieg Pirates.
Oh yeah, I heard.
"Don Krieg" is the strongest
and most evil pirate
in this part of the ocean.
That's right.
Hmm?
After all, he's the don of
a pirate fleet that controls
the captains of 50 pirate ships.
He's no less than a monster...
So, what's the big deal?
I heard that his extraordinary force
consists of more than 5,000 pirates.
For example, if that guy from earlier
told Don Krieg what
happened to him here,
this restaurant would
probably be crushed
like a large parade of
elephants stomping on ants.
Oh, yeah?
Then you're saying that
I should've just treated him?
That's rude to the other customers.
It will ruin the reputation
of the famous fighting cooks
at the Sea Restaurant Baratie!
How many pirates do you
think we've beaten off?
If you're that scared, just quit!
What'd you say?!
Oh yeah, all the waiters
quit because of those words of yours!
Patty! It's your fault
that we're this busy!
Ha! Those wimps were
useless from the start!
Go for it!
Carne, take him out!
Patty, beat him!
Hey, you idiots! Get to work already!
Yes, Owner!
So long, then...
But I'm still going to the Grand Line.
Yeah. Do whatever you like.
I'm a stranger to you. I don't
have the right to try to stop you.
I just wanted to warn you.
And Sanji-san, thank you so much!
I owe my life to you. The food you
gave me was the most delicious.
Is it okay if I come back for it?
Any time!
Hey, you, chore boy!
Ugh! Pops!
There you are!
Go, Ghin.
Ahh, sorry.
You're gonna get yelled at,
because you fed me free, right?
Well...
...there's no proof, so there's no
reason for me to be yelled at.
Don't ever get caught again, Ghin!
Thank you, Sanji-san!
I'll never forget your kindness!
Sanji! Chore boy! Get to work already!
Hey, table three is ready!
I'm Luffy!
I'll be the chore boy from now.
Nice to meet you all!
Isn't the dessert for
table six ready yet?!
Hey, who's responsible for that order?!
Isn't that you?!
I'm too busy right now!
That's because you keep spacing out!
What'd you say?! Wanna fight?!
If you have nothing to do, wash
dishes or something, chore boy!
Where's Sanji?
He's hitting on a customer
in the dining room.
Again?!
I'm already annoyed by him just
being the Sous Chef to begin with!
It can't be helped since he's
worked here the longest.
Do you know why he keeps staying here
when he doesn't get along with Owner?
He's aiming to be the next Head Chef.
You can tell if you watch him.
--Huh?
Hey, chore boy!
How many dishes have
you broken so far?!
Oh, sorry. I forgot to count.
That's not what I meant!
Apologize for breaking them!
Forget about washing
dishes. Clean that area!
Okay, leave it to me!
Don't take food!
That's a main dish!!
Oh, don't worry about it!
Ouch!!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Would you get out
of the kitchen already?!
You go take orders, okay?
Go ask what customers want
to eat! You can do it, can't you?!
Yes...
Chores're sure tiring. It must've
been a lot of work for Koby, too.
Hey, chore boy!
Ugh! You guys...
I hear you have to work for a year here!
Is it okay if we redraw
our flag for the ship?
Ahhh... You're eating
yummy food without me?!
How could you?!
That's our business, right, guys?
Take this!
Y-Yeah...
Well, it's true that
the food here is good.
I feel bad for you, but...
...drink it yourself!
--I can't believe you did that!
My stomach hurts! That was nasty!
How noisy... Could they be his buddies?
Do it yourself.
Oh, dear ocean!
I thank you for today's encounter!
What?!
Oh, love, I can't bear this hardship.
Go ahead and laugh at me.
I'm now prepared to be a lowly
pirate or devil if I'm with you!
However, how tragic it is! There's
too great an obstacle between us!
That obstacle is me, right, Sanji?
Damn geezer!
This is a good opportunity. Why don't
you become a pirate with them?
You're no longer needed
at this restaurant!
I see...
That cook saved your life,
and you were able to come back here...
Is that what you're saying, Ghin?
Y-Yes... B-But...
I never imagined the main
ship was in this condition...
Don Krieg!
What?
I'll take you there...
to the Sea Restaurant Baratie...
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
The customer is king.
That's right! Smile no
matter who the customer!
Hey, a big fish is here!
--That's...
--Krieg Pirates!
That's a large pirate group
with a 5,000-pirate force!
5,000? I wonder if we
have enough chairs...
Idiot! They came to attack this
place! Close the restaurant!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Strongest Pirate Fleet!
Commodore Don Krieg"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!