It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Armée de l'Air Power Shoot!
Go!
Goal!
Goal! Goal!
Team Straw Hat is victorious!
Shelly!
Wh-What's this?!
Captain Monkey D. Luffy has
chosen Shelly, Tonjit's former horse!
What in the world is he thinking?!
Old stilts guy. I took Shelly
back from those guys.
You guys...
Now you can always be together.
I truly appreciate this. Thank you.
Well, that explains that.
Guess it couldn't be helped this time!
That's a good girl!
Chopper!
Got a problem with that?
Nope!
Chopper...
Leave it to me! It'll be just fine!
Yeah, sure. Uh-huh.
I wonder what the next game will be.
Let's get started!
We will win Chopper back!
"Round 3!
The Round-and-Round Roller Race!"
Don't worry, Shelly. I'm sure it'll be all right.
Let's have faith in them.
"Delectable oden"
Two daikon sticks and two
mochi tofu pouches, please.
You got it!
--Bring Support Pillar #6!
--Hurry it up!
Hey, where'd you put my wood plane?!
This next game sounds fun.
"Foxy Life!"
Fun? How can you say that, Robin?
Put yourself in Chopper's shoes. Poor guy...
That's a good point. I apologize.
It's no big deal...
...compared to these carefree dimwits!
Oh, ladies!
--You're both so lovely!
--Oh! Are you ready?
What are you eating, Luffy?
A Long Kiwi!
That old hooorse guy gave
it to me! It's pretty good!
--You can't have it.
--I don't want it!
Mellorine!
It's time for Round #3,
the "Run Roller Round" roller skating race!
It's a head-to-head race on an outdoor track!
Once again, the rules are simple!
First, each team's scorer will start
skating at the sound of the first whistle,
and team defenders will follow suit after
the second whistle 20 seconds later.
Defenders can hinder the opposing
team or root for their own!
Anything goes!
After five minutes are up, the team
whose scorer is in the lead wins!
Naturally, being even a single step
ahead means victory in that round!
Incidentally, yours truly will
be doing the play-by-play
from a special seat by the starting line!
All right! It's time for
both teams to come on out!
Okay, guys. We have to
get Chopper back this time.
Let's do it!
Yeah!
Oh! The Straw Hat Dangers
come out with a war cry!
And lying in wait are the
indomitable Foxy Devils!
First is the team's playmaker, Porche-chan!
Next is the speedy Chiqicheetah
and Masshikaku, the defense's linchpin!
Then there's the fishmen Jube and Girarin!
Oh, and last but not least!
Our own Foxy is the head coach,
with Hamburg as manager!
A truly powerful lineup, indeed!
H-Huh?!
Oh, my! Chiqicheetah is clashing
even before the starting whistle?!
What's with this guy?! He's creepin' me out...
He's indeed a quick runner,
but he's also sensitive to smells!
You ate something pungent, didn't you?!
Ha! You didn't eat that old guy's
rotten hunk of milk, did ya?
Oh, is that why?
You did eat it?!
M-Man, you're rude!
Shoo! Shoo!
Looks like nothing happened...
Allow me to continue explaining the rules!
Each team has a coach and a manager!
Neither is allowed to directly
participate in the game!
Be aware that a person
can only be a scorer once!
Oh, but there are only four
Straw Hats who can serve as scorers!
They're one man short!
What will come of this?!
All right! I'll let one of you
participate twice, since I'm a nice guy!
Pride permitting, of course!
I can't stand his tone!
You're so generous, Boss!
Your kindness seriously moves me to tears!
You're a real man!
Oh, you guys!
You're too much!
He's actually taking that
lame flattery seriously!
Man, Split-Head sure is dumb.
It's like watching a lame play.
Oh, Boss! Come back!
But maybe we should take him
up on his offer! You know?
Well, as much as I hate to
admit it, it is our only option...
It's for Chopper's sake. This is
no time to get hung up on pride.
Thanks!
A match is a match, though! We won't lose!
You're too soft-hearted.
Wanna know why I would make
an offer that benefits you?
It's because...
...we're the best--!
All right! Let's win Chopper back!
Yeah!
Boss!
Both captains have agreed
to the rule amendment!
Straw Hat Dangers, please
select a scorer for each round!
With five rounds, the odd-numbered
rounds of 1, 3, and 5 are key.
Especially the very first round...
Put me in two rounds! Okay?! Okay?!
Okay! Just shut up! I'm trying to think!
Okay, so I'll stick Luffy in
Round #1 and Round #5...
All right!
But I can't ask too much
out of Nami-san and Usopp...
Robin-chan.
I hate to ask, but could
you switch to Round #3?
Sure. Any round is fine with me.
Thanks-- Oh, wait.
Could the other team have the same idea?
In which case...
Come on! Hurry up!
Okay! All set!
Luffy has Rounds #1 and #5. Nami-san has #2.
Usopp has #3, and Robin-chan has Round #4!
Hold on! Why do you get to decide that?!
Huh? 'Cause I'm the coach
and you're the manager, duh.
Screw that! Why do I have
to take orders from you?!
Isn't it obvious?!
You can't be coach with all that
moss seeping into your brain!
Your eyebrow's funnier than you are.
Looks like coiled poop.
Poop?!
There's one more very important
thing to keep in mind!
Knock it off! I can't hear him!
Be aware that going in reverse
or leaving the course
will result in immediate disqualification!
Starting before the whistle
means disqualification, too!
All right, everything appears
to be set! The first round pits...
Oh! It's a clash between two big shots!
Straw Hat Luffy versus Porche-chan!
This looks to be a heated
battle from the very start!
Now let's get underway!
Talk about exciting!
--I love these races!
--Me too!
Porche-chan! Beat that rubber dude senseless!
Check it out!
Wha...?! Wh-What in the world?!
You can't be serious...!
Th-This is hard...
A-Am I seeing things?!
I don't see it! I don't see anything at all!
Oh, my! He can't skate at all!
And according to the roster, Straw Hat
Luffy plans to skate in two rounds!
Is this game already over?!
Are you serious?! This'll be a cinch!
Upsy-daisy...
Now what do we do?
Wait... Does this mean the third round's
gonna be extra important now?!
Both teams are finally at the starting line,
but will this even be much of a race?!
It's time to begin!
I can't believe you asked to be in two rounds!
It's not my fault! I didn't think it was this hard!
It's over! It's all over!
We have no choice, though.
We'll have to pick up the slack.
Okay, it's time! Scorers, get in position!
Hey! Not you again!
You'll have hell to pay if you
try any funny stuff again!
There's no need for "funny stuff";
it's already clear we're going to win!
It's time for the third game:
the Run Roller Round!
Will Straw Hat Luffy emerge
from Round #1 victorious?!
Or will it be our own Porche-chan?!
On your marks! Get set!
There she goes! Porche-chan
starts off with a spectacular dash!
Meanwhile, Straw Hat Luffy is...
...flat on his face!
He's collapsed before even
crossing the starting line!
That was an impressive fall...
Stupid things!
Whoa, now! Removing your skates
will mean instant disqualification!
Darn it!
Oh! I can just grab those--!
Ooh! This is too easy!
Twenty seconds have passed!
It's time to let the defenders loose!
Masshikaku!
Hey! He's about to get pinned! Help him!
Are you crazy?!
Wha...?
Gum-Gum Balloon!
That's it! Now, Usopp!
Huh?
H-Hey!
Listen! We're gonna keep
knocking you forward!
Don't you dare exhale, Luffy!
Talk about low!
Cien Fleurs! Delphinium!
Robin!
--It's her again!
--Awesome!
What speed!
He's well on his way to
catching up with Porche-chan!
Oh, no!
Flower Shurikens!
Amazing! I've never witnessed
a race like this before!
But the Foxy Devils have some serious defense!
I'm a wall...
Oh! But he clears the wall with a skillful toss!
Is it only a matter of time
until he catches Porche-chan?!
Nice, Robin-chan!
Nope!
Killer Sword Festival!
What a turn of events!
Straw Hat Luffy has gone outside the course!
--No way!
--He cut him!
You okay, Luffy?!
Rest easy! My Killer Swords don't cut!
They're all show!
I-I don't feel so good...
What kind of bragging is that?
This is bad...
Luffy's in the fifth round, so me,
Usopp, and Robin all have to win...
Chopper might not be
the only one at risk now...!
The winner of the first round is Porche-chan!
One point to the Foxy Devils!
Darn it!
Just get down from there!
All right! Let's move right along!
The second round match-up
pits the heartless Navigator Nami
against the King of Defense,
the Human Wall: Masshikaku!
I just have to give it everything I've got!
Round #2!
On your marks! Get set!
And they're off!
Oh, but what a shock!
Masshikaku is slow!
Like, really slow!
The heartless Nami quickly increases her lead!
What's with this guy? Is he even trying to win?
What is this?! What's going on?!
Is this some sort of tactic?!
Forget about him, Nami! Just keep movin'!
Right!
There's the second whistle!
Let's do it, Robin!
Wh-What are they doing?!
Just try and get through, if you dare.
Not even water can get past us!
Little late to be playin' roadblocks!
We're the ones in the lead...
Wh-What's with you guys?! Move!
Wait! Don't push yourself, Luffy!
We're gonna win if things stay as they are!
Yes, maybe!
Flower Hypnosis!
What...?
We were asleep?!
So it would seem...
Luffy! Get up! Hey!
But things still look the same... right?
Yes...
Nami! Hurry!
Hurry up!
--You need to get moving!
--Five!
--Huh? Why?
--Four! Three!
Two!
One!
Team Foxy wins two rounds in a row!
Victory is already within reach!
That can't be...!
They did a full lap while we were asleep...?
Yep! Sucks to be you!
I can't believe we beat 'em with Masshikaku!
Is this for real...?!
Team Foxy scores twice in a row!
Luffy's team is in a real pinch!
The third round is now a crucial one!
It pits long-nosed Usopp against
Chiqicheetah the speedster!
M-My chronic sickness--
Don't give us any crap about
a "Can't Race Anyone" disease!
Eep...
Are you kidding me? Chiqicheetah is a cheetah!
--I don't stand a chance...
--Oww.
No. Relax more and use your hips.
You've skated before?
--No, but just watch how the others do it!
--Can't expect much help...
--Stand with your legs spread out more!
--What I need is a strategy...
Like this? Oww...
--No!
--Like this?
--Oww!
--No!
Like this?
--Ouch!
--No! Listen to me, dammit!
On your marks!
--Get set!
--Nothing comes to mind...!
All right, whatever! I'll just go
as fast as I possibly can!
Oh! I'm in the lead?!
So fast!
No one's a match for Chiqicheetah's speed!
He doesn't need any support, ya know!
Damn! It's hopeless after all?!
No way! A full lap already?!
Maybe you two should sit back and relax too?
It's not over until it's over!
Twenty seconds are up! Defense, go!
--Let's go, Robin!
--Yes!
My! How admirable!
He's already back?!
Take this!
--Oh...
--Oh?!
That's it.
Now do it just like I explained!
Oh! Is he gonna make it?!
Just a little more! You can do it!
That's it! Stand up, Luffy!
--Oh!
--I'm so moved!
Totally!
Luffy!
All right! I'm up! Hang on, Usopp!
Hang on, Chopper!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Straw Hat Luffy has finally found his footing!
All right! I'm not gonna lose now!
But standing is all you can do!
Can't this idiot who's inferior to me
in every way do something?!
Don't be sneakin' insults in!
Wait! I know just how to turn the tables on 'em!
Look forward to seeing me in action!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Seriously Heated Race!
Into the Final Round!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!