It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Luffy and friends have agreed...
...to another Davy Back Fight
with the Foxy Pirates.
Despite putting up a good fight,
Luffy soon found himself all alone.
Straw Hat Luffy is out!
Wha...?!
Team Foxy emerges victorious in
Round #1's game of Hit and Dead Ball!
"Showdown on the Cliff!
Red Light, Green Light!"
Our Foxy Pirates have claimed victory
in Round #1 of this second fight!
It's time to claim our booty...
...and take one member of Team Straw Hat!
Who will our boss choose?!
--The one I want...
--...is obvious to us all! Right, Boss?
You!
The archaeologist, Nico Robin!
Me?
Oh, my! Our captain has chosen
Nico Robin, the archaeologist!
Oh, Captain! You naughty man!
Oh, no! Why didn't you choose Choppy, Boss?!
She's dangerous as an enemy.
Taking her first will give us
the advantage from here on out.
--Still...!
--We can get Doctor Chopper
for sure in the next round!
Now I get it! You're so smart, Boss!
--Robin!
--Robin-chan!
Bye.
I can feel the deep sorrow
hidden behind her smile!
The pain of having to part with me...!
Damn! How dare they take
Robin-chan against her will,
even if it is in the rules?!
Robin!
How do I look?
--Suits you perfectly!
--You look great, black-haired lady!
I wanted you to join us from the very start!
Ugh! She's so popular!
R-Robin's really gettin' along with 'em...
I never trusted her to begin with...
Don't be crazy! Robin is counting on us!
I think.
Good point as always, Nami-san.
I'm gonna win her right back in the next round.
Okay! Let's do the next round already!
You can't play in the next round, Luffy.
You're in the third round.
Learn the rules already, will ya?
Oh. I guess I'm on cheering duty then.
But there's only five of us for Round #2...
Pathetic Straw Hat team!
You've lost more than another member!
You've lost a major part of your offense!
How do you like them grapes, err, apples?!
Now let's start the next round!
Round #2 will be a game held on
Long Reef: Dash Touch Domination!
Or "D.T.D." for short!
It's a six-on-six group competition,
but without Nico Robin, Team Straw Hat
will only have five players!
The rules are simple!
Basically, it's like the
"Red Light, Green Light" game!
Move even a muscle after the
"stop light" stops calling and you're out!
Whichever team touches
the "stop light" first wins!
But this is no kid's game!
Keep in mind, this is a pirate
version of "Red Light, Green Light"!
All weapons are okay to use!
D.T.D. is a truly perilous game!
First is Team Straw Hat...
with the same ol' lineup.
Leave us alone!
Team Foxy is led by our idol
Porche-chan and Hamburg the oddball!
I'm going to win Choppy
with my own two hands!
Then there's the ever-swift Chiqicheetah,
the swordfish fishman Capote,
as well as "Tackle Machine" Pickles
and Big Pan the wotan,
who have both vowed revenge
for their Groggy Ring defeat!
Those losers will pay for humiliating us!
These are the six members
of the truly mighty Team Foxy!
What's the old stilts guy doing up there?
I forgot an important detail!
Tonjit the nomad here
will act as the "stop light"!
The great fool, err, man of bravery
who stood atop stilts for ten whole years,
reaching high into the heavens!
Tonjit is the only logical choice
to be our "stop light"!
I'm seriously sick of heights, though...
Hold on!
If he's the "stop light," doesn't that
give us a big advantage in D.T.D.?!
Don't abbreviate it too!
But Usopp's right! Luck's on our side!
You sure about this, Boss?!
It's nothin'! We pirates have to
battle the deep blue sea all the time!
Don't sweat the small stuff!
--Talk about generous!
--Wow! What a great guy!
Generous, my butt!
Right off the bat, we're given
a clearly unfair course!
I guess that Idiot-Idiot Beam is his only talent...
--Lame Fox!
--Split-Head...
Idiot-Idiot Beam...
Lame Fox...
--Split-Head...!
--Boss!
--Pull yourself together!
--You really take things to heart, Boss.
First, as the D.T.D. rules state,
both teams must start by calling out...
First step!
Oh! Team Foxy suddenly takes a big lead!
Bastards...!
This'll be a cinch if we
follow the plan! Let's do it!
Yeah!
I'm sure it goes without saying,
but there's more to this than rushing
ahead to touch the "stop light"!
This terrain makes it easy to lose
your balance during a sudden stop,
so we can also expect the
enemy to use that against us!
Split-Head! Get in the way
and I won't sit by quietly!
Split...
Ha! Like I need to interfere!
This is going to be a piece of cake!
Are you ready, Stop Light?!
--Mm-hmm.
--All right, then!
You can do it!
After Team Foxy's victory in the first round,
it's now time to begin Round #2's
Dash Touch Domination!
Ready! Go!
"Green..."
Dash, Hamburg!
Chiqicheetah is already ahead of the pack!
He's followed by "Full Dash" Hamburg!
Meanwhile, Roronoa and Sanji
are leading the Straw Hat pack!
--Move, dammit!
--No, you back off!
This is no time to argue while running!
Knock it off, Sanji-kun! Zoro!
Yeah, Sanji-kun! Zoro!
They're awesome!
"...light..."
Man, that's long! How can you hold
your breath so long, old stilts guy?!
He's an ideal "stop light"!
"Red..."
--You lovey-dovey loser!
--Say what, fish flake head?!
These are the two Straw Hats to look out for!
Let's knock 'em outta the game
right away, just as planned!
Go, Big Pan!
Punk Attack!
They're in trouble!
He's about to call "red light"!
This isn't the time for that!
"...l..."
"...ight...!"
Stop!
I-If we move now, we'll be out...!
Out!
Wow! Pickles and Big Pan of Team
Foxy are already out of the game!
All right, Zoro! Sanji!
No big deal! All we need is
one person to touch him to win!
Chiqicheetah, Porche, and Hamburg
have a huge lead over the Straw Hats!
Ooh! We're in a "totally going to win" mood!
They're too fast!
Zoro and Sanji are our only hope, but...
Damn Moss Head!
Stupid Love Cook!
Just so you know, I have the important task
of getting Robin-chan back.
I've had enough of you!
--"Gree..."
--I don't give a damn about you!
--"...eee..."
--Hold on, you protected species head!
Despite losing two players,
Team Foxy is closest to
reaching the "stop light"!
At this rate, Team Straw Hat
has no chance at all!
Go! Go!
Yes, that's it! Just like that!
"...een..."
Crap! It's your fault we're so
far behind, you damn Moss Head!
How did this happen?!
The path is gone!
I know you have no sense of direction,
but this takes the cake!
How can you even get lost in
a place with such a clear view?!
It might be easier to catch up
here than on a curved track...
Guess it's do or die!
Oh! Sanji is taking a chance now!
Yikes...!
Sanji's big gamble pays off!
He's now right behind the lead group!
Oh, that's no fair! Hurry, Hamburg!
Wh-What do you want...?
Never hurts to reduce the number of opponents!
Time for all three of you to kick the bucket!
Crap!
N-Nami! Usopp!
We've got no choice...
--Everyone run for it!
--Roger!
Hmph! There's no getting away from me!
Get back here!
Man, old stilts guy's "Green"
is really long this time...
Oh?!
H-He's asleep...!
--Get up!
--Hey, you! Wake up!
--Don't be sleepin'!
--"...light, red light!"
C-Crap!
Out!
Even though the "stop light" was napping,
Capote was caught off guard!
He's out of the game!
What kind of nerves does this guy have,
napping in a place like that?!
That's old stilts guy for you!
All right!
They're in firing range now!
It was gonna be such an easy win, too!
Now I'm a little worried...
The four players in the lead are now
within 100 meters of the "stop light"!
Will it be a mad dash to the end?!
It'll be one of these four
who touches the "stop light"!
Come on, Sanji!
No one's paying any attention to us...
Yeah, they're completely ignoring us...
I do feel a little useless.
At least there's comfort in knowing
we're not the only useless ones...
T-The path ends again...
Brr! I hope this'll end soon so
I can go eat something warm...
Outta the way!
Get him, Hamburg!
This time... I will make mincemeat out of ya!
You wanna fight, you damn gorilla?!
I'll get you this time!
Hamburg intercepts Sanji!
Meanwhile, Chiqicheetah heads for
the "stop light" at breakneck speed!
Sanji has fallen right into Porche-chan's trap!
What?!
Victory is ours!
Dammit!
Chiqicheetah rushes straight
for the "stop light" from behind!
"Ggg..."
Grachoo!
Out!
Oh, my! It was just a sneeze!
Tonjit hasn't started calling out
"red light, green light" yet!
Has his speed backfired on him?!
Chiqicheetah is out for jumping the gun!
Blast! Don't sneeze, Stop Light!
We were so close to winning, too!
Even your snot is long, old stilts guy!
Sure lucked out there...
He was sneezing...
This is no time to be laughing, Hamburg!
We have to win and take Choppy!
Both teams are closing in on the "stop light"!
At this distance, the next play
should decide the game!
Will the "stop light" be touched by
the duo of Porche-chan and Hamburg?!
Or will it be Sanji?! Which will it be?!
This is the moment of truth!
"Green..."
It appears he's indeed
calling out his line this time!
Take this! And this!
See you later!
H-Hamburg! What are you doing?!
--"...light..."
--Here comes Robin-chan's savior!
Oh! Sanji!
--What?!
--What's Porche-chan doing?!
--Stay still, Porche-chan!
--Do something!
"...rrr..."
Now Robin-chan's ours again.
She's totally gonna fall in love with me!
Sanji! Hurry up! Touch him!
--"...eeee..."
--Good work, old man.
The game's over now.
"...dddd..."
Oh, my! Sanji is turning back
before touching the "stop light"!
What is he doing?!
Even if you are my enemy,
I can't turn my back on a lady!
Incredible! Sanji, the nefarious cook,
has saved Porche-chan!
"...light!"
Hamburg is fighting to remain still!
But Sanji is as good as out,
despite having saved Porche-chan!
No, wait! There's Sanji!
And he has Porche-chan!
Not only that, Sanji is completely still,
despite his current situation!
He's not moving in the slightest! He's safe!
Impossible...!
How can he stand completely still
in the middle of the ocean?!
Oh! He's treading water!
All while carrying Porche-chan and
keeping his upper body motionless!
Just like a swan!
He's kicking furiously beneath the
surface while looking elegant above!
As long as the "stop light"
can't see him moving, he's safe!
Sanji is incredibly determined to win!
I will save Robin-chan, no matter what!
Sanji still has a chance to touch the "stop light"!
--He's one heck of an opponent!
--Impressive, Cook!
Sanji! You're too much...!
Oh, my! I could really fall for you, Mr. Cook!
Oh! Both Porche-chan and Sanji
have dived underwater!
You're both out!
H-Hey! Keep swimming!
You're gonna make me drown!
Oh, what have I done...! Robin-chan...!
"Green..."
Here we go again!
The only ones left now are
Hamburg of Team Foxy, and...!
--We're almost to the "stop light"!
--There's no one to stop us!
I can't believe we're gonna touch him!
"...light..."
Let's all touch him together!
Yeah!
Oh! The trio of forgotten Straw Hat
slowpokes is poised to touch him!
An upset's in the making!
Who would've thunk it?!
Just when I finally get on the real path...
Ugh! Kicking is that crappy
cook's specialty, but...
Get outta the way!
"...red..."
Yes!
Victory is certain for Team Straw Hat!
All right! We win!
"...light!"
Hamburg has touched the "stop light"!
Team Foxy is the winner of Round #2's
Dash Touch Domination game!
That's two supreme victories in a row!
Huh? It's over already?
You ended it!
In the worst possible way!
It's all your fault, Zoro!
I'm up next, right?
I'm gonna take back my crew! I'm their captain!
Haven't you forgotten an
important fact, Straw Hat?
You've lost twice now, which has cost
you Nico Robin and one other member!
But you can only win back
one crew member per game!
In short, if by some incredibly
rare chance you win the next round...
Get to the point, Split-Head.
Split...
In other words, there's only one round left,
so even if you win it, you can
only take one person back.
Huh?
Struggle as you might, Straw Hat,
you can't change the fact
that you've already lost one
of your crewmates for good!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Hey! Split-Head! Quit your blabbing
and start the next match already!
--Do you even understand the situation?!
--Luffy!
He's surprisingly cold-hearted.
His brotherly soul is burning
red-hot for you guys! Ain't it so?!
Oh, yeah!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Captains Square Off!
The Final Combat Round!"
King of the Pirates! Oh, yeah!