It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Now, Let's Get Back Our Memories!
The Pirate Crew Lands on the Island"
"Golden Pavilion"
There's no mistaking that this is my handwriting.
Sky islands... Navy base G8...
And this gold...
If this is all true, everything makes sense.
If I could go back to Cocoyashi Village,
I should be able to figure everything out!
But there aren't any decent ships.
How can I go back...?
And, of all the places, I'm in the Grand Line?
According to this sea chart,
you can't exit the Grand Line midway
through to get to the East Blue.
Wh-What'd you say?!
You're the captain, you say?!
At any rate, that was close.
If I hadn't remembered things, I would've
remained Usopp's underling forever.
Shut up! I'm never gonna believe it!
No matter what anyone says,
I am the great pirate, Captain Usopp,
who leads 8,000 underlings
in the Usopp Pirates!
That's the spirit! That's our Usopp!
But you're the sniper of
the Straw Hat Pirates, Usopp!
Shoot... Now he's above me.
This guy is a monster just like me,
and yet he's a captain?
Chopper!
Ahh! Don't come this way!
Are you still acting like that?
Let's play like we always do!
I'm the ship's doctor, and yet I was
really doing something like this?
Sure, this is your signature party piece.
You did it whenever we had a party.
A one! A two!
--A one, two, three!
--That rubber monkey said
that he regained his memories,
but he acts just like he did before.
It means that our captain doesn't change,
no matter what happens.
Hey, let's sing the usual song!
Even if I'm part of a pirate crew, if I'm
nobody, they might just slave drive me.
On top of that, being around monsters like them,
no matter how many lives
you have, it won't be enough.
Now it's clear.
It's not that everyone lost their memories.
Their memories were taken away.
And the culprit, after all, is...
Who's that damn brat?
Yeah, what does he want with our memories?
Good question.
Ah! Shoot!
What?
I have to bring back Nami
and Zoro. Let's go, everyone!
Huh?
Let's wait until morning.
Hm? Why, Robin?
We've never been to this place.
On top of that, it's the dead of night.
It won't be that easy to find them.
Hmm... I guess you're right.
Wouldn't it be better to
sleep a little until dawn?
That boy seems to have learned a lesson.
I don't think we have to worry
about him showing up again tonight.
Okay! We'll leave tomorrow morning then.
--Hold on.
--Hm?
I'm all for bringing back that lady, Nami-san,
but I don't see why we're
going after that Zoro guy.
Me neither! If you wanna go,
you two can go by yourselves!
I-I...
What're you guys saying?!
We're saying, why do we have to include Zoro?
He's a pirate hunter, you know!
Why do we have to go to the
trouble of chasing after him?
Why else? It's because he's one of us!
Even if you say he's one of us... Right...?
He doesn't feel that way even a bit.
You know that, too, don't you?
The fact that he left in a hurry is proof of that.
Usopp is the sniper. Sanji is the cook.
Chopper is the ship doctor.
Robin is the archaeologist.
Nami is the navigator.
And Zoro is the swordsman.
We, the Straw Hat Pirates, can't leave
anyone out, not even one person!
We just have to get the
swordsman's memories back.
If so, then I just have to beat up that brat,
just like I did earlier, right?
Right, Chopper?
Well, looks like we'll have a busy day tomorrow.
Let's get some sleep while we can!
The key to solving all the
mysteries is on that island...
I underestimated Monkey D. Luffy.
If I make an enemy out of him,
I could be in big trouble.
But I'll definitely make my wish come true.
In order to do so, I have to make friends, too.
And you can't go wrong
with a skilled swordsman.
That's right. It's different from yesterday.
This is Zoro, a pirate hunter.
If I carelessly get closer,
I may make another blunder.
Okay. I won't do it now.
There'll be another chance, anyway.
Yeah, when that time comes,
I'll have you do your job but good.
It's said that the All Blue has
foodstuffs from around the world.
I used to dream of going to that legendary sea.
I didn't ask for your help!
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
Why...? Why did you?!
Because you had the same dream as me.
Restaurant?
Yeah. I was thinking that I'd build a
restaurant as my final purpose in life...
All right, then, I'll help
you do that. So don't die!
Ha! It's impossible for a
weak little brat like you!
I'll become strong, too!
There's no way that I'd leave that
damn annoying geezer, my benefactor.
Why...? What happened to me?
Pepper, Carrot, Onion... I wonder what
the Usopp Pirates are doing now...
Alright! Let's go, Usopp Pirates!
To protect this village's peace!
So what adventure are
you going to tell me today?
Hmm, let's see...
The story of when I fought the giant
goldfish at the South Pole when I was five!
Goldfish?
Yeah! What first shocked me
was the immense size of its poop!
It was so big that I landed on it,
thinking it was solid ground!
I had a dream that I wanted to
become a pirate like my old man.
But to think that I became a pirate
when I had to leave them to do so...
Why am I with humans?
The only ones I trusted were
Dr. Hiriluk and Doctorine.
Even among the reindeers, I had
no friends. I was always alone.
I will never shoot you!
My name is Dr. Hiriluk!
I'm a doctor!
In other words, there's no disease
in this world that can't be cured.
No matter what anyone says about me,
I'll save this country as a doctor!
That's why I raised this skull
towards all the diseases!
Skull...
That's right! This is a symbol of
the belief that nothing is impossible!
By raising this, I'll fight just like pirates do!
My friends? On top of that, six of them?
I can't believe that I'm the
ship's doctor for a pirate ship!
But what if it's true...
They won't.
My dream won't be lost. It must
be the same for you guys, too.
Nami, Zoro, just wait. I'm coming for you now!
Everyone! Wake up!
We've been up for a while now.
The cook and the ship's doctor
said that they're coming along.
Hm?
We can't just abandon that lady.
Also, Robin-san needs a bodyguard, too, so...
If someone gets injured, you'll be in
trouble without me, a doctor, right?
So I'm taking on the job of guarding the ship!
--Come along with us too, Usopp!
--Like I said...
Well, actually, I've got "My Heart Will
Stop Once on the Island" disease.
--Ow, ow, ow...
--Just come with us.
I know that Usopp, a brave warrior
of the sea, has his moments.
Well, I guess.
All right! We'll all go!
Shoot! I just got too elated...
So, how are we gonna get to the island?
How about using a raft?
Oh, that's a good idea.
We're counting on you, Usopp!
Why me?! I'm Captain Usopp!
Yeah, yeah...
At the very least, I'm a sniper!
Either way, there's no way I could
do stuff like a shipwright would do.
To make a raft, all you have to do
is to put logs together, right?
That's easy!
Are those knots done right?
Well, that's pretty much it.
Hey, hey... Knots like that will untie
right away and the logs will drift apart.
If we're gonna make one,
I want a cool-looking one.
How about this?!
No! This one is cooler!
According to my tastes, it should be this!
Hey!
You guys call yourselves pirates when
you can't even make a decent raft?!
Whoa...
What amazing workmanship!
Usopp has his moments!
I admit, I have no idea myself why I built it...
All right! We're off!
Thanks for letting me stay.
How much do I owe you?
Hm? Who are you?
What? I'm your inn guest
who stayed here last night.
Do you know her?
No, I don't know her.
Is it possible that she's a thief?
Wh-What?!
Hold on a sec! I'm your guest!
I met all three of you yesterday, right?
"Inn" "Inn"
You guys really don't remember me? Manager?
Manager? Me?
He's the manager, right?
Oh, is he?
I'm lucky that I got a free stay out of it,
but what on earth is going on?
Could this be...
Who are you?
You guys lost your memories, too?
I was like that...
...yesterday...!
About yesterday?
Yeah. I think they came to this village.
A moss-head swordsman and a woman
on a strange vehicle. Did you see them?
Yesterday... what did I do?
You too?! Seriously, what the heck
is with the people on this island?!
To think no one even
remembers about yesterday!
What carefree people!
Is it an issue of being carefree?
We can't complain about them.
--What?
--We, too, can't...
The cause might be the same.
What're we gonna do? It'll be kinda
tough finding them in this situation.
Okay, then. Let's go back to the ship.
Staying on this creepy island won't
do us any good. Right? Let's go back.
Nami!
Oh, shoot!
Wait up.
This is terrible...
Why did you run away, Nami?
I'll never give this to you!
Even if you kill me, I won't give this to you!
Don't say that! There's no way
we'd hurt a pretty lady like you!
We won't even lay a finger on you!
Though I want to, to be honest...
What kind of disease does he have?
Do something about it, doctor.
It's definitely a serious condition,
but I'm also sure that there's no cure for it.
Then, let's make a deal.
A deal?
I'll give you 10% of this treasure.
So take me to Cocoyashi Village using that ship!
--No.
--Then, how about 20%?
--Then, 30%!
--No.
--Pretending that there's no tomorrow, 50%!
No.
Just how much do you want to rip me off for?!
You love treasure.
There's no way you're thinking
of sharing any of it with us.
How can you tell what I'm thinking?!
Because we're friends, of course!
Me, friends with you guys?! Give me a break!
There's no way we're friends!
The negotiations broke down. See ya!
Please move.
I won't. Nami, you come along with us, too.
No way! Why would I go with you guys?!
Please move!
I won't.
Navigator.
You've been feeling something's odd too,
since you came to this island.
Am I wrong?
What's the matter, lady?
A child with a strange horn...
I kicked his ass. And then,
smoke came out from the horn.
When I thought it went into my body...
The captain's memories came back.
No way. Wasn't it a dream or something?
It's true. I saw it clearly with my own eyes.
That damn brat... I feel like I saw
him the night before last, too.
Why did he come twice?
Maybe because he couldn't steal
all your memories in one shot.
Even with just what I know,
you guys have experienced an
incredible number of adventures.
He couldn't eat them all in one shot, so he
returned yesterday on an empty stomach?
I think that's what happened.
Oh? I wonder if memories taste good.
Then that kid is...
See you later!
All right, then! Let's kick that kid's ass again
and get everyone's memories back!
If we do that, Zoro will
probably come back, too.
I'm doubtful whether it'd go that smoothly,
but we have to get even with that damn brat.
Why don't we forget about Zoro?!
Even if we regain our
memories by some chance,
it's kinda unsettling to be on
the same ship as a pirate hunter.
Zoro is the swordsman. Nami is the navigator.
Both of them are our friends that we need.
Even if you say so, I'm in a bind!
To think that I'm one of you...
I'm the one who'll be in
a bigger bind without you.
Without a navigator,
the ship can't go anywhere!
Robin, can you tell where that kid is?
Well... there's a place that I want to check out.
Okay then! Let's go!
H-Hey! My gold is...!
I won't let a lady carry stuff!
If I can be with you, Nami-san,
this is no trouble at all!
Ahh... I have a bad feeling about this.
No matter what they say, they all follow Luffy.
I wonder if it's true that I now have friends...
What're you doing?! Hurry up, Chopper!
Okay!
If you wanna eat, help yourself.
It's true that I am hungry,
but I don't eat this kind of stuff.
I see.
Why aren't you asking who I am?
Oh, yeah... People on this island
don't even remember their own names.
You thought it was no use asking, huh?
You set out on a journey to become
the world's strongest, right, mister?
Then, to you, Monkey D. Luffy is
the perfect opponent, you know.
I'm Luffy! Nice to meet you!
That straw hat guy?
I'm surprised that Roronoa Zoro
couldn't perceive his strength.
I couldn't perceive it?
That's right. In the East Blue,
he destroyed the vicious fishman
pirate group, Arlong Pirates.
Here in the Grand Line,
he brought down Crocodile,
one of the Seven Great Pirates, all by himself.
Seven Great Pirates?
That's not all.
On the sky islands, he even
beat up the god named Eneru.
Oh, yeah... He went on a
rampage in a Navy base, too!
Against Luffy, even the
Navy throws up its hands.
I've never seen a pirate like that before!
Don't talk nonsense!
I don't have time to listen to lies like that.
Hey, now you want to fight Luffy, don't you?
You jerk! What on earth...
Hm? What's this place?
Is that weird brat here? This is kinda creepy.
I-I wonder if I caught a cold or something.
I've been feeling a chill for a while.
I wish we had a doctor at a time like this.
That's me!
I bet these people are trying to take me
to a deserted place and steal the gold!
I won't let that happen!
Nami-san has been giving me
passionate eyes all this time!
There's no doubt! She fell in love with me!
--Wink!
--Wh-What?!
Is that a sign that he's gonna steal
the gold?! What a creepy guy!
I see...
Ah, a butterfly!
Did you find something out, Robin?
I figured out the culprit who
took your memories away...
No... I mean, the real culprit.
That damn brat isn't the culprit?
Now, let's head to the Sea God's Palace.
The Sea God's Palace?
What the heck is that?
I'm calling it that for now...
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Ahh, this really was a bad idea!
I feel it's pointless to go with you guys!
She's right. Hey, let's go back. Let's go back!
No. We're going to bring Zoro back.
That damn swordsman is coming this way.
Oh, you're right. Hey!
Wait. Something is odd.
Really? Zoro is always like this.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Zoro Bares His Fangs!
A Savage Animal Stands in the Way!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!