It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Vice Admiral! He's not around!
"Justice"
"He's not around!" doesn't cut it!
Where the hell did he go?!
Since his bicycle is gone,
he probably went to... sea.
Contact the Five Elder Stars immediately!
Yes, sir!
Oops. Sorry about that.
That man again? He probably
just went to do some sightseeing.
Seriously... Doesn't he realize his position?
We can't just have him wandering about.
One of the Navy Headquarters'
ultimate powerhouses, Admiral Aokiji...
At any rate, there's not a single
good egg in this guy's family...
"Proud Man! Silver Fox Foxy"
Hey, Captain! Stop fooling around!
Help me out here!
Whoa! What a huge wave! It's scary!
He sure looks like he's having fun.
Tell me about it. I bet he'll be laughing
even if the ship gets capsized.
Wouldn't this thing snap before that happens?
Really?! If that happens,
what's gonna happen to us?!
Don't worry.
Even if the mast gets broken,
it doesn't mean the ship will sink.
Besides, we have an excellent,
cute navigator on this ship.
Oh, no! It looks like the mast is about to break!
Really? What's gonna happen to us?
Don't worry!
Even if the mast gets broken,
it doesn't mean the ship will sink!
Ah...
Ahoy! Guys! Long time no see, huh?
Boss! That's Straw Hat!
Ahoy!
How dare you, Straw Hat?! Don't look this way!
We haven't fallen so low as to need your help!
What?!
See ya!
Hey! If you want to help us,
we're okay with that, you know!
Boss... look behind you...
This is nothing! Slow-Slow Beam!
Beam!
This is it for us!
Hey, isn't this bad?
A small boat like that won't stand a chance.
Guys! Stay back!
Hold on to this!
Idiot! No! I meant the rope!
Luffy!
Well, I feel ashamed.
First, I lost 500 subordinates.
And now, to think I even lost my ship...
This is finally the end of Silver Fox Foxy...
It might've been better if I'd let fate
take its course and sank into the sea.
Boss...
What do you think about that?
Well, I may not be in a position
to say this, but that's a lie.
Therefore, I'd like you to take pity
on me and let me stay on this ship!
Okay. Since you don't have
your own ship, it can't be helped.
Here's some soup. It'll warm you up.
Whoa! This looks good! I'll have it with Choppy.
Sanji! I wanna have some, too!
There isn't any left. Wait until tomorrow.
What's wrong? Don't hold back.
What's this?! There's nothing in the soup!
Don't act so full of yourself!
--Ahh! Sanji!
--How about I put you in the soup?!
Hey! Calm down! Calm down, Sanji!
You too! Apologize to Sanji! Okay?! Okay?!
Huh?!
Oh, no! What's this?! This is amazing!
Lots of gold... I didn't know they were rich.
Oh, shoot. The soup will get cold.
Choppy! You're here, right?
Choppy!
Oh...
It was just a candleholder...
Hm? Where's Boss?
Ahhh!
Choppy!
As if I'm gonna sit around fishing. I'm a guest.
Besides, we have food right here, too!
He's an idiot.
That's...
Boss! I see the Sexy Foxy!
What?!
--Ahoy! Ahoy!
--Good! You guys're gonna get off our ship, huh?
--Ahoy!
--Are they leaving the ship?!
--Ahoy! Ahoy!
--Hurray! Hurray!
Sodium...
Hydrogen phosphate.
What are those guys doing?
They've already gone to their ship.
Guys... You all couldn't forget about Boss
even after we got separated, huh?
I see, I see...
You can all come back to the Foxy Pirates.
What's the matter, you guys?
Let's have fun together again!
That's not possible, Foxy-san.
What'd you say?! Who the hell are you?!
This ship is now under the control
of the Fang-Frog Pirates!
Those guys are now my underlings!
Fang-Frog? Who's that?
Ah... If I remember right, they're the ones
who lost in the Davy Back Fight
and had stuff taken away.
And this time, Foxy got
his ship taken over by them?
What a stupid guy that Split-Head is.
Well, it is a motley crew of pirates
won by playing games, after all.
I think I'll pass on the send-off.
Hey, let's go. We've got no business here.
Hold it!
I've got some business with you.
My underlings still won't
take off those strange masks.
It's quite annoying, but it seems they're
still devoted to their former captain.
It's probably because they
don't like their new captain.
Whoa! Boss is kinda cool.
For a split-head.
Like it or not, small fries
follow the strong after all.
If they see you get beaten up,
they'll probably come to their senses.
Fight me, Silver Fox Foxy!
How conceited... You think you can defeat me?!
Looks like he'll accept.
Hey, Split-Head is on fire!
Come check it out already!
His head...
...is on fire?
Boss...
What's the matter, Porche, Hamburg?
Show some happiness.
He's gonna give this ship
and my subordinates back to me.
We Foxy Pirates challenge you
Fang-Frog Pirates to a Davy Back Fight!
I'll teach you who the real captain is!
You said you'd beat me up, huh?
If it's duels you want, why don't
we start with us captains?!
I assume you have no objection?
Boss is quite confident, isn't he?
He's got that stuff, so...
Is he gonna use that?
Well, what else would he do?
Here I come! Slow-Slow Beam!
Whaaa...
...aaat?!
Guys! Take him down!
That beam of yours is no
threat at all once I reflect it!
I already know your trick.
Boss!
Hey! What're you doing?!
Stop right there!
Drop your weapon!
Damn... it...!
Guys, did you see how stupid
your former boss looked?
You don't have to be loyal
to a guy like that! Got that?!
Hey, you! Wasn't it supposed
to be a duel?! That's dirty!
You're an outsider, so shut up!
To start with, I never said that
I'd accept the Davy Back Fight.
That bastard...!
Don't. It's their fight.
It has nothing to do with you.
He's right.
Just shut up and watch, Straw Hat...
Watch the proud Silver Fox Foxy fight!
Ah! What the hell is that?!
The fox guy is gone.
Where did he go?!
That way! I saw him go that way! It's true!
Oh, that way, huh?!
You think we'd fall for that?!
I wonder if they're having a party or something.
Maybe I'll go check it out.
Oh, so, you'd rather have that girl
chasing you than stay with me, Doctor?
Okay, it's your turn, Robin.
One roasted fox, coming up!
Boss...
Boss!
Get back here! I'm your boss!
Hey...
Aren't weapons something
you use against your enemy?
Why do you hurt your own subordinate?!
Hm?
If you rely only on power, you're nothing
but the head of a group of thugs.
You don't have the caliber
to be the captain of a ship.
Just give up on this ship
and my subordinates as well.
I won't give you anything-- not a single thing.
Shut up!
Boss!
Hey, Split-Head!
Hang in there!
Hey!
Oh... It's you, Straw Hat...
I guess that was pretty pathetic, huh?
Say... would you do me a favor?
This...
Would you take this...?
That match was the best stage of my entire life.
Hey... that's...
You're super groovy right now!
I'm your opponent!
Now, bring it on, Fang-Frog Pirates!
Afro!
Hey, hey, this has nothing to do with you.
--It does!
--I don't wanna fight a guy with a
100-million-Berry bounty on his head.
What good will it do me to fight you?
What're you saying?
If you defeat the Straw Hats,
you'll get the 160-million-Berry bounty.
And, that's not all.
They have a mountain of gold on their ship.
I bet that's worth quite a bit.
Yep, yep.
Are you shocked?! Just take it, you thieves!
Geez... When did they...?
Why is he talking proudly about it?
I'd better check later to
make sure nothing is missing.
A-A mountain of gold...
Seriously...?
Prepare to fire! The target is Straw Hat!
Yeah!
Fire!
--Let's go join him!
--Yeah!
What're you gonna do?
Hey!
Just hand over the gold nice and...
I guess this won't be settled unless
we take them all out, huh? Good grief...
Ha! We've got 500 crew members!
Take him down!
We weren't listening!
Hey!
Too bad they weren't listening, huh?
Hey, look at that!
Hm?
Ah! Hold it!
So, how is it, Fang-Frog?
My brother is strong, isn't he?
After all, he's so strong--
that you can't find anyone besides me--
who can defeat him.
You guys, go easy on them--
you don't wanna kill them.
They're just ordinary humans.
Take this!
Sword... Catch...!
What're you doing, you damn cook?!
You bastard! You pushed Nami-san
down earlier, didn't you?!
I did it to save her! Got a problem with that?!
What're you gonna do if she gets
seriously injured, you idiot?!
To start with, you don't know how to treat ladi...
Sword...
Like I said, what's your problem, you bastard?!
Shut up! We weren't done yet, were we?!
What's the deal? Wanna fight?!
Out of the way!
Oh... a human firework.
Looks like they're in full swing.
My chronic abdominal spasms...
H-Hey, are you oka--?
You got tricked, young fellow.
Oh, no. This is bad. I'm a doctor.
Let me take a look.
I hate doctors!
That was Ketchup Star.
Ow, ow, ow... My back...
Hey, pull yourse--
Ouch!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
...Pistol!
That was splendid, Straw Hat.
You're as marvelous as ever.
I was just pulled in by your passion.
Let me tell you just one thing.
Oh, stop it. We're friends.
You don't have to thank me.
Slow-Slow Beam!
Huh?!
That's our Boss!
Remember this good, Straw Hat!
I am Silver Fox Foxy, a man
who obtains whatever he wants.
Your luck ran out when you
got on this ship, you fool.
Just clearing up the humiliation of
the Davy Back Fight wouldn't satisfy me.
I'll take the 160 million Berries
along with the gold.
You... idiot...!
All right!
This time for sure, I'll show you
that we, the Foxy Pirates,
are the strongest pirates!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Zoro! You put the afro on, too!
That's right! Fire up your brotherly soul!
Stop it!
The moss-head man looks cool!
--Black moss-head.
--I'm gonna cut you down, you jerks!
His wildness awakened!
Geez... Like I said, what's with this afro stuff?
--You put it on, too, Nami!
--No!!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Guy Who's the Closest to Invincible?
And the Most Dangerous Man!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!