Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Here, Ghin. Let him eat it.
Sanji-san...
Thank you!
This is a good restaurant.
I'll take this ship.
So... that's what you want...
Meat Ball of Doom!!
You're damn annoying!!
Don't defy me!
When I tell you to prepare food,
all you have to do is
obediently follow orders!
Don't defy me!
There's probably enough
for 100 meals in this.
Bring it to your ship right away.
--Owner Zeff!
Z... Zeff?
"Protect Baratie!
The Great Pirate, Red Foot Zeff!"
What're you doing?!
What're you thinking?!
If we revive even those on the ship,
our restaurant will be
completely taken over!
If they have the will to fight, that is...
Right, defeated warrior
of the Grand Line?
C... Can't be...
Don Krieg is a defeated warrior...
Then even the ruler of
the East Blue couldn't...
Even the pirate fleet with
50 ships couldn't sail across...
Grand Line?
Y... You must be Red Foot Zeff!
So you are alive...
An incomparable pirate who was
a cook and yet also a captain...
So what if I'm alive?
It has nothing to do with you.
As you can see, I live as a cook now.
If you put it that way, it sounds nice...
...though rather than living as a cook,
it looks like you can live only as a cook.
Red Foot Zeff was a master of kicks
who never used his hands in battle.
I hear that his strong
legs crushed bedrock
and even left footprints on steel.
And Red Foot referred to your shoes,
which were covered in the blood
that spattered as you
kicked your enemies down...
But you no longer have
that precious leg of yours...
I've heard the rumor...
How unlucky for you to
have an accident at sea...
To you, losing one of your legs
must mean you are unable to fight.
What about fighting?
I can cook without a leg
as long as I have these hands.
What're you trying to say?
Just come right out and say it!
Red Foot Zeff.
You're the man who once entered
the Grand Line and came back unhurt...
There should be a
logbook with the full year of
your journey chronicled in it...
Give that to me!
Whoa! You've been to
the Grand Line, too, pops?
Yeah...
My logbook, huh?
Indeed, I have it with me.
But I can't give it to you.
The logbook is the pride of all
the crewmen that I traveled with.
It's too important to give it to you.
Then, I'll just take it from you by force.
It's true that I fell from the Grand Line.
Even if that's the case, I'm still
Don Krieg, the strongest man.
It's merely a dark sea route.
To sail across it, I had enough power...
...and forces... as well as ambition!
The only thing that was regrettable
was that I lacked information.
I just didn't know things...
I'll take your logbook.
And I'll form a large pirate fleet
again and seize the One Piece.
And then, I'll stand on top
in this Great Pirate Era!
Hold on a second!
I'm the one who's gonna
be King of the Pirates!
Chore boy!
Hey, back off, chore boy!
You're no match for him!
I can't back off on this.
Did you say something, kid?
I can let it pass...
You don't have to. I just stated a fact.
This isn't a game.
Of course not.
I'll conquer the Grand Line.
It's no joke, you brat!
It's true that we didn't
have information,
but a fleet with 5,000 men was
wiped out in just seven days!
That's a devilish sea!
There's no way someone
like you can sail across it!
S-Seven days?!
Krieg's pirate ships were
wiped out in just seven days?!
What on earth happened?
Unfortunately, I don't find
those kinds of jokes funny.
If you're not going to let it drop,
then how about I just crush you here...
Go ahead if you can...
Fine by me.
As you wish, I'll send
you to the netherworld.
Gonna fight, Luffy? Need a hand?
I-If you don't need help,
though, th-that's fine too...
Zoro! Usopp! You stopped by?
Don't worry. Just watch from there.
Y-Yeah? T-Too bad,
but if you say so, what can we do...
B-But if push comes
to shove, we'll help you.
S-S-So, g-g-good luck!
What'd you do that for, Zoro?!
Shut up! Just keep quiet!
Are they your crewmembers?
That's quite a small group you got!
What're you saying?!
I've got two more!
Hey! You counted me, didn't you?!
I'll deal with you later.
I'll go feed my underlings.
Those who don't want to die can
abandon the restaurant and escape.
All I'm after are the
logbook and this ship.
But if you still wish
to be uselessly killed...
...it's a bother, but I'll
bury you into the sea.
Know that.
It's gotten quiet.
Big Bro Zoro went in there.
It should be all right.
Hmm... Are they really okay, though?
If you put it that way...
Say, Big Sis Nami, should we go in, too?
--Big Sis?!
--Ahhh! Ugh!
B-Big Sis Nami?
Hmm? Ahh, what is it?
Is something wrong?
I'm sorry, Sanji-san.
I never imagined this would happen...
That's not something you
should apologize for, underling.
Each cook at this restaurant acted
as they felt was right. That's all.
Owner! Why are you acting as
if you're taking Sanji's side?!
That's right! He's responsible
for this whole thing!
He's going to put your precious
restaurant out of business!
Shut up, you idiots!
Have you felt what it's like to
be on the brink of starvation?!
Losing food and water
on this grand ocean...
Do you know how scary it is?!
Do you know how hard it is?!
What?! What do you mean, Owner?
The difference between Sanji and you all
is whether you know it or not.
Hmm? What does he mean?
What's he saying that Sanji knows?
If you have time to grumble,
leave the restaurant from
the back door already!
I'll stay and fight.
I couldn't bear it if I was just
beaten and didn't fight back.
I'll stay, too! This is the
restaurant where I work!
We don't have anywhere
else to go anyway!
What do you think you're doing?!
You saw how powerful Don is, right?!
Hey, Ghin!
Let me tell you something.
Feeding someone who's
hungry is my morality.
But...
...those we'll be dealing with
are plunderers with full bellies.
I won't let you complain even
when I beat up your fellow pirates.
If someone's going to
take over this restaurant,
even if it's you, I'll kill
them without hesitation!
Got that?
Ha! Letting him live and now
killing him? You're hopeless, Sanji...
Shut up, you damn cook!
You see? He's kinda cool, isn't he?
Who cares about him?!
We'd better get out of here now!
Calm down! Even if it's Krieg,
he's a wreck with injuries.
Ghin! You said you didn't know
anything about the Grand Line.
Even though you've been there?
It's still true that I don't know.
What happened on the seventh day
after we entered the Grand Line...
I don't know if it
was a dream or reality...
I still haven't been able
to come to terms with it...
I still just can't believe...
...that the 50-ship fleet...
...was wiped out by only one man...
--What?!
It happened suddenly...
As soon as this man appeared,
he sank the ships one after another.
If we hadn't been lucky enough
to have that storm then,
our main ship would've been
completely destroyed as well...
I don't know how many
ships we have left...
It was just so dreadful that I
don't want to accept it as reality...
I don't want to remember...
...that man's...
...sharp, hawk-like eyes whose glare
alone gives one the chill of death.
Wha...
What did he just say?!
That...
...must be Hawk-Eye...
What?
That you felt his eyes were like
a hawk's isn't proof in and of itself,
but what this man did is
enough proof that it's him...
Hawk-Eye!
Huh? You know him, Zoro?
Yeah... He's the man I'm looking for.
I went out to sea to meet him.
I see...
Isn't it possible that that man had
some deep grudge towards you guys?
We never did anything to him!
Like you guys disturbed
his nap or something...
Don't be ridiculous!
I'll be damned if he crushed
our fleet for such a reason!
Don't get so worked up.
It's just an example.
I'm just giving an example of what
kind of place the Grand Line is.
What the heck kind of place is that?
It probably means that
anything can happen.
Hey Luffy! Let's not
go to a place like that!
Luffy!
Hey, Luffy?
Ahhh! It sounds so exciting!!
That's how it should be!
You need to get the concept of
"danger" into your thick skull!
But my goal is now completely
narrowed down to the Grand Line.
What?!
That man... I can see
that man if I go there...
Are you guys stupid or what?
Guys like you die before anyone else.
Yeah, but you didn't
have to call us "stupid."
When I decided to become
the strongest swordsman,
I decided to devote my life to it.
Since it was my decision, the only
one who can call me stupid is me.
Ahh! Me too, me too!
Me, too! That's just natural
as a man of the sea!
In your case, that's a lie.
What nonsense...
Hey!
Do you idiots understand
the current situation?!
The ship moored in front
of the restaurant
is the huge Galleon that
belongs to Don Krieg,
Commodore of the "pirate fleet"!
If you wanna escape from reality,
do it after surviving
this life-or-death crisis!
--We're saved!!
Great! We're still alive!
It seems like a dream!
We're free from that nightmare!
We came back alive from
the pirate graveyard!
That's right...
which means that we can now
head to the Grand Line again.
Huh? What's with those faces?
A-Are we going to that place again?
No more objections, right?
First, abandon this wrecked ship
that could sink at any moment
and take over the restaurant.
Our enemy's just some punk cooks.
Even if you take your opponent lightly,
that's still more than enough...
Attack!
Here they come!
We can hear their war cry!
We'll protect the ship to
the end! It's our restaurant!
Out of our way, cooks!
What the...?!
What happened?!
Don Krieg!
The main ship was... cut!
Cut?! It was cut, you said?!
This huge Galleon was?!
That can't be true!!
Raise the anchor! Or we'll be
swallowed along with the ship!
Yes, sir!
This is bad! Nami, Yosaku and Johnny
are still on our ship out there!
Dammit! It might be too late!
Big Bro! Big Bro!
Yosaku! Johnny!
Are you all right?
Where's the ship?! It's gone!
What happened to Nami?!
That... I'm sorry, Big Bro. She's gone.
See ya! Tell them...
Big Sis Nami...
...that if we're linked
by fate, we'll meet again.
She took all the treasure and ran off!
--Wh-What'd you say?!
That man is...
Th-That son of a bitch!
He followed us!
Is it possible... that's...
...Hawk-Eye!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Who's that?
The man I've been looking for. I never
thought I'd be able to see him this soon.
--Are you gonna fight him?
--Yeah. I went out to sea to meet him.
Hey Zoro, what's wrong?
Am I this far from
the world's strongest?
So this is the world's strongest...
--Zoro!!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hawk-Eye Mihawk! The Great
Swordsman Zoro Falls on the Sea"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!