It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
They... are... so... soft...!
Yummy!
--What?! Is it that good?
--I don't understand what you're saying.
Well, actually...
I decided not to pay--not even a single Berry.
Thanks for the perfect repairs!
Sir, it'd be wise not to tease craftsmen like that.
Oh, pardon me.
The pirate way of doing things doesn't
work on craftsmen's turf, now, does it?
That tower-like thing is the one.
Things are huge all over!
They're strong...
...and skilled.
They're the pride of Water Seven.
Scary!
Whoa! What's that?!
That's a mask shop.
CP9...
Robin?
I thought we were attacking you in your sleep...
"The Franky Family and Iceberg-san"
Who are you bastards?
Identify yourselves!
"Identify yourselves"?
Pirate hunter Zoro...
We're bounty hunters...
...the Franky Family! Even a crying child
stops crying when they hear our name!
Your head's worth 60 million!
We'll gratefully take it.
And we'll wait in ambush inside your ship...
...and catch the entire crew in one swoop.
We'll make a killing! How lucky!
I'm the first!
"Lucky"?
You mean, "unlucky," right?
Don't flinch!
Two-Sword Style...
...Rhino Cycle!
How senseless...
D-Dammit!
This is the place.
So, what do you want?
We want cash for our stuff.
How much is this gonna be?
Owner! This is serious!
G-Gold... Th-This much!
What?! Take them to the VIP
room im... im... immediately!
Wow! This is comfy!
Yeah! Hey, this is really bouncy!
Does this one also have water in it?
Hm? Hey, don't tell me you're
gonna say they're fake.
F-Far from it! I've been
an appraiser for 25 years.
This is roughly estimated at...
O-One hundred million Berries?!
I-Idiot! You're too loud! Everyone can hear you!
Y-Y-You're gonna give us that much money?!
L-Like... Like I said, Luffy, you're too loud!
This is indeed worth that much.
This is wonderful gold, taking its
historical value and purity into account.
With that much money,
we can fix the Merry good!
Yeah! We'll even get some change.
Then, we'll spend the rest of the
money to buy a bronze statue!
Don't. Don't buy it.
If you accept that amount, please sign
and put your thumbprint here.
I'll go prepare the money immediately.
Okay! I'll put however
many thumbprints you want!
If that's not enough, I'll put mine, too!
What? What's the matter, Nami?
There're three things I
want to say, Mr. Appraiser.
First... I forgot to tell you, but this guy's
got a 100 million bounty on his head.
Second...
...I don't accept the appraisal
you've just given us.
Third... if you lie to us again,
we'll go after your head.
That is all.
I... I'm sorry!
Th-Three hundred million Berries?!
Isn't this a dream?
Our adventure on the sky islands
has finally borne fruit!
I'm super rich!
That should be "we"!
P-Please come again!
I-I-It became 300 million! I-I'm scared!
I'm carrying 100 million?
Well, Nami can really make scary threats, huh?
I estimated it to be that much from
the start. But then he said 100 million.
You two were restless,
so he didn't take us seriously.
Hey, Luffy. If you flail it like that...
Well, anyway, I'm glad it went well.
Huh?
Ahhhh! The river!
100 million Berries are gonna sink into the river!
Phew! That was close!
--I'm gonna knock you out!
--I'm gonna break your teeth, you son of a bitch!
I-I'm... I'm sorry.
Did you hear that?
Yeah. They said 300 million Berries.
They must be members of the Straw Hats.
That's a bigger amount than their total bounty.
We're changing the plan.
Hey, go let the guys who
went to their ship know.
S-Say, Nami, maybe we really
should take it back to the ship.
That'd be a waste of time.
The shipyard is right over this hill.
Hey, I'm a bit shocked you guys
won't let me near the money.
Once we see a shipwright,
we'll probably need to go back to the Merry
right away so that he can assess the repair fee...
I see.
That's true.
I don't really know what to do, since I've
never carried so much cash around.
Well, that's only natural.
I can't understand why a
person would flail it around.
Ah! Hey, look over there! They're selling
water buns! Let's buy 100 of them!
--Shut up.
-Then, let's buy 1,000 of them!
--Then...
Shut up!
Okay...
We're back at the entrance to the shipyard.
Good! Looks like the
crowd from earlier is gone.
Anyway, let's find... well...
What's his name again?
Iceberg-san.
Right, that's it! Ice pops!
I wonder who he is.
The granny at the station told us to ask him.
Yeah...
More importantly, I wonder if
it's okay to go inside there?
I'm coming in!
Not again!
--Hold it!
--Hm?
Wait.
You're an outsider, aren't you?
Let's talk outside for now.
Only authorized people can go inside the plant.
Heave-ho.
Do you have some business at this dock?
Oh, it's you, Usopp.
Hey! I'm right here, Luffy!
Yeah. He's square-ish!
Which means, he's square Usopp!
No, I'm not a triangle or a square.
Oh, yeah! Um... We'd like to see Iceberg-san.
Hm? Iceberg-san? Are you a customer?
Oh, I see.
This is a reference letter from
Granny Kokoro at Shift Station, huh?
Hm? Are you an old guy?
I'm 23.
23... You talk like an old man.
People often tell me that.
So... do you know this Iceberg person?
Know him? Well, Iceberg-san
is the mayor of Water Seven.
Whoa... So he's that high up?
Not only is he the mayor,
he's the president of our company,
Galley-La Company,
and he also manages the sea train.
So he's the most powerful guy in town?!
Well, in Water Seven, there's no
one who doesn't know him.
Where do we have to go to see him?
Hmm, I wonder where he is right now.
He can be hard to find,
since he's a very busy person.
Oh... Can't you get in touch
with him or something?
That's probably possible, but...
Are you in a hurry?
It's not that we're in a hurry, but...
In short, you want to talk about
having your ship repaired, right?
Where did you anchor your ship?
Rocky cape.
Well then, I'll go run and check
the condition of your ship.
It'll save some time when you see Iceberg-san.
You can talk about the repair fee, too.
"Go run"...? On a Yagara bull?
If I do that, you'll grow tired of waiting.
Well, just wait for ten minutes.
Ten minutes?
That's right. Ten minutes.
Whoa!
--He's fast!
--Whoooa!
Oof!
Ahhh! He jumped!
What... but wait! Over there is...
...a precipice!
--Ahhhh!
--He fell!
Amazing!
Is he okay?
He runs freely in town.
--What?
--Huh?
People call him the "Mountain Wind."
He's a shipwright foreman of
Galley-La Company's Dock #1...
His name is Kaku.
Well, well... I see...
The city of water... This is amazing!
Clear springs and rivers...
Clean streets and lively crowds...
And many pretty women.
I wanna go out on a date with Nami-san
or Robin-chan in a town like this!
Being between two pretty women is good, too.
This side is Nami-san
and this side is Robin-chan.
Hey, mister. Stop making that weird face.
So which water-water napa
cabbage are you gonna buy?
Hm? Oh, yes, I'll buy both. Oh, and...
I want to get some food that's in season
from this town. What's available?
Water-water apples and water-water pears!
Interested in fish that are in season?
My hubby runs a fish shop.
Where is it?
Get back on the land, turn right
six times and turn left twelve times.
Huh?
Let's see... Hm? What the heck...?
In any case, it sure is
inconvenient when we have to walk.
Another dead end? Shucks.
Did I get lost? This is bad...
I'm just like a certain damn swordsman.
Hm?
Oh! Robin-chan!
Hello! It's me! Yoo-hoo!
Robin-chan!
Hm?
She disappeared?
When there're no doors or streets?
Did she fly or something?
Hm?
Usopp?
What's with this town?
Am I the one who's off here?
Oh... That ship must be the one.
Pardon me.
Oh, it's just Usopp.
I see. It's damaged.
The mast needs to be replaced, too.
Usopp...
Hold on a sec! Who the hell are you?!
Oh, I'm sorry. I woke you up.
Boy... was I shocked!
He jumped from there!
Well... Don't make light of my craftsmen.
--Come to think of it, who's this guy?
--Beats me.
In order to build a faster, stronger ship quickly,
an ordinary physical ability isn't good enough.
By the way, Kalifa...
Yes, I've already checked.
Straw Hat Luffy,
pirate hunter Zoro, Nico Robin...
Their group has those three members
with bounties on their heads.
Their total bounty is 239 million Berries.
It was formed in the East Blue.
They're the Straw Hats, and they
currently have seven crewmembers.
Th-They know about us big time.
I see. I'm glad you came.
I'm Iceberg, the boss of this city.
And this is a mouse I found earlier.
His name is... let's see...
...Tyrannosaurus.
I have to prepare his food and cage.
I've already taken care of them, Iceberg-san.
Well, that's my Kalifa.
Thank you.
More importantly, you're dining with
an executive from a glassware factory
at the hotel in Chiza in ten minutes.
After that, you'll give a
talk at the Liguria Square.
When that's done,
a conference with Mr. Bimine,
the mayor of the gourmet town Pucci.
You'll also be interviewed by
a newspaper company there.
After that, please go back to the main
office and go through some documents.
I don't want to!
Well then, I'll cancel them all.
Hey! Is that okay?!
I'm someone powerful enough
to do things like that.
You're completely unfit to be a mayor.
What a selfish guy you are!
But isn't this guy the one
that granny was talking about?
Yeah, he's "that guy."
How insolent!
What'd you do that for?!
Holy crap!
Where're your manners?! Referring to one
of the world's leading shipbuilding engineers
as "this guy" and "that guy"...!
What's going on?
Kalifa, the secretary, has exploded
for the first time in a while!
I wanna be kicked by her, too.
Pardon me. I lost my head there for a moment.
However, Iceberg-san is admired
by the citizens. Please be polite.
Try not to get Kalifa angry.
When she gets angry...
"Ouch"
...she is indiscriminate.
You kicked him big time!
You're the one who's impolite!
Um, but in any case, you're Iceberg-san, right?
Please look at this. It's a reference letter.
From Granny Kokoro...
"Take a look at their ship.
Kokoro"
"Take a look at their ship," huh?
Ahhh!
What?! You won't?! Please!
Please repair our ship!
We have money!
The Merry is beat up after
our voyages! Please, pops!
--Okay.
--How frivolous! So it's okay?!
--Yep.
--Then why did you rip it up?
Her lipstick mark was unpleasant.
Granny Kokoro and I have
been drinking pals for ages.
Well... that being said, Kaku has
already gone to make an assessment.
The matter is already in progress. Don't worry.
It's a boring day today anyway.
Shall I show you around the factory?
Whoa! Seriously?
Well then, this way, please.
Is that the attitude a man who
canceled his appointments should have?
All right! We're gonna go
to the shipbuilding plant!
Oh, that's right. The money...
Money... What?
What? What? What?
Whaaat?!
Hm? What's the matter, Usopp?
Th-Th-The money... The money is gone!
Whaaat?!
--Look for it thoroughly!
--I can't find it!
--Hm? Huh?
--It's gone! I can't find it anywhere!
Ahh!
Ahh! Over there!
H... Hey, you bastards! Who the
hell are you?! Who are you?!
Why are you taking our money?!
Hey! Hold it!
Thanks for the money!
Give us our money back!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Hey, Usopp! Did you give them the money?!
Why would I do that?! They stole it!
At any rate, your ship...
Oh, how was she?
...must've had some tremendous journeys.
Yep, she has. Please fix her good!
Frankly speaking, your ship...
I won't give up the bronze statue!
--...can no longer be fixed.
--What?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Galley-La Company! A Grand Sight, Dock #1!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!