It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Shall we go follow Franky?
Where?
Drat. Looks like they really
don't know where the money is.
Even if we strangle this Franky guy,
if he already spent the money...
What do we do now? Even if we wait for
him here, he won't be back for a while.
Staying here talking won't get us anywhere.
Let's go back to the ship for now.
We left Nami-san alone there, too, so...
We have the thing with
Robin-chan to deal with...
...and the issues with the ship, too.
Yeah.
Hey, Luffy!
About the ship...
I've made a decision.
Hm?
Let's say goodbye... to the Going Merry here.
"Big Fight under the Moon!
The Pirate Flag Flutters with Sorrow!"
Ah!
Hey! Usopp woke up!
Really?! Good!
Now we can relax a little.
Hey! Usopp!
Robin-chan isn't back yet...
Seriously, don't worry us so much!
She's right. To think that you marched
in by yourself... That was so reckless.
You were lucky that you didn't die.
Think a little before you act.
Look who's talking!
Just because I'm so good-for-nothing...
I'm sorry...
Really... I'm ashamed! Guys!
That money was so crucial to
us and yet, I let it... I let it...
Hey, hold on a sec! Calm down!
I-I get it, so let me go!
But... the huge amount of money we got,
after all that we went through...
Usopp, you should still be in bed.
Hey, listen to Chopper.
Then, as I was afraid...
...the money won't come back?
Well, we won't know for sure
until this Franky guy comes back.
I see... I'm sorry.
Well, even if we don't get it back,
we still have the 100 million Berries.
So that's okay. Don't worry about it.
It's not okay about the money!
--Nami...
--Ah... Sorry.
No, that's okay.
But Luffy... What about the ship?
What about the Merry?
Can we somehow have her repaired
with that remaining 100 million?
We're lucky that we can have her
repaired in such a first-class shipyard.
In order for her to be able to travel in
the seas ahead, I'd like her to be stronger.
I want her to be repaired perfectly.
Say, does it look like those guys will
repair her if we pay 100 million Berries?
Does it, Luffy?
Er... well...
Usopp, about the ship...
I decided to get a new ship.
What?
I'm sorry that I made the
decision without consulting you.
But I've already made my decision.
The Going Merry took good care of us,
but our journey with her ends here.
And...
I took a look at the catalogue
that Ice pops gave us.
While checking the ships in it, I noticed
that there're quite a few kinds.
If we get a used one, 100 million will
allow us to buy a bigger ship than Merry.
Wait.
Wait... Wait a sec. You're taking
the joke too far. That's ridiculous.
Right?
See? Chopper took it seriously.
Seriously, what'll we do with our captain?
Say something to him, Nami.
Well... does that mean that we don't
have enough money for the repair?
Because I got that 200 million stolen by them,
w-we're now short on money, right?
Hey, that's what's going on, right, Luffy?
The cost of a first-class shipyard
would also be first-class, so...
No! That's not it!
Then why?! Spit it out! Are you
trying to be considerate to me?!
I'm not! It has nothing to do
with that money being stolen!
Then why are you saying stupid stuff
like that we're gonna get a new ship?!
Hey, stop it, both of you!
What good will fighting do?
Calm down and talk!
How can I calm down when he
starts saying stupid stuff?!
Hey! This is an important matter.
Don't get so worked up.
She's right, Usopp. You need
to rest, or you won't get better.
Who cares about my body?!
How can I be quiet when our captain
casually says we'll get a new ship?!
It's not casual! I made the
decision after agonizing over it!
What and how did you agonize over
to make this kind of decision?!
How dare you talk about it
while waving this stupid thing?!
What'd you do that for?!
It's an eyesore.
Hey, Luffy, if it wasn't because we
got our money stolen, then why?!
Luffy, why don't you say it?! Hey!
Why are you keeping quiet?!
If you're not being considerate
to me, then don't hold back!
Say it! I won't accept it unless
I hear good reason! Hey!
The Merry can no longer...
What... did you just say?
Don't make me repeat myself.
The Merry can no longer be repaired.
No matter what we do, she won't be fixed.
Otherwise, I wouldn't say something like that.
This ship?! Are you talking about this
ship that we're on board right now?!
That's right. This ship will sink soon.
What're you talking about, Luffy?
It's the truth. They told us at the shipyard.
They said that she can't
even reach the next island.
Oh, really... She can't, huh?
So you were persuaded by
strangers you just met today
and gave up just like that?
What'd you say?
Just because first-class
shipwrights told you that this is it...
...you gave up just like that?!
We've traveled together all this time!
We made it through all sorts
of waves and battles together!
She's our dear friend!
Are you gonna abandon her in a place like this?!
Is that how little this ship means to you, Luffy?!
You shouldn't shout like that, Usopp.
--Sorry, but step aside.
--What?
I'm not done talking with him.
Usopp...
Then can you make an accurate assessment?!
We don't have a shipwright on this ship.
That's why we asked them to check her!
Fine! We don't have to
ask those guys to fix her!
I'll repair her, as I always have!
That's how we've continued
to travel in the first place.
Okay, let's start now. Hey, help me, guys!
Hey, wait, Usopp.
Oh, yeah, we don't have enough lumber.
I'll go buy some at the shipyard.
Now, we're getting busy.
You're not a shipwright, are you, Usopp?!
Hey, Luffy!
Yeah, you're right. So what?!
But I don't trust irresponsible
shipwrights who easily give up on a ship
just because it belongs to someone else
by taking advantage of
their position as craftsmen!
Usopp...
This must be a lesson that we should
protect our own ship by ourselves.
I'll never... give up on this ship!
Are you guys stupid or what?!
You probably got fooled by the shipwrights'
convincing argument, didn't you?!
The Luffy I know would've believed
in the strength of the Merry first
rather than buying those guys' sales talk!
Such a clear-cut answer that sounds
like one made by an old man
who understands everything...
How can you make a decision like that,
suddenly acting all captain-like?!
I misjudged you, Luffy!
Wait a sec, Usopp! Luffy, too, first--
Stay out of this, Nami!
This is something I decided!
I won't change my opinion.
No matter what you say now,
we're gonna get a new ship!
We'll say goodbye to the Merry here!
Don't be ridiculous! I won't allow that!
Listen, Luffy! It's not like everyone
can live looking ahead like you do!
I can't just leave our wounded friend
here and move on to the seas ahead!
Don't be ridiculous! Even if she's a friend,
ships and humans are different!
They're the same! Merry has
the strength to live left in her!
--Considering how you are, aren't you
excited thinking about the new ship
--Hey, that's enough, you guys!
--while pretending to be concerned about Merry?!
--You can't have a conversation
if you're worked up like that!
Enough, already!
Luffy!
Don't think that you're the only
one who feels pain over this!
Everyone feels the same way!
If so, there's no way you'd
decide to get a new ship!
Fine! If you dislike what I decide
that much, then get off this--
Sanji...!
You idiot... What were you about to say?!
Cool down! Be careful about
what you say! Got that, Luffy?!
Sorry. I just...
That's okay, Luffy. That's how
you really feel, isn't it?
What'd you say?!
Go ahead and cut off useless friends
one after another and move on.
If you're gonna abandon the Merry...
...why don't you do that to me, too?!
Go ahead and cut off useless friends
one after another and move on.
If you're gonna abandon the Merry...
...why don't you do that to me, too?!
Hey, Usopp. Don't say stupid stuff like that.
No, I'm serious.
I've been thinking about this for a while.
To be honest,
I've been thinking that I can't keep
up with your monstrous strength.
Like today... I can't even watch over money.
I'll just keep causing you guys trouble.
You don't need weak friends, right?
Luffy... you're the man
who'll be king of the pirates.
But I don't have to go that high up.
Thinking back, when I was about to sail out,
you guys asked me to join you.
What're you talkin' about? Get on already.
We're friends now, aren't we?
That's all that's tying us together.
We don't have to travel together
when we have a difference of opinion!
Hey, where're you going, Usopp?!
Where I'm going is my own business.
It has nothing to do with you guys anymore.
I'm...
...leaving the gang.
Usopp...
Oh, no...
Hey! What're you doing, Luffy?!
Is it okay to let him go like this?!
Hey! Go after him!
Stop him now!
We've come this far together.
Is it okay to part like this?
Usopp is our precious friend.
Stop him!
Hey, Luffy... You are the captain, right?!
Why aren't you saying anything?
Usopp!
Wait! It shouldn't be like this!
Hey! Turn around!
Hey! Come back!
Don't go! Usopp!
Come back!
Luffy...
Luffy! I can't go along with you anymore.
Sorry to cause you trouble until the end.
It's true that the ship
belongs to you, the captain.
So fight me...
Monkey D. Luffy!
Fight a duel with me!
What? What? Er, hey... what're you saying?!
At 10 o'clock tonight, I'll come back here.
Then we'll fight a duel over the Merry!
I'll defeat you and take the Merry.
That's...
...the end of the bond
between you guys and me.
What's with you?! Stop this nonsense!
Why do you have to fight
a duel with your friend?!
If you give it a little time,
you two will cool down, right?!
Usopp, too. He just got flared up
because things were moving quickly.
Now that we've come this far, we can't go back.
That's not true!
You can apologize to him and talk it over again!
Like I said... it's no longer possible.
Why not?
Usopp isn't stupid enough to risk
his life under the influence of anger.
Besides, if talking it over
would change his opinion,
this wouldn't have happened.
If you get it, leave me alone.
Luffy...
I'm saying, the Franky Family
came here this afternoon, right?!
Huh? So what?
Why didn't you beat them
all up beyond recovery then?!
If you had, Usopp wouldn't have
been attacked and felt guilty!
Then, instead of going shopping,
you should've stayed and fought them!
I went to get necessary food as your cook!
Stop fighting at a time like this!
There's been enough fighting.
Don't fight over what's done.
Nami-san...! But this idiot is...
Chopper... Didn't you... go follow Usopp?
I wanted to continue treating his wounds,
but he turned me away.
He got a place to stay in town.
He said...
He said, "You and I are no longer friends,
so go back to the ship!"
All that fun time up until this
morning seems like a dream.
If something is happening
to Robin on top of this...
I feel like... the gang is falling apart.
The Straw Hats, huh?
Well... I somehow feel restless tonight.
It's 10 o'clock, the promised time.
Usopp is coming.
You guys, don't leave the ship.
Got that?!
--There he is!
--Usopp!
So you didn't get cold feet, huh?
You'd better be sure you're not going
to regret this, no matter what happens.
This is the duel you wanted.
Of course. You'd better fight seriously.
I'll turn the tables on you.
I've already figured out how to defeat you.
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Stop it. It's ridiculous for friends to fight a duel!
Once what we protect becomes
different, we're no longer friends.
It's over between us!
Don't say that. Luffy, you restrain yourself, too!
Precisely because we're all friends,
be prepared and watch quietly!
Come on, Usopp!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy vs. Usopp! Collision of Two Men's Pride"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!