These guys are really strong...
Dammit! What's with you guys?!
Tell me the reason at least!
We're the ones who'd like to know why.
The culprits who attacked
Iceberg-san last night were...
...from your gang, weren't they?!
Iceberg was attacked?
What're you talking about?
Wh-What did they mean?
D... Don't be ridiculous! Why...
Why would we do such a thing?!
So you'd play innocent to the end, huh?
But we really didn't...
The culprits...
When Iceberg-san came around, he told
us that he remembered the two culprits.
One was a big man with a mask on.
The other was a tall woman.
When we asked the government,
they said that she's one of you guys...
Nico Robin, the woman
with a bounty on her head!
Robin?!
Did you come to this island in order
to kill Iceberg-san from the start?
Or did you decide to do so after
you guys met him yesterday?
I don't know what you pirates think...
...but now that we've come to know you're
the culprits, we won't leave you at large.
So he's one of the culprits?
We can't forgive him!
We definitely can't forgive him!
Oh, no...!
Hey, hey, so did Iceberg die?
Heaven forbid that he'd
get killed by fools like them!
Precisely because he's still alive,
this guy could go after his life again.
So we'll take care of him right here, right now.
Dead or alive...
They don't care if you're captured alive or not.
Do you know what it means
to be on the wanted list?
You pirates can't complain,
no matter who does what to you.
In other words, the world's
laws won't protect you guys.
That's right.
We are outlaws.
I know that. But...
...don't say things like that when
you know nothing about Robin!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"The Straw Hat Pirates Are the Culprits?
The Protectors of the City of Water"
Luffy...
Let me see Ice pops!
I'm sure he was mistaken!
There's no way it was Robin!
Why would we let you get closer
when we don't know what you'd do?!
He's right! Tie up the culprits!
They tried to kill our town's hero!
Send them to the gallows!
H-Hey! What're you saying?!
You bitch!
Hey! You were with that Straw
Hat guy earlier, weren't you?
You must be one of them, too!
Is that right?!
Yeah, he's right! I saw her, too!
We're not gonna let you get away!
Don't fight!
Hey! Stop it!
Nami!
Let go of me! I said let go
of me! What did we do?!
Don't play innocent! You bastards are assassins!
How dare you shoot Iceberg-san?!
We won't let you get away!
Hey! Stop it, you guys!
We're saying we didn't do anything!
That's right!
First off, Robin doesn't have a reason
to go after Iceberg-san, either!
Just keep insisting that.
In any case, this is it for you two.
Learn that harming Iceberg-san
means that you're turning us,
Galley-La Company, into an enemy...
That you're turning this city,
Water Seven, into an enemy.
Why are you saying
groundless things like that?!
Let me talk to Ice pops!
Just give up, pirate!
The information will spread
throughout this town immediately.
There's no longer a place for you to escape!
We'll bring down everyone in your gang!
Beat him up, Galley-La Company!
What's the matter, Straw Hat?!
You've only been defending.
Don't you wanna fight back?!
Like I said, I don't have any reason to fight you!
We now know that pistols don't work on you.
Dammit. Looks like they're
all serious about this.
It was a direct hit!
No... He got away.
That was close...
Shoot! I can't move!
--Luffy!
--All right! They got him!
Yay! Just as you'd expect from our
pride and joy, Galley-La Company! Yay!
That feels great!
Right. A guy like that should be blown away!
Well, well, well...
But, you know, that Straw Hat shorty
is the Franky Family's detestable enemy.
I was the one who was fighting him first.
Don't you come and snatch
my prey when I'm fighting!
Just how many times do I have
to repeat myself, you bastards?!
Galley-Laaa!!
Just hold on a sec. We'll deal with
you after we capture him completely.
Like I said... why in the hell
are you capturing my prey?!
Well, never mind. Seems like you
guys don't get what I'm saying.
Paulie! Watch out!
Galley-La! Run!
Franky is gonna launch a crazy attack!
Hm?
Connecter set...
He brought down a huge crane
earlier with the same attack!
Brought down a crane?
A cannon?
Run! Galley-La!
Go! Get them, Bro!
Well, I'm not gonna shoot a cannonball.
What I'll shoot out is an air bullet.
But its speed exceeds the speed of sound.
Air?
It's dangerous! Run!
What the hell?
Coup de Vent!
Ow... What the hell was that?!
It felt like high-pressure winds crashed into us!
Another crane is coming down!
Run! It'll reach this far!
Hurry up!
It's coming down!
Yeah! Get crushed!
A shipyard like this should be... crushed!
What is he?! A cyborg? Where did
he get that kind of technology?
And what was that weird cannon?!
Ah... but...
I was able to escape thanks to that.
Nami! Run!
Luffy!
Are you okay?
No way I'd get brought down
by something like that!
Anyway, I don't get it.
Let's go see Ice pops somehow!
What?! We're going?! It's not
possible in this commotion!
Hey, look! Straw Hat is getting away!
Oh, shoot!
We're gonna be surrounded!
--Nami!
--Hm?
Hold on tight!
Hey, wait!
Don't let them get away!
--They got away!
--Go after them!
I don't see him.
Yeah... Maybe he still can't move...
But it wouldn't be good if
we go closer and he finds us.
Yeah...
Chopper, are you ready?
Yep.
Hey! I heard that a storm surge
called Aqua Laguna is approaching!!
Yep! This town will be
submerged by midnight tonight!!
This shore will be totally submerged, too!!
That's terrible!! We shouldn't
stay around here!!
That's right! We shouldn't stay around here!!
We'd better hurry up and
evacuate to high ground!!
That's right!! Let's hurry up and evacuate!!
--Evacuate!! Evacuate!!
Evacuate!! Evacuate!!
Run!
What were those voices just now...?
Make sure you evacuate!
Evacuate, Usopp!
They were saying something
about a storm surge.
Come to think of it... the wind is awfully strong.
Bro?
Hm?
They got away. Don't you
have to go after them?
No... I ran out fuel with the
Coupe de Vent I just shot.
Look at my ducktail.
Yeah... It looks like a
willow swaying in the wind.
Those damn bastards got in my way.
Once I'm done refueling,
I'll eliminate him for sure.
Just as you'd expect from a man with
a 100 million bounty on his head...
He sure is a man of mettle.
Seriously...
Franky has really done it...
What a terrible day today is!
At any rate, we can't let them get away.
Aqua Laguna is coming tonight.
Except for the two sea train
departures left today,
they have no means to leave this island...
...since they can no longer
use the ship they came on.
We'll gather information.
Have every Galley-La craftsman
spread around the island.
We're gonna settle this before sunset!
Grandma! Grandma! It's Water Seven!
Be careful not to get too
excited and fall into the sea.
That must be the Galley-La
Company's main office.
It's connected to Dock #1.
Look.
People who look like reporters are all over.
Shipwright-looking people
are gathered there, too.
Iceberg-san must be in that building.
Are you serious about going?
Of course.
I'll go ask Ice pops in person why
he said Robin was one of the culprits.
Let me warn you.
Just remember that we're also being
chased after by the entire island!
Make sure you get some idea
where his room is beforehand,
and seize an opportunity to carefully sneak in.
Well then, I'm off.
Huh?
--Hey!
--They said they couldn't find them.
Who's that?!
Ah... He is...!
The window got broken!
What happened?!
An attack!
Straw Hat Luffy has broken into the main office!
What?! In the middle of the day?!
To think that he attacks the
main office again out of the blue!
Where is he?!
He went to the mezzanine
stairs to the third floor!
--Where are the foremen?!
--They're stationing craftsmen all
over the island, so they're all gone!
He's wearing a red vest and a straw hat!
Protect Iceberg-san!
It's Straw Hat!
Where did he go?!
Where is he? Where is he?
Idiot! Don't shoot a pistol!
We're inside, remember?
It's not good for Iceberg-san!
I'm sorry about the
commotion outside the room.
Well... what's going on?
I was told that Straw Hat Luffy
has broken into this building.
Kalifa... I have a favor to ask.
--There he is!
--Dammit!
Whoa! So many of them!
He's going to Building #2!
Go around from upstairs!
Straw Hat!
She is...
Kalifa-san, didn't a pirate come here?
No, he didn't. More importantly,
chase after him more quietly.
Iceberg-san still needs to rest quietly.
I'm sorry.
Looks like the Straw Hat
hasn't reached this far yet.
Let's stand watch around here.
His target is definitely this room!
Well... you wanted to see me...
right, pirate lad?
That's right. Thanks for
calling me in. That saved me.
I doubt you came all the way here by
yourself to kill me in this commotion.
I came to hear the truth!
Last night, I saw Nico Robin with my own eyes.
And... she is one of you.
That's the truth.
Was it really Robin?!
Don't say a word.
Your words no longer mean anything.
I called you in here...
...because I have a favor to ask.
Let me see Nico Robin again now!
Extra! Extra!
The culprits for Mr. Iceberg's
attack were the Straw Hat pirates!
We, Water-Water Newspaper, will buy
any information on their sightings!
The culprits are on this island!
Find the Straw Hats and send
them all to the gallows!
Yeah!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
It's gotta be a mistake that
Robin is the assassin, right?
I wonder where she went.
Craftsmen are everywhere on the island.
We have to find her soon.
They say that a crazy storm is approaching, too.
What're we gonna do?
Maybe Robin really betrayed--
No! I don't believe it!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Eternal Farewell? Nico Robin,
the Woman Who Draws Darkness"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!