Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
"Hawk-Eye Mihawk! The Great
Swordsman Zoro Falls on the Sea"
--Ugh...
--What'd you just say?!
Nami ran off with the Going Merry?!
What do you mean by that?!
It happened just a moment ago!
What's the matter, Big Sis Nami?
Huh?
You were looking at wanted posters.
Oh... Nothing...
You're impressive as usual.
So you've set your eyes
on a big bounty pirate.
But Arlong is the one pirate
that you shouldn't go after.
I hear he's super terrifyingly strong...
He kept himself quiet
and out of sight for a while.
But he started going
wild again recently.
Well, it's hard to give up on that
20-million berry bounty, though...
This guy's so strong that
there's a shred of possibility
that even we may be killed by a hair...
Huh?
Big Sis Nami?
Uhm, I'm sorry, but could you
turn around? I want to change...
What?! W-Well...
Change? Here? Now?!
May I?
Please go ahead!
True to her looks, she's so bold!
It wouldn't hurt if we take
a quick peek, would it?
Oh, yeah...
Wh-What're you doing?!
What am I doing? Of course, business!
I'm a thief that only targets
pirates. I'll take this ship.
I never said that I became a member.
I just joined forces with them. That's all.
I only spent a short time with Luffy
and the others, but I had lots of fun.
--Tell them...
--What?!
...that if we're linked
by fate, we'll meet again.
Big Sis Nami!
H-Hey! We'll be in trouble!
We were more or less
asked to watch the ship!
So that's how she took the ship...
We're sorry!
Dammit! She's making
this crisis worse for us!
Kaya gave that ship to us!
Wait! I can still see it!
It's the Going Merry!
Where's your ship?
We still have it here...
Zoro! Usopp! Leave right away!
Take that ship and follow Nami!
Forget about it.
Just give that ship to her.
No need of going after that woman.
I won't accept anyone
but her as our navigator!
All right, all right...
What a high-maintenance captain...
Hey Usopp, let's go!
Uh? Okay...
--Big Bro Zoro, the ship is ready!
Luffy, what about you?
I can't go since I haven't settled
anything at this restaurant.
Be careful.
The situation here isn't normal.
Yeah, I know.
Wh-What? What the hell just happened?
The ship's been split into two!
Look at that!
It's him!
Don Krieg! It's him!
It's the man who destroyed our fleet!
Th... That man!
So that man is...
That son of a bitch!
He followed us here... to kill us!!
We're done for!
Zoro?
Who's that?
The man I've been looking for.
Hawk-Eye Mihawk!
Hawk-Eye Mihawk...
The world's strongest man...
That's the man who sank Krieg's
50 ships on his own in the Grand Line?
Then, the one who destroyed
Krieg's ship just now is also...
But he looks just like
an ordinary human.
It doesn't look like he
has any special weapons.
His weapon is on his back...
That... can't be!
Did he really slice up that large
sailing ship using that sword?
He's the master swordsman Hawk-Eye...
...the man who stands above all
other swordsmen in the world...
I never thought I'd be
able to see him this soon...
It's finally... time to fulfill my promise...
Y-You son of a bitch...
What grudge do you
have to come after us?!
Just killing time.
Wha?! Don't mock us!
Wh-What?!
I'm sure I aimed straight for him!
He averted them.
He gently changed
the course of the bullets
using the point of his sword.
That can't be true...
Hey! Who are you?!
Three swords... Could it be...
I've never seen a sword
moved so gently...
There is no strength in
swordplay based only on force.
Did you use that sword to
slice up this ship as well?
That's right.
I see... You're the strongest...
I came out to sea to meet you.
What's your goal?
To become the strongest!
Hmph... How foolish...
You've got spare time,
right? Let's fight!
Th-This guy is Zoro! Roronoa Zoro
of the Three Swords Style!
What?!
Oh, a pirate hunter, huh?
He is?!
Hey, this isn't good, Luffy!
The Going Merry will
be out of sight soon!
Hey, Luffy!
Fight? Hmph! How pitiful, weak one...
If you are a competent
enough swordsman,
you should be able to see
the disparity in our abilities
even before we cross swords.
Is it your courage or ignorance that
causes you to turn your sword on me?
It's my ambition!
And it's also because of a
promise I made to a dear friend!
Hawk-Eye Mihawk,
the world's strongest swordsman,
and the pirate hunter Zoro...
What kind of fight will it be?
There can't possibly be anyone
who can defeat Big Bro!
Big Bro is the strongest already!
Hey, what's the meaning of that?
I'm no beast that goes all
out when hunting a rabbit.
Even if you're a swordsman who's
earned a bit of a name for himself,
this sea, the East Blue, is the
weakest among the four seas.
Unfortunately, I don't carry any
smaller sharp instrument than this one.
That's enough making fun of me!
Better not regret it when I kill you!
Frog in the well...
Know how big the world is.
Oni... Giri!
Wh-What?!
Zoro?!
Wha... Big Bro's Oni Giri was stopped!
Even a big technique that never
fails to blow any enemy away was...
What's going on?!
I... I can't move them! What did he do?!
No one has ever seen
through this technique,
and he stopped it using a toy like that?!
This... can't be happening!
Our abilities are this far apart?!
That can't be right!
There's no way that it's this far...
The world's strongest can't be this far!
This can't be happening,
right, Big Bro?! Get serious!
Big Bro!
We can't be this far apart!
What ferocity your swordplay has...
He's taking Zoro's Three Swords Style
attacks with such a small knife...
He's a monster even beyond
the monstrous Zoro!
I didn't pursue
swordsmanship all this time
to be dealt with by a toy like this!
Zoro...
You're lucky, Zoro. You're a boy.
I want to be the world's
greatest swordsman, too!
If only... If only I had been born a man!
Don't be whining like
that after you beat me!
That's not fair! You're my goal!
Zoro...
Promise me!
Someday, one of us will be
the world's greatest swordsman!
Promise me!
--It's a promise!
To become the world's strongest!
I... I'm going to get
stronger for her, too!
I'll be the world's greatest swordsman
so that my name will reach heaven!
I promised her... I...
Only to defeat this man...
What do you bear on your shoulders?
What do you desire once you've
obtained power, weak one?
You called Big Bro a
weak one? You cross bastard!
I'll teach you a lesson! He is...
Stop it! Yosaku! Johnny!
Don't intervene!
Be patient!
Luffy...
I can't lose...
Tiger...
That sounds great!
The world's greatest swordsman?
The King of the Pirates would need
no less than that on his crew!
...Trap!
Are you just going to
let me pierce your heart?
Why aren't you withdrawing?
I don't know...
I don't know why, but...
...if I withdrew even a step,
I feel like those various
important things such as pledges
and promises in the
past will be shattered,
and I won't be able to come
back to where I am now...
Yes, that's what defeat is about.
Then, all the more reason
I can't withdraw...
Even if you'll die?
I'd rather die.
What a strong heart!
So he chooses death over defeat!
Kid! State your name.
Roronoa Zoro.
I'll remember it.
I haven't seen anyone like you
in a while, strong one. Thus...
...as a swordsman's courtesy,
I'll sink you using the world's
strongest black sword.
I appreciate it.
H-He took it out!
That's the sword that sliced up the ship!
So this'll be the last hit...
Will it be the world's strongest?
Or death?
Big Bro! That's enough! Please stop!
Three Swords Style Secret Technique!
Fall!
Three Thousand Worlds!
I lost...
I never imagined I'd ever lose...
So this is the power
of the world's strongest...
What are you...
Scars on the back are
a swordsman's shame...
Admirable!
Zoro!!
Don't live so hastily, young man.
--Big Bro!!
Why?
When I decided to become
the strongest swordsman,
I decided to devote my life to it.
He's crazy! His opponent
is the real world's strongest!
How it'd turn out was clear. He should
give up his ambition rather than die!
It should be easy...
to give up your ambition, right?!
So this is the power of the Grand Line...
the power of the world!
To think the pirate hunter Zoro
is as helpless as a new-born baby!
Damn you, damn you... Damn you!!
--Big Bro!!
Wh-What's that?
So that brat... has the
power of a devil fruit!
You bastard...
Are you that young
swordsman's comrade?
You also impressed me for
watching it to the very end!
Don't worry. I didn't kill that man.
What?
Big Bro! Big Bro! Say something!
Zoro?!
Zoro!!
Now, hurry up and get
him up on the ship!
This is medicine! Throw it over him!
It's still too early for you to die.
My name is Dracule Mihawk!
Learn about yourself!
Learn about the world!
And become strong!
No matter how many years it takes,
I will hold this seat of
the strongest and wait for you.
Surpass this sword!
Try to surpass me! Roronoa Zoro!
Big Bro! Big Bro, say something!
Big Bro!
To think that he got Hawk-Eye
Mihawk to say this much...
Kid, what is your goal?
King of the Pirates!
It'll be even harder than surpassing me!
How would I know when
I haven't done it yet?!
He's alive!
He's just unconscious.
--Big Bro!
--Big Bro! Say something!
Zoro?
Big Bro!
L... Luffy...
Can you hear me?
Yeah!
Did I worry you?
You need no less than the world's
greatest swordsman, right?
Big Bro! Please don't talk any more!
Big Bro!
I... I will not be defeated ever again!
Until the day I defeat him
and become a master swordsman...
I'll never... be defeated!
Got any problems with that...
...King of the Pirates?!
Nope!
You're a good team.
I want to see you guys again.
Hey, Hawk-Eye!
Didn't you come to take my life...
...the life of the East
Blue's ruler, Don Krieg?
I was going to, but I had enough fun.
So I'm going home to get some rest.
You may have had enough,
but I'm tired of getting beaten.
D-Don?
Why are you trying to keep him here?
Die before you leave!!
As I expected...
he never learns a lesson...
Damn! He escaped...
Usopp!
Luffy!
Go! I'll leave Nami to you!
Got it! Zoro and I will
bring Nami back for sure!
Make sure you get that cook to join us!
When all five of us
are reunited, let's go to...
...the Grand Line!
Yeah! Let's do that!
Guys! We ran into some interference,
but the real fight starts now!
We'll take that ship!
Yeah!!
Pops, can I stop doing
chores if I drive them away?
Suit yourself.
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Krieg and his pirates are coming!
Honestly, what an
ungrateful bunch they are,
when they were given food!
Come to think of it,
there's another ungrateful one
who took treasure and ran off...
You shouldn't worry
about it! Get some rest!
Hey, a weird guy came out...
He's fully armed with shields!
Ow, ow, ow! Fire! Fire!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Deadly Foot Technique Bursts Forth!
Sanji vs. the Invincible Pearl"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!