These are the fake blueprints
that you passed off on us earlier.
When I look at it carefully,
there're signatures by the architects.
"Tom," "Iceberg," and "Cutty Flam."
At the end, there's a
company name: "Tom's Workers."
I remember hearing this
name Cutty Flam before.
Tom's other disciple Cutty Flam is still alive...
...and lives in this town...
...after changing his name to Franky!
Now, you go ahead! Ahead of us!
Cut down the door and make a dash!
--Go ahead!
--What the hell?! Don't order me around!
Where's Robin?!
--Luffy!
Robin! I've finally found you!
Hey, Luffy! Where the hell have you been?!
Robin! I'm glad that I could see you again!
Hold on a sec... What's going on here?
Well, well, well...
I-Iceberg-san...
Wh-What the hell...
...is going on?!
Paulie... Why... didn't you run?
What's going on?
This looks... as if...
...they're the culprits who tried to kill you!
Why are you guys dressed like that?!
Hey! Kalifa...! Blueno...! Kaku...! Lucci...!
Stop joking, you bastards!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Come Back, Robin! Showdown with CP9!"
Oh, yeah!
They're some of the shipwrights
who were with you! Right?!
Come to think of it, I know
that square long-nosed guy.
Could this mean... that the
assassination was an inside job?!
What? What do you mean?!
Paulie, to tell you the truth,
we're Government intelligence agents.
Well, you'd forgive us if we apologized, right?
We were fellow shipwrights who worked
together building ships every day.
If you can't believe me because this is too sudden,
shall I step on Iceberg's face or something?
Stop messing around! That's enough...
After all, the bull-masked man's voice I
heard earlier is the same voice as yours!
Dammit, you bastard! You can talk just fine!
How dare you mock us?!
Don't, Paulie!
Pipe Hitch Knives!
Finger Pistol!
You still haven't learned your lesson, Paulie?
Hey! Rope guy!
Why...?
You guys...
Stop this pointless resistance.
We've mastered techniques beyond
the limits of human abilities.
After years of training, these techniques,
called the "Six Powers," allow human
bodies to be a match for weapons.
Once one masters them, he alone
is as strong as 100 people together.
Coo coo! Don't get carried away with gambling.
You dummy! I was lucky today.
That's why I'm treating you guys!
Blueno! Bring us more alcohol!
Okay!
Kalifa! You're dressed like that again?!
Stop it, Paulie. Just don't look at her. Right?
Why are you guys...?
Well, never mind.
Either way, you're gonna be killed.
This is sad, but my friend...
Lucci! You...!
Stop it! You jerk!
Gum-Gum...
--Iron Body.
--...Gatling!
What? It's not working at all!
How annoying... Shave!
He disappeared!
Finger Pistol!
Luffy!
If you had a flesh-and-blood body, you would've
gotten a hole in your neck and died instantly...
...rubber man.
What're you doing, Straw Hat?
You're planning to kill him, aren't you?!
I thought you were all shipwright
friends who worked together!
Up until earlier, yes.
But that's no longer the case.
Then you guys really are traitors?!
Fine, then!
At any rate, I promised him
that we'd beat the crap out of those
who're trying to kill Ice pops together!
Why are you siding with Paulie?
Because I have some business
with you people, too!
Hey, Robin! Why are you with jerks like them?!
If you wanna leave us, tell us the reason!
He's right! They said they work
for the Government! So why?!
You're not listening, are you?
I did say goodbye to Cook and Doctor.
You didn't tell them?
I did! But I can't accept it, either! Why, Robin?!
To make my wish come true...
A wish that can never come true if I'm with you!
In order to make it happen, I don't
care what sacrifices need to be made!
That's why... you set your friends up
as assassins without hesitation?
What's that wish of yours?!
I don't need to tell you.
This is insane!
That woman is...!
Are you out of your mind, Nico Robin?!
Do you realize what you're about to do?!
You no longer have the right to say anything!
Keep your mouth shut!
Iceberg-san!
I won't let anyone get in my way!
Hey, Robin! What're you doing?!
Do you really mean it?!
Robin! What happened to you?!
Are you really our enemy now?! Robin!
Sorry, but I need you guys to stop now.
We have to find an important
person now, so we're in a hurry.
We no longer have business here.
We don't have any business
with you guys, either.
Kalifa, how much time is left?
Two minutes.
I know this is sudden, but this building
is to be set aflame in two minutes.
--What?
--What?!
What'd you say?!
Fire is an effective tool for
destroying various types of evidence.
If you don't wanna burn to death,
you should leave the building immediately.
Well, of course...
...that is, if you could.
Looks like they intend to eliminate us.
It also seems that Nico Robin
wants to be on their side.
Luffy, were you able to accept
Robin's leaving the ship?
How could I?!
Well, you don't have to shout like that.
Soon, several rooms on the first
floor will burst into flames.
Well, the culprits are pirates.
Things like this can happen.
You bastards...!
To think that you do as you please
while pretending someone else did it...
You sure have bad taste!
You guys are already criminals. No harm done.
Well, then...
I'll go on ahead and leave now.
Yeah, you completed your job. Thanks.
Wait, Robin!
I won't allow it!
Goodbye.
Robin!
Don't...
...let Nico Robin go.
Where're you going this time...
when we finally found you?!
Outta my way, you bastard!
Iron Body.
Why are their bodies so hard?!
Our bodies are well trained.
We can raise our bodies' solidity
to be as hard as iron crust.
However... that's not to say
defense is all we can do.
I said outta my way!
Paper Art.
Ahh... He's dodging all the
punches... when he's that big!
He's fluttering like paper!
Robin!
Wait!
You son of a...!
Gum-Gum...
--...Pistol!
--Shave!
He disappeared, too!
If your legs are so tremendously strong
that it appears as if you disappeared...
--You bastard!
--Moon Walk.
...you can even kick the air and float.
He's flying! What the...?
And... Tempest Kick.
A slashing attack?!
You two...!
Duck!
Why?!
Luffy!
Did they just cut the wall by kicking?!
That's possible if you can kick fast
enough to cause a gust of sharp wind.
We call it Tempest Kick.
We met on your ship, didn't we, Roronoa?
You aren't a shipwright, then?
Then, could that assessment
of our ship you made be...
Unfortunately... I made the
assessment of the ship seriously.
That's indeed unfortunate.
Luffy!
Don't go, Robin!
We're not done talking yet!
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
Robin!
Luffy! Hurry up and catch Robin!
Roronoa! You're quite confident,
aren't you, taking your eyes off of me?
Ah! Zoro!
Finger Pistol.
We don't need bullets to
shoot through human bodies.
You...
...bastard...! Let me go!
Luffy got caught so easily!
Go, Nico Robin.
Robin!
Dammit...
Luffy!
Zoro!
How can they be that strong?!
What are you people?
We've lived in a different environment.
Ever since we, CP9 members, can remember,
we've been prepared to risk
our lives for the Government
and trained to surpass the
limits of human abilities.
As a result,
we've mastered the superhuman
techniques called the Six Powers.
I'm sure you've fully learned by now
that the four of us, who have been entrusted
with the World Government's vital tasks,
are in a whole different league
from you guys, a mere pirate group.
This is a world-class top secret.
It's not a matter that people
like you can get involved in.
Lucci...
It's about time for the igniters
to go off. We have to hurry, too.
Yeah.
But this is a rare occasion.
Let me show you something
interesting before we go.
--What?
--Th-This is...
Lucci... What the hell are you?
He's huge!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Whoa! He's huge!
What's with that appearance?!
This is how I really look.
We're done with you guys now.
Straw Hat, can you defeat him?!
He's huge, but I'll beat him up!
Hmph! I'll let you experience
my strongest power!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Straw Hat Pirates Annihilated?
The Menace of the Leopard Model!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!