Don't go, Robin!
We're not done talking yet!
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
Luffy! Hurry up and catch Robin!
Robin!
How can they be that strong?!
What are you people?
We are CP9.
This is a world-class top secret.
It's not a matter that people
like you can get involved in.
It's about time for the igniters
to go off. We have to hurry, too.
Yeah.
But this is a rare occasion.
Let me show you something
interesting before we go.
A Devil Fruit!
Which one?!
Lucci... What the...?
The Cat-Cat Fruit...
Leopard Model...
A leopard human...
H-He's huge!
What's with that appearance?!
What the hell are you?!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"The Straw Hat Pirates Annihilated?
The Menace of the Leopard Model!"
Fire!
Hey, everyone! Wake up!
Dammit...! Is this the pirates' doing?
There must still be a lot of people left inside!
Where's Iceberg-san?!
What's going on upstairs?!
Let's go check!
Hurry! The rest of you, put out the fire!
Looks like the fire has started to spread.
I don't know if you're a
leopard human or what, but...
...I won't let you lay a finger on Iceberg-san!
Oh, no! Carnivore Zoan types
become more brutal!
That's right. Logia types,
Zoan types, and Paramythia types...
Many unique powers exist.
Genuine physical augmentation
is the trait of Zoan types.
The more we train, the stronger we get.
The Zoan type is the strongest species
when it comes to a close attack.
Shut up!
I don't wanna hear stuff
about monsters like that!
We don't want to waste time, either...
...since we have to take care of you guys
before we get wrapped up in flames.
Iceberg-san!
Foremen!
Lucci... the craftsmen are coming upstairs.
Don't worry. They can't make it this far.
Tempest Kick!
Go back! The ceiling is...!
Nami!
Chopper!
Paulie, what're you doing?
I'm taking you out of this place no matter what!
It's not possible! Your injuries
are too severe! How can you...
Stop it, Paulie.
Don't call my name... as if we're friends!
Get... out of our way!
Damn you...!
Why did it have to be you guys?!
I...
...at least...
I considered you guys my friends all this time!
It was just you.
Pigeon jerk...!
Straw Hat!
Finger Pistol.
Luffy!
Have a nice flight off the island!
You bastard!
Iron Body.
Zoro!
You too.
Grandma! Grandma! There's a big fire!
That's Galley-La's main office.
What a terrible thing to do...
A terrible thing? Did someone set the fire?
Well, I don't know...
...but often, a bad feeling turns out to be right.
I hope Iceberg is okay.
Seriously, this is all because of
that thing. It just shouldn't exist.
What pirates say cannot be evidence.
This incident will now be shrouded in darkness.
Iceberg-san... No matter how good
of a shipbuilding engineer you are,
or even if you're the mayor of a big city...
...you, a mere citizen, shouldn't have disobeyed
the powerful World Government.
Let's go. We'll find Tom's
other disciple Franky--
rather, Cutty Flam, and take
the blueprints from him.
Did you get everyone out of the building?!
We can't go inside anymore!
Have each team account for its men!
Hey, where's Iceberg-san? Did you see him?
Don't tell me he's still in this fire...
I'm sure he's okay!
Three of our foremen are with him.
There's no way he got left in there.
You guys go check around there, too!
This woman...
She's one of the Straw Hats. There's no mistake!
Did she jump out a window?
She was probably surrounded by
flames and had trouble escaping.
What do we do with her?
Seriously... what a terrible thing they've done.
We'll make her tell us where the others are!
We'll capture all of them and
hand them over to the Navy!
Blueno... So Franky was at your bar?
Yeah.
But he rushed out to find Straw Hat.
I see...
Seems like he doesn't stay in one place for long.
But people with bad timing really exist.
Look.
Listen, Straw Hat!
We've got Long-nose with us!
That's right, we do!
If you don't want him to sing in the key of C...
Idiot! That's not it! How many
times do I have to tell you?!
That's "If you don't want him to sink in the sea"!
In the key of C...
"In the sea"!
Geez, what were you listening to?!
What's important is to get the
message to Straw Hat, right?!
We're saying that message ain't gonna work!
Bro is gonna beat you up.
You say it like, "If you don't
want him to sink in the sea,
come to the warehouse under the bridge!
Franky sends his regards!"
Got that?!
Mind you, even if he comes, Bro is
gonna beat the crap out of him, though.
Who did you say is waiting for whom where?
Hm? Who the hell are you?!
We're busy right now! Get lost!
If you don't wanna die,
answer my question in three seconds.
Huh?!
This guy's talking nonsense.
Do you know what family we're in?
Which place do you mean by
the warehouse under the bridge?
Franky is there, isn't he?
What business do you have with Bro?
If you wanna talk to him, then talk to us first!
To think that you left the friends
you traveled together with
all the way from the East Blue, for the ship...
What are you guys crying for?
You dummy! We're not crying, you dummy!
But it's true that I was moved by your
protecting this ship all by yourself
while all those things were happening!
We're not crying! None of us are crying!
What the heck is their problem?
Anyway, now you know that those guys
and I are no longer friends, right?!
I'll...
I'll sing about your hardships!
The song title is, "Severed Friendship!
Northern Wind Chop!"
Yay! Bro!
Are you making fun of me?!
Hey, is the tea ready yet? I'm thirsty.
Okay! We'll bring it right over!
I'm exhausted from crying...
Not that I cried, though.
Here you go, Bro. It's a little hot.
Thanks.
Then, I get it, brother, you know...
Ouch, it's hot!
Settle down a little, will you?!
I'm sorry, Bro.
Why don't you take a break
and have some tea, too?
I can't blame you. You must be
holding quite a grudge against us
for taking 200 million Berries
away from you guys...
...since it led to such a big fight.
It was meant to happen, that's all.
Holding a grudge doesn't do me any good.
You're a good sport.
I see...
That 200 million...
I used it all, though!
You want me to knock you over?
Now, now... Don't get so upset.
You've shown me how manly you are.
So, now I have to calm my anger
over the complete destruction
of the Franky House, which was
my home and demolition factory.
On top of that, you guys
annihilated my subordinates!
How dare you bastards?!
--Bro!
--The anger welled up!
You bastards!
Well, brother, although a lot happened,
let's calm our anger towards
each other on this matter,
and settle it as "Heave-ho! Heave-ho!"
You mean "fifty-fifty."
You mean "fifty-fifty," Bro.
Well, there you go.
What're you gonna do now that you're alone?
You have nowhere to go anyway, right?
If that's the case, I can
take you in. Work for me!
I like you.
No way! I don't wanna
become a demolition worker.
Even though I left my group, I'm still a pirate!
Please listen to my song.
It's titled "The Pirate Code."
Yay! Bro!
Like I said, are you making fun of me?!
Geez... I'm trying to think what
you should do next, for your sake!
It's none of your business!
Besides, is it okay for you
to relax in a place like this?
A storm surge is coming soon, right?
Yeah, that's exactly why...
When Aqua Laguna comes,
we all have to help each other.
From now until late into the night,
houses will be submerged
up to the second floor.
If you're in the backstreets or capes at
a time like this, you don't stand a chance.
You don't have to worry if
you keep your ship here too.
Oh... Thanks... I appreciate it.
You dummy! Don't act like we're strangers!
In any case, it must be tough to have
flood damage like that every year.
Well, everyone's used to this
annual evacuation, though.
What's more problematic
is that the water level of the sea
has been increasing every year.
The backstreet area you can see above
the sea now is a town built on the rooftops
of an old town that existed
several hundred years ago.
It's said that the shipbuilding
island and the backstreets
were completely on one land a long time ago.
But now, so much of the area is under
water that it's called a floating city.
All the sidewalks became canals.
Properly speaking, rather than saying
that the water level is increasing,
they say that the foundation
of the island is sinking.
As it stands, the areas in town we can
live in will get smaller and smaller.
I see... Even this pretty floating
city has hardships too, huh?
But, well, if push comes to shove,
you can take the sea train
and go live somewhere.
You can say that... now.
But it was only a bit over a decade
ago that the sea train was created.
Before that time, it wasn't quite
that easy to go across the sea.
Huh?
Naturally, people were rarely able to
go back and forth between the islands.
On this isolated island,
the residents vaguely imagined
their land being submerged someday
and grew completely hopeless.
What relieved people's
worries even about the future
was the sea train, Puffing Tom.
You can now go across the sea
whenever you want without a Log Pose.
So this was big progress!
I see... I didn't know.
The sea train really is an incredible thing, huh?
Water Seven came back to life.
It's all thanks to a great shipwright
named Tom who created the sea train.
We were all saved by him.
Bro!
Help...
I'll say hello to "Bro" for you.
We now know the location.
Let's go.
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
Hey, Long-nose. What're you
gonna do after you fix that ship?
What else? I'll go on an
adventure with her again and...
That's not possible. You can't.
--What'd you say?!
--That ship can't even reach
the next island anymore.
I'll help you demolish that ship.
Stop it! What're you doing?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Man Who Is Loved Even
by His Ship! Usopp's Tears!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!