Mozu!
Kiwi!
Pardon me... for interrupting.
It's just, these two ladies didn't let us in, so...
What the hell are you bastards doing here?!
--Iron Body!
--Hm? You son of a bitch!
Blueno! What's the meaning of...
Huh? What's this? How cocky...!
Who do you think I am?!
Who are you trying to pick a fight with?!
You're only a dull bar owner!
What's up with that getup?!
You seem different from your usual self!
Tsk.
Don't, Blueno.
H-Hey! A-Are you okay?!
--Hang in there!
--We can't kill him yet. Don't forget our mission.
--Sorry.
--Wh-Wh-What's going on?! Hey!
I thought I saw them working at the shipyard!
What the hell? Why was he able to...
You bastards! What are you people?!
You sure are acting pretty super, aren't you?!
How dare you hurt innocent girls?!
They're like my little sisters, you jerks!
To start with, how the hell
do you know about this place?
This is my secret base!
We don't care about that. I'll keep
this simple. Listen carefully.
Our lives in this town were a cover.
In reality, we are World
Government intelligence agents.
You must know what that means...
...as well as the reason we came here.
Franky... we already know everything.
Cutty Flam...
Tom's other disciple, who was said
to have died eight years ago...
That's you.
I don't know how you found
that out... but that's splendid.
At the same time, I'm starting to feel uneasy.
Is that idiot Iceberg doing okay?
We killed him.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Franky's Past! The Day
the Sea Train First Ran"
Don't try to play innocent now...
...as we already know everything.
It's only a matter of time before I get targeted.
Leave the island with them... Franky.
Tom handed them down to Iceberg...
and Iceberg to you.
Both of you, come over here.
I wanna entrust something
important to you two.
Our mission took quite a while,
but it's finally checkmate.
Now, hand over the blueprints for the
ancient weapon Pluton, Cutty Flam.
Flam...? That's a strange name.
"Franky" would do, right? "Franky" would.
Anything is fine.
Can you hear me?
I'm saying hand them over to us, Cutty Flam.
I've got nothing I could give you jerks!
Wha...!
Wh-What just happened?! It was so
fast that I couldn't see anything.
Hey! Are you okay?!
This is...
What's the matter, Lucci?
What is this filthy room?
A drafting room?
Oh?
It's a good place to hide blueprints. Find them!
These are... nameplates?
Cutty Flam.
Iceberg.
Tom.
This name is...
Hm?
This is...
Don't you dare touch it!
Don't intrude upon someone's memories!
This is where we grew up.
The shipbuilding company, Tom's Workers!
It's where the world's best shipwright lived!
"Water Seven, 22 years ago"
He's gonna eat me!
Take these!
Move! Move aside, Iceberg!
Well...! What the hell are you doing, Franky?!
Well...! What the hell are you doing
instead of helping me with work?!
To think that you keep
making unstable stuff like this!
Shut up! It's none of
your business, Stupid-berg!
This is my precious battleship,
the Battle Franky!
I don't know what that is, but ditch the
whole thing before someone gets hurt!
This is the scrap heap island! It's my
own business to keep whatever I want!
Just wait and see!
Next time for sure, I'll build a
battleship that will beat Sea Kings!
Well...! There's no way you can
beat them! I hope you get eaten!
--I can beat them!
--Well...! You can't!
--I can!
If you're a man... do it resolutely!
That concludes the launch ceremony!
We were resolutely able
to make a solid, good ship!
Right, Yokozuna?
Ribbit! Ribbit!
Let's finish it up tomorrow, shall we?
Now, let's go home.
Ribbit, ribbit!
Boy, I'm hungry.
--Ribbit, ribbit!
--I wonder what we're having for dinner.
Ribbit, ribbit!
Hey, wait up, Tom-san!
So which Battle Franky did
you build this time, Franky?
The eighth one! It was close!
Don't lie!
Geez... Since you let him do this stuff,
Tom-san, he gets full of himself!
All he makes are weapons!
Shut up, Stupid-berg!
What'd you say, Moron-ky?!
--Now, now, stop fighting, both of you.
--He said "Moron-ky"!
But Kokoro-san! This idiot was...!
Geez...
You too, Tom-san. You're laughing
too hard. What was so funny?
Oh... yeah... I just remembered...
I heard that another trading ship with
lumber on it was attacked by pirates.
After the King of the Pirates was executed,
the number of pirates grew considerably.
It's all over for this town. It's being
overtaken by the pirate era.
People are in low spirits.
"Merchant"
We can now get lumber and iron
only from other islands due to
the floods caused by Aqua Laguna,
and yet, violent seas and pirates hinder trading.
Shipyards scramble for customers
due to the shortage of work.
They start fighting. They lose their jobs.
If nothing is done, Water Seven,
an island that once left its mark
with its shipbuilding business,
will become weak-minded,
just waiting for floods to happen.
That's right! Tom-san built
an incredible pirate ship, too!
Say, teach me how to draw
blueprints for a pirate ship!
What's so funny?
Franky, there's no such thing
as blueprints for a pirate ship.
If the sailors who board a ship put up
a skull flag, then it's a pirate ship.
If they put up a seagull flag,
then it's a Navy ship.
I don't care what you wanna build,
but a man should be resolutely
proud of the ship he built!
Aren't you going to bed yet, Tom-san?
What're you drawing?
Mm... It's this island's hope.
Hope?
Hopefully, it can revive Water Seven.
Now, go to bed.
Yeah.
Hm?
Ahh!
The Government's Judicial Ship is here!
What's a Judicial Ship?
It's a mobile court.
Who did they come to judge?
Wait a sec! What did
Tom-san do to deserve this?!
Hey! Outta my way, you jerks!
Give us Tom-san back!
I'll be fine. Don't worry.
Tom-san! Tom-san!
The King of Pirates, Gold Roger,
was executed the other day.
We consider shipbuilding engineer Tom's
act of building Gold Roger's pirate ship,
the Oro Jackson, to be aiding and
abetting this vicious world-class criminal.
Hence, Tom will be taken to
Enies Lobby to be executed!
What?!
This is terrible! Tom will...
Tom will be executed!
They say it's on the charge of
building the King of the Pirates' ship.
So it's finally time, huh?
It caused problems for the
entire world. They had no choice.
Normally, no matter whom a shipwright
sells a ship to, it's not a crime.
However, the King of
the Pirates is an exception.
We consider all those who have
assisted in his pirating activities
to be dangerous individuals!
Hence, he's sentenced to the death penalty!
Take the offender away.
Yes, sir!
--Now, let's go.
--Hurry up and walk!
--What's the matter?
--Go already!
Hey, what're you doing?!
I'm currently designing...
...a paddle steamer that resolutely runs
on a railway set on the ocean's surface.
--Hey! What're you saying?!
--Why, you...!
Suppose this island's decline is due
to trade not happening as we wish it...
Suppose the hopelessness that people feel
is coming from the worries
about this sinking island...
Putting a sea train into operation...
...will definitely save Water Seven someday!
I-I'm sorry! We'll take him out right away!
No... wait a moment.
Huh?
Sea train, you said?
It's a ship that puffs smoke
and runs from one island
to another on a sea railway.
It'll carry people and goods as well as ships.
Without having to worry about the weather,
everyone will be able to freely cross the ocean.
Stop kidding yourself!
A railway? It'd be destroyed
once Aqua Laguna comes!
That's right! Besides, there are
also Sea Kings in the sea!
The sea railway doesn't have to be fixed.
It'll sway a little below the surface of
the water, never resisting the waves.
As if pulling in a rope, the sea train
will just use the railway as a guide.
Furthermore, I'm thinking of adding
a mechanism that generates
a discordant sound that fish hate
between the paddles and the railway.
Then Sea Kings won't come close to the railway.
Is something like that possible?
If we connect St. Poplar, Pucci,
San Faldo, and this island,
industries can grow through trading.
How wonderful...!
The blueprints will be completed soon,
but it's not so simple that
ordinary shipwrights can build it.
Is it possible to connect Enies Lobby as well?
Of course it is!
Once this technology is completed
and eventually crosses the ocean,
the relationships among islands all
around the world will resolutely change!
The sea train is the hope of Water Seven!
How long will it take?
Ten years.
Then build it!
As the development period for the sea train,
I give ten years probation
to shipbuilding engineer Tom!
This is incredible!
Good luck, Tom!
Please save Water Seven!
I'm resolutely still alive!
This is no laughing matter, Tom-san.
I thought that your time had come
and I got a chill down my spine.
But anyway, if things go well, they may
let the matter with Roger go, huh?
Well...! At any rate, you're great, Tom-san!
To think that you've been
thinking about something like that!
Everyone was overwhelmed!
The sea train really is...
Thanks for the dinner! Come, Yokozuna!
I'll teach you how to do the front crawl!
Ribbit!
Hey, Franky! What's with you?!
You've been sulking for a while now!
Shut up! I'm angry at everything!
Gold Roger's ship is the only ship in the
world that went around the Grand Line!
Why does Tom-san, who built such
a great ship, have to get executed?!
The people there were also
saying that it was just natural,
even though those idiots can't even build a raft!
I also know that the reason
our company is under a bridge
is because you were kicked out by the
townspeople over Roger's ship, right?!
Why the hell does the world's best
shipwright have to be treated like this?!
What's funny, you horned raccoon dog?!
Who're you taking it out on, Moron-ky?!
You are not gonna get away with it!
I can't stand that the person
himself is like that, either!
No, no! That's not it!
Stroke with all your might
to push the water backwards!
Ribbit! Ribbit!
No! No! Stroke more vigorously like this!
--Ribbit!
--No! Like this!
--Seriously, what's with him?!
You should just kick out an idiot like him!
Well, don't say that. He's a fellow shipbuilder.
In terms of shipbuilding skills,
there's already no big difference between
him and the craftsmen on the island....
...though what he makes is shaky.
He's just always honest, that's all.
Two years ago, when I saw a kid who had
resolutely appeared on the scrap heap island
make a cannon using junk,
I was really surprised.
Old man, take me in!
I was abandoned by my parents!
He told me that his parents said,
"What an uncontrollable brat,"
and threw him off the ship.
It seems that they were worthless
pirates from some place, though.
--That was so funny!
--Tom-san...
He's tough, isn't he?
Despite his circumstances, he isn't crooked.
You two will definitely become world-class
shipbuilding engineers someday.
You should be nice to each other.
Franky can't do it. He's crazy
even at the cellular level!
Well, as soon as I finish the blueprints,
we'll start building the sea train!
Yeah... but I bet he won't help us.
He can do as he pleases!
Suicide?
I heard that it was the president
of the No. 4 shipbuilding company.
It must be because of that accident.
Since they didn't have materials, he went
to purchase lumber on his own ship
and got fifty people killed on the sea.
His shipyard is closed, too.
How weak humans are, huh?
Is this really it for this island?
Hey! Did you guys hear
about the scrap heap island?!
H-Hey, is that true?!
Tom's Workers has finished
building the sea train, you say?!
Whoa! Does a ship like this really run?
It's a ship built by a criminal. It's dangerous!
I'll get on board!
Me too, then.
Tom! You are not gonna explain?!
We're leaving! Get on board!
It's moving!
The paddles are grabbing the railway!
--It's moving!
--Whoa, amazing! It's running!
Twelve years ago...
...leaving a closed, declining town,
with worried people on board...
...the sea train Puffing Tom crossed
the sea for the first time.
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
I see. So this is a place that holds
your memories with Tom, huh?
The blueprints aren't here!
Get out of here already!
Hmph! Well, fine.
You're a criminal, just like Tom was.
You should know what'll happen to you.
You don't know anything about Tom-san!
Don't talk like you know everything!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Spandam's Scheme!
The Day the Sea Train Shook"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!