Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Only to defeat this man...
Three Swords Style Technique!
Better not regret it when I kill you!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Zoro!!
"The Deadly Foot Technique Bursts Forth!
Sanji vs. the Invincible Pearl"
All right!
They want to fight, too!
Umph!
I'm getting fired up!
Pops! You promised, okay?
Once I drive them away,
I'll quit doing chores. Okay?
Couldn't ask for more.
If you do chores for a year,
this place will get messed up.
All right!
You said you were going to be
King of the Pirates. Are you serious?
Yeah, of course! I'll definitely
be King of the Pirates!
I've come across tons of roughnecks.
But you're the first one in a long
time who said that so clearly.
I heard that you were
an incredibly strong pirate.
Were you going to be
King of the Pirates?
I forgot about the past.
I'm the owner of a restaurant
now and that's enough for me.
Guys! As long as we take that ship,
the Grand Line is
nothing to be scared of!
We can get closer and make a surprise
attack on enemy ships more effectively
than pretending to be a Navy ship
or raising the white flag of surrender.
We can make a definite sneak attack.
It's true that no one would think...
that pirates are on board
such a silly-looking ship.
B-But, Don... Even if we enter
the Grand Line again using that ship,
if we come across someone
like Hawk-Eye Mihawk again...
Are you still afraid of
someone like that? Huh?!
N-No...
You think an ordinary human
can slice up a large sailing ship?!
That's probably the
power of a devil fruit.
Although those with devil fruit powers
are considered by society to be legends,
the Grand Line is crawling with them.
Mihawk must've used some strange
power when he sliced up the ship.
Even that straw hat brat is a mere
pirate once he enters the Grand Line.
But Red Foot Zeff
traveled there for a year.
I can't but think that he had ways
of confronting those monsters.
And those methods must
be written in his logbook.
If we're lucky, so is
information on the One Piece.
I see... That's our Don Krieg!
So long as we have
that ship and the logbook,
we'll find a way to the One Piece again!
Got that, guys?! Let's go!
We'll take over the restaurant!
--Yeah!
This ship belongs to us... to the cooks!
We can't let them have it...
no matter what happens!
N-Now... what do we do
to operate this again?
Hurry up!
As it stands, the restaurant
will be a battlefield...
I wish there was a restaurant
in the middle of the sea...
I was thinking that if I
could leave this place alive,
I'd build a restaurant as
my final purpose in life...
A restaurant as my
final purpose in life...
Go to the operating room
and open up the fins.
What? Open up the fins?
That's gonna give
a foothold to the enemy!
That's fine. We can't make the inside
of this restaurant a battlefield.
If it becomes a battlefield,
that damn geezer will complain.
Did you say something, you damn brat?
Yeah, I said you like
to complain! Now, go.
O... Okay...
Here they come! They're finally coming!
Here I come! Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Ugh! He's flying over here!
And Gum-Gum...
...Giant Scythe!
Oof!
Hey, that chore boy is pretty good!
--J-Just what the heck...
--...is he...
The Grand Line is crawling
with guys like this?
--Sanji!
--Hmm?
Watch carefully how he fights.
Don't take your eyes off him until
the moment this fight comes to an end.
Hmm?
To think that you attack the
restaurant after they gave you food...
I'll beat up an ungrateful jerk like you!
So you actually want to fight on
the water when there's little foothold?
Those with devil fruit powers are
helpless in the sea. I know that much.
--Anchor boy!
--Instead, I can stretch.
Sanji! The fins are gonna open up now!
--Hmm?
--What's going on?
From the sea...
...a foothold has appeared!
Whoa! Check that out!!
We'll fight to the utmost,
you damn pirates!
I see. You set up that battlefield so that
the restaurant itself won't be damaged.
That works out for us too,
since that ship's gonna be ours.
I want this ship all the more.
We won't let you have this restaurant!
That's right! Don't make light of us!
We're fighting cooks!
Take sail! The Baratie's sea
battle weapon, Mackerel Head 1!
If you don't wanna die,
get out of here now!
What the hell is that?
That's so cool! I want it!
--Paddle faster!
--I'm paddling as fast as I can!
Fire!!
I'm gonna sink!
--All right! Good job!
--Patty! Carne! Get them!
They're pretty good!
Don't look away! We're aiming at him!
Yeah!
Krieg! Be prepared!!
Watch how powerful the Sea Restaurant
Baratie's sea battle weapon is!
What? Did we bump into something?
Hmm? We can't move!
I'm Don Krieg!
I'm the man who will
rule the world's oceans!
I told you that's gonna be me!
I don't have time for your games!
What Herculean strength he has!
It's coming this way!
The restaurant will be destroyed!
--Sanji!
--W-With his foot?!
Wh-What strong legs!
He kicked back that weird boat!
That foot technique is...
There goes! Sanji's kick!
He's pretty good!
You son of a bitch, Sanji!
Are you trying to crush your allies?
--Yeah...
--Don't "yeah" us, you crazy stew!
You almost lost powerful assets,
you stupid spaghetti!
Do you really think you have
time to crack jokes, cooks?
Let's get them!
Even with a weapon, a cook's a cook.
We're expert fighters who're in
a whole other league from you.
Now, be good little cooks and go
find a land restaurant to cook for.
Hey, you guys! Why are you letting
those guys beat you up so easily?!
Do you still call
yourselves fighting cooks?!
Well, they're strong!
They're totally different from
those we've fought before!
Don't lump us in with
those average pirates.
We're the Krieg Pirates,
the rulers of the East Blue.
Just decree to them... that the ship
already belongs to the Krieg Pirates!
Don't be mistaken.
We won't let you take even
one step into the restaurant.
He's exactly right!
I've been a cook for
more than ten years.
I visited 300 restaurants.
I got fired for causing a scuffle
all the time and I lived a rough life.
This is the place we finally came to
after going to restaurant
after restaurant...
Anybody there?!
Is this the restaurant
run by Red Foot Zeff?!
This "Damn Cooks Wanted"
better be true!
Yeah, it's true.
Be they arch rogues or jail breakers,
if they badly want to eat and
find their way to this restaurant,
we'll feed them until they're stuffed.
Can you handle that?!
Y-Yes, sir!
We can't serve such a nasty
soup to the customers!
What did you hit me for?!
That's a sign for determination!
Shut up!
Scuffles... cooking...
We're allowed to do whatever we like.
There's no other
restaurant as good as this.
So they say. Got that, Krieg?
Committing ourselves to cooking
every day is a fierce battle.
Compared to that, the pirates
we're facing today are nothing!
He's exactly right!
--Fight!
--Yeah!
--Protect Owner!!
--Protect the restaurant!!
Th-That's...
Hmm...
Just what're you guys doing?
What's with that guy?
Unassailable! Hence invincible!
When someone says,
"Pearl-san, the Invincible Shield
of the Krieg Pirates," they mean me!
Pearl-san!
Patty! Carne! Are you all right?!
They're not all right, because they
took my killer punch, "Pearl Surprise."
Whoa! This is a nice knife. I'll take it.
Hmm? Hey, let go. Give it to me!
Let it go, you damn loser!
He's really got some good kicks!
I didn't come to like him for nothing!
A kitchen knife is a cook's soul.
Don't you amateurs
carelessly put hands on it!
Sanji...
Hold this tight and stay down there.
I'll take care of them.
We won't be beaten by a mere cook!
A mere cook, you said? I'm gonna
cut you in three, you bastards!
Ha! How impudent you are
to beat them using only kicks.
Is that your policy?
To cooks, hands are most important.
I can't have them hurt in battle.
I'll take you down with this leg as well.
Take me down? That's impossible.
I'm an invincible man that won
all 61 of my battles unharmed.
I've never shed blood in
a battle, not even a drop.
Winning unharmed is
the very proof of my power.
I'm a shield man and a gentleman.
I'm refined, aren't I?
Was that supposed to be a gag?
It wasn't funny at all.
Hey, straw hat brat!
If you're not paying
attention, you'll get hurt!
Even battleship cannons
don't work on me.
I come out of any attack unharmed!
Boy, that startled me.
Good thing I didn't fall in the sea.
What?
Ahh... This isn't good.
Blood! Oh, no!
Pearl-san, don't worry.
--It's just a nosebleed!
--It's not a wound from fighting!
--Please calm down, Pearl-san!
--What's going on?
Th-Th-Th-These guys are dangerous!
What's with him? He's acting strange.
What about his nosebleed?
Stop it, Pearl! It's just a nosebleed!
Don't lose your cool!
What the heck is he about to do?
Danger! Danger! Danger!!
Oh, no! It's started!
When Pearl-san gets upset,
he catches fire!
What was that?
Fire Pearls... Special Treat!!
Ouch!
Pearl-san! Please stop!
Burn! With this flame
and the flame shield,
you have no idea how invincible I am!
That idiot! Is he going to burn down
the ship that we're gonna take over?
--Ow, ow, ow, ow...
--Dammit!
Crap! There's no escape from a sea
of flames in the middle of the sea!
This isn't good!
The restaurant will catch fire!
This restaurant will burn?
--Burn! Burn!
--You son of a bitch!
You idiot! You'll get burned, Sanji!
I'm not just gonna let you...
burn this restaurant down!
H-He's so reckless!
Does he want to turn
into a human torch?!
When even fierce animals would
stay away from Fire Pearls...
You fool! I'd be unfit to be
a cook if I was afraid of flames!
D-Dammit! What a refined guy he is!
Here I come!
Ahh! That hit him good!
He broke through
Invincible Pearl-san's wall!
What's with this cook? He's really crazy.
Y-Y-You son of a bitch!
Fire! I need more fire!
I need to feed more Fire Pearls!
Ahh! The restaurant will catch fire!
If the fire gets into the kitchen,
the restaurant will be blown away!
Owner! Please get out of there! Owner!!
--Whoa!!
M-My Fire Pearls...
Something like that is child's play!
The gust from his kick
put out the flame!
What the hell?! That's
definitely a divine technique!
So Red Foot Zeff is still strong?!
Pops is really cool! I'm impressed!
Now that it's come to this,
I'll sink you all with the fins
before the restaurant catches fire!
Sanji! Watch out!!
Oh, no! He's surrounded by fire!
--Ow, ow, ow...
--Chore boy!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
--Ow, ow, ow...
--He hit that iron ball back!
Pearl-san is really down this time!
--Pearl-san is...
What the heck?
That guy sure is dumb.
Geez... They're all...
In the end, I can only count on myself...
The battle ends here.
That's right! Shoot Red Foot Zeff!
All we need to do is kill him.
Then the restaurant will be ours!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
There's no way I'm gonna
let them take this restaurant!
Taking a hostage! That's dirty!
I'm gonna kick that bastard's ass!
Butt out, chore boy!
Keep your hands out of this!
Then, is it okay to use my legs?
I'm gonna cut you in three,
you damn Straw Hat!
I can't let the damn geezer's
purpose in life get taken away!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Zeff and Sanji's Dream;
The Illusory All Blue"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!