Give Tom-san back to us!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Your chief? Hm?
Please go ahead, Chief.
Ouch! It's hot! It's hot! It's hot!
I spilled the coffee!
Dammit! Stupid coffee!
What the hell?
Are you there...
...Cutty Flam?
--Hm?
--It's been a while.
I never thought you'd survived that...
It's hard to believe, but I'm happy to hear it.
Who the hell are you?
You don't remember me?
I'm the man who was from Cipher Pol No. 5
and arrested Tom's Workers red-handed for
attacking the Judicial Ship eight years ago!
You bastard! Spanda!
"M"! You're missing the "M"! It's "Spandam"!
I'll be very much looking forward
to your arrival at Enies Lobby.
Now, guys! Hurry up and bring
that criminal here already!
Hm?
Ouch! It's hot! It's hot! It's hot! Stupid lamp!
--Roger.
--Click.
Ow, ow, ow...!
Dammit! Let me go, you jerk!
Let's go.
Hey, hold it, you bastards!
Let him go!
Ah... I'm sorry.
Hey! You only shine for a second?!
If I remember right, you are...
one of the Straw Hats, aren't you?
What?
"The Truth Behind Her Betrayal!
Robin's Sorrowful Decision!"
The only departure left today is
for government personnel, huh?
To think they have to travel when Aqua
Laguna is about to hit. Must be a pain.
Did you know that some real big shots
are gonna get on today's special train?
What're you taking about?
This is what I overheard when the
Navy people were talking earlier,
but these big shots seem to have been
on a secret mission in Water Seven
for the past several years,
hiding their true identities.
Secret mission?
Yeah. I don't know what they
were actually doing, though.
Hiding their true identities?
Then it might be people we know, huh?
To tell you the truth, I kinda
think I know who they are.
What?! Who are they?!
--Do you think I'm wrong?
--What?! From the backstreets?!
I sometimes see those guys
having secret conversations
in the corner at Blueno's bar.
But that's not enough reason
to suspect them, you know.
But despite the fact that they don't
work much, they're quite prosperous, right?
Yeah, that's true.
They often take the first-class cars.
Right? In any case, we'll know who they
are when they get on the sea train later.
I bet this will be the talk of
the whole town tomorrow.
I see...
This isn't working! The wind is too strong!
The fire isn't going out at all!
If people are still inside,
they'll be done for if this keeps up!
Iceberg-san...! Paulie-san!
Nami... Oh, no...
I have to... treat her... right... away...
Hurry! Give them treatment!
They've got terrible burns!
Hey! What're we gonna do with this reindeer?!
Him, too! He saved their lives!
Y-You're right. Hey! Give me a hand!
Oh, boy...
He got his butt whipped...
So, in short, you're no longer
part of the Straw Hats,
but you still haven't quit being a pirate, huh?
If you're a pirate, then we'll take you.
--Kalifa!
--Yep.
And this ship...
You didn't take it down yet, huh?
Hey! Don't you dare touch her!
What're you doing?! Hey! Are you listening?!
Although it was an assumed identity,
we are recognized shipwrights in this town.
You should listen when we say
it's no good no matter what you do.
So what?! Just leave her alone!
She's not even your ship!
This will release the water, huh?
Wait! Don't do anything stupid! Hey!
Hey! Stop it!
Don't worry.
I'll carry you guys for a little bit longer.
Merry!!
Move back! It's gonna collapse!
Dammit!
You idiot! Run!
Dammit! Isn't there anything we can do?!
Iceberg-san has recovered consciousness!
Really?! That's great!
What a relief! He's okay!
Iceberg-san!
It's all thanks to that reindeer!
But I heard that he's a pet of the Straw Hats.
Hey! This one, too! The woman woke up!
Wh-What're we gonna do?
Should we make her tell us the
Straw Hats' whereabouts now?
But she's severely injured.
And she's a woman, too.
But that's...
Iceberg-san! You shouldn't move around yet!
Guys... give us some space.
I wanna talk to this woman alone.
I wonder what he wants to
talk alone with her about.
Beats me.
Ow! What'd you do that for?!
Quit standing around! Lucci-san and
the others may still be inside!
Give us a hand, you idiots!
Oh, that's right. Hey!
Yeah. Sorry!
Well...
First... I'm sorry.
We falsely accused you of the crime.
I'll clear up the misunderstanding later.
I wanna talk about Nico Robin.
Do you know something?!
Did that woman change after
you guys came to this town?
Yes, suddenly.
After she went out to town,
she suddenly disappeared,
and by this morning, she was the
suspect of your attempted assassination.
When my friends finally found her,
she said she would no longer come back to us.
We didn't know what was going on.
So we came here tonight
in order to ask her directly again
why she's leaving the ship.
To make my wish come true...
A wish that can never come true if I'm with you!
What is this wish that can never
come true if she's with us...?
Let me tell you what I know.
It was probably when you lost
sight of Nico Robin the first time.
CP9...
The Government's operation
was already in progress.
There is, of course, a reason
for that woman's actions.
But before I tell you about that,
I want you to know that Nico
Robin and I both have a means
to bring back the ancient weapon
that could destroy the world.
Destroy the world?
That's right.
A problem occurred in our plan.
Everyone, come to the bedroom right away.
Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
Now, you get it, Nico Robin?
The blueprints you guys were after are fakes.
Even if I am to be killed, I won't give
those blueprints to the Government!
But if you're sniffing around
the Poneglyphs on another front
and helping the Government as well,
then I have to stop you right here, right now.
I'm not seeking the Poneglyphs
in order to bring the weapon back.
I just want to know the history, that's all.
Such a claim doesn't mean anything!
I told you, didn't I?
Over... and over again...
Even if you don't intend to do so...
Weapons hurt people despite your intentions!
They can even hurt those
who mean a lot to you!
That which hurts people doesn't
necessarily have malicious intent.
If that simple curiosity of
wanting to know the history
leads to the destruction of the world,
you should die right here,
right now, Nico Robin!
Even after you saw the Ohara devils' fate,
you still want to chase
after the world's history?!
Don't talk like you know
everything about Ohara!
You don't even know how much the
World Government messed up my life!
If you hate the Government that much,
then why are you helping them?!
Because I have a wish I want to come true
even if I have to give up everything.
There're two conditions that
CP9 forced on me in this town.
One is to pin the assassination
on the Straw Hats.
The other is to turn myself in
to the Government and obey them.
If you do that, you'll die, too.
Why do you accept such conditions
after evading them for 20 years?
In this lone instance,
CP9 has been given permission
to exercise Buster Call against the Straw Hats.
Buster Call?
It's an emergency order to
summon five of the vice admirals
from Navy Headquarters and
ten battleships to one place.
Once you've been targeted by the
national war-class military power,
nothing will remain of you.
Normally, in the Navy, this authority
only belongs to the three admirals
and the head of the Navy, the fleet admiral.
But this time,
through the admiral Aokiji,
CP9 was given the authority
to exercise it just this once.
If I didn't accept the conditions,
Buster Call was going to be exercised on us.
When I heard the name Aokiji, I gave up.
I was always able to make good
my escape for the past 20 years
because I had nothing to protect...
Because I could betray people
and use them as a shield.
But I really can't do that any longer.
The life I once gave up on...
The heart that I lost...
The dream I could no longer have...
They picked them all up for me.
I was able to make friends who
would believe in someone like me.
Then, your wish is...
That the six Straw Hats, excluding me,
can leave this island safely!
Are you saying, for that, you don't care
if the weapon is brought back?!
You don't care what happens to the world?!
That's right. I don't!
Enough of that nonsense!
I couldn't pull the trigger.
Of all people,
over the lives of everyone in this world,
she chose the lives of the six of you.
It was for us...
Now that I might have the weapon's
blueprints taken away by them,
I don't have the right to criticize her, though.
Hey! What's wrong?!
Good...
So Robin didn't betray us after all.
I'd better gather everyone
immediately and let them know!
Thanks, Iceberg-san!
Wait! Straw Hat and the others were beaten!
What do you think you can do now?!
"Now"?!
It starts now! Luffy and the others are fine.
It'd take a lot more than that to take them out.
We're gonna get Robin back!
When unsure, anyone can be weak.
There's no limit to their strength
when they know it's okay to save her!
Chopper! Chopper!
Chopper! Wake up! We have to find everyone!
Chopper! Hey, wake up!
Hey, hey, he's really
seriously injured, you know...
Wake up! Chopper!
Chopper...
You go join Luffy and the others and tell
them everything that just happened...
...without leaving a single word out.
What're you gonna do?
We'll part ways here for a bit.
Well, don't worry. I won't do anything reckless.
What's the matter?
I wonder... if Robin doesn't like us anymore.
Chopper...
Hm?
Remember one thing.
When a woman lies...
...a real man forgives her.
For today's last service to
Enies Lobby, departing at 11 PM,
please board from the second floor
lobby due to the raised water level.
--Okay, let's go check them out!
--Yeah!
Since this involves a secret operation,
you're forbidden to see them board.
Oh, darn...
You were chased after for the past 20 years.
I'm surprised that you gave up now.
Bingo...
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
Then, it's not that Robin
doesn't like us anymore?!
That's right! We'll all go and rescue her!
Okay, let's go! Where are Luffy and Zoro?!
We have to hurry up and find them.
There's only thirty minutes left
before the sea train departs.
Just wait, Robin!
We'll fight for you no matter
who we're up against!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Steam Whistle Forces Friends Apart!
The Sea Train Starts to Run"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!