Of all people,
over the lives of everyone in this world,
she chose the lives of the six of you.
Robin! Get off the train!
We'll fight for you no matter
who we're up against!
Wait!
Robin!
So you didn't make it...
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Sanji Barges In! Sea Train Battle in the Storm!"
Ow... Seriously, what's that man thinking?!
No matter what he's thinking,
that train was for Government use,
so he'll get caught and it'll all be over for him.
Hm? That's Galley-La's... Paul...
Don't be thoughtless!
It looks like there's something
going on between them.
Hm?
Train stations are a place for
people to meet or part ways!
As station employees, we should
quietly watch over them, right?!
Oh, that's right.
Quietly, got that?
Yeah, quietly.
The train left quite a bit early, huh?
What?!
Ah, yes.
All the passengers were already here, so...
Also...
...the sea started getting
rougher than we thought.
At this rate, we thought Aqua
Laguna would come very soon,
so we moved up the departure time.
This place is dangerous, too.
You should evacuate to
the shipbuilding island soon.
That lady, too.
Yeah...
Hey, you... Once the train
has left, we can't stop it.
It's not easy to say this,
but this Enies Lobby place is...
Are you crying?
Um... well, I do understand how you feel, but...
We're gonna go after them!
Oh, she was angry!
Those idiots from the Government!
They're not gonna get away with this!
Hey, let us borrow a ship!
What's with you, all of a sudden?
A huge and strong ship!
Are you trying to sail out
when the sea is like this?!
You idiot!
Don't say such stupid stuff when you
don't know how awful Aqua Laguna is!
We will make it through!
This is a whole other level from the
type of storm surge you're thinking of.
The sea will now get terribly rough!
You can no longer sail out! If you did,
you'd basically be sailing to your deaths!
But Robin, too, laid down her life for us and...
That was close...
Th-Thanks...
Paulie-san! Thank you very much!
We almost got dragged into the sea.
Look at that. That big schedule
board got torn apart by a wave.
Nothing like this has ever happened before.
What's with the power of this ebbing?
It's already this strong
when it's only approaching?
The speed of the waves of
this Aqua Laguna are abnormal.
Hey... Is the sea train Robin is on okay?
It'll probably get through the stormy
area right before the storm surge hits.
Unless it gets hit directly, it'll make
it through most of the big waves.
Hey, are you Nami?
Hm?
An inconspicuous letter
was left in the station plaza.
It's probably from one of your friends.
A letter...? From whom?
I'm surprised that you found such a small thing.
Here! It was left here in
an inconspicuous manner.
"Nami-san! Please read this!
(Those other than Nami-san don't
have to read it, since they're idiots.)"
That idiot...!
What does it say?
Hmm... hold on a sec. The first half
is just a pointless love letter, so...
She said it's a love letter.
The third man has appeared.
No... Judging from the situation,
the third man is actually...
Hm? Why are you looking at me like that?
Here is the important part.
P.S. Since I saw Robin-chan on the
11 o'clock train, I'll get on board, too.
What?! Sanji-kun got on that train?!
And... Usopp?!
Also, a big thug with a ducktail... Who's that?
There's no one like that except Franky.
Right, there's no one else.
The fourth man... And to think
that the fifth man is Franky...
Poor Paulie-san...
Maybe it'd be better if he flatly gives up...
What's with you guys?!
Um... also, this was with that letter.
There should be at least one
transponder snail in the sea train.
So I'll get in touch with you as soon as I can.
I want you to always keep this portable
transponder snail I got in town with you.
That's right. Think of it as
your dear beloved San--
I see. So he'll call this one.
Then he foresaw where Nico Robin
was going to be? That's amazing!
"Nami-san! Please read this!
(Those other than Nami-san don't
have to read it, since they're idiots.)"
Yeah!
For the time being, Robin has Sanji-kun.
We'll definitely go to Enies Lobby, too!
Geez... I can't even have a smoke here.
Is that right?! So Sanji went
to the station after that?
Yep!
Usopp is on the same train, too. I'm glad...
So, anyway, no matter what means
we take to follow the sea train,
we can't do anything unless
we find Luffy and Zoro first.
Okay, got it!
I'm not mistaken about the direction
they flew to. So search those areas.
Everyone, please help us out!
Guys! We're counting on you!
Yeah!
Leave it to us!
Now, how should I quietly infiltrate?
Whoa! What a crazy storm outside!
Collier Shoot!
Who are you?!
Ahhh!
Hold it.
Where do you think you're going?
Don't move!
I saw his kick earlier.
He's no ordinary civilian!
If you say...
...something like that so openly...
...you'll make me blush.
That wasn't a compliment!
He's mocking us!
Hey! Let Lucci-san know that
a suspicious man infiltrated!
Wait!
This isn't something that
we need to bother CP9 with.
No matter how violent the suspicious man is,
there's no need to fear, because in this car...
Whoa! It's smoky!
...you've got me!
Jerry-san!
I'm a champion on a South Blue
island where karate is popular.
That's right. I'm a boxing champion!
Then, do karate.
You can make a comment like
that after you see my punches.
That's cruel!
Jerry... Aurora Flicker... Jab!
J-Jerry-san! The enemy is behind you!
Hm? He escaped?
Hey, kid! Just because I'm so tall,
don't think that I'm at a
disadvantage in this small car.
This is the first time I've been warned
by someone from between their legs.
My boxing rather puts me at
an advantage in a narrow space.
This is a yoga style!
Yoga one, two! One, two!
Your reach has gotten shorter!
So I made it look like, and then...
Screw...
...Drop Kick!
Now you're ignoring the rules of boxing?!
This is a waste of time.
Brochette!
First, the one who leads Government
officials in car #7, the very last car, is...
In order of increasing strength,
the one who leads forty
marines in car #5 is T-Bone,
a Navy Headquarters'
Captain and former knight.
Next, the one standing by in car #4 is Wanze,
a martial artist from Cipher Pol No. 7,
who is also the head steward on this trip.
And the one standing by in car #3 is
Mr. Nero, the newest member of CP9.
Anyway, though we are escorting criminals,
there's no possibility of a raid.
But just in case, we have military
power ready in each car, so...
Straw Hat!
Roronoa!
We're on your side! Come out!
Straw Hat! Where are you?!
Foreman! It must be hard even to move, right?
Why don't you take a little break?
Idiot! This is nothing.
Hurry up and find those two!
Yes, sir!
Did someone let Iceberg-san
know what's going on?
Two men went to give a report to him.
Where are you going? Iceberg-san...
Roronoa!
Straw Hat! Answer if you hear us!
Luffy!
Zoro! Where are you?!
Food... you say?
That's right. I want meat! Meat!
I want you to bring all the
meat you can gather. Hurry up!
But why are we being slave-driven like this?
No, this isn't for that girl.
Let's do our best for Paulie-san,
who's devoted to her even after being dumped!
Yeah!
In any case, she must be really hungry.
She's a growing girl, I bet!
This one, too. There really
aren't any stores open right now.
Oh, that's right. How about the kitchen
at the station's employee dining hall?
We can't take the backstreets.
I bet the area is already flooded.
Then we have no choice but
to search this area, right?
--But--
--Let's go!
You think that girl would forgive us
if we went back empty-handed?!
Rain...
This isn't good.
When the strong winds are already
interfering with my sense of smell...
Say, we've been calling out this much,
and yet there's no answer.
Could it be...
Stop saying stupid stuff! We'll just do our best!
Where are you guys? Luffy... Zoro...
You guys wouldn't be taken out
by a leopard man like that, right?
We finally know why Robin left us.
Where are you, Straw Hat?!
Answer us!
Just wait, Robin.
I'm coming to rescue you with
Luffy and the others without fail!
Hey, what's the matter?!
Ah, Paulie-san! Please take a look!
The more the water ebbs,
the bigger the returning wave becomes.
If you see how the tide ebbs,
you can tell the scale of the storm surge.
I'm being blown away!
Now, if we try to see how much lower
the water level goes this year...
Look at that, Chimney.
Whoa! This is incredible!
The sea looks as if it dried up.
Even I haven't seen a sight
like this in the past few decades.
Can the tide ebb this much?
I've never seen something like this before.
Just how big of a wave is coming this time?
The backstreets are gonna
be completely swallowed up.
There aren't any people
in the backstreets, right?
If there are, they'll die instantly.
The roar of the sea... has stopped.
Oh?
Grandma! Look, look! There's something there!
Is that right?
There's something between two houses!
Hey! Look! Look!
Hmm...
Kokoro-san!
Oh, you're that pirate girl.
Ah! Pirate lady! Hey, look over there!
There's something there!
Something?
Just what is it you're going on about, Chimney?
Hey...
What's with this dried-up sea?!
Luffy...
Hm? That straw hat...
Isn't that your King of the Pirates?
Right?
That idiot!
Hey! Where are you going?!
Don't go down to the backstreets!
Backstreets?! Hey, someone! Stop that woman!
Do you wanna lose your life?!
Aqua Laguna is already coming! Come back!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
Luffy! Luffy... Luffy!
Oh, hey, Nami! Well, I got completely
stuck when I got sent flying.
Listen! Robin was lying to us!
What? She was lying?
She sacrificed herself in order to protect us!
Let's go! We'll protect Robin!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Nami's Soul Cries Out!
Straw Hat Luffy Makes a Comeback!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!