"Car #7"
Captain T-Bone... Hiding in a
small place like this would be hard.
Hm?
Good evening!
There they are!
They're behind the door!
We've found three suspicious men,
including the criminals!
I hate crooked sword attacks.
Right-Angle Flash!
Bone Soir!
Th-They're not here!
Don't tell me...
The cars are detached!
What?!
Dammit! They're the ones who did it!
You bastards! You'll regret this!
So it was too late...
Well then, gentlemen! Watch out
for Sea Kings! Have a nice trip!
Take care!
"Car #4"
I'm Wanze! I'm mad, mad Wanze!
Huh?
Now, now, now!
I'm Wanze!
If you want to pass through this car,
you'll have to defeat me first!
Are you trying to stop us?
I will stop you! Now, now, now!
For this escort mission on the sea train,
I'm here to deal with attacks
like this just in case they happen!
If you want to let the criminal free,
then beat my Ramen Kenpo!
The rear two cars were detached?
What on earth are you all doing?
We're very sorry.
The fact of the matter is that even
Captain T-Bone, one of our powerhouses,
was in one of the detached cars.
So, tell me the current situation in the train.
Yes, ma'am! There are five cars
remaining besides the engine room car!
However, all the soldiers in
car #5 have been taken out.
So that leaves only Mr. Wanze in car #4,
Mr. Nero in car #3,
Nico Robin in car #1,
and everyone here in car #2!
It seems like our enemy isn't stupid.
However, if there is a problem here for us,
it's only that Franky is walking around free.
Our mission only requires us to bring
Franky and Nico Robin to Enies Lobby.
Other than that, no matter
how the other enemies die,
or no matter what happens to who on our side,
it won't interfere with our mission.
So, did you see our enemies?
Yes, ma'am! First, there were
the two that were in custody,
although one of them
was wearing a weird mask.
Also, a blond guy dressed in a suit,
who we've never seen before.
So, a total of three!
Hmm, just like the long-nosed man,
that man is probably one of the Straw Hats.
Naturally, his purpose is to recover Nico Robin.
Franky is helping them out.
That's probably about it.
Lucci, shall I go stand watch over Nico Robin?
That's not necessary.
Think only about recapturing Franky.
It's definitely not possible for them...
...to get Nico Robin back.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Showdown Between Cooks!
Sanji vs. Ramen Kenpo"
"Car #4"
At any rate, leave this guy to me.
You guys go to the next car.
Don't forget that this is
Operation Rescue Robin-chan.
"Flour"
That's impossible!
I... won't... let... you... pass... through!
I'll knead alloy flour and...!
Is he gonna bring out ramen noodles again?!
Ramen...
...Beam...!
They can prick you!
Yikes!
Cut it out!
Oof!
Tsk!
Let's go around via the roof!
Yeah!
W-Well then, Sanji-kun! I wish you good luck.
Now, now, now!
They got away so easily!
But that's no use...
...because Nero's waiting
for them in the next car.
Although he's a newbie, he's a member
of CP9, a group of assassins for justice!
They'll die! Nero loves to kill!
Now, now, now, now!
Flanchet...
...Shoot!
Oof.
I was born on the island of snipers
"Sniper Warrior
Sogeking"
I never miss my mark
Hmm...
If I at least knew which car Robin is in,
Lulu lala lu
I could just go on the roof
and infiltrate at once.
Whether it's a mouse's eyeball, lock on!!
What're you mumbling about?!
Hurry up and go, you damn Squidy-king!
Or even your heart, lock on!!
Who're you calling "Squidy"?!
The man who hails from the island of snipers
Hmm... Squidy...?
Hurry up, you damn idiot!
Lululu, lulu lala
Hey, bikini guy.
Now... run away!
Huh?
I've got a brilliant idea.
Listen carefully.
Tsk...
This'll take forever if you
keep dodging my attacks.
How many times do I need
to tell you I'm in a hurry?
Well then, here comes my attack!
Ramen Kenpo... Noodle Slicer!
Fire...
...Skate!
Ow, ow, ow...!
I got kicked about ten times
the moment he dodged my attack!
Actually, twelve times.
Is it possible... that you're super strong?
It's probably just that your
bark is worse than your bite.
Hey, hey! Not even my
old man has said that to me!
Stop saying that! How rude of you! I'm Wanze!
Even considering that your rare
swirling eyebrows made me dizzy,
you're actually pretty good!
You're one to talk about a rare face!
"Flour"
Okay, then! I'll show you
right away why I was chosen
to be in the team to escort the criminals!
Ramen Kenpo! Secret technique!
I'll finish the noodles by beating
them over and over again!
Wha...? What the hell is this?
This is an edible, dream combat uniform!
Ra-men's Formal Suit!
Now, now, now!
The secret of Ramen Kenpo
is controlling noodles at will!
You bastard...
How dare you play with food all this time?!
Speed, power, and special abilities...
I'm at a different level now in all those areas!
I'll exhibit incomparable strength!
Enough jabbering. Bring it on already.
I'll make you eat all
those noodles, so be prepared.
So...
...who are you?
The one waiting on car #3 is a
newbie in CP9, a Four Powers Master,
Nero the sea weasel. Hiss!
At any rate, I guess you're
one opponent I can't kill...
...since you're one of our important criminals.
Hey, buddy! Why are you out on the roof?
If you had just waited, I would've come to you.
Well, you can't tell that for sure, right?
You might've cheated and
skipped this car, right? Hiss!
How cautious you are!
But being on guard is important, huh?
By the way, what's that thing behind you?
Huh?
That was dirty!
Dirty is right! In my town,
I'm the boss of a gang of rogues.
Hm? Where's Luffy?
Hm...? Beats me.
"Beats me"?! What if he
happened to fall into the water?!
Oof! It's slippery!
Can't be. He was right here up
until just now. Right, Chopper?
What? Yeah.
That's no answer! I'm worried because
the person who was here isn't here now!
Maybe he's stuck in the chimney of Rocketman?
He's not me-- Hey, Chopper! You little...!
Just wait, Robin...! And Usopp.
Welcome to the Ramen Kenpo world!
You call this "powered-up"?
Now, now, now! Take this!
Ramen Kenpo! Pork Bone Spank!
That's a useless punch
that you just made bigger.
Now, now, now! Another one!
I-It's stuck!
Oof!
Now, now!
Now, now, now! You dummy!
Are you taken aback by my Ramen Kenpo?!
You look unsightly with your leg
and arm buried in ramen noodles!
How dare you beat the crap
out of me like that earlier?!
--Ah!
--Hm?
What're you getting dizzy for, you jerk?!
You just tried to make me dizzy using
your eyebrows again, didn't you?!
I'm not gonna let you get away with it!
Now, now, now!
Dammit! I can't pull out my leg or my arm!
I can't fight back like this!
Noodle Soul Press!
I'm just getting started!
Another helping! And another!
And another! And another!
And another!
Take that, and that, and that,
and that, and that, and that, and that!
They finally came off.
Now, now, now! Aren't you
underestimating me, you fool?
This is the mad, mad Ramen Kenpo!
To think that I get buried if I attack...
I guess I can't touch those ramen noodles.
Now, I'll keep it coming!
Ramen and Pot Sticker Combo! Clapping!
Then, there's only one area that I can attack.
Escalope!
Ramen Beam!
Now, now, now!
I've got no blind spot!
From what I've been seeing,
your means of fighting is kicking, isn't it?
Kicking is the only means you have, isn't it?
Now, now, now! It's no use! It's no use!
No matter what you do, you'll only
end up being buried in my suit!
Here goes! Try dodging this!
Ramen Kenpo!
Multi-Noodle Spank!
1.4 mm pasta, fedelini...
Huh?!
Sleight of hand?
Ah! My noodle fists are now in pieces!
Hands and kitchen knives are sacred to cooks.
So it's my policy not to use them in a battle.
But if this is a kitchen...
...and my enemy is foodstuff,
then it's a different story.
You're more troublesome than I thought.
Thousand Noodle Whip!
Trying to look cool? How saucy!
An amateur like you who can't even
cook shouldn't hold kitchen knives!
They're different from the
knives that delinquents use!
Pardon me for being saucy.
This isn't quite a token of my apology...
...but I'll show you...
...the exceptional way that a first-class
cook handles kitchen knives!
Hiss!
Shave!
Strong... Hammer!
Paper Art.
Tempest Kick!
Hiss!
Fresh Fire!
Shave!
Wha...?! What's with him?!
He jumped towards the sea on his own!
Moon Walk!
Why did he bounce back
in the air?! I don't get it!
Why can't I cut him with Tempest Kick?
There's something weird about his body!
What...
...the hell...
...are you?!
Octopu-shoes... Octopu-shoes...
Long-nose!
Why are you here?!
I was--
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
What the hell's up with your body?
Well, I guess I'm probably the only
guy who can chill cola in his belly.
I knew it! You aren't human!
But I found your weak point!
Hey, hey, buddy. Don't be silly!
I'm invincible!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Rooftop Duel! Franky vs. Nero"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!