Long-nose!
Here goes! Try dodging this!
Ramen Kenpo!
Multi-Noodle Spank!
Hands and kitchen knives
are sacred to cooks.
So it's my policy
not to use them in a battle.
But if this is a kitchen...
...and my enemy is foodstuff,
then it's a different story.
I'll show you...
...the exceptional way
that a first-class cook
handles kitchen knives!
What...
...the hell...
...are you?!
What's the matter, Ramen Kenpo guy?
You don't seem to be
as lively as you were earlier.
Dammit! You're a criminal!
Don't talk saucy!
My noodle fists are gone!
Am I...
an onion or something?!
It's pointless to keep fighting.
Accept your loss and let me pass.
Accept my loss? Why would I?!
I'm not losing!
I'm Wanze, the ace of CP7!
Sorry, but I understand the
importance of this mission.
Nico Robin, one of your crewmates,
is a woman who the Government
has been pursuing for many years.
How could I hand her over
so easily, you fool?!
Ramen Kenpo!
Noodle Stake Knocker!
First, cut off the stem and the root
without hurting the flesh.
If you cut the fiber in one shot,
the cut surface looks nice
and it retains its gloss.
Stop it! Stay back!
Ramen Beam!
Epluchage!
Although he's just a third-class cook
who plays with his food...
...I'll at least give him credit for taking
good care of his kitchen knives.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together,
let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail--
let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Rooftop Duel! Franky vs. Nero"
It's a star shield.
What's up with his body?
He's no longer human.
More flame?!
Master Nails!
Moon Walk!
He jumped again!
This is getting nowhere!
I guess it can't be helped
if my Four Powers don't work.
Sorry, I'll use some props,
since I haven't mastered
Finger Pistol yet!
All right!
I'm going to the next car while I can!
Hey, hold it, you bastard!
You can't be too careful with this guy!
He fell for it.
Beans Left!
Sorry...
I knew...
...you'd do something like that!
Owww!
It worked!
You son of a bitch...
Ouch Finger!
Shave!
Dammit...
He noticed it...
Tempest Kick!
It grazed me!
He sure moves around a lot!
So your weak point...
...is your back, huh?
I've already figured out
your petty nature, too.
Now it's just a matter of time
before I win, isn't it?
Don't get so carried away!
I have no weak point if I do this.
Franky...
...Invincible! Tada!
"Invincible"
Now, do you give up, you weasel jerk?!
I don't know what to say to him...
What's going on?
Why are you here?!
How'd you get on board?!
I can't answer if you bombard me
with questions like that.
Well, calm down a little.
Ah, shall I pour you
some coffee or something?
Stop fooling around!
What on earth...?
How do you do?
I'm Sogeking,
the king of snipers.
To make a long story short,
I've come to rescue you.
Long-nose...
It's not just me.
Sanji-kun and a thug named Franky
are currently engaged
in battle on this train.
During their fights, I found
a chance to come here.
Furthermore, Luffy-kun and the others
are also on this railway following
this train using the other sea train...
He's bringing a big group.
On my way here earlier,
I peeked inside
of the train through the windows.
Frankly, those four people in the
car behind this one are dangerous.
It'd be best if I could rescue you
before Sanji-kun confronts them.
Now, let's run...
together!
What's the matter?
There's no need to worry.
I'm all prepared.
These Octopu-shoes are for you.
If you put them on your hands and feet,
you can get out through the window and
stick to the outer panels of the sea train.
Now, put them on before they notice.
Wait.
"Wait"?
How could this be happening?
I thought I clearly
told you all goodbye.
I'll never return to the Straw Hats!
They know why you are
so insistent about that.
I heard that Ice pops at the
shipbuilding yard clarified everything.
So he survived?
No... Even so, I won't return...
to you guys...
Enough with that!
You still don't get it?!
They're not so weak that
you need to worry about them!
Before you took such a stupid deal,
they really wanted you
to talk to them first!
You really think
they'd be happy to be alive
knowing that it was because
their friend had to sacrifice herself?!
Now that they know why you left them,
they'll follow you
to the depths of hell
and take out your enemies!
You
still don't get what
kind of man Luffy is!
It's you guys who don't get it!
I don't have the slightest
desire to be rescued!
Don't just do as you please!
What'd you say, you...
What are you making a
racket for, Nico Robin?
What's the matter?
Now that Enies Lobby
is getting closer,
is it hard for even you to remain calm?
Even if you cry about your destiny now,
it's not like your life
will be saved or anything.
It's nothing.
What was that?
It looks suspicious!
In addition, she seems
different than before.
Is it just my imagination?
It's nothing...
so leave me alone.
What the hell?
Why is this
woman goofing around?
A rabbit?
Hey! Cut it out!
Enough with the jokes!
Be serious!
Get up!
Watch your mouth, you weasel jerk.
I'm not joking.
In any case, how unlucky...
Really, how unlucky... you are.
You made me angry...
and I happen to be super this week.
Say, buddy...
Do you know a monster
called the centaur?
The one that's human from the
waist up and horse below, right?
What about it?
Con...vert!
"Convert"
"Pervert"
Don't tell me he's gonna...
Franky...
...Centaur!
Wrong way!
Your body should be in front!
Wait to complain
until you see its attacking power.
Aren't we catching up
with Bashing Tom yet?!
That's "Puffing"!
Hey, Luffy! Stay inside!
You just changed,
but you're soaking wet again!
That's okay!
I like this place!
Geez...
Gum-Gum...
Three-Hundred Pound...
...Cannon! Boom!
Splash!
Ahh! This is it! Laguna!
This is no time for playing!
We're bored.
Polish your weapons or
something, you idiots!
Well, um...
I'll talk to those guys later, so...
Hm?
Hey, guys!
I see a train ahead of us!
It's gotta be Puffing Tom, right?!
Isn't it too early?
Dammit!
What's gonna happen to us?
There's no engine on this car.
We have no choice
but to wait to be rescued.
Whoa! We're rocking!
But will someone really come
to rescue us in this storm?
They have to. Or we're screwed.
Hey, guys.
There's something
coming from behind!
Really?!
It must be a rescue ship!
Well... it looks like...
it's coming on the railway.
Can't be...
There's only
one sea train in the world.
Besides, it was impossible to leave
Water Seven after the last departure.
Then...
...what's coming?
Hey, that's a sea train,
but it's just cars
without the engine room!
It's sitting motionless on the railway!
What?!
What's going on?!
Does this mean that they got detached?
Ah! Sanji and Usopp may be on them!
Big Bro Franky, too!
This isn't good!
If we keep going like this,
we'll collide with them!
Granny! Where's the brake?!
I said it doesn't work, didn't I?
Do something.
We're gonna crash!
Luffy! What're you gonna do?
I'll go check inside!
Gum-Gum... Rocket!
Something is flying towards...
What happened?!
Ow, ow, ow...
All right! I got in!
Wh-Who are you?!
Hello! Sanji!
Are you in here?!
Usopp...
Hello! Sanji!
Hello!
I wonder if they're over there.
This guy... Could it be...!
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
Hello!
Are you here, Sanji?!
Sanji!
Hey, shut up!
Straw Hat!
There's no escape for you!
Where's Sanji?
Wh-Who's that?
Sanji! He's my friend!
We don't know a guy like that!
I see...
Then, see ya.
Shoot him!
Straw Hat is coming out!
He's saying that they're not
in there... while being shot!
Then, everyone in there is
Government personnel, huh?
So what're you gonna do if so?
Unless we move those
cars out of our way,
we'll take a lot of damage, too!
That's a sea train, after all!
We're gonna be knocked off!
Well, if things go wrong, it could
possibly cause a huge explosion!
Stop!
It's the Franky Family's
turn to work now.
We'll demolish them
right before we collide!
All right! We'll give
you guys a hand, too!
Guys! It's time to work!
Yeah!
Hey! Zoro!
Hey, Roronoa.
He's calling your name.
Cut them.
They're in our way.
Sure.
"Sure"?!
We're gonna collide!
Stop!
The ego of the entropic world...
...can be slashed into pieces.
Two-Sword Style Sword Draw...
...Rashomon!
What?!
Whaaat?!
--Whaaat?!
Hey, you guys!
If you were going to
do something like that,
you could've at least told us.
You heard me saying,
"Cut them," right?!
Who would think he could?!
We would've collided
if we didn't cut them, right?!
Well, that's true,
but we needed
to be prepared, you know!
Even a monster like him
isn't the leader of the group?
He's something else.
Anyway, you're amazing!
In any case, to think that
there was another sea train...
With that speed, they might catch up.
If, by any chance,
the criminals
under escort are taken away...
That's not going to happen!
He is between them and
the preceding sea train!
That's right!
As long as
we have him in the Navy,
our justice will never sway!
All right! Here goes!
Two-Sword Style Sword Draw...
...Rashomon!
Hey! You're supposed to be the train!
Why me?! You do it!
No, you do it!
No! I don't wanna be cut in half!
Get cut in half!
No!
Hey, guys!
Huh?!
We're not done yet.
What the hell is that?!
It's a Sea King!
A huge monster like this was...
Sashimi!
It's been split in half!
Grilled fish!
Something that huge was...
It was so huge that it could've
swallowed Rocketman in one gulp!
Further ahead on this railway...
...lies the one who
cut that thing up...!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross
the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring
than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end,
we can all surely smile
Who the hell is that?!
Ahh! That's the Ship-Slasher!
Ship-Slasher?
Ship-Slasher T-Bone,
a Captain at Navy Headquarters!
He's a crazy guy
who cuts ships like steaks!
Interesting.
Hey! I'll tell you only once!
Get out of our way!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Clash! Demon-Slasher Zoro
vs. Ship-Slasher T-Bone"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!