There's a dead end ahead!
He'll crash into it and die!
Gomorrah! Stop! Don't run randomly!
Stop!
Dead end? Do you see one?
Nope... I don't see anything of the sort.
This report is for all units!
The King Bull with the pirates on it broke
through the encirclement in Block D!
They've just reached the courthouse plaza!
I repeat! The pirates...!
To all units on Enies Lobby!
All soldiers! Head to the
courthouse plaza immediately!
The pirates have reached the courthouse plaza!
Huh?
Also, the giant gatekeepers
at the main island front gate,
Oimo and Kashii, went over to the pirates' side!
They're currently around the center of the
main island running towards the courthouse!
Get outta our way!
The casualties of our guards are...
...over 2,000!
And the captain, Straw Hat Luffy,
who beat over 1,000 all by himself,
suddenly disappeared, so we're
searching for him right now!
This is probably unprecedented--
the worst situation we've had
in the history of Enies Lobby!
What's going on?
What the hell is happening
on this island right now?!
You jerk!
He jumped!
Finger Pistol!
Shave!
Iron Body! Smash!
Gum-Gum... Bullet!
Iron Body!
Tempest Kick!
Not like this.
Hm?
I'm no good like this.
When Aokiji defeated me, I thought...
"If I am to encounter more
strong guys like him in the future,
I won't be able to protect my friends...
unless I become stronger."
I have friends I want by my side
even if they're not strong.
So if I don't get stronger
than anyone, I'll lose all of them.
Then what're you gonna do?
I came up with a way to
fight with all my might...
...so that I won't lose anyone...
So that no one will go far away.
What's he doing?
What's happening inside his body?!
You'll now... no longer be
able to keep up with me.
What?
All my techniques will evolve one step further.
Second... Gear!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Everything Is to Protect My Friends!
Second Gear Activated!"
Baskerville! Chief Justice
Baskerville! Come in! It's me!
Whoa! Chief Spandam!
"Courthouse"
This is Left Baskerville on the left!
This is Right Baskerville on the right.
And in the center, I am "All Alone
Traveling the Central Main Line"!
--Who the heck is that?!
--Give me a status report!
I heard that the pirates have already
made it to the courthouse plaza!
Status?
Hmm... Status...
As for the status...
More than the plaza,
the inside of the courthouse is...
...in the most terrible state!
What?!
Ch-Chief Justice! I have a report!
The courthouse's huge stone
doors were finally cut through
and the pirates have invaded!
I can see that already, you idiot!
I thought we'd see more enemies in here.
Looks like we can move straight ahead,
but what the heck is that?
What?! His head...!
He's like that guard dog from hell
I heard about in some story!
Berberus?!
You mean Cerberus!
Men! Order!
This is a sacred chamber of law!
We'll now cast judgment
on your inevitable fate!
Ribbit!
All right, guys, head to the
rooftop where Straw Hat is!
A group of us along with Yokozuna
will stop pursuers at the doors.
We've got your back, so just charge ahead!
Got it.
--Hey, look at that.
Looks like the trial has started.
--Their crime is as follows!
--First, the act of stepping into Enies Lobby,
--Ignore it. It's just a bother!
Which way do we go?!
--which belongs to the World Government, is...
--Straight ahead! There are stairs on both sides!
We'll take them to the upper floors!
All right!
Ahh! How rude! They ignored our sacred trial!
That's unforgivable! How dare
they mock the judicial island?!
Damn you! Die!
What's going on? His swords
look like they're bending!
Enbima Yonezu...
...Oni Giri!
Is he the one who cut open the door?
Okay, let's go. The path is now open!
Yep!
So why is a guy who's that
strong not their captain?
Wait! Wait! Wait! Outta my way!
Reindeer! Moron swordsman!
Suit guy...
This is a dangerous enemy camp!
I'll clear the path for Nami-san
to move forward! Outta my way!
--Whoa!
--Hey, watch it!
What?! Why is he starting a fight?!
You jerk! Are you picking a fight?!
Shut up! Don't you guys
get in Nami-san's royal way!
Nami-san, this way! Follow only me!
Hey, we came to rescue Robin, right?
Ah! That's right, Robin-chan is
waiting for me to rescue her!
Could she be crying right
now out of loneliness?!
Seriously...
Hm?
Ahhh!
We take our eyes off Zoro
for a second, and now he's...!
What?!
Wait, Zoro! That's the wrong way!
I said the stairs! Just what made
you think you should go that way?!
What're you?! A fantasista?!
Shut up! It was because
you didn't explain it well!
There's no way it was my fault!
Zoro, I'll try making some medicine...
...that works on hopelessness.
Hopelessness...? Hey!
--Chopper.
--Hm?
--Robin-chan! I'm coming now!
--Make sure it works on that guy, too.
Er... Yeah, okay, got it.
I wonder if Bro will be rescued safely.
They're the type that gets it
together when the going gets tough...
...probably... I'm sure... yeah...
This is a big crime.
This is a huge crime.
Then, we'll pick the one in the middle...
--Death penalty!
--Agreed!
Are you okay, Zoro?! This way, okay?
I know!
I'm the Chief Justice. Don't ignore me!
Chopper. Nami. Go on ahead.
I'll follow you after I take care of this guy.
You think you can defeat me?
What a cocky pirate!
I'll show you how fearful I am!
Pull!
S-Stop it!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho...!
S-Stop...
We'll take you on, Cerberus!
Franky Family!
How dare you...?!
Let's go!
Ah... yeah.
Gear? Your techniques will evolve?
Are you trying to imitate a
steam engine or something
by blowing off steam from your body?
What kind of bluff is that?
I...
I'm glad that I met you guys here.
Hm?!
Thanks to that, I won't have to lose my friends.
I'm glad that I met you guys here.
What're you saying? I don't get it.
Isn't it because you met us that
you're about to lose your friend?
You're starting to say weird stuff now.
Have you become confused or something?
Gum-Gum...
Are you trying to aim and attack?
It'll only give me a chance to dodge.
Hmph! Why don't you aim
well and hit me if you can?
--Shave!
--...Jet Pistol!
Rifle!
I can't see him at all!
Stamp!
And Spear!
Missile!
Can't be...!
No, there's no mistake about it.
I'm glad that I met you guys here.
That man has a good command
of Shave, one of the Six Powers!
Air Door!
He disappeared...
This is impossible!
To think that a mere pirate has
a good command of Shave...?!
No... Besides the fact that he used Shave,
he strengthened his body enough
to be able to use Shave easily.
Does this mean that he's had that
much potential from the start?
What a bad joke.
But there's no way someone could
be faster than a Six Powers master!
A Six Powers master can't lose!
If I turn his body into a door and
contain his movements, it'll be easy.
I'll go all-in and end this battle in an instant!
Door-Door!
When you guys moved as
if you were disappearing,
I saw you moving by kicking the
ground over ten times in a moment.
I got the hang of it, too.
I'm glad I came to know a technique
for moving like that exists.
I'm glad that I met you guys here.
Thanks to that, I can continue
to protect my friends.
Gum-Gum...
I'll take it... with the strongest Iron Body!
Iron Body! Strength!
...Jet Bazooka!
Your body sure is made tough, huh?
Well then, I'll show you more
interesting stuff. Just watch!
Third...
I'm so exhausted.
As I thought, my body can't keep up yet.
Well, I don't care about my body right now.
I got set back quite a bit.
"Gates of Justice" "Tower of Law"
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
Dammit! What's going on?!
Cannons! Fire the cannons!
They're gonna stomp on us!
That's useless! I'm not gonna stop,
you shorty guards!
Me, neither! You can't stop me!
Really, I can't believe it!
To think that the troublesome
gatekeepers are now on our side!
It's thanks to the bond between warriors!
Now, my brothers!
The courthouse is very close now!
Move forward!
"Main Island Front Gate"
"Courthouse" "Tower of Law"
What're you doing?! Hurry up and go in!
The pirates are inside
the courthouse, aren't they?!
Yeah, but a frog is stationed at
the main door and we can't go in!
A frog?!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...!
Don't let even a single person inside!
Stand firm, Yokozuna!
If this defense line gets broken,
thousands of guards will surge in here!
Bear it until the drawbridge comes down!
Ribbit!
"Courthouse Right Tower"
Even just one of us would do!
Get to the top floor!
We have to pull the lever there to bring
down the drawbridge, no matter what!
Yeah!
"Courthouse Left Tower"
Big Sis Mozu!
Don't worry about me! Just go!
Bring down the bridge
and let the Straw Hats go over
to the Tower of Law without fail!
Stop them! Whatever you do,
don't let them get through!
Get out of our way!
Why did the swordsman and the
others from earlier head upstairs?!
I don't owe you any answer!
What?!
Forget that! You'd better hope
that Big Bro Franky is okay!
"Upper Floors of the Courtroom"
After them! Bring down the pirates!
Those damn guards! I didn't realize
that there were still a bunch inside!
There they are! Attack them!
Outta our way!
Hey! Don't throw them my way, Chopper!
Guilty! Guilty! Guilty! Guilty! Guilty...
What the hell are you?
Actually, where the hell am I?!
"Tower of Law"
We're taking Franky and Nico Robin
to the Gates of Justice already?
That's right! Just do as I said!
But the escort ship departing from
the Gates of Justice isn't ready!
That's fine! We can wait on the other
side of the gates as long as we need!
In any case, we first have to
take away the pirates' goal!
After all, once we go
through the Gates of Justice,
they can no longer do anything at all!
Also, gather all the members of CP9!
Yes, sir!
Now... stand up, you two!
I'll take you to hell immediately.
After that, we can take our time
and drive the pirates into a corner.
Giants! Giants!
The giants are on our side!
--Giants! Giants! The giants are on our side!
--Every single thing those guys do is interesting.
Those who have common sense
wouldn't meddle with this island.
Just wait and see, Chimney.
Whether they end up surviving this or dying,
the entire world will be shocked
to learn of this incident...
Something that no one has been able
to do in the past several hundred years.
After this battle,
the name of that straw hat kid will
be known throughout the whole world!
Robin!
He's here!
Luffy...
I've come to get you!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
Why did you come to rescue me?!
Go back! I don't wanna see your faces again!
What the heck are you talking about?
Like I said, I wanna die!
Listen, Robin. We've already come this far.
So, we're gonna rescue you anyway.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Give Us Your Answer, Robin!
The Straw Hats' Outcry!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!