Robin!
You can go ahead and say
you wanna die or whatever,
but say those things... by our side!
Just leave the rest to us!
They've come all this way
after crossing Aqua Laguna.
When you think about it, it's incredible.
Seems like they've at least got good luck.
This time, we have permission to kill them.
It's easy when we don't have to
worry about going easy on them.
Drawbridge?
Yeah. The Franky Family is
currently fighting to bring it down.
Once it comes down, we can go
over to the other side at once.
Geez... When it's right in front of us...
You idiot...
Seriously, just how terrible is
the burden this woman is bearing?
Hey, CP9! Listen!
I give you permission to kill them,
but take them on here at the Tower of Law!
The most important things of
all are my life and promotion.
If I let them do as they want,
who'll protect me when something happens?!
You stupid pirates!
Get it in your heads that putting on
a brave front doesn't change anything!
You're up against the power
of the assassin group CP9
and the weight of the Gates of Justice
that can't be opened by human strength.
And above all things, right now...
...I have the authority to exercise Buster Call
by using this golden transponder snail!
Buster Call...!
That's right.
It's the power that wiped out your hometown
exactly twenty years ago, Nico Robin.
I remember that the following year, the name
"Ohara" had been wiped off of the map.
Robin's hometown?
That damn masked jerk!
There's no place for me to go or go back to.
Don't!
Not that!
I like that reaction. It gives me a chill.
What? Does it mean that you
want me to press this button
to activate Buster Call? Hm? Does it?
Do you really understand what'll
happen when you press it?
I do. It'll eliminate the possibility of
the pirates escaping from this island!
Just with this single button.
It's that simple.
It won't be that simple!
Are you remembering something?
If you like, shall I try pressing it?
Right here, right now?
What're you doing?! Stop it!
You sure talk cocky, don't you?
You said that "Ohara" had
been wiped off the map.
Can you see humans on a map?!
Because you guys see the world that way...
...you can do such a cruel thing!
Buster Calls are a heartless power that
even makes you lose sight of your goal.
You mustn't use it. Not that.
Never...! Not that!
"20 years ago - 'West Blue'
Ohara"
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Robin's Past! The Girl
Who Was Called a Devil!"
Hey, Robin's there!
Get her!
Ow!
All right!
Hey, monster!
You're creepy!
Monster! Monster! Monster! Monster!
Ahh! The monster hit me!
She's creepy!
We'll get you for this!
Hey, you!
My children came home crying,
saying that you hit them for no reason.
Stay away from my children.
Pfft!
Why don't you say something?!
Geez... You really are a creepy child.
Hey, wait!
I'm not done with you yet!
Mommy, Mommy, what're we
having for dinner tonight?
What'd you like to eat?
Um... Um...
Rice omelet!
You sure like rice omelets, don't you?
--Yep!
--We have to buy lots of eggs, then.
All right!
I'm back. I'm sorry I'm late.
Aunt Roji?
"To Robin. Today is..."
...our daughter's birthday.
So we decided that the three of us
would go out for dinner as a family.
There's some bread,
so just have that for dinner.
Don't use too much jam.
After dinner, before we get home,
do the dishes, clean the house,
and take the laundry in, then go upstairs early.
Mommy, Mommy, what're we
having for dinner tonight?
What'd you like to eat?
Um... Um...
Rice omelet!
You sure like rice omelets, don't you?
--Yep!
--We have to buy lots of eggs, then.
All right!
Oh! There she is! Robin's here!
Looks like she came to return a book.
Everyone, to your positions.
Good evening, Professor Clover!
I came to return the book I borrowed.
One, two...!
Congratulations, Robin!
--You're amazing, Robin!
--Just as we'd expect from a genius!
We've got a cake for you!
Robin, the exam for the doctoral
degree you took the other day...
You quite amazingly got 100% on it!
Hence, from today on,
we acknowledge you as an archaeologist.
Now you're one of us and
we'll do research together.
Here, this proves that you're
a scholar. Take this, Robin.
I'm happy for you, Robin.
Congratulations!
Listen, Robin. You must understand well
what it means to be an archaeologist.
Yes, Professor Clover!
Knowledge comes from the past.
This Tree of Knowledge is 5,000 years old.
A massive amount of literature
has been brought to this tree
from all over the world over
a very, very long period of time.
It's an irreplaceable treasure for all humanity.
This is the biggest and oldest library in
the world whose pride is its knowledge.
And superior archaeologists
from all over the world
gathered under this Tree of Knowledge.
When using these books,
there's no historical mystery
that we can't solve.
Got that, Robin?
Yes!
I'd like to see you contribute to the
world by researching various cultures.
Professor! I'd like to solve
the mystery of "Blank History"!
Wha... No! You shouldn't! I forbid
you to do it, just as I always have.
What? Why? If we research the Poneglyphs,
we'll know what happened during
the "Blank Century," right?
Why do you know that much?
Did you peek into the
basement using your powers?!
But...
You should know that trying to decipher
the Poneglyphs is a criminal act!
What...?
But... you guys have been
researching the Poneglyphs
in the basement late at night!
Robin! How come you know that?!
Explain yourself! Are you saying that
you've been spying on that, too?
Answer me, Robin!
That's because...
...you wouldn't let me in the room
even if I openly came and asked!
I thought... you'd let me be part of your
research if I became an archaeologist.
So I studied very hard!
Robin...
It's true that you've acquired enough
knowledge to be called a scholar.
But you're still a child.
If they find out what we're doing,
our heads will roll.
We're doing it fully aware of the risk.
Ever since it became law 800 years ago,
there actually have been numerous
scholars who lost their lives.
This is a good opportunity,
so let me tell you this.
We of Ohara are the only ones in history
who managed to decipher the ancient texts.
We cannot go back.
Swear to the Tree of Knowledge!
If you try to approach the basement again,
I'll forbid you from entering the
research lab and the library! Got that?
Robin!
She's following in her
mother's footsteps in every way.
She still doesn't know about
the incident from the other day.
Robin's mother, Olvia, has been captured.
You can tell what fate awaits her.
"The following day"
Grrr!
W... Wa...
Worms?
That hit the spot!
I somehow survived...
I wonder if she's okay, too.
I'm saved for now. Thank you.
Is there a town or something on this land?
Yeah.
I see.
If I was going to drift to somewhere,
I would've liked an uninhabited island.
You can stay there if you want,
but nothing's gonna happen.
My leg got injured, so I'll stay put here.
I'm planning to make a raft or
something and leave here eventually.
This your first time seeing a giant?
Yep.
I'm telling you, don't lump me
in with those guys from Elbaf.
There are peaceful giant tribes, too.
I see...
I know it's a long shot, but I'll ask you anyway.
When you get home, I don't want
you to tell anyone about me.
Okay.
That was too easy. She'll definitely tell.
I won't tell.
That's a lie! There's no way
that a child can keep a secret.
I won't tell because I'm not interested in you.
"Dereshi"?
What does that mean?
What does it mean? I'm just laughing.
You're laughing?
You're a funny girl.
That's a weird way of laughing.
I've always been told that
I'm not good at laughing.
You're cute when you laugh.
--What?
--You should laugh more.
My name is Saul. Jaguar D. Saul.
"D"?
Yeah. I don't know why, but everyone
in my family has it in their names.
What's your name?
Robin.
I see. To tell you the truth, Robin,
I'm being pursued right now.
So if people find me, I'll be in trouble.
I said I wouldn't tell!
"Three days after the giant drifted ashore"
This is yummy!
Here's another one.
I appreciate the thought,
but you go ahead and eat it.
I'm not hungry, since I caught some
fish and ate them during the night.
Okay.
Well, it'll be completed soon.
I'll keep working on building a raft.
In any case, you sure have lots
of time on your hands, huh?
You've been with me all day
long for the past several days.
Your friends and parents will get suspicious.
I don't have parents.
Well, I do have a mother,
but she set sail for work when
I was small and hasn't come back.
So I don't even remember her face.
I like those archaeologists, but they
don't let me be part of the research,
so I'm being left out.
Kids in town say that I'm creepy,
so I won't play with them.
Oh, so you're a Devil Fruit power holder, huh?
You aren't scared?
I used to travel in the Grand Line,
so I saw many dreadful
Devil Fruit power holders.
I see... I envy you.
That looks convenient!
You really do laugh in a weird way.
Weird or not...
...you know...
...if you laugh, it'll make you happy.
Why?
"Why?" When you're having fun, you laugh.
Which means if you laugh, it'll become fun.
Although you're only a child,
you seem to be having a hard time.
So laugh. When you're
having a hard time, just laugh.
It seems stupid to laugh
when you're having a hard time.
That's not true.
Now, you try, too.
Dereshi.
That's right! Do it like this!
That's good! That's good!
This is Navy Headquarters.
Chief Spandine, please come in.
They want to talk to you, Chief.
Just ignore it. I'm sure they
just want a status report.
We'll contact them when we see the shore.
I don't care whether it's Ohara or Opera--
why do I have to come all
the way to the West Blue?
Seriously...
What a worthless mission...
"The following day, four days
after the giant drifted ashore"
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
So you don't even remember your mom's face?
No, but I wanna see her.
Is your mom also an archaeologist?
Yep. She's traveling in search of
the history no one knows about.
Wh-What's your mom's name?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Fated Mother and Daughter!
The Mother's Name Is Olvia!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!