Stop it! Saul!
Be prepared!
If you make an enemy of me,
I'll make you pay for it!
What's going on?!
It's Vice Admiral Saul!
Vice Admiral Saul, who deserted
with Olvia, is attacking us!
Why is he here?!
W-We don't know!
This is the end of this island!
Everything will be burned down!
Don't give up! Preserve the books!
We have to pass down the history!
Drop them to the lake through the windows!
It'll be better than them being
burned up and gone! Hurry up!
Now!
Saul! Stop it now! You'll die!
Throw the books out of the library!
Save as many books as we can!
Preserve as many sentences as we can!
So that our predecessors' words from
the past several thousand years...
...will reach the future!
Robin! What're you doing?!
Run to the evacuation ship while you can!
You can no longer survive
if you remain on this island!
Mom!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Say You Want to Live! We Are Your Friends!!"
Shoot Saul!
Robin! Hurry up and run!
What was your mom's wish?!
Live, Robin!
We're sailing the evacuation ship out!
Wait! Someone's coming!
That's...!
Ah! Isn't that the monster?!
Yeah, it is!
Go away, monster!
Hey! Don't be ridiculous!
Well... Wait!
Isn't she the daughter of Olvia,
a criminal, who was in the paper before?
That's right! If we let her on the ship,
it might cause us trouble!
Don't be ridiculous! She's only a child!
Hurry up and get her on the ship!
Evacuation ship! Don't let
that brat come on board!
What?
Although she's a child, she's an archaeologist.
She's a target of our attack!
Chief Spandine! I-Is that true?!
See? If we let her come on board,
we'll be in danger!
Robin!
That must be CP9! How absurd!
Chief! Vice Admiral Saul is coming this way!
Really?! I guess we didn't have to
ask Olvia about his whereabouts.
Fire! Fire! Fire the cannons at him!
Ice Block!
Partisan!
Saul!
Kuzan-san!
Kuzan...!
Oh, my, my...
It doesn't look good
if a Buster Call is blocked by
a former marine, now does it?
Kuzan!
Can you take pride in this attack?
Pull back!
This isn't right! You should know it, too!
This is a warning!
They're wiping out Ohara
to make an example of it!
If it is for the future of the world,
it can't be helped.
In fact, these scholars are
violating the laws, right?
Justice changes its form
depending on the position you're in.
So I won't criticize your sense of justice.
But if you're in our way, I can't let you be.
Ah! The evacuation ship got blown up!
Wh-Why...?
It was cannon fire! From one of the battleships!
It was from Vice Admiral Sakazuki's ship!
That idiot...!
If we're gonna do it, we'll do it thoroughly.
If even a single scholar is hiding
on that ship by some chance,
the sacrifices made in this
operation will all be in vain.
We need to eradicate
even the possibility of evil.
Is this something "justice" would do?!
Can you still keep your head high?!
I don't intend to go as far as that idiot does!
We're gonna run, Robin!
He's abnormally strong!
Saul ran away!
He's taking a scholar with him!
Ice Time Capsule!
Saul! Are you okay?!
Robin, run away!
Run with all your might!
You'll die if you stay on the island!
Sail out on my raft!
What about you, Saul?
This is it for me. I got caught.
Go!
No! There's no one on the sea!
Listen carefully, Robin!
You're alone now, but you'll
meet friends someday for sure!
Friends?
Right. The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
No one is born into this world to be alone!
Run, Robin! Don't look back!
When you're having a hard time,
laugh like this, just like I taught you!
Watch out, Saul!
Ice Time.
Saul!
Go meet the friends
who're surely waiting for you
somewhere at sea, Robin!
Live together with them.
This is it!
This is also the history that humans chose.
How thoughtless humans are...
I'm sorry, Robin.
I couldn't even give you...
...any parting words as a mother.
The Tree of Knowledge... is coming down!
Absolute justice can
sometimes drive people mad.
I've decided to let you escape from this island.
What on earth will sprout
from the seed Saul protected?
Who you bear a grudge against is up to you,
but for now, just be happy you're alive.
Live as quietly as possible.
I drew lines on the sea with ice.
If you just go straight on that
small boat, you'll reach land.
And remember this.
I'm not your ally.
I'm your enemy. I'll be the first to
come after you if you cause trouble.
My mom is on the island!
No one will survive.
If that pain makes you want to die,
you're free to do that as well.
This is the best library in the world.
Do you like books?
Today is Robin's birthday!
Happy birthday, Robin!
Be proud, Robin! Ohara is honorable!
We cannot give up the future
you young ones will live in!
So laugh. When you're
having a hard time, just laugh.
It seems stupid to laugh
when you're having a hard time.
That's not true.
Go meet the friends
who're surely waiting for you
somewhere at sea, Robin!
Survivors?
There's no possibility of that.
--Hey!
--Hm?
Take a look at this lake.
Th-This is...
There are enough books
to fill the lake completely.
Was this by chance?!
Yeah, this is the brat!
There's no doubt about it!
Where'd you find her?! Did you capture her?
No, sir! Keeping in mind to
look out for "a suspicious girl,"
we found a girl on a passenger
ship that was leaving an island
far northeast of Ohara,
but we lost her right after that.
She's got the devil's luck.
I definitely saw a brat escaping
from burning Ohara on a small boat!
I wanted to go after her, but the helm
suddenly got stuck as if it was frozen!
I bet Mr. Saul must've let her
escape right before he died!
To think that she can decipher Poneglyphs...
Although she's still small, she's dangerous.
This operation will go down
the drain unless we capture her
as soon as possible--I don't care how!
79 million Berries?!
Such a high bounty for an eight-year-old child?!
They said that she's a
survivor of those Ohara devils
who planned the world's annihilation.
Ohara?
I don't know how, but they said
that she sank six Navy battleships.
So that's why her bounty is so high.
I heard that the Government and
Navy Headquarters are going after her.
She seemed to have inherited the
ideology of the executed scholars.
It'll be a problem if she's left at large.
She is a child of the devil
who shouldn't be allowed to live!
Thank you for always helping me.
Sure. Thank you for letting me work.
By the way, before lunch, you have guests.
What?!
Don't let her get away!
Now, give me the money!
I reported her to you, right?!
She works very hard, although she's still small.
Oh? You're still up?
We have to get up early tomorrow
morning to go purchase stock.
Go to sleep now.
Okay.
She's a good kid, but if we're
with her, we'll be in danger, too.
Besides, look at this bounty amount!
Honey! She isn't in her room!
Dammit! That little brat picked up on it!
I'm sorry, but I don't have any food.
I know about you, Nico Robin!
I'm a wanted man, too.
If you do chores, I'll feed you.
--Captain!
--Contact Navy Headquarters!
Where's Robin?! Hand her over, dammit!
That darn jinx!
Your sin is being alive!
What?! Nico Robin is in this town?!
Find her! Hand her over to the Government!
I found one...! A Poneglyph...!
Don't come inside! I've got nothing to sell you!
I'm sixteen. I'll do anything.
Please let me be part of your organization.
You betrayed me, Robin!
Nico Robin. I want you to help me.
I heard that you can read Poneglyphs.
If... you exercise a Buster Call
right here, right now,
then together with Enies Lobby...
...you guys, too, will disappear.
D-Don't be ridiculous!
There's no way we'd be eliminated
by our own people's attack!
What're you saying?!
Twenty years ago,
everything was taken away from me
and many people's lives were ruined.
It was caused by a single attack--Buster Call.
That attack is now...
...targeted on the friends I was finally
able to find, whom I can be myself with.
The more I wish to be with you,
the more my fate will show its fangs to you!
No matter how far I go on the sea,
I have a huge enemy that I can't shake off...
...because the world and
its darkness are my enemy!
The incident with Aokiji, as well as this time...
I've already dragged you
into my troubles twice!
If this continues forever, even though
you guys're good-natured...
...you'll eventually feel that I'm a burden!
I'm sure you'll betray me
one day and abandon me!
That's what I'm most afraid of!
That's why I didn't want
you to come to rescue me!
If I'm going to die someday anyway,
I want to die right here, right now!
Robin...
Robin-chan...
Now it makes sense.
I see! That indeed is a sound argument!
That's true. No one is stupid enough
to think that having you isn't a burden.
Look at that symbol, you damn pirates!
That logo indicates the unity
of over 170 member countries
spanning the four seas and the Grand Line!
This is the world!
Do you now realize how completely
powerless you guys are to fight against it?!
Do you realize how huge of an organization
this woman has been pursued by?!
I now understand well the
identity of Robin's enemy.
Sogeking.
Hm?
Shoot through that flag.
Roger.
Huh?
This is my new weapon,
a huge slingshot... named Kabuto!
Have a good look at its power!
Special Attack... Firebird Star!
Oh, no...!
Mission accomplished.
Th-They've gone and done it!
Do they understand what it
means to attack the flag?!
The pirates declared war
against the World Government!
Are you insane?! Don't think
that you'll be able to survive
after making the entire world your enemy!
Bring it on!
Robin!
We still haven't heard you say it!
Say you want to live!
Robin...
Robin!
To live...
You shouldn't be allowed
to live in this world, Robin!
Your existence itself is a huge crime, Robin!
I thought it was something I dared not wish for.
No one ever let me wish for it.
I want to die!
Right. The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
Believe in Luffy.
If... it's really okay for me
to utter my wish for once...
I...
I want to live!
Take me to the sea with you!
You guys...! I love you guys, dammit!
Let's go!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
When I was a kid, I swore that I'd
gather a crew and become a pirate...
...like the pirate who protected me.
So, just like he protected me
that time, I'll protect you, too!
You're already one of us, Robin!
I'm gonna rescue you without fail!
Let's go!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Jump Towards the Falls! Luffy's Feelings!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!