Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Throw that gas mask away!
You're no longer one of us.
Die!
I won't let you shoot poison gas!
Stop scampering about, anchor boy!
D-Dammit!
Ghin! You don't have to listen
to what that weakling says!
I'm gonna kick his ass now!
Don't mock Don Krieg!
He's the strongest man.
You can't defeat him.
Come to your senses, you idiot!
That man is trying to kill you!
I deserve it...
since I couldn't fulfill my role,
shamelessly losing to emotion...
This is... This is a
well-deserved punishment!
--Ghin!
--Why... Why?
Ha! So you showed your pride
at the end... But it's too late.
Die together with that cook!
Deadly Poison Gas Bomb... M... H... 5!
"I Won't Die!
Fierce Battle, Luffy vs. Krieg!"
--It's coming!!
--Dive into the sea!!
Owner! Get inside the restaurant!!
Let me borrow those.
Sanji! Ghin! Use these!
--Chore boy!
--Now for mine!
Ahh! Everyone dived into the sea!
Ahhh! What do I do?! What do I do?!
What do I do?! What do I do?!
Huh?!
This is force.
I... I'm saved... Good thing
I found that mask when I did...
Wh-What a crazy bastard...
I can't believe he used
poison gas in battle...
He's a devil...
Yeah, no human being
would do something like that!
Are Sanji and the chore boy okay?
Not sure... Look!
The poison mist is clearing up!
Ghin!
Let go...
Let go of the mask!
--Ghin!
--Where's your mask?!
Did you... give me your mask?
Ghin!
What an idiot.
You're in pain right now
because you feel indebted
just because someone
gave you some food.
Well, I guess idiots
don't learn until they die...
That bastard... even after he threw
the gas mask away as ordered...
Is that how he talks
to his loyal subordinate?!
Don... Don Krieg...
Ghin...
Ghin... It seems...
It seems that you picked
the wrong man to follow...
So you're actually sympathizing
with that idiot scum?
--Scum?!
--That's right.
An idiot who loses sight of our
goal and can't follow my orders
no longer holds value to me.
There's no guarantee that
he won't betray me again.
It's out of love that I put him out of
his misery now. Wouldn't you agree?
I-I never imagined that Don would
actually kill the Chief Commander...
C-Can't be true...
There's no way he would!
Ghin-san is his right-hand man!
That's right. No one has been more
faithful to Don than Ghin-san!
That time, too. When Fullbody's
Navy ship came after us
right after we escaped
from the Grand Line...
Yeah... He acted as
a decoy all by himself,
pretending to be Don...
He always risked his life
fighting for Don Krieg...
I never imagined... that Don
would actually try to kill him...
--How evil...
--Patty! We have an antidote, don't we?!
Yeah, we do...
but that's for food poisoning.
It doesn't matter what it is,
just bring it over here!
Idiot! If you wanna save him,
put the mask on him right away!
It should have some sort
of detoxifying effect!
Bring him to the second floor
and let him breathe well.
If there's a chance to save him,
that's the only way!
Hurry up, Patty! Carne!
All right already!
Me too?!
Ha! It's no use. Even if he stays alive,
it'll be an hour at most...
Don't you dare die, Ghin.
Don't let someone like him kill you!
Cling to life! Got that?!
I'll kick his ass for you!
D-Don't. You can't... defeat him...
Cool down! Attacking head-on
would be playing right
into his hands. You'll die!
I won't die.
--Go ahead and shoot
as much as you want.
--Hey!
Such a fool... The easiest enemy
to kill is one who's in a frenzy.
The sea is your hell, anchor boy.
You're heading towards...
--Here comes...
--Bombs!
...your graveyard!
My graveyard?!
Oh, no! Get out of there, chore boy!
He got hit!
He's dead...
Chore boy...
--You little...
--Gum-Gum...
Hit me...
--Here it comes!
--...if you can!
How dirty! That's...
...Pistol!!
What?!
Don Krieg got beaten!
What the hell is he?!
He hit him along with the porcupine!
Ouch...
Holy shit...
We've never even seen
Don brought to his knees...
He hit Don in his face! And he did it
through that Porcupine Cape!
C... Can you believe that?!
Is this... my graveyard?
Or... your graveyard?
My... graveyard?!
Don't think... you can send me
to my grave with stuff like this.
I'm not gonna die here.
He's crazy...
You see idiots like that
every once in a while...
...ones who will fight to the death once
they've set their eyes on a target...
Fight... to the death...
You're in trouble if someone
like that becomes your enemy.
But you know, win or lose,
I like guys like him...
--Hey, underling!
--Hang in there!
Now, breathe!
Breathe in a lot of good air!
Are you all right? Hey!
Do you want to drink some water? Hey!
This isn't good.
Do you wanna eat my
special pudding? It's good!
Idiot! You want to feed
poison to a poisoned man?!
Hey, what do you mean by
poison?! You're one to talk!
What'd you say?! People say my
meat dishes are the best in the world!
They're considered so delicious
that people think they're in heaven.
--Ahh! You can't die on us!
--Hey! C'mon! Don't die, underling!
A-Are you dead? Are you really dead?!
Hey! Really? Are you dead?
Hey! Are you dead? Really?
Are you really dead?!
Shut up!!
Phew, he's still alive...
D... Don Krieg... Is Don Krieg...
Wh-What's gonna happen to this fight?
Idiot! That was just dumb luck!
There's no way Don would be defeated
by a stupid brat like that! Don't worry!
Chore boy...
"I'm not gonna die here," you said?
If you won't die here... then...
...who the hell will?!
You will, right?!
You will!!
Don got beaten again!
What the hell is going on?!
E-Enemies are supposed to die
without even touching Don Krieg...
Don's supposed to be
invincible... What the...
What the hell is that brat?!
He's really good!
Yeah... I'm blown away...
--He's amazing!
--Get Krieg!
Yeah, he can do it!
That brat is fighting Don
at his level, without a doubt...
This isn't a dream, right? Don getting
beaten by someone like him...
Don's supposed to be invincible...
As it stands, the legend of
Don Krieg the strongest will be...
Stop talking nonsense!!
What the...
F... Finally, Don Krieg's
strongest weapon...
The Mighty Battle Spear!
What's that? It exploded.
Now... I'll see how long you
can keep avoiding this...
It'll be a sight, anchor boy.
That puny spear from earlier still
left you standing after a few attacks,
but this Mighty Battle Spear is different.
As soon as you touch it,
you'll be blown to pieces!!
Wh-What's with that spear?!
I'll fall, I'll fall, I'll fall...
Wh-What's with that spear?
It explodes every time
he strikes it down?
What? My knees...
A long battle will be trouble...
He's shed too much blood...
He's not gonna last long...
Your overdoing it has
taken its toll on you.
You must be reaching your limit...
Darn! With the foothold
rocking like this,
I can't fight with full power.
I'm stumped.
That Mighty Battle Spear
never ceases to amaze me.
Yeah. The stronger that
big spear is struck down,
the bigger the explosion it causes.
It's something that no one
other than Don can handle!
But how powerful he is...
To think he easily swings around
that super heavy spear,
which weighs 1 ton with
those two shoulder guards!
That's exactly the reason
why Don is the strongest!
--Wooaahhh...
--Take this!
Die!!
Chore boy!
Phew... That was close...
You... damn caterpillar!!
Waaahhh!
Chore boy!!
--Chore boy...
--Are you all right?!
Ha! I'm not quite done yet...
You made me angry.
I won't let you die so easily.
Dammit! That bastard Krieg brings
out weapons one after another...
There's no way that chore boy can...
Even if hundreds of
weapons are built in,
he can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
Hmph! How easy...
Now that makes you worth crushing...
Life or death...
In a pirate battle, if you fear death
for even a moment, you'll fall to pieces.
What're you talking about?
At least...
...that kid doesn't have any hesitation!
Is it a survival instinct?
Or does he not fear death
because he has faith in himself?
Faith...
Y... You son of a bitch!!
--Alright! You're amazing!
--Chore boy! Go for it!!
--Get him!
I told you... that this is where you die!!
I am the strongest man!!
The fleet Krieg gathered...
His hundreds of weapons and poison...
If they're all force...
...then that kid's spear is also force...
The spear held in his heart...
I know an idiot who's holding back
that spear for a stupid reason...
M-My Mighty Battle Spear is...
What the hell did you do?!
I gave it five punches.
I guess that's it for your spear.
Prepare yourself...
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Why is he fighting when
his body's falling apart?
Is he trying to get himself killed?!
No, he isn't even thinking about dying.
Risking life for an ambition and dream...
I used to have a dream like that!
--This is it!!
--Chore boy! Don't die in a place like this!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Conclusion of the Deadly Battle!
A Spear of Blind Determination!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!