Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map
has been verified,
it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the world
to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
That's...
Hey... don't tell me...
...those are the ancient
weapon Pluton's blueprints...!
They're the real deal.
Do you believe me?
Hey, Spanda.
What Tom-san and Iceberg
risked their lives to protect is...
Hand them over to me already!
...the wish of this weapon's architect--
that is, if the ancient weapon fell
into the hands of an idiot like you
and started being used to cause trouble,
he would want another weapon
to be built in order to stop it.
It's true that if you use Nico Robin,
you can revive the ancient weapon.
Even if she doesn't want to help you,
as long as there's a chance
that she could be used,
she's still dangerous.
But she's got friends
who would be willing to risk
their lives to protect her.
So I'll...
...take a chance.
You bastard! What're you doing?!
It's burned black!
Now, there's no longer power to
fight back against the ancient weapon.
If nothing is done and Nico Robin
falls into your hands, it'll be hopeless.
But if the Straw Hats win...
...there won't be
anything left to you at all.
I made a bet on their victory.
Cutty Flam...
How dare you...
...burn my blueprints?!
Ahhh! Bro!
Bro is falling into the falls!
Franky!
Hey, pirates!
What the hell is that?!
Jump with all your might
towards the falls!
R-Rocketman?!
It's flying again!
This brings back memories,
doesn't it, Tom-san?
About assisting that Roger guy...
I'm resolutely proud of it!
I'm Luffy. I'm the man
who'll be King of the Pirates.
Really?!
Yeah.
Roger was an idiot
like him, too, wasn't he?
And you helped him out.
Seems like we didn't learn our lesson.
Everyone in Tom's Workers
is helping this pirate kid.
You would've done the same,
wouldn't you, Tom-san?
We're gonna collide!
W-We're gonna crash!
"Obtain the Five Keys!
The Straw Hat Pirates vs. CP9"
Run!
They're here...
Yoyoi!
They're here!
Dammit!
Hey, come with me!
If only I could get these
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs off...
Now, I'm freeing you
of any restrictions, CP9!
Beat the crap out of them
here at the Tower of Law!
I'll give you permission
to slaughter them!
Lucci! Come with me!
Protecting my life is your
top priority!
Got that?!
Funkfreed!
All right, good boy.
An elephant...
who ate a Devil Fruit
with sword powers?!
No, it's actually the other way around.
This is a sword that ate
the Elephant-Elephant fruit.
In other words, it's an elephant sword.
I've got this treasured sword,
in addition to CP9.
When I think about it calmly,
I've got nothing to be afraid of.
Now, let's head to the Gates of Justice!
Go ahead and get this woman
back if you can, Straw Hat!
Big Bro Franky is okay!
The Straw Hats have finally
reached the Tower of Law!
Bro is no longer a prisoner!
Looks like he's gonna join in the fight!
That's right!
He's that kind of person!
Get them, Bro!
Go! Straw Hat!
We're leaving the rest
to you, Straw Hat.
Hey, are you guys okay?!
Old Hag Kokoro?!
Little ones?!
What'd you come here for,
bringing out a dangerous thing
like Rocketman?!
W-Well, it saved me, too, but...
Hey! Hey, old hag!
Hang in there!
Hey! I beg you! Don't die!
Don't die!
I've got a nosebleed.
How could you walk away from this
sort of crash with just a nosebleed?!
All right! We're here!
Straw Hat...!
Hello!
Thanks, monster granny!
Hey, you guys!
Get up already!
That was nothing!
You're rubber. Don't lump us with you.
Us flesh-and-blood humans were
forced to charge in like that.
You think we're okay...?
No way!
Yup, they're all fine.
You guys are all weirdos, too, so...
Just sayin'.
There are stairs over there!
Let's hurry up and catch up to Robin!
Wait.
What the heck is that?!
Chapapapa...
We got invaded.
Even if you go
to the room you saw earlier,
Nico Robin isn't there anymore,
since Lucci took her to
the Gates of Justice.
What?!
Oh, and our Chief did, too.
Oh, is that right?!
Thanks for giving us
such valuable information.
Chapapa... I spilled the beans...
What a funny guy.
Oh, well...
They're headed there right now,
but I won't tell you how to get there,
and we, CP9,
won't let you go there, either.
We have an order to annihilate you guys.
Annihilation order...?
Unless you guys defeat us,
you won't be able
to set Nico Robin free.
Yeah.
You don't have to tell us that.
We're gonna do it anyway.
Chapapa...
What a high-spirited guy.
But let me tell you one more thing.
What?! Do as you wish.
Ah, thanks.
Then, I'll speak frankly.
Look at this!
A key?
What for?!
This is the key to unlock
the Sea Prism Stone
handcuffs on Nico Robin!
Sea Prism Stone?
It's a stone that cancels out
Devil Fruit powers.
I heard that it's as effective as when
Devil Fruit power holders fall into the sea.
So that's why Robin isn't fighting now,
despite how strong she actually is.
Yeah.
Under normal circumstances,
she isn't so weak that she'd helplessly
stay held captive by guys like that.
She must be feeling frustrated.
I see.
Even if you guys can rescue
Nico Robin by some chance,
since the Sea Prism Stone
is hard like diamonds,
the handcuffs will be on her forever.
Chapapa...
I spilled the beans again.
He really is funny.
If that's okay, keep on going to
rescue Nico Robin.
Chapapapapa!
Well, then...
...give that to us!
Looks like he can use
that technique, too.
Don't be so hasty.
I didn't say that this is the right key.
What?!
It might be
for different handcuffs.
Chapapa papa!
There are five CP9 members,
including me, in this tower.
Each one has a key
One, two, come on!
One, two, bad!
and is waiting for you.
Yow?!
Then, until we defeat you all
and get the keys,
and try them on Robin's handcuffs,
we won't know which one
is the right key?!
How stupid... Buying time?
While we're fighting,
you guys are trying to take Robin-chan
to the Gates of Justice, aren't you?!
That's right!
I spilled the beans again...
Catching up with Robin
quickly should be our priority.
We'll first get Robin back
and then worry about the key.
Let's ignore that weirdo and hurry!
Chapa!
"That weirdo"
Chapapa!
You're smart.
But if you do that,
I'll ditch this key
into the sea! Chapapa!
We're giving you a chance.
See ya.
Ah! Wait, you jerk!
Hey, wait!
You wait!
Stop! Just a little bit longer!
Just wait until we decide
what each of us will do!
Ah! Let me go!
Calm down, Straw Hat.
Let me go!
Is Lucci that pigeon guy?
Yeah, that's right.
If he's with Robin-chan,
we should let at least
Luffy go on ahead.
Luffy.
At any rate, you just
beat up the pigeon guy.
Let me go! Let me go!
There are six of us excluding Luffy.
He said there are five CP9 members here.
We'll get the five keys for Robin-chan's
handcuffs from them and go after Luffy.
If Robin-kun goes through
the gates, it'll all be over.
It's all a race against time!
If we lose against them,
that means we lose time!
Everyone! Take them down
even if it costs you your life!
Yeah!
Good luck!
Let me go! Let me go!
There are six of us excluding Luffy.
He said there are five CP9 members here.
We'll get the five keys for Robin-chan's
handcuffs from them and go after Luffy.
If Robin-kun goes through
the gates, it'll all be over.
It's all a race against time!
If we lose against them,
that means we lose time!
Everyone! Take them down
even if it costs you your life!
Yeah!
Good luck!
Pirate guys!
Chimney? Gonbe?
Where did they go?
They were there up until just a bit ago!
I'm sure I'll bump into them somewhere!
I'm not gonna let you go to
the Gates of Justice!
Robin!
A secret passage!
A secret passage! A secret passage!
Geography!
Physics!
Stigma!
Marimba!
Bats...?
I-I wonder how far this goes...
I can hear something.
I've got nothing to be afraid of!
Let's go there!
Help won't come, Nico Robin.
They don't know how to get to the
Gates of Justice in the first place!
Come out! You pigeon jerk!
Is it this way?!
Is it that way?!
Which way is it...?!
Which way is it?!
Ooops.
That way?!
Which way...?!
Which way?!
Is it this way?!
This way! Robin!
Even he shouldn't be able
to follow us this far.
That's a weird room.
I have to do this and do this
one like this... and like this.
I wonder what he's doing.
Open, doors!
Whoa...
This is bad... Before I fight...
Where's the kitchen?!
Coup de Boo!
Because I used a bottle and
a half of cola for Coup de Boo,
I've used more than two bottles today!
Unless I fill up all three bottles,
I can't fight CP9!
That area looks like a kitchen!
Chapapapapa...
I'm Silent Fukurou!
I like rumors!
Do you want the key?
Dammit!
I still haven't refilled my cola yet!
Chapa...!
I wonder what this
dungeon-like hallway is?
Yoyoi!
You damn pirate!
You're doomed now that
I've caught you here!
Wait...
a second...!
Yoyoi!
What a noisy guy...
No one was in there.
No one's in here.
Hmm, no one's in here.
All right, no one's in here.
What's going on?
I can't find anyone anywhere!
If no one's around, that's fine, though.
They must've gotten scared of me...
Ahhh...!
Someone's here!
He's sleeping...
Is he part of CP9, too?
H-He's sleeping with the
key right in front of him!
"Liquor"
Couldn't this be a huge,
lucky chance?!
What about this room?!
Dammit...
No one's here, either.
Please make yourself at home.
Shall I... make some tea?
Yes, please!
You've already drawn your swords?
Yeah, since they're
crying out for blood.
Ahh! Where'd you come
falling from, Zoro?!
Why the hell are you with a wolf?!
You're with a giraffe, too.
So this means that both of
them have Devil Fruit powers.
What's with CP9?!
Hey, hey... What is this place?! A zoo?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Devil Fruit Powers! Kaku
and Jabra Transform"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!