Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map
has been verified,
it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Let me go!
Is Lucci that pigeon guy?
Yeah, that's right.
If he's with Robin-chan,
we should
let at least Luffy go on ahead.
Luffy.
At any rate, you just
beat up the pigeon guy.
Let me go! Let me go!
There are six of us excluding Luffy.
He said there are five CP9 members here.
We'll get the five keys for Robin-chan's
handcuffs from them and go after Luffy.
If Robin-kun goes through
the gates, it'll all be over.
It's all a race against time!
If we lose against them,
that means we lose time!
Everyone! Take them down
even if it costs you your life!
Yeah!
Good luck!
Help won't come, Nico Robin.
They don't know how to get to the
Gates of Justice in the first place!
Come out! You pigeon jerk!
Chapapapapa...
I'm Silent Fukurou! I like rumors!
Do you want the key?
Dammit!
I still haven't refilled my cola yet!
Chapa...!
Yoyoi!
You damn pirate!
You're doomed now that
I've caught you here!
They must've gotten scared of me...
Ahhh...!
Someone's here!
What about this room?!
Dammit...
No one's here, either.
Please make yourself at home.
"Devil Fruit Powers!
Kaku and Jabra Transform"
Yooo!
Yoyoi...! Yoyoi!
Now... are you...
...prepared?!
Prepared?!
No matter how I look at it,
I'm at a disadvantage.
Obtaining the key is my
priority here! Okay, then!
Hey, assassin! Where's the key?!
If you don't know...
...I'll tell you where!
The key is...
Yep, yep. The key is...?
Yes, yes. And...?
The key is...
I'm listening!
...right here!
Oh...?!
Where did my key go?!
He's loud, and a pain to boot.
That's no good.
What?
Mademoiselle.
That water is too lukewarm
to make good tea.
Here are the golden rules
for making black tea.
First, boil fresh water
and pour it into a teapot
that was warmed beforehand.
When coin-size bubbles start appearing,
that's when you should stop heating it.
By doing so,
the leaves move around
due to the circulation of hot water,
which brings out their scent and color.
Then, cover the teapot
immediately and steam it well.
Once it's done,
pour it into warmed teacups.
Just a little bit of consideration
makes a difference in the taste.
You sure do know your stuff.
I'm a cook, so...
Thanks for the lesson.
You're so beautiful!
This is probably the place.
I finally made it.
I had to go
up and down all those stairs.
Robin!
Hey! Robin!
It's me!
Robin!
Where are you?!
Dammit!
So they really did leave already.
That damn pigeon guy!
Oh, yeah...!
I know where they're headed.
So I just have to head to the
Gates of Justice, too, right?!
You have the key
to Robin's handcuffs, right?
Want to give it to me
before I take you down?
That's a foolish question.
I was disappointed that I didn't
get to see your real ability
at the Galley-La mansion.
I never thought that pirates
would come this far, either, so...
Be careful, as I'm far
stronger than that time.
I can imagine,
with all that energy you've got...
Energy like that of a beast.
What a fearsome man you are.
But
my swordsmanship is the best in CP9.
Don't underestimate me.
Two-Sword Style, huh?
Tempest Kick.
So, no... Sorry, but I use four swords.
No problem.
Come to think of it,
your entire body is a weapon.
Seventy-two...
Tempest Kick.
--...Pound Phoenix!
--White Thunder!
Shave!
This is fun!
I don't have time to have fun!
Then you just have to take me down.
Tempest Kick.
Slaughter!
To think that he uses
slashing attacks so freely...
You bastard... Are you mocking me?
Whoa... I'd expect no less from you.
If you're in that much
of a hurry, I'll show you...
...my new powers.
Wh... What the hell?!
At any rate, what the heck is this room?
No matter how you look at it,
someone went nuts on the gardening.
This is practically outside!
No, no...
More importantly, I have to get
the key to Robin's handcuffs right now!
That key...!
Tiptoe...
No need to hesitate!
Carefully, tiptoe...
Move step by step
without making noise...
"Wolf"
That was close!
Okay, I'll try again!
If I quietly grab it,
then quietly run away...
I'll accomplish my mission.
It'll be a victory without wounds!
That's right.
I'm a lucky king!
Hey, heart!
You're beating too loud!
Stop!
Ahh! My heart stopped!
H-Hey! What're you doing?!
Start beating!
You can't stop!
Oh, yeah, at a time like this,
I have to perform a heart massage!
Boy, that scared me.
Calm down. Calm down.
Do your best!
I'm a man who makes
everything he does work out...
...probably...
I can do it...
I can do...
Wh-What?! A bee?!
Stay away! Go away! Huh?
What're you doing?!
The tip of my nose
isn't a flower!
There's no honey there!
Go somewhere else!
I'm saying go somewhere else!
Wh-Why are you looking at me?
What's with that sparkle in your eyes?!
D-Don't tell me... you're going to...
Don't do it! Don't!
Don't! Don't!
My nose! My nose!
It hurts!
Dammit!
I came back to where I was earlier.
At any rate, to think that he
still hasn't woken up yet...
He's quite a sleepyhead.
If I take the time to do it properly,
it'll be fine this time for sure!
Tiptoe...
Tiptoe, tiptoe...
I'm almost there...
I'm almost there...!
A-A chicken this time?!
Oh, no! What is the noisiest
bird of them all doing here?
Oh, no!
If it crows, it's all over!
If it crows, he'll get up,
find me, and kill me!
Hey
What're you looking at?!
Are you trying to crow?
Are you?! Are you?!
Shhh! Shhh!
Chicken-kun! Chicken-san!
Chicken-sama! Please!
Please don't crow!
Don't crow!
Don't! Don't!
No chicken would crow like that!
Oh, you're here, pirate.
Th-That damn chicken!
Well then, why don't
I give you a beatdown?
That damn chicken!
H-He's strong...
So you're the one who came?!
You're the one who shot through
the Government flag, right?
"Liquor"
It seems that you're skilled at sniping.
He delivered a punch like that
right after he woke up?
Sorry for attacking you half-assed.
Forgive me.
It must've hurt.
"Liquor"
Huh?
Don't worry.
I may not look like it,
but I'm not into tormenting my opponent.
A-A devil fruit...!
The Dog-Dog Fruit, Model Wolf!
I'll just tear up your windpipe
and that'll be it.
You'll die anyway.
You don't have to suffer.
Isn't that right?
W-Wolf...!
D-Dammit!
What?! Are you gonna fight?
You don't look strong, though.
S-Strong or not, I'm gonna fight!
Shut up!
I came to rescue Robin!
Whoa! The ceiling is...
...collapsing!
Oh, shoot!
I was gonna
stop the transformation
when I reached my human-beast form,
but I became a giraffe!
A talking giraffe is falling towards us!
Kaku!
That power of yours is too cool!
A wolf?!
What is this place?! A zoo?!
The Ox-Ox Fruit, Model Giraffe!
You poor guy!
To think that you'll be
a giraffe-man for the rest of your life!
What's wrong with giraffes?!
I said I like it!
That pigeon guy
was a leopard, wasn't he?
To think that there are two more power
holders who transform into animals...
Is CP9 that kind of group?
S-So he is a Zoan-type power holder...
A wolf-man and a giraffe-man?
What crazy guys we're facing!
But it was good that Zoro
fell with that giraffe.
While it appears to be a
two-versus-two fight, I'll just wait for Zoro...
...to pretty much take them both down.
"I said I like it"?!
I'm sure you do!
Giraffes are cool, aren't they?!
Wh-What're you talking that way for?!
At any rate, for comrades,
they sure don't work together.
What's that?
It looks like a safe
with the door left opened.
Whoa!
Could those
weird-looking handcuffs be...?!
I said don't laugh!
Hey, giraffe!
Just how long are you gonna
stand there arguing with him?
I thought I told you
that I don't have much time.
If it's okay for you to stay like that,
I'll just cut you down like that.
How foolish... Don't underestimate a
giraffe's limitless destructive power!
Transform...
Human-beast form!
I'll show you
the power I gained when I was reborn!
How lame!
Gasp!
What'd you just...?
What a shallow thing I said!
That was bad!
I was so shocked
that it just came out of my mouth!
Don't lose your composure, Zoro!
Or your techniques will weaken!
Just how long are you gonna
continue to laugh, Jabra?!
S-Sorry.
I can't stop after all!
At any rate, it's interesting.
How in the heck did his square
parts get reflected like this?!
Wh-What're these handcuffs?!
Ahhh!
Shoot! I'm sorry, Zoro-kun!
Hey! What're you doing?!
Th-They're probably Sea Prism
Stone handcuffs just like Robin's!
Since our enemies are both
Devil Fruit power holders,
I thought they'd get weak if
they were handcuffed with them!
So why are they on me, you idiot?!
B-Because...
...the giraffe's face is so
funny that I just lost my grip.
A giraffe with square parts everywhere...
He's right!
How dare you all...?
Experience the fighting
power of a power holder...!
Tempest Kick!
Whoa! What's that?!
He's gonna do something!
Sky Slicer!
This isn't good.
Duck, Usopp!
No! This is no time for having tea!
Oh, that's too bad.
Are you in a hurry?
Robin-chan's life is at stake.
If you're gonna be in my way,
I won't
go easy on you, even if you are a woman!
Then I guess teatime is over?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Won't Kick Even If It Costs
Me My Life! Sanji's Chivalry!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!