Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Chopper! What's wrong?!
Take a good look at me! It's me! I'm Nami!
Chopper!
Chopper! Stop it!
I'm gonna hurry up and finish it here.
Tempest Kick!
This is bad! Even the soles
are slippery. I can't dodge it!
Huh?! I could dodge it!
Ah... My right leg went back to normal.
Why? What caused it?
It's wet...
It got wet in the earlier
commotion. Oh, that's right!
Water! I can wash off
the soap power with water!
Aren't you being too optimistic?
Even if you figured out
how to undo Golden Bubbles,
there's no way I'd let you do that.
Sheep Cloud! Relaxing Bubbles!
I'll blow away those bubbles with wind!
Cyclone...
Shoot!
O... Oh, no... My strength is...
Supple Finger Pistol!
Takt...
Whip!
That was helpful.
Helpful?
If you blow me away like that,
the annoying bubbles on
my body get blown away, too.
That's a bluff. If you so wish, I'll keep
blowing you away until you die.
The weather forecast is cloudy!
Cloudy Tempo!
This is different from the
magic show stuff I used to do!
Clouds? More lightning?
Thunder doesn't get generated
from such thin clouds.
Instead, they'll condense!
Don't tell me...! No, she might do that!
The weather forecast is rain!
Cool Ball!
Shave!
Pour down! Rain Tempo!
You're not sweet at all. After I was nice
enough to make your skin silky smooth.
If being sweet means not
putting up a fight, then I'll pass.
Cool Charge!
What?
Mirage Tempo!
She disappeared?!
Now I understand... your powers...
...as well as the strength of CP9.
What's this?!
Mirage Tempo!
Fata Morgana!
"Nami's Decision!
Fire at the Out-of-Control Chopper!"
The mirage from earlier...
In the end, you've only got one body.
That's right. One of them is the real me.
The other four are illusions
being reflected by the chilly air.
Illusions, you say?
That sounds mysterious and lovely.
But when you think about it calmly,
it becomes obvious that illusions
don't have offensive power.
In other words, this is just an empty threat.
That's right.
So you turn defiant? You're not sweet.
Thunder Charge!
Only one of the five of me is real.
So what?
And... Thunder Ball!
Only 20% of my attacks are real as well.
Why don't you try dodging them?
Oh, shoot! I have to guard myself!
Which ones are the real ones?!
Its power, on the other hand, is 100%.
I told you... that I'd throw
you off your guard, didn't I?
This is very different from the old Clima Takt.
A mere Thunder Ball attack
has this much power.
With my next powerful attack, you'll fall.
What kind of prediction is that? How cocky...
It's not a prediction. It's a forecast.
I've controlled both humidity and temperature.
The weather in this room belongs to me!
What's the big deal with
controlling the weather?
The Six Powers are techniques
that exceed human abilities.
How insolent!
That wasn't the real one!
The possibility of catching
the real one today is again 20%.
According to today's sky forecast,
although atmospheric pressure is stable,
small dark clouds with violent
air currents will remain stationary
for a while, and soon they will shoot
thunderbolts through your chest.
Please watch out for paralysis of the heart!
Dark Cloud Tempo!
If this is lightning, I showed you at
the beginning that I can guard myself.
As long as I'm being careful...
The flaw in that technique is that
you can't move around while using it.
You sure take me lightly. Are you
telling me to break it with an attack?!
Then... Soap Sheep!
I don't have to know which one is the real one.
I'll swallow everything with a
big wave of Relaxing Bubbles.
Sheep Cloud!
Tidal Wave!
I'll be a goner if I get hit by that.
The one on the floor after I
swallow everything is the real one.
That's not gonna happen!
Cyclone Tempo!
She used wind to blow the bubbles away!
But it looks like the one who got
through it is the real one, huh?
Finger Pistol!
Oh? I thought it was another illusion.
I won't let you run around anymore.
I'll just turn your body into Swiss cheese.
You've already forgotten it, haven't you?
You should pay attention to the
weather forecast by a navigator.
From the dark clouds to the Clima Takt...
...a thunderbolt will burst forth...!
Come on!
The one from earlier...!
Thunder Lance Tempo!
No matter how strong you are...
...my forecast is never wrong.
My friends are waiting. I'll be taking your key.
That son of a bitch... Damn deer-gorilla!
This entire island is a mess!
They all had better be okay.
Hey, Navy! Come back!
Take us with you!
Tempest Kick!
Sky Slicer!
Chopper! What's taking you so long?!
What do you think you're doing?!
Hold it, Nico Robin!
Coo coo!
All right!
Deer-gorilla! Where'd you go?!
What? Franky! What are you doing there?!
Oh, hey, lady.
That monster deer-gorilla in
your group came here, didn't he?
Deer... You mean Chopper?
Yeah, that deer-gorilla.
Yeah, he did. What's the deal?
What happened to him?
How should I know?! I wanna
ask that question myself!
He isn't someone who can
transform into something like that?
How would I know?!
I've never seen him in that form.
I see... I thought you guys
might know how to deal with that.
Then, I guess I'll just kill him anyhow.
If you say that again, I'm gonna kill you.
I-I'll never say it again. Ever again.
But we still need to do something.
If he rampages about while he's that huge,
you never know how long this tower will last.
Yeah. He isn't in a state
where he'll listen to us.
It seemed like he didn't recognize me,
so I think he's lost his memory.
What's causing it?
I'm not totally sure,
but it may have something to
do with his Devil Fruit powers.
Then there's only one way
to solve this problem...
By the way, you're not bad at all.
You took this woman down?
Her key is important. The #2 key is.
Key... Hold on a sec. I was searching for it.
Key! Key! Where'd you hide it?
Yow! Nice scandalous action!
Ahh! Stay back! Stay back!
Listen, you guys! To tell you
the truth, 8,000 men are under m...
I mean, under my close friend Usopp-kun!
S-So, this island is already surrounded.
Stop the useless resistance and surrender!
Eight thousand guys? It'll be
worthwhile killing all of them, huh?
Hurry up and call them in here.
Don't be a fool. He's clearly lying.
To think that you easily fell
for such an obvious lie...
You're a disgrace to CP9.
Who's the fool here? I knew it was a lie;
I was just making fun of him.
I can't stand how ridiculously honest
and incredibly serious you are.
What's wrong with being serious and honest?
I'm saying the "ridiculously" and
"incredibly" parts are bad, blockhead!
My plan worked. Yay...
But now...
The Buster Call is imminent, so...
Eek!
We've wasted too much time, but...
Let's both get serious and...
Huh?
--...settle this, shall we?
--...settle this, huh?
What?! H-Hey, hold on a sec. Calm down!
We're calm!
Tempest Kick!
Oh, shoot!
--Pick it up!
--Okay!
Finger Pistol--!
Finger Pistol!
Looks like playtime is over.
Don't let your guard down.
Oh no...
Shave!
Ow, ow, ow...
This is bad. They're pretty fired up.
We'd better hurry up and take these off.
Chopper! Hurry up!
What the hell is this monster?!
There was another Zoan type power holder?!
Does that mean that this
guy's also part of CP9?!
Come to think of it, I feel
like I've seen him before.
Ch-Chopper?!
What're you doing, Chopper?! It's us!
Ahh! Stop it!
Hey, is that really Chopper?!
How come he doesn't recognize us?!
I don't know, but it must be Chopper!
Who else has those antlers and wears that hat?!
Then, what about our hope and the #2 key?!
Who knows? This is it! We're gonna die.
But something is wrong.
Isn't he the one who looks
like he is about to die?
It seems as if his vitality is rapidly dimming.
Wh-Wh-What does that mean?
It may be that him staying in that form
uses up too much energy or something.
What the hell?! What do we do
about him and the other two?!
Hey, what's gonna happen
to the key? The #2 key?!
I don't know what happened,
but he must've fought incredibly hard...
So hard that he transformed into that.
#2...
We got interrupted. What's that monster?
When the Buster Call is imminent...
Of course he'd interrupt us.
It seems like he's one of those pirates.
Anything that gets in our way...
...should be eliminated.
Although this is a small fry...
...we've got another prey now.
Dammit! They're gonna attack Chopper!
Straighten your back,
renowned sword Nose Storm.
H-Hey! What're you gonna do?!
Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
You bastard!
Step aside, you guys!
--Huh?
--That guy...!
Franky! What're you trying to do?!
This is one of our...
I know! Just be quiet.
This is the only way that I
can think of to deal with him.
Power holders have a weakness...
I'll push him off to the sea.
I'll go easy, so bear with me!
Coup de...
...Vent!
You bastard, Franky! That's reckless!
What're you doing to our friend?!
Don't worry. He discussed
this with me beforehand.
What?
What're they doing, attacking their own?
They sure do make a big fuss.
So you're finally released?
You'd better stop laughing
and start regretting.
Never again...
...will you get a chance like
you had earlier to slay me...
...World Government!
Why don't you run around like you
did earlier, you stupid masked man?!
Please! Don't kill Usopp!
You fool! You'll die next!
Now, this is it for you!
Don't!
--No way...
--Who the hell are you?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hunter Sanji Makes an Entrance?
Elegy for a Lying Wolf"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!