Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Demon Aura... Nine-Sword Style...
...Asura!
Sky Slicer!
Hardships are fine by me!
I choose to walk the path of Asura!
Asura... Silver Mist!
Second Gear.
Jet Whip!
Shave!
Finger Pistol!
Gum-Gum...
--Iron Body!
--...Jet Bazooka!
Franky!
Please save Robin!
Just super leave it to me!
You bitch! You still don't get it?!
I said this is useless!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
There's no hope left for you!
I'm not going anywhere!
They'll all come to rescue me for sure!
"Spandam Frightened!
The Hero on the Tower of Law"
H-Hey, look at that!
I've never seen this before!
Yeah... I've never even heard
anyone talking about it!
To see that the Gates of Justice
have completely opened!
It's so that the battleships from
Headquarters can come here!
It's for the Buster Call's cannon attack!
Granny Kokoro surely said
that those doors never
open all the way, and yet...
What's this air of intimidation?
What on earth is Buster Call?
The Straw Hats picked a fight with the world.
So they really are going to blow them
away along with the entire island!
Bastards!
Don't die, Bro!
Yeah!
Come back alive!
Straw Hat!
I entrusted Franky with saving Robin.
It was careless of me. I never
expected him to be this powerful.
It seems that you're really out of breath.
Isn't it because of that steam?
Defeating you is all that matters.
I see... You're tough.
I'd better make it!
Don't go yet, Nico Robin!
You look so stupid!
That's because of your pointless
resistance, you dumb woman!
Now, stand up!
I said, stand up!
Seriously, the gate is right there, and yet
you're causing me all sorts of trouble!
Guards! Go outside!
Yes, sir!
Guards at the Gates of Justice,
and marines on the escort ship
sent by Navy Headquarters...!
Cipher Pol's Chief Spandam is currently
taking a criminal of utmost importance
across the bridge from the Tower of Law.
All line up and salute!
Yes, sir!
Look at that. They're all ready to set sail now.
There's no longer anything standing in my way.
Oh, yeah, Nico Robin.
I'll let you in on a little secret.
Before we crossed the bridge,
I turned on the landmine
set on the upper part of the
stairs that we just ascended.
If, by any chance, someone
tries to make their way here,
they and the stairs will both go boom!
What do you think? Isn't that interesting?
But, well, don't worry about it,
since no one's gonna make
it to those stairs anyway.
But I won't go through... the gate...
Huh?
...because they said they'd rescue me.
No one will come, you dumb woman!
Everyone will burn to death in
the raging fire of Buster Call!
It'll even erase the utter humiliation of the fact
that pirates shot through our sacred flag!
Just like in Ohara twenty years ago,
when that giant marine attacked us.
Now, walk!
Walk with your own two feet!
Saul...
You bitch!
Chief! Please hurry!
I know! Shut up! I'm a hero!
You probably think that I don't
know anything about it, don't you?
The misconduct by Jaguar D. Saul,
a former Navy Headquarters Vice Admiral!
Your mother, Olvia...
What happened in Ohara at that time...
I know about it all!
Why do you think that is?
That's because I was told.
The one who commanded a raid on
the land of Ohara, where devils lived,
exposed their terrible crime
and issued a Buster Call
was my old man, then-CP9 Chief Spandine!
Well, scholars of Ohara!
Your death sentence has now been decided!
Eliminate him!
Professor!
Ohara has...
...come to know too much.
I'll initiate a Buster Call!
Take care of the rest.
Now, go, Saul!
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
No! I'll stay here, too! Mom!
Mom!
I was happy to hear you call me that.
Thank you!
From now on, for you and me both...
Live, Robin!
They all thought that everyone
in Ohara at that time died, but...
...the Government missed
one brat who escaped then.
How was it?
Who knows how many times this
eight-year-old brat almost got killed
by adults who wanted money...?
You couldn't trust anyone who came near you.
You had nowhere you could sleep safe
and sound. You didn't have food, either.
I don't even wanna imagine how crappy
the last twenty years were for you.
So you were so unhappy it'd make you cry?
The person who put a bounty
on your head twenty years ago...
...was my old man!
He did it for world peace!
Now, after twenty years...
his son hunts down the only survivor,
and the battle of Ohara comes to an end.
Ohara lost!
Robin! Be proud, Robin!
Your mom is honorable! Ohara is honorable!
Someday, pass down this
island's history, Robin!
Ohara fought against the world!
Not while I'm still alive!
But you're gonna die, aren't you?! Right?!
Whoa! What?!
C-Cutty Flam! What is he doing here?!
But that's okay. He fell for it! How stupid!
That idiot got caught in the landmine!
He came to rescue me!
Oops. This isn't good. It was
good that I made doubly sure.
We've gotta hurry. Come!
I can't even put it in words...
Hey! Set sail, marines! I'm gonna jump on!
Y-Yes, sir! Roger!
We're setting sail!
Yes, sir!
I'm so angry that I can't stop my tears!
Just watch carefully!
This is the first step of a hero
that will be engraved in histo...
Just watch carefully!
This is the first step of a hero
that will be engraved in histo...
Wha-cha houie ouchie owow!
Are you okay, Chief?!
What was that?! Who did this?!
There's no one on the bridge!
There must be! They must be
hiding somewhere! Find them!
Where are they?!
Hey! What're you guys doing?!
Why aren't you attacking?!
But, Chief, we can't find the enemy!
Ah! There he is!
Run with all your might!
You'll die if you stay on the island!
Sail out on my raft!
What about you, Saul?
This is it for me. I got caught.
--Go!
--No! There's no one on the sea!
Listen carefully, Robin!
You're alone now, but you'll
meet friends someday for sure!
Friends?
Right. The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
No one is born into this world to be alone!
Run, Robin! Don't look back!
When you're having a hard time,
laugh like this, just like I taught you!
Watch out, Saul!
Ice Time.
Saul!
Go meet the friends
who're surely waiting for you
somewhere at sea, Robin!
Live together with them.
Chief! Please look at that!
Huh?! What?! Where?!
Ahh!
On top of the Tower of Law...!
Tower of Law?! What can
he do from that far away?!
--Snap!
--Who the hell is that?!
--♪ I was born... ♪
--He's aiming at us from that distance
without the slightest error, in this wind?!
--♪ ...on the island of snipers ♪
--Who the hell is that?!
Long-nose!
See that?! Our sniper is amazing, isn't he?!
--♪ Or even your heart... ♪
--Damn well serves them right!
Robin-chan! Run!
♪ ...lock on!! ♪
Does he really have to sing?
How dare you...?!
Chief!
Dammit! What're you guys doing?!
Shoot him dead already!
We're trying, but our bullets won't
reach that far, much less hit him!
That sniper's got really incredible skills!
Nico Robin is getting away!
Don't let her get away!
Idiots! You can shoot her!
--Yes, sir!
--Shoot her dead enough to keep her alive!
Huh?!
Fire!
What?!
What the hell is he?!
You are...
My body is strong because it's iron.
That landmine wasn't nice, Spanda!
Eek!
Well... Franky-kun, Franky-kun.
This is Sogeking.
Hm? Oh? This transponder
snail is supposed to...
I got it from Nami.
More importantly, you should find a
red cloth bundle on the ground near you.
Red cloth?
Yeah, I see it!
It's got two keys in it.
Together with your keys,
you should have all the keys.
All the keys?!
I delivered them to you without fail.
Mission accomplished.
Let's hurry. This isn't good.
#1...
#3...
#4... Doesn't work!
#5!
They came off!
Not possible! Th-They're the real keys?!
Hey, hey... Pull yourself together!
Oh, no... Does this mean...
Ahhh! You guys defeated everyone
in CP9 in the Tower of Law?!
No, that can't be true!
You must've stolen them and run! Dammit!
This is Franky! Hey, Long-nose!
I got the handcuffs off of Nico Robin.
All right!
Thank you, Long-nose!
You can thank those who fought hard
to gather the keys when this is all over.
You are, without a doubt,
one of Luffy-kun's gang!
You can now do as you wish!
Yes.
Seis... Fleurs!
What?! What's going on?!
Slap!
Whoa...
I'll do this to my heart's content.
Chief!
Okay, guys! Hurry up and get over here!
I'll get things ready for our escape!
Roger!
Come down already, Sogeking!
This is bad! The Sea Prism Stone
handcuffs are off of the criminal!
Capture her again!
Everything went according to my plan.
Hm? What's that?
Did I hear something just now?
I don't care if my body falls apart.
I'll do whatever I can do!
That's not really smart.
That technique of yours is
shortening your life, you know that?
You're too ambitious!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Robin Freed! Luffy vs. Lucci,
Showdown Between Leaders"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!