Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
"Boss Luffy Is the Culprit?
Track Down the Missing Great Cherry Tree"
Spring has come here in Grand Jipang, too.
They say one sleeps right
through the dawn in spring.
So you'd think the townspeople
must be taking it easy,
but it's not really the case.
It's finally tomorrow! With this weather,
it'll be the perfect time to view them.
Yeah, it puts me in a good mood.
On my way here, I ordered catered
box lunches from Pinwheel for my family.
What a treat!
And this is what the townspeople
are all worked up about.
Under this millennium cherry tree,
which is the pride of Grand Jipang,
they hold a huge party once a year
that everyone in town attends.
That's enough to get anyone excited.
Sounds like I can expect lots of offerings.
Even a hungry monk can get antsy.
Shut your trap.
A-Anyway, even at a time like this,
there are also those who have
more pressing matters to deal with.
Influenza? What the heck is that?
It's also called the flu...
It's a kind of infectious disease.
It's contagious, so don't go outside,
just stay in bed, okay?
What?!
Oh, no! We promised to go to the cherry
blossom viewing together tomorrow.
That's out of the question!
If he does that, he'll get worse,
and he could even die.
Oh, no... Carrot's been
looking forward to it, too.
Doc! Please do something!
You're a doctor, right?!
Don't be unreasonable.
Even a doctor can only do so much.
I'm sorry, guys.
It's my fault that I got sick.
Don't blame Dr. Bluenose.
Don't worry about me.
You guys go to the cherry
blossom viewing tomorrow.
Geez...
"We are accepting box lunch
orders for cherry blossom viewing"
Everyone's talking about the cherry
blossom viewing. How annoying!
Oh, don't say that.
Thanks to the cherry blossom viewing,
we have a flood of box lunch orders.
The millennium cherry tree is a blessing for us.
That's right.
Ha! Put yourself in my shoes.
While everyone else's out partying,
we have to patrol the town.
What're you saying?
The entire town becomes empty.
You policemen have to work hard
at a time like this. Right, Boss?
Isn't there something we can do...?
Yeah, I wonder...
I wish there was some way I could
show him the millennium cherry tree...
I wish there was some way
I could cure his disease...
What's up with those two?
Beats me. But they've been like this for a while.
No good. I can't come up
with a single good idea.
Me neither.
Hey, you two! Are you leaving?
See you later, Dr. Bluenose.
Yeah.
Hey, that's not like him, and tomorrow is
the long-awaited cherry blossom viewing day.
To think that Boss didn't finish his food...
And... the day of the cherry blossom
viewing event has come at last.
Your medicine is ready, Carrot.
What the hell is this?!
The millennium cherry tree is...
gone without a trace!
This is indeed quite mysterious.
What reason could there be
for stealing such a huge thing?
Good point. If it was about stealing money,
I'd have an idea who did it...
...but my guess is that...
...our lord is the culprit!
Our lord?!
Yeah. In order to take the
townspeople's pleasure all for himself,
he must've moved the tree
to his estate during the night!
He wouldn't do such a thing!
Seriously, I should never have asked you.
Where's Straw Hat during
an emergency like this?!
W-Well, I went to get him, but he wasn't there,
so I just assumed he was already here.
I wish there was some way I could
show him the millennium cherry tree...
The millennium cherry tree...
Don't tell me...
Hey! Is Boss here?!
Wh-What? What happened?
Well, since the cherry tree is gone,
we had a flood of box lunch order cancellations.
Thanks to the cherry tree thief,
we're taking a huge loss.
This might be the end of Pinwheel.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Hey...! Hey, got a minute?
--What is it?
--Well...
Boss is the cherry tree thief?!
Shhh! It's not like I know anything for sure yet,
but he was acting
strange yesterday, wasn't he?
Come to think of it, he wanted to
show the cherry tree to someone.
Yeah, exactly!
I haven't seen him this morning,
so my guess is...
Who'd you say was the cherry tree thief?
That damn Straw Hat!
W-Well, like I said, I don't know for sure yet!
You guys! You know what
you're supposed to do, right?!
It doesn't matter if it's the Boss or not--
just arrest the culprit and resume
the cherry blossom viewing event!
Get going!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Hey, did you find him?!
--No, no luck.
--What about Dr. Bluenose's place?
I haven't checked Doc's place yet,
but someone saw the boss
going into Carrot's house earlier,
so I'm on my way there right now.
Carrot's house?!
Yeah. It seems that he was mumbling
about cherry blossoms as he walked.
What?
♪ Cherry blossoms! La la la...
Cherry blossoms! La la la... ♪
♪ The March sky... La la la... ♪
♪ As far as the eye can see is... La la la... ♪
--♪ Hazy like a mist... ♪
--Ahhh!
Hm?
Oh, hey! What're you two doing here?
Don't "What're you two doing here" us!
Hey, Straw Hat! Where'd you
get that cherry tree branch?!
Hm? Oh, this?
Don't play dumb! Where'd you hide
the actual millennium cherry tree?!
The actual millennium cherry tree?
You just don't know when to give up, Boss.
Surely you wouldn't say the millennium
cherry tree's disappearance
has nothing to do with that branch, would you?
What?! The millennium cherry tree is missing?!
Say, Boss, you can trust me,
so just tell me the truth!
Truth? All I did was pick this up at the door.
Are you trying to talk your way out of it?!
I've lost respect for you, Boss!
I left it there in the middle of the night!
See, I told you?! "I left it there..." Huh?
You said, "I"?
I'm sorry.
After we left here,
we were thinking we really wanted to
show the millennium cherry tree to Carrot.
So Pepper, Onion, and I went
to the millennium cherry tree.
Are you okay?!
We're all right! Don't worry!
Okay, let's get this one.
I'm sorry, but please let
us have this one branch.
Someone's coming!
What?!
Both of you! Come down quickly!
We don't have time to go down!
Take that branch and go on ahead!
No! Come down already!
Don't worry! Once they go past,
we'll come back right away!
Just leave it at the door
of Carrot's house, okay?
Don't get caught.
O-Okay.
Hurry!
I see... So you left that
cherry tree branch after that.
I'm sorry.
H-H-Hold on a sec!
Then, the culprit for
stealing the cherry tree is...
There's no way it's Pepper and Onion,
and obviously it's not me, either.
So those who came later
are the true culprits, huh?
This is bad, Boss!
Before we came here, I stopped
by Pepper and Onion's houses,
but they weren't there! Which means
they're gone along with the cherry tree!
What?!
Hm?
Ahhh!
Boss!
Don't worry! Just leave it to us!
Orika! Take care of the rest, okay?
O-Okay!
Oh, hey, Dr. Bluenose!
Please take care of Carrot!
What's going on?!
Oh, Doc! Good timing! Please check on Carrot!
O-Okay!
Hey, Boss! Couldn't the information
in that letter on the arrow be fake?
No, this isn't fake!
Anyway, let's hurry to the harbor!
Wh-Wh-What's gonna happen to us?!
I'm scared!
What do you think, my foreign brother?!
I bet you've never seen such
amazing cherry blossoms before.
Isn't that right, "Silver Fox" Foxy,
collector of rare items
who travels the world and
always obtains what he desires?
Indeed, Buggy, my brother.
Its prettiness makes it a
perfect fit for my collection.
I'm sure Porche, who's waiting back in
our country, will be very pleased, too!
So this means our contract has
successfully concluded, huh?
With the money from this, I can start
my big advancement this time for sure!
Now, as promised, pay me
the 10 million Berries.
Oh, I don't have any money.
What?!
Y-Y-You don't have any money?!
Wh-Wh-What the hell are
you tryin' to pull here?!
Do you have any idea how hard we
worked to bring it here, you jerk?!
Are you saying you deceived me
when you were flat broke?!
No, no... I've got lots of money.
I'm loaded with money.
And if I sell this cherry tree to
another country, I'll get tons more money.
Thing is, I've got no money,
not even a single Berry, to give to you.
What'd you say?!
How dare you mock me so flashily?!
Guys! Prepare a Buggy Ball!
It's already ready!
You'll regret it.
Whoa!
Oh, she's...
Thanks! You sent me this letter, right?
Where's the cherry tree?
It's hiding behind that island.
The entire tree is on a big ship.
It's such a fine cherry tree.
They're probably planning to
sell it to some other country.
Fortunately, there's a river ferry
available. You should hurry there.
That's the island where the Government
is turning the surrounding sea
into reclamation ground so
that people can live there.
Right now, there's nobody there,
so it's true that it's inconspicuous, Boss.
At any rate, why don't we go there?
Thanks!
Huh?
Whoa! She's gone!
What a mysterious woman!
Well, whatever. Let's go!
What?! Hey, wait up, Boss!
Lady...
Y... o... u...
This is my power--the power
of the Slow-Slow Fruit!
This is a perfect technique to mark the
end of you idiots' lives, don't you think?
Don't worry. You'll be able
to move in 30 seconds.
Now, your precious cannon ball
will be wasted if you stay there.
Why don't you move to the center?
There, in the middle!
How... dare... you...?
Wh-What was that? What's going on?
Pepper and Onion had better be okay.
Pops, thanks! We can go on our own from here.
Oh, you will? I'm sorry I
couldn't take better care of you.
How does it feel to be
attacked by your own men?
You bastard!
You're not gonna get away
with this! Guys! Get him!
Yeah!
Morons!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Ah! Boss!
Boy, that was a surprise!
Hey, are you okay?
Boss!
Ah! Hamburg!
Hey, hey, who are you guys?!
Hm? Ah! Cherry tree!
Are you the cherry tree thief?!
What?! You sure run your mouth
for someone who broke my ship!
Who are you?!
I'm Straw Hat Luffy! I'm a policeman!
Don't resist, Split-Head!
Split-Head?
What's with him? He got depressed big time.
More importantly, Boss...
there's someone we know over there.
Hm?
Ah! Buggy! You again?!
Give us the cherry tree back!
What the heck?
What're you doing?
Thanks to my Slow-Slow Beam,
his reaction is slow, too, you moron!
Be careful, Boss! He uses weird techniques!
Pepper! Onion!
Huh?! What's with him?
He just got blown away!
I'll make you experience the same thing.
My name is Foxy! I obtain whatever I desire.
Don't stand in my way, you lowly policeman!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Ah! Boss!
I don't care if you're a
policeman or a diseased man--
it's a thousand years
too soon to go against me!
In any case, looks like a bunch
of nuisances got on board.
I guess I'll get rid of them
all at once with a cannon.
I'm not gonna let him!
Boss...
How noisy...
Geez...! I can't even sleep in.
--Mr. Monk!
--Is it morning already?
Oh, yeah, today's the
cherry blossom viewing day.
Hey, where the hell am I?! What's going on?!
What're you doing there?
We got kidnapped along with the
cherry tree in the middle of the night.
This is no time for cherry blossom viewing.
What?! Then what about the
offerings?! What about food?!
Give us the cherry tree back!
Why would I?!
He stopped in the air!
Dammit!
Special Attack! Exploding Star!
Here you go!
Didn't work! Dammit!
Hey, are you the one...
...who ruined the cherry blossom viewing event?
Geez... There's no end to these guys...
Enough already!
That's exactly what I wanna say to you!
Gum-Gum...
Hm? It's been 30 seconds?
I'm not gonna let him get away!
Double Slow-Slow Beam!
Chop-Chop Festi...
He repelled it with his sword!
Oh?
How dare you take away what
everyone was looking forward to?!
I'm definitely not gonna forgive you!
I'm the one who won't forgive you!
How dare you do such a terrible thing to me?!
Don't yell so much. It'll come back soon.
What'll come back?!
My right hand.
Ahh!
...Billy Club!
Whoa! He sure went flying pretty far!
So, Boss, what do you wanna do with this one?
You're such an idiot.
What'd you come out for this time?
Come back when you get a clue!
Gum-Gum...
Billy Club Bodhisattva!
Okay, then, shall we go back?
Yeah.
You're coming to view the cherry
blossoms too, right, Mr. Monk?
Yeah.
Good job, guys!
This is strange. Theoretically, it should work.
Carrot! Carrot!
Carrot!
Hey!
Ah...!
Ah!
Hey! We brought the millennium cherry tree!
Isn't this incredible?!
Take a look at this and cheer up!
Let's play together soon!
You dummies!
You guys worried me!
Here you go! Thanks!
There! There! Heave ho!
Thank you! I'll get better soon!
Oh... he's fine.
I wonder if the medicine
finally started working...
No... This must also be
a form of medical science.
I thought I was able to meet a man
with some backbone. How disappointing.
Did you run out of strength
from your doping earlier?
If it's backbone you want,
I'll show you... another tactic!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Can't Protect Anyone Unless I Win!
Third Gear Activated!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!