Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Are you insane?! Don't think
that you'll be able to survive
after making the entire world your enemy!
I'll pursue that woman to the very
ends of the earth and eliminate her...
I want to live!
...Jet... Gatling!
Luffy!
Luffy...!
The first column is...!
Th-This is a report to all ships.
This is a report to all ships!
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9 has just...
Has just been defeated...
by pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy...
It's over...
We'll be okay now.
We're gonna go back together!
Robin!
"From the Sea, a Friend Arrives!
The Straw Hats Share the Strongest Bond"
Th...
Th-This can't be happening!
Mr. Rob Lucci, the leader of
the current CP9, is considered
to be the strongest in the history of Cipher Pol.
To think that even he has
been defeated by a pirate...!
Luffy won!
Coo, coo, coo...
Coo, coo.
He had me worried there.
So you finally did it, Straw Hat!
Luffy!
Everyone! Get on the escape ship
right away! We're gonna set sail!
You did it! Luffy!
You did it, Straw Hat!
Hm?
Y-You morons! They can hear us!
That's okay! We'll let him know!
Hey! Who're those voices?!
We don't know! They're coming
from somewhere via transponder snail!
Bro!
What?! This voice...
Stop it! If we had just taken off,
we would've been considered dead!
You guys...
Those guys...
Are they possibly the pirates
we took out at the main gate?
Well, they can't be...
I'm sure they all fell off the cliff!
There's no way they could've survived.
Dammit! It's a cannon attack!
Bro!
Hey, idiot! Don't push!
Don't move!
--We're gonna fall!
--The ropes are gonna rip!
You morons! Galley-La's ropes never tear!
Seriously, after I told you
to keep your mouth shut...
We're all okay!
The giants took all the cannon fire for us!
Ribbit!
Whoa! They sure are tough.
Grandma! They're all alive!
Sodom and Gomorrah are okay, too!
I'm so glad to hear that!
Now, if we take our sweet time here,
the battleships will come again!
Let's hurry up and get out of here!
Anyway... we have a means to escape,
so don't worry about us!
We'll see you after we
make it out of here alive!
That's right!
Let's hurry!
You guys need to hurry up and climb already!
The blood is rushing up to my head!
Actually, it's rushing down!
Okay, climb up!
Climb up slowly!
We're gonna fall!
--Ribbit!
--Don't shake!
You guys...! Dummies...!
I wasn't worried about you guys! You dummies!
Those idiots are alive!
I'm glad...! I'm glad! I'm so happy!
Yeah. It's really a relief.
But there's no point if you die here, is there?
Yeah. You're right.
Should we head over to
the main gate right away?!
Do it later. Right now, we have
to focus our efforts here.
What're you all doing?!
Carry out your duty already!
Yes, sir!
Hey! Bring on as many guys as you'd like!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Tiger Trap!
Oni Giri!
Pound Phoenix!
Cien Fleurs!
Keep an eye on Straw Hat in the first column!
Y-Yes, sir, but...
Hm?
Pirate Straw Hat Luffy also
appears to be severely wounded!
He isn't moving at all!
What?!
Hey, Luffy!
What're you doing?! Hurry up
and get your butt over here!
We have to run or we won't survive!
What's the matter! We're almost there!
Use your Gum-Gum to shoot yourself over here!
Once you're here, I'll carry you!
We're surrounded by the sea
and a bunch of battleships!
If we stay here, we're gonna be killed!
It seems that the pirates are trying
to escape using the escort ship.
Yeah.
Luffy!
Luffy! Can you hear me, Luffy?!
I-I can't...
My body...
What?
...isn't moving at all.
It isn't moving...?
Don't be ridiculous! You defeated the enemy!
We got Robin back, too!
All that's left is for us to go back!
Please! Try hard!
Usopp!
Let's take the ship to
the column where Luffy is!
Everyone! Hurry up and get on the ship!
Fire!
No! Our escape ship is...!
Oh, crap...! Now it's hopeless...
Besides that ship, there's no other
way for us to escape from here!
Kokoro-san... Chimney... Gonbe... Chopper!
O-Oh, no...
I'm gonna die!
They're okay somehow!
Outta our way!
Good!
Sanji-kun! Where on earth have you been?!
Well, sorry about that.
I had to take care of something.
But at any rate, this is terrible.
We're in serious trouble!
Since we have Robin-chan,
I thought they weren't gonna
attack this area. But the ship was...
That's it, you bastards!
Release the old lady now and...
This is no time for that!
Mermaid Kick!
Fire.
They're even firing on their own people!
Corner them at the second column!
Fire!
Watch out! Run! Run!
Dammit! They've finally
taken out the entire bridge!
We're cornered on this column!
We're out of options!
We have no choice but to
fight them all from here!
Don't be stupid! There's gonna be
wave after wave of stronger guys!
Prepare all cannons to fire on the first column!
Eliminate Straw Hat Luffy immediately!
Luffy!
Luffy's in danger! We have
to at least bring him over!
Oh, crap...!
Luffy!
It won't work. Because of the distance,
even if I try to pull him,
I'll drop him into the sea.
Luffy!
This is bad. Things are in a terrible state!
Straw Hat won, but he can't stand up!
It seems like his life is in danger!
What?!
--Straw Hat!
Ribbit! Ribbit!
Stand up, Straw Hat!
Get ahold of yourself, kid!
Pirate guy!
Luffy! Stand up! Please!
Isn't there something you can do, Luffy?!
Luffy!
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat! You can do it!
Ribbit, ribbit!
Oh, crap... I'm seriously in trouble...!
Luffy!
Do something, Luffy!
Straw Hat!
Get ahold of yourself, Straw Hat!
Again...!
Who is that?!
Hey! Do you wanna get killed?!
This is no time to be spacing out!
Just whose voice is this?
Th-That's right! This is the
same voice from that time...
What's going on?!
--Straw Hat!
It's obvious! My underlings are...
No! Not those voices!
I've been hearing it for a while!
Huh?!
Below...?
Look below?
I'm not mistaken. I can hear it. What? Below?
Who's that?!
What the hell is this?
It's telling us to look below!
What're you talking about, reindeer?
In five seconds, fire at Straw Hat
Luffy in the first column!
--Luffy is gonna...!
--Straw Hat!
You're such a... Really, you're such a...
Jump into the sea!
Four seconds!
Into the sea!
Usopp?!
Robin! Can you drop Luffy into the sea?
--Leave it to me!
--You idiot! Are you trying
to get us to commit suicide?!
Getting desperate won't save us!
Three!
We're gonna be saved!
She came to rescue us!
We've got one more friend, right?!
Two!
Chopper! Did you look below?!
I did!
Cien Fleurs!
One!
Delphinium!
I'm moving! Is Robin doing this?!
Into the sea!
Into the sea...!
Follow Luffy!
Here we go!
Here we go...!
Into the sea!
The pirates are jumping into the sea!
How stupid! There's no way that they
can survive after jumping into this sea.
Did the pirates lose their minds?!
Let's go back, everyone!
Fire!
Back to the seas of adventure!
Get on the Merry!
Merry!
I came to get you!
I have been alone all this time.
To think that what Saul said came true...
Friends...
I appreciate them for rescuing me
from the bottom of my heart.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Everyone Makes a Great Escape!
The Road to Victory Is for the Pirates"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!