Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
"Witch of Cocoyashi Village!
Arlong's Female Leader"
What's this guy saying?
Let go.
I told you, that's mine!
Say what?! Who decided that?!
I took it myself and put it on my
own plate, so of course it's mine!
Oh. Really? Then you should've said so!
And I was saving that for last, too!
Okay, I'm sorry! You can have this!
You know I can't eat that!
I'm not a dog, you know!
Quiet!
Something's down there...
It's big...
What's that?
A sea monster!
It's a cow! It's huge!
A cow? They don't swim. It's a hippo.
What's something like this
doing in the East Blue?!
This is a Grand Line creature!
Huh? What's this guy doing?
--He's after the food!
--What?!
Hurry and give it to him!
He'll flip the boat over!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Stay away from my food!
You did it! You're incredible,
Big Bro Luffy!
Looks like you made it mad!
--Another one, huh?!
--You dumbass!
Don't beat up someone
who's hungry for no reason!
He's probably hurt or something
and can't catch his own food.
Right?
What love...
Here, eat up. No need to hold back.
Die, you damn thing!
What're you doing?!
What happened to that love?!
The bastard just tried to eat me, too.
Here he comes!
He's gonna sink the boat!
--That jerk!
--Get back. I'll do it.
Collier Shoot!
Damn hippo...
Alright! Back to food!
That was good exercise.
These guys are crazy...
W-Where am I?
My house.
--You awake?
--W-Who are you?!
I'm Nojiko. I grow tangerines here.
That's right! You thwacked me!
Just when I was trying
to save you, too!
I'm the one who saved you.
Had you done anything to that fishman,
there's no question
you would've been killed.
This is why I hate outsiders!
But you're a kid from Gosa, right?
Surely you know all too well
from firsthand experience
that you'll be killed if
you mess with the fishmen.
I know!
I know, but... they killed my daddy!
They stole everything,
destroyed our town,
and killed tons of people!
They have to pay!
No matter what, they have to pay!
So I went to Arlong Park!
But a girl on his side got in the way!
She... was like a witch!
I hate this! I don't care if I die;
I'm going to avenge my daddy!
Then die.
If you're prepared to die,
then go get your revenge!
But know this much.
Now that me and that witch
at Arlong Park have stopped you,
you've escaped death twice now!
Leave when you're done with your tea.
Hey! Isn't that being
a little harsh on the kid?!
Kid or not, if someone wants to die,
then just let 'em die!
He doesn't have the guts to live
through hard times anyway!
Say what?!
I know a kid who's staring
fixedly at the distant future
while she endures a life
more painful than death.
That's why I hate people like him
who consider death right off the bat!
What... should I do?
I hate this! I'll endure it!
What should I do?!
What about your mom?
She's alive...
She's worried about you. Go back to her.
Okay...
You're actually a nice person!
Even though you have tattoos...
Prejudice!
I don't know anything
about you, you know...
Oh, right!
My name is Captain Usopp!
I'm looking for a girl named Nami...
Nami?!
You know her?
What?! Nami's a leader
of the Arlong Pirates?!
Yep. She's infamous in this area.
Even that little boy said
she seemed like a witch.
Even more surprising, that witch
grew up in this very house!
Me and Nami are adopted sisters.
So this is...
...Nami's house?!
Me and Nami are both orphans.
We were brought up in this house.
Our foster parent is dead, too,
but the three of us used to live
happily here in Cocoyashi Village.
Then... Nami betrayed her own
parent and fellow villagers
and joined Arlong's group?!
Yeah, pretty much. A real witch, huh?
Damn it! So that's the deal?!
So she had us fooled the entire time!
She was after treasure
from the very start!
Even after she helped
fight to protect my village
and smiled so happily aboard our ship!
Oh? Happily?
Her?
We came here to
bring her back with us,
but I guess there's no need for--
That reminds me, a friend
of ours was unlucky enough
to be caught by the fishmen...
This is bad... I wonder
how the guy's holding up...
Well? Now do you see?
I was only using you guys
from the very start.
You had some decent skill, and you
were good suckers worth using.
So you had them completely fooled!
This girl's like a cold-blooded witch--
she'll even forget about her
own parent's death for money!
Just chalk it up to bad luck
that you crossed her and give up.
I see.
Though it's not like I ever
trusted her to begin with.
Even if she were a homicidal maniac,
I wouldn't be too surprised.
In that case, could you get the hell
out of here?! You're an eyesore!
What happened?! Why'd he
suddenly jump into the water?!
Is someone pulling
some kinda lame joke?
No, it's not like he slipped or anything...
Then he ran away!
No, his arms and legs're tied!
He can't swim like that!
It's a suicide!
Leave him be.
Can't believe he'd kill himself...
He was terrifyingly good at giving up!
It's like, damn, value your life more!
T-That idiot!
--He's back up!
--Hey! What's going on, Nami?!
What do you think you're doing?!
No, what do you think you're doing?!
You're just a small fry who
can't even watch one guy die...
Quit tryin' to act cool!
Save me sooner next time, you idiot!
I thought I was gonna die!
Screw you!
Mess with me any more
and you will die!
I wonder.
That's a lot of bandages you have.
Didn't have a change of clothes,
so I used these instead.
Hey, Nami.
What should we do with him?
Lock him up! I'll deal with him myself!
Arlong-san! Arlong-san!
What is it, brother?
I'm sorry! That guy had a long-nosed
friend with him, but he got away!
What the hell, Usopp?!
You wound up getting spotted anyway?!
I think he might've escaped
into Cocoyashi Village...
Cocoyashi Village, huh?
Perfect. I have other
business there, too.
Guess I'll head out for a bit.
Hey! Arlong's coming!
What?! What for?! We just
paid our tribute money to him!
It's probably about the
weapons of mine they found...
Return to your houses, everyone.
Gen-san...
They're here!
So you're the bastard who
was in possession of weapons...
Yes. That's right...
Because I've always
enjoyed looking at weapons.
Are collections not allowed
under your rule, either?
No, I can't have that.
Weapons breed nothing
but evil thoughts and violence.
They're the chief things
that undermine peace.
He's huge! That's Arlong?!
H-He's not human!
--Nope. Because he's a fishman.
--Yeah...
I control 20 towns and villages.
As their manager,
I can't afford to have rebellions.
I destroyed the great port town
of Gosa as an example
to the other communities!
The blunder of being
unable to pay tribute money
is an act of rebellion against us!
Hey! Tribute money?
Exactly as it sounds.
It's money that we offer to them.
We buy our lives
every month with money.
Adults and kids...
If anyone in a village can't
pay the tribute money...
If there's even just one person...
...the village gets
wiped out just like Gosa.
Then that huge town was destroyed
just because of one person?!
That's how Arlong governs.
They're species-obsessed and don't
give a damn about killing people.
Listen. You lowly humans simply need
to keep paying up without thinking!
I need enormous funds!
Your tribute money will
eventually become the cornerstone
of the Arlong Empire,
which will rule the East Blue!
A-Arlong Empire?!
They're planning to turn the entire
East Blue into a fishman empire?!
Hurry and escape.
Before Arlong comes back.
Gen-san!
The possession of weapons
is a clear sign of rebellion!
To keep any more rebels
like you from showing up,
I'm going to kill you right now,
as an example to the other humans!
No way! He'll kill someone
just for having a weapon?!
--He has no right...
--H-H-Hey, you!
You have no right to do this, Arlong!
For these past eight years straight,
we've paid you your tribute money!
Why would we want
to rebel now, of all times?!
Take your hands off Gen-san!
Yeah!
It's not like he used any weapons!
--Stop this!
--Let Gen-san go!
I'm saying that the possession of
weapons indicates the will to rebel.
Or what? Shall the entire
village be destroyed?
If just one of you lays a hand on us,
your village will meet its demise.
Either way is fine with me!
Get inside, everyone!
If we cause trouble now, the last
eight years will be for nothing!
If you're going to fight to
the death to defy his rule,
then you should've done so
eight years ago instead!
But we all swore to fight
the patient fight! To live!
--Gen-san!
--But...
What a valuable opinion!
You're a great speaker!
Yes! Being alive is enjoyable!
Even for puny insects like you!
Gen-san!
Not all living things are born equal!
--Damn you!
--Stop!
Don't do anything!
B-But, Gen-san!
If you die, it's all over!
Don't stop fighting the patient fight!
Even if I die!
That's nice resolve!
Pay close attention, humans!
This is what happens to those who
have even a sliver of evil thoughts!
Exploding Star!
W-What was that?!
Look! Up there!
There's someone on the roof!
Who the hell are you?!
My name is Captain Usopp,
Brave Warrior of the Sea!
Him!
T-The world fears me
and calls me Demon King Usopp,
the man from the Netherworld!
If you run away now, I'll forgive you!
--I have 8,000...
--Arlong-san! That's him!
--The guy who got away earlier!
--Eep.
Bring all the tens of
thousands of men you want.
I'll tear apart every last one!
He's not scared, and the
Exploding Star had no effect!
What has a human...
...a mere, lowly human... done to me?!
Arlong-san! Wait!
We'll lose another source
of tribute money, after Gosa!
Human settlements are easy to destroy,
but our goal is to rule them!
If we lose some,
we can just get some more!
We are the supreme species!
Now he's destroying the village!
Is he--
Whoa! I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
--H-He's still alive! After 'im!
--Crap!
Catch him and kill him!
Hey! Let's get back to Arlong Park!
He's seriously about
to destroy the village!
Yeah!
Do not let him get away!
Who does he take us for?!
We'll be back another day.
Looks like you're spared for now!
I'm sorry... I caused you all trouble...
What are you talking about?
You're not at fault here!
--Yeah!
--But who was that youngster earlier?
Everyone! It's good to see you again!
--Nami!
--It's Nacchan!
--It's her!
What's going on? You never walk
right through the village...
I heard a loud sound...
Arlong, huh?
Just seven million Berries left to go...
You have as horrible
a reputation as ever.
That's fine. I am a pirate!
But Arlong's a reasonable guy.
Money will fix all this, so it's just
a little more until our agreement.
No matter what, I'm going
to earn 100 million Berries
and buy this village!
She tells me to run, but I got
nowhere else to go but here...
Plus I promised Luffy I'd bring her back.
What's he up to now?
Things're starting to get messy.
Yahoo! So fast! So fast!
Big Bro Luffy! I see it! Arlong Park!
Go! To Arlong Park!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Hey! Luffy!
Why're you flying here in a boat?!
'Cause I was in a hurry!
That's not what I meant!
What the hell are you doing?!
I'm here to get Nami back!
Have you still not found her?
About that... it's a long story.
That reminds me, where's Long-nose?
Crap! He's been caught by Arlong!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Usopp Dead?! When is Luffy
Going to Make Landfall?"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!