Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Ah! Zoro! Sanji!
We've got trouble!
Your grandpa is back, Luffy!
They're at the opposite seashore.
They're looking for us now!
They're going to attack us!
What?! Why?! I thought he said
he wasn't gonna capture us.
How would we know?!
Hurry up and get ready to set sail!
I'm giving this back!
Now, come on board, Franky...
Board my ship.
Don't be so cocky!
You guys are total amateurs who
could only manage makeshift repairs!
It'd be a pity for such a magnificent ship
not to have a shipwright on board.
I guess I don't have much choice
but to help you guys out!
I, Franky, will be the shipwright on your ship!
"Departing the City of Water!
Usopp Mans Up and Brings Closure to the Duel!"
Vice Admiral Garp!
Hm?
We've found the Straw Hats!
They're on the scrap heap island at
the southeast seashore, about to set sail!
We're gonna head there right away!
Get on board immediately!
Yes, sir!
"Navy"
Vice Admiral Garp! We lightheartedly
parted with Luffy-san and the others.
This is quite embarrassing!
If you wanna complain, talk to Sengoku!
He's the one who chewed me out
and made me come back here!
How bossy of him.
That's because you said,
"It's my grandson, so..."
on the transponder snail.
Shut up! Mind your own
business, you greenhorn.
A-Admiral, what about you?
Is it okay for you to be here?
It's a lot of work going back by bike.
Well, don't worry. I won't do anything.
Er... I think that also can be a
problem when facing our enemy.
Set sail!
Bro! Take good care of yourself!
The Franky Family will live on forever!
Straw Hats! You guys take care, too!
Hey, Luffy!
Luffy!
Are you really sure you don't have to
wait for one more person, Straw Hat?
I did wait. Ever since I heard what Sanji told us,
I tried so that our room at
Galley-La wouldn't be empty.
What? Usopp is coming back?!
Yeah. He was by himself rehearsing
how he'd rejoin us at the seashore.
Really?! So he really wants to come back.
Then let's go get him right away!
Yeah!
He's always gotta do things the hard way.
Usopp is coming back!
Hold it, you guys!
I won't allow any of us to go get him.
What? Why?
Whatever you do, don't assume a
subservient attitude towards him, Luffy.
Zoro...
I'm not gonna accept him
until he apologizes first.
--Zoro! Why?!
--Hey! Who are you to decide...
Shut up!
No matter what feelings were involved
in Luffy and Usopp's first argument,
or no matter who the right one is...
...once a man decides to fight a duel,
the outcome of the duel decides that argument.
It's true that the ship
belongs to you, the captain.
So fight me...
If I win, I'll take the Merry.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Fight a duel with me!
He lost...
...and walked out on us on his own.
Now, listen, you guys. He might be
an idiot, but he's still our captain.
If Usopp can't treat him with
respect when things are critical,
we're better off not having him in our gang.
If a captain stops commanding respect,
his gang will fall apart without fail.
Listen! I don't care if you
want to act happy-go-lucky,
but if you, the man who is above me,
ever shows weakness,
next time, the one leaving the gang will be me!
What?!
Hey, that won't solve anything!
It's good that that idiot
now wants to come back.
But...
...if he tries to fudge on this issue
without taking any responsibility,
I won't accept that no matter what!
If that happens, we'll leave him on this island.
What?
Hold on, Zoro. It's true that
his actions weren't appropriate,
but we can give him a good
talking-to once he comes ba...
Is leaving the gang such a trivial matter?!
No.
But...
Nami-san.
Unfortunately, this time,
what he's saying is correct.
There's no way we can trust a man
who'd do such a thing on impulse.
Here is what it boils down to.
If the first words coming from Usopp are
a sincere apology, then we're all good.
Otherwise, there's no place
here for him to come back to.
We're not little kids playing pirates.
Do what you want with the Merry.
We'll get a new ship and
move on to the seas ahead!
Well then, bye, Usopp...
It's been fun.
You're right.
We went our separate ways.
We still have several days before the
ship gets completed and we set sail.
Let's just stay here and wait for him.
I waited for him there all this time,
but he didn't come.
That's his answer.
Straw Hat...
I'm sure... he'll have a fun life, too.
He probably won't quit being a pirate,
so I hope I'll see him some day on the sea!
All right! I'm gonna go back to my friends!
We've got a magnificent ship!
They're all waiting for me!
The question is, how will I rejoin them naturally?
Well, no matter how they act,
I've got 100 strategies!
The strong candidate for my first
words has to be these, after all.
"If you're begging me so
much that you're in tears,
I suppose I can come back if
you make me Vice Captain."
"Thank you, Vice Captain Usopp! Yay!"
"We'll do whatever you tell us, so please
come back." They might say that!
I'm so good!
I'm the very example of a man who
turns even his mistakes to good use!
In this adverse situation, I'll further
endear myself to them and live happily.
Okay! I'd better hurry up!
I'd love to stay, but goodbye,
Water Seven, the City of Water!
Usopp...
Luffy, let's wait a little longer.
We're not in a rush or anything.
Hey, Luffy!
What was that?!
Dammit! They found us! It's the Navy!
Grandpa?!
It's Vice Admiral Garp's battleship!
Bro! Straw Hat! Get out of here!
Hey, Luffy! Can you hear me?!
This is Grandpa! This is Grandpa!
If you can hear me, say something!
Hey, Grandpa! What're you doing?!
You said you weren't gonna capture us here!
Well, the thing is, a lot
has happened since then.
Sorry, but I'm gonna send you
to the bottom of the sea!
What?!
Well, I'm not doing this as an
apology for that or anything,
but I'll fight your gang all by myself!
Give me a cannonball.
H-Here you go, sir.
What's he trying to do?
Meteor... Fist!
Whoa! H-He fired a cannonball
with his bare hand!
That came flying at us with more
power than the ones fired by cannon!
It's not like he was just throwing a baseball!
My power's been declining lately.
We have no choice!
We're getting out of here for now!
Or our new ship will be blasted to bits!
Bring 1,000 cannonballs to me!
Yes, sir!
Hurry!
This isn't good! A whole bunch of those
things are about to come flying at us!
Meteor Fist Shower!
Oh, boy... Against that,
no ship would stand a chance.
Now, let's get started, shall we, lads?
Don't think that you can
run from me! Be prepared!
Full speed ahead!
We'll take care of the cannonballs!
Got it!
Dammit! Is he really not coming?
What's he doing?
He's here!
Usopp's here!
Hey, everyone! Usopp's here!
Really?
Yep!
Out of my way! Out of my way!
S-Sorry! L-Let me through!
Hey, nose guy! What're you doing here?!
What?
Wh-What's going on?
Why are they setting sail
just because the Navy's here?
I just assumed that you were on the ship.
What're you guys doing?! I'm still right here!
Why? Why? Why?!
When we fought together
even after our argument?!
Sogeking.
Hm?
Shoot through that flag.
Roger.
This is my new weapon,
a huge slingshot... named Kabuto!
Have a good look at its power!
Special Attack... Firebird Star!
--Hm?
--That's...
Snap!
You are a sword!
Someone get me a lawyer!
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
I'm the one who fought outstandingly
as that king of snipers, Sogeking!
You gave up on me because I disappeared?!
Wait!
Hey! The stairs are broken! Be careful!
What's wrong?! Hey!
Hey! Guys! No more worries!
I'm back for you guys!
You jerks...
Stop...!
Gum-Gum... Balloon!
Usopp's coming, Luffy! Usopp's coming!
Protect the ship!
Hey! Rejoice! It's me!
Chopper! It's a fine day today! Let's go fishing!
Well, I guess this is no time for that, huh?!
Oh, yeah, I've got good news!
Believe it or not, when I'm back,
I don't mind becoming your Vice Captain!
What do you think? Well?!
Hey, Luffy! Guys!
I know!
You guys're crying with joy over there, right?!
Hey, you are, aren't you?!
Luffy! I can't go along with you anymore.
Sorry to cause you trouble until the end.
Don't tell me you actually
believed that joke I made!
We've been friends for so long!
There's no way I'd say
something like that seriously!
Although we said all sorts of things
to each other, we're friends!
I'll let these little things go!
Now, hey!
Say something!
Enough already, you jerks!
Luffy! Usopp's talking to us!
I can't hear it.
Zoro!
I can't hear anything!
That's a lie! I know you can hear it!
Stop... joking.
So that's how it is.
So you really are trying to part with me?
I see... Fine, then.
Listen, Luffy! It's not like everyone
can live looking ahead like you do!
I can't just leave our wounded friend
here and move on to the seas ahead!
Go ahead and cut off useless friends
one after another and move on.
I've been thinking about this for a while.
To be honest,
I've been thinking that I can't keep
up with your monstrous strength.
You don't need weak friends, right?
Luffy... you're the man
who'll be king of the pirates.
But I don't have to go that high up.
Thinking back, when I was about to sail out,
you guys asked me to join you.
That's all that's tying us together.
We don't have to travel together
when we have a difference of opinion!
If that's what you want...
...let me say one last thing. You guys...
Where I'm going is my own business.
It has nothing to do with you guys anymore.
I'm...
...leaving the gang.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for being bullheaded!
I was wrong!
Usopp!
I know I'm being pathetic.
I know I said I was leaving the gang.
But... is there any chance
that I can take that back?!
Can I?!
Please!
Please let me...
...stay with you!
One more time...
...let me join you guys!
Luffy...
You idiot! Grab my hand already!
You're the one who's an idiot!
You guys are so lame!
Everyone's finally on board!
We're gonna hurry up and get
through this cannonball attack
so that we can get on with our adventure, guys!
Yeah!
Say, Chopper. We finally have a bounty, too.
Like I said, I can't accept that!
50...? 50...?
Nojiko, Gen-san, and everyone
in Cocoyashi Village...
I wonder how they'll feel when they see this...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Wanted Posters Make It Around the World!
Celebration in Their Hometowns
as the Ship Moves Forward!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!