Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
The bounty hunters have left
to hunt the Straw Hat Pirates,
who have fallen for their trap.
A total bounty of 600 million Berries, eh?
I can't wait to see their Jolly Roger!
Why don't we celebrate early?
May our beloved Papa, Don Accino,
and the Accino Family's knit
blood relations be blessed!
And here's to our present for Papa--
the heads of the Straw Hat Pirates.
Cheers!
"The Dream Sinking in the New World!
The Disillusioned Pirate, Puzzle"
The icebergs moved?!
Are you morons?
Freezing!
It's only natural for icebergs to move.
Water moves!
Perhaps that's not quite what they meant.
Right.
They aren't moving because of the currents.
They're moving of their own accord!
Of their own accord?
Hey, don't give us this crap
first thing in the morning!
Watch and see!
Sanji-kun, if you please.
Okay!
Wh-What the heck?!
Once more!
For chunks of ice, they're bossy punks!
It's just a mass of ice.
But it definitely moved to block our path...
The iceberg itself seems normal enough.
There were also those
Marine ships last night.
It feels like something is
trying to lure us somewhere.
I have no idea who it is,
but they've got guts!
Let's duke it out!
But first we have to figure out
who exactly is behind this.
Vigaro...
Wait...!
Puzzle-san?
Vigaro...!
Vigaro...
Vigaro!
Ow...
What is it?
What happened?
Puzzle-san...!
Puzzle-san is...!
Ow...
Puzzle-san...
Thank goodness!
Thank you, Doctor!
You really are a great physician!
I-I'm not happy about getting called a
"great physician" or anything, you punk!
Jiro, what am I doing here?
Don't you remember, Captain?
We were attacked by some really
strong guys in the New World...
What the hell?!
Who are those guys?!
Put out the fire!
Don't drag your feet!
Please help me!
How is an attack like that even possible?!
Hurry and carry the injured!
Retreat!
Get us out of here as fast as possible!
We still weren't ready... for the New World!
What's gotten into you?
It's not like Puzzle the
Phoenix to sound defeated...
I'm not a phoenix!
I'm just a whippersnapper
that got in over my head.
Listen to me, Puzzle.
We've followed you because we believe in you.
That's because--
It's no use, Captain!
They're too fast!
Puzzle, I'll buy some time!
Stansen, bring out the raiding dory!
First Officer!
Hurry!
R-Right!
Wait, Vigaro!
I'm going with you!
Idiot!
You can't leave the ship!
You're the captain!
But...!
Puzzle, I believe in you.
You are the man who will
become the King of the Pirates!
Hey, Vigaro!
Wait!
Captain, here it comes again!
M-Meteors?!
Vigaro!
Even First Officer Vigaro didn't last more
than a few seconds up against them...
But during that brief period of time,
he managed to destroy their rudder.
Thanks to him, we were able to escape...
That's why everyone who
survived swore an oath!
We should be like our first officer
and protect the captain with our lives!
You're absolutely right, Jiro!
I'd be willing to lay down
my life for Puzzle-san.
Same here!
Let's protect the captain!
Yeah!
Let's do it!
Sounds good.
I'm going to the New World!
But then Stansen-san...
Why do you think Vigaro was willing
to sacrifice his life to protect yours?
Don't you dare throw your life away!
You're working for a group
of bounty hunters...?
It's true that they're incredibly strong
and we were a mess after the New World...
I can understand why we lost,
but then they stole our Jolly Roger...
our pride as the Phoenix Pirates....
How could he...?
Stansen-san is a coward!
But that's all coming to an end today!
Puzzle the Phoenix has risen once more!
Puzzle-san!
Don't push yourself!
It's okay.
I feel fine now...
Gather the whole crew up on the deck.
Aye, Captain!
The captain has regained consciousness!
Hey, is that true?!
The day we've been
dying for has finally arrived!
This is the revival of the Phoenix Pirates!
Now that damn Stansen will
get what's coming to him!
Puzzle-san!
Men, I'm sorry to have put you out.
It was nothing!
Imagining today made it easy!
Puzzle-san, I'm glad you're okay!
Let's go, Chopper.
Uh-huh.
Puzzle-san!
Dr. Chopper!
Luffy-san!
Thank you so much.
It was nothing.
I only did what any doctor would do.
I'll be sure to pay you back someday!
Next time we meet will
be in the New World, huh?
That's right!
You were also headed for
the New World, weren't you?
Then that means we'll be
rivals from here on out!
I can barely wait!
Captain, we need to hop to
it and build up our forces
so we can return to the New World...
Captain?
Hey?
Puzzle-san?
We...
aren't going back to the New World.
No...
Stansen's decision was right.
We're going to continue working
for those bounty hunters.
No way!
Why?
Why?!
H-Have you lost your mind, Puzzle-san?!
Everyone is willing to fight to
the death, just like Vigaro-san!
That's right...
Vigaro died... all for me.
Puzzle, I believe in you.
You are the man who will
become the King of the Pirates!
But we have you on our side, Puzzle-san!
We've been waiting this whole time
for the Phoenix to rise from the ashes!
What happened to Puzzle the Phoenix?!
The Phoenix...
only existed
in the world of fairytales.
I have no right to go to the New World
when I couldn't protect my crew!
How could you say that, Captain...?
I can't accept that...
Our flag...
What about the Jolly Roger
they stole from us?!
We don't need a Jolly Roger anymore.
Damn it!
Have you lost all sense of pride?!
Hey, Luffy...!
Hey, wait!
I'd love to thank you for tending to me,
but I'm afraid we lost
everything in the New World.
Those waters...
The New World isn't as
forgiving as you think.
That's okay.
I'll find out when I get there.
Besides, we're strong!
That's okay.
I'll find out when I get there.
Besides, we're strong!
Don't take the New World lightly, Puzzle.
Don't worry, Vigaro! I'm a phoenix!
I see.
Then do as you please.
Jiro...
Let's go, Chopper.
But...
He's given up on their Jolly Roger.
They aren't pirates anymore.
R... Right...
Goodness!
Luffy!
Chopper!
They'll be fine without us!
Guys, take care of the ship!
You can count on me!
We're going to swerve around to the right!
'Kay!
Hard a-starboard!
Bad move!
Turn us around!
To the left!
Stop!
The icebergs are gathering together.
Hey, Sanji!
Where do you think you're taking us?!
Damn it!
The rudder's not responding.
No, look over there!
When the waterways got blocked,
it created those whirlpools.
What is with these waters?!
Th-That's...!
I wanna turn that into
shaved ice and gobble it up!
Shaved ice?!
It's huge!
Looks good!
This isn't the time for that!
I'll be back in just a sec!
Gum-Gum...
Gatling!
He's a Devil Fruit power holder?
And...
It's a waste of time.
Battle Axe!
My shaved ice...!
The Sunny is gone!
This is the Arctic Path.
Any ship that wanders in never
sees the open ocean again.
There is no mistaking him!
That's Puzzle the Phoenix,
with a bounty of 100 million Berries.
Wasn't he supposed to be dead?
We've been had!
That Stansen guy tricked us.
Straw Hat Luffy,
a 300-million-Berry bounty, is with him,
bringing them to a total
of 400 million Berries.
This is turning into something else!
Let's hurry and inform Blend-sama!
Puzzle the Phoenix is still alive?
How dare the fallen pirates
deceive the Accino Family?!
They've got some nerve!
Siblings, we can add another present
to the list for our beloved Papa!
I'm going to check on it right quick.
You may handle things here!
Jerk!
How dare you take advantage of the
confusion to grab onto Nami-san?!
Why are you using the paddle wheel?
Franky, where have you been?
I was fully charging the cola
barrels in the energy room.
If my guess is right, there will definitely
come a time when we need them.
At any rate, if we're ever going
to get out of these crazy waters...
...first we've got to unravel the
puzzle behind the moving icebergs!
There has to be some sort of trick.
That doesn't mean squat to us!
It doesn't?!
It'd be a cinch for us
to get out of this place!
Oh, yeah!
We finally found you!
Dearies, now that you've
wandered into the Arctic Path,
you'll never get to see
the open ocean ever again.
Say your prayers!
I have to agree!
Don't you?
We always see eye-to-eye, don't we?
They're stifling.
That beautiful lady is
with such a hideous man!
Hey, you there!
I challenge you to a duel right here--
I'm afraid we don't have
time to play with you.
Yeah.
It's about time we took our leave.
You sure are dense!
We were just telling you
that there is no escape!
None at all!
In other words, it's impossible!
Nice!
That expression was nice!
Wasn't it?
We always see eye-to-eye, don't we?
Do it, Franky!
Got it!
Here I go!
Coup de...
...Burst!
Wh-What type of ship is that?!
Nice!
That's really nice!
What's the matter, Salchow?
The ship...
is f-flying away in the sky!
Do you expect me to believe that nonsense?
But...!
Hand that over!
Brother, he's telling you the truth.
The ship is flying away
right before my very eyes.
Papa, we've run into some trouble!
Why not get the flag first?
Way to go, Papa!
That's a splendid idea.
He said to get the flag first, my darling.
Sure thing, my honey!
Hey, Lil-chan!
Could you summon
that one critter for us?
No!
Eh?!
Er, um, I'm sorry, but you can't just--
Lil-chan, you'd be doing it
as a favor for me, too.
Plus it was an order from our beloved Papa.
Go, my kite, Uo!
A strange fish?
At long last, we can finally relax!
The ocean really is great!
Blue skies and white clouds!
The shining sun and the flapping Jolly...
It's gone!
Our Jolly Roger is gone?
And Zoro appears to be missing, too...
I can't believe they got lost again!
Are they stupid?!
Brrr!
It's freezing!
Not only are the icebergs
cold, but they keep moving!
I bet the others are taking it easy,
drinking tea on the ship.
What's that gaudy building?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Assassins Attack!
The Great Battle on Ice Begins"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!