Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
The Straw Hat crew
encountered the Accino Family
in the ice-enclosed ocean, the Arctic Path.
We finally found you!
Dearies, now that you've
wandered into the Arctic Path,
you'll never get to see
the open ocean ever again.
Say your prayers!
Meanwhile, Luffy and Chopper
tried to return to the Sunny
after treating Puzzle's wounds, but...
The Sunny is gone!
In order to escape from
the surrounding icebergs,
they tried to blast free with the Sunny.
Coup de...
...Burst!
But the Accino Family implemented
a certain plan to foil their escape.
Why not get the flag first?
A strange fish?
"The Assassins Attack!
The Great Battle on Ice Begins"
Our Jolly Roger...
It's gone missing?
When'd that happen?
Wh-Where'd it go?
It's gone!
Gone! Gone! Gone! Gone!
Go, my kite, Uo!
What's up, Nico Robin?
It couldn't be...
Huh?
Is something over there?
Found it!
Jolly Roger, found!
Where?!
A bird-like fish has it!
I thought so.
What?!
The people we saw earlier
have stolen it from us.
What?!
I saw one of them issue that fish an order.
Hey!
It's taking our Jolly Roger back
in the direction we just came from!
Damn it!
Sanji-kun?
Hey, where do you think you're takin' us?
Isn't it obvious?
We're going back!
What?!
Don't be stupid!
We just escaped.
Calm down, Sanji-kun!
We're still missing both Luffy and Chopper!
Yeah, and Zoro!
At times like this, you should
think before you leap!
Hey, you!
Quit moving!
Hey, I said to quit moving!
C'mon!
Freeze!
We can't afford to stay put.
A Jolly Roger is as important
to a pirate as his own life!
We can't allow even one to get stolen!
We know that, but first we
should meet up with Luffy--
I've got another reason!
Guys, do you want our captain
to scold us for screwing up?!
I can't believe you guys!
Really!
No!
Anything but that!
I couldn't take it!
My pride won't let me endure
a lecture from that moron!
Dang...
Those two...!
Okay!
Let's go!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Crap!
Not again.
How can they move?
They're just ice!
It looks like we can't get any further
until we learn the truth
behind these icebergs.
Franky!
Yeah?
I'd like to borrow something.
The punks!
Where did they go?!
I, Hockera-sama, will find them first!
Just you wait and see!
Lan la-lan la-lan!
We really don't have time for this, Honey!
We need to hurry and find those pirates!
Don't be in such a rush, Darling!
No matter how hard they try,
there is no escape from the Arctic Path!
Indeed, it's impossible!
Nice!
That expression was nice!
Honey, you're the best!
But it's strange how we haven't found
them despite all of this searching.
I wonder what rock they're hiding under...
Soldier Dock System, Channel 3!
Shark Submerge III, take off!
Well?
How does it feel inside
my Shark Submerge III?
Ain't it super?
Sanji-kun, do you copy?
She blew me off...
I read you loud and clear, Nami-san.
So?
Have you learned anything yet?
It looks like we'll have
to dive a bit deeper...
Franky, please take us
directly under the icebergs.
Sure thing!
Huh?
What's that?
What is it, Nami-san?
Did you find something?
Please slow down a bit.
Stop right there!
What is that...?
They noticed us!
What did?
I don't know!
What?!
They're headed straight for us!
What are?!
Just get us outta here!
Whoa! Whoa!
Wh-What's going on, Nami-san?
Crap! Crap! Crap!
What's going on?!
Go faster!
Darn it!
Nami-san!
D'oh!
Crap!
What was that?
Found 'em!
Let's go.
Wait for me, Honey!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
That hurts!
We must have fallen from up there...
Dang!
If it isn't a cute penguin.
Penguin!
Pen-pen!
Youch!
Hey, look.
It's a penguin colony!
Wh-What should we do?
What type of question is that?
Our only option is to run!
Damn it!
What's with these birds?!
Someone please tell me!
Please save me!
Help me!
Sweet!
Now I can get back.
Savage Penguins?
Yeah.
They're a violent breed of
penguin that inhabits these parts.
They're what has been moving the icebergs.
Awesome!
The bounty hunters use them to
round their prey into one area.
That is why it's said there is
no escape from these waters.
Got it.
Hey!
Chopper, we're going back to the Sunny!
Y-Yeah!
Thank you for everything.
Later!
H-Hey!
Let him go.
It's all the same, no matter where he goes.
On the ocean, there is no
defying fate.
Isn't that right?
Thanks for having us!
Later!
What is it?
What's this?
And here I'm sure you told me he was dead...
It's an honor to meet you in person,
Puzzle the Phoenix.
We managed...
to get away...
What the heck were...
those birds?
Lan la-lan la-lan!
I-It's the couple from earlier...
I swear, you certainly are stupid.
Didn't I warn you that there was no escape?
Yahoo!
It's an honor to see you once more!
As a sign of our growing closer...
Don't get near me!
Dang, that was close!
Oh?
Would you like to fight a round?
I see you're halfway decent.
But you're doomed now that we've found you!
This is the end of the line.
Nice!
You sounded so cool, Honey!
Thank you, Darling!
Not in front of me!
Hey, get away from her!
Kissy!
Mr. Ugly!
Quit kissing right in front of me!
Guys, you're so annoying!
I thought I was gonna die!
That was a nightmare!
What now?!
Show yourself!
I've finally found ya!
Who're you?!
I'm Hockera, the third
boy in the Accino Family!
You're going to be my presents to Papa!
Presents to Papa?
What're you talking about?
Take this!
I'm gonna put you on ice!
Franky!
Bring it on!
If you're looking for a
playmate, I'm game, kiddo!
Let's play, Miss!
Who are you?
I am Lil.
So?
Will you play with me?
Do you think the Sunny is okay?
Sure!
There's nothing to worry
about with them around.
By the way, do you know which
direction I'm supposed to be rowing?
Nope!
We were the ones in a bind!
It's pushing us back where we came from!
Whoa! Whoa!
What?!
What gives?!
It looks like you live up to your
reputation as the "Phoenix."
But I'm afraid you'll be
stripped of that title today.
P-Please wait!
Y-You must be mistaken!
This isn't our captain.
This is just a worthless
crewmate who got injured.
Our captain died a long time--
How dare you bastards try to trick us?!
I should teach you a lesson!
Stansen!
What's going on?
What made that noise?
Oh, Stansen!
Are you okay?
Well?
Come out and say it!
Fess up that the useless man
over there is your captain.
Puzzle, I believe in you.
You are the man who will
become the King of the Pirates!
Hey, Vigaro!
Wait!
Captain, what are you doing?
Let that creep have it!
Go on, Captain!
That brat just let the cat out of the bag!
You're the captain of this ship.
In other words, you have
a 100-million Berry bounty!
Although it still stands to be
proven whether you're a man worthy
of such a bounty.
Captain...!
Captain!
Oh, yes!
What happened to Straw Hat?
He was supposed to be here.
Are you also hiding him somewhere?
Well?
Out with it!
Stansen!
Captain, why?
Go back to the way you used to be!
Please!
Come back to us!
Damn it...!
Hey!
We came back.
Incoming!
What's that?
Sorry!
Could you give us a lift after all?
S-Straw Hat?!
Didn't you return to your own ship?
Ow...
An iceberg forced us back.
And I didn't know which way to go!
D-Didn't they think of that before they left?
Dunno...
That hurt...
Whoa!
True, it must be terribly difficult to find
a pirate ship that has lost its mark.
Eh, Captain Straw Hat?
But today is my lucky day!
To think I ran into two
wanted men at the same time!
You mean three.
And who are you?
Your luck bites.
I am Blend-sama, the second
son in the Accino Family!
Hey, geezer!
What happened to you?
Listen to me!
You see, that flag of yours has been
added to our family's collection.
Your collection?
We stole your pirate flag of
a skull wearing a straw hat.
What about a flag...?
Th-They stole our Jolly Roger, too.
I don't know if it's your symbol or
your cymbal, but you're not all that great
if you've got something that easy
to steal out on display, Straw Hat.
Hey, if you know how to
pick a fight with a pirate,
then you're prepared to face one, right?
Where is our Jolly Roger?!
Your Jolly Roger should be
in Lovely Land by now.
If you want it back, I dare you to go get it.
Lovely Land?
It's freezing!
What... is that?
You jerk!
Your "Boho boho" is getting old!
Give our Jolly Roger back!
That flag--our Jolly Roger--
represents our pride as pirates!
We can't let you keep it!
Wait, damn it!
Luffy, watch out!
You're gonna fall!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Desperate Battles for the Straw Hat Crew!
Pinning Their Pirate Souls on the Flag"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!