Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
On their way to the New World,
the Straw Hat Pirates
were confronted by the
Accino Family bounty hunters.
Coup de...
...Burst!
The Straw Hat Crew dodged the Accino Family
and managed to get the Sunny
outside of the Arctic Path once,
only to lose their Jolly Roger,
the embodiment of their pirate souls.
And the flapping Jolly...
It's gone!
Our Jolly Roger is gone?
The secret behind the
Arctic Path's moving icebergs
were the peculiar Savage Penguins.
D'oh!
Crap!
Now that the Straw Hat Pirates
have been split up,
the Accino Family is swooping
in to claim their heads.
Let's play, Miss!
Your luck bites.
I am Blend-sama, the second
son in the Accino Family!
"Desperate Battles for the Straw Hat Crew!
Pinning Their Pirate Souls on the Flag"
"Lovely Land"?
Love...?
That's right!
Your flag is in Lovely Land!
The Accino Family's base of operations
is none other than Lovely Land!
Where do you see cuffed pirates smile
as they're handed to the Marines?
That's right!
Lovely Land!
Whoa!
I don't care about that!
I was still in the middle of my explanation.
Wait!
Luffy!
Oomph!
Oh, well.
You caught me off guard a second ago--whoa!
But that won't happen again.
Hey, raccoon!
I'm not a raccoon!
Your captain isn't too bright, is he?
It's no wonder you lost
your precious Jolly Roger!
Hey, ex-pirates!
Get ready for the worst!
You're going to see Hell,
all because you covered
for that pathetic excuse of a captain.
If you dilly-dally, who knows what
will happen to the flag we stole?
Gum-Gum...
Gatling!
Crap!
I figured I'd let him attack me until
he wore himself out and screwed up...
...but he isn't showing any openings!
In fact, his openings are getting smaller!
You have a cute ship!
What was the name?
It's the Thousand Sunny.
Thousand...?
No, I meant your name.
My name?
I am Robin.
Nico Robin.
Nico Robin?
Right.
Didn't I see you earlier?
You recognize me?
Of course!
I was surprised when you
showed up so suddenly.
Say, Lil, do you know where
the rest of the crew is?
The Thousand's crew?
I don't know!
I see...
But I know where your flag went!
Aren't you searching for it?
Yes.
Where is it?
Could you tell me?
Will you...
play with me?
Huh?
What was that?
Will you play with me?
I'll tell you if you do.
All right, I'll play.
Really?
Yay!
My big sister hasn't been
playing with me lately.
She's always playing with him.
She's always with that creepy guy.
Nice!
This is really nice!
Yes, Salchow!
We're looking truly terrific!
What is with these two?
It's not like they're launching an attack!
They're just circling around us
over and over and over again!
All righty!
Jump and kick!
Arbell, the rink today...
is perfect for... skating on!
Darn him!
Jump and kick!
You're right, Salchow!
I think... we're going to
get... some good skating in!
They aren't gonna let us
up and leave, are they?
Hey, Sanji!
Yeah?
Don't we need to hurry back to the Sunny?
Yeah...
Then do something about these two!
La-la!
Arbell-chan, that's sexy!
So sexy!
That's right...
You're super easy on the eyes!
This is just how he is...
You're super sassy!
...all the time!
Darn it!
Hey, punks!
You're the ones who stole
our flag, aren't you?
Arbell, you're nice even on the rink!
Where did you put that flag?!
Really nice!
Listen to me!
La la-la la!
What is with this couple?
I bet Papa-san would be tickled pink
if we finished these two off
and brought back their heads.
Definitely, Salchow!
I'm sure he would be!
I'd say that was enough for our warm-ups.
O-Our heads?!
S-So they really are...
It's show time!
Love Throw!
Arbe--
Damn it!
Once more!
Love Throw!
The lady is flying into my chest!
D... Damn it...!
I can't believe he sent a lady flying...!
What a vile thing to do!
It's the guy from earlier...
Yeah.
You're the guy who stole
our Jolly Roger, aren't you?
Huh?
Your Jolly Roger got stolen?
Who coulda done that?
It wasn't you?
Then let's go!
We're wasting our time.
Yeah.
I swear, this place is too cold!
W-Wait!
Timeout!
Don't quit the game!
Y-You were right!
M-My Family stole your flag.
Where is it?
The location?
Where, indeed?
If you don't know, we're leaving!
W-W-Wait!
Timeout!
Don't go!
Don't go just yet!
I actually do know where your flag is.
Then where is it?!
Er, where was it again?
We're gettin' nowhere fast!
Timeout!
I didn't know you had projectiles!
That isn't how real men fight!
You shoulda played nice and told me
you packed that stuff from the start!
It's too cold for this!
Please send him flying already!
Sure thing!
Let the game begin!
If it's my projectiles versus yours,
I'm not gonna lose!
Tch!
This defeats the point of my winter outfit!
Damn it!
Crap!
I'm starting to lose visibility.
I thought he was just goofing off,
but I'll never get anywhere if
I can't see where I'm shooting!
And the cold is starting to numb my movement.
I need to finish this fast!
It looks like you're struggling!
You're wasting your time if
you can't see your target!
Now eat this!
You can't see me!
Tsk!
I don't have time to play with an idiot!
Y-You found me...?
Yeah!
Long time no see.
Now, which hand is the coin in?
Hmm, give me a second.
This one!
Hmph!
Say, Lil?
What?
Where is our flag?
I don't know!
Please!
Won't you tell me?
But I don't know!
Okay, okay!
I'll tell you!
I'll tell you where it is!
Really?
Really!
Honest!
All of our flags are in Papa's room.
Your Papa?
Right!
He has a whole bunch!
His room is covered with Jolly Rogers!
It's filled with them?
Today is his birthday, so everyone
came to pick up a birthday present!
Was the flag the present?
Boo!
Bad guess!
These are the presents.
This person has a 300-million-Berry bounty.
This one has a 120-million-Berry bounty.
This one has a 44-million-Berry bounty.
And then...
...you have an 80-million-Berry
bounty, right?
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Is your flag all that important?
Of course it is!
That flag represents our pride!
It's more important than anything else!
Gum-Gum...
Battle Axe!
Careful there!
That means nothing to a raccoon like you.
We're talking pirate talk right now.
Shut up!
I am a pirate!
Don't think you'll get off lightly for this!
What could a raccoon possibly hope to do?
Shut up!
Whoa!
Aren't you the feisty one?
What was that?!
I don't mind if you take me down,
but what will you do about your flag?
If you take me out, who will
guide you to Lovely Land?
Luffy!
No worries there!
I'll ask for directions after I whack you!
I suppose a 300-million-Berry bounty
won't go down without a fight...
It'd be safest if I threw in the towel for now
and finished them off at Lovely Land.
All right!
You win!
Just give me a--
Give back my Jolly Roger!
You bastard!
W-Wait!
I give!
I surrender!
I'm raising the white flag!
Actually, I have your flag right here.
I'll hand it over now...!
Luffy!
Give our Jolly Roger back!
Ah, crap!
Luffy!
I can't believe you fell for it!
I dare you to come after me
if you want the real flag back!
As for you ex-pirates!
You'd better prepare yourselves!
Puzzle-san?
Puzzle!
Luffy!
Love Throw!
They're the ones who stole our Jolly Roger.
I'm sure of it!
You've incurred the wrath of the almighty
Usopp-sama, you stupid doting couple!
Special Attack: Flame Star!
Bull's eye!
Arbell!
Oh, Arbell!
This is what happens to the fools
who damage a pirate's pride!
Arbell!
How dare you hurt my partner?!
We were really in the groove!
I'm gonna break your nose!
I'm sorry!
L-Luffy!
Luffy fell into the ocean!
Was it all for their Jolly Roger...?
Why would he do that if he couldn't swim...?
Luffy!
No, you don't!
Doctor, you can't swim either!
Now that you mention it...!
S-Stupid!
How are we supposed to set
sail without the Jolly Roger?
Everyone, go look for it!
Yeah!
Hey, it's about time you put that back.
They're in an uproar, claiming that
the Jolly Roger "went missing."
Yeah!
I'm going to become the King of the
Pirates under this Jolly Roger!
I'm tired of hearing that,
but I have to agree.
That's what makes you the captain!
I don't think anyone can defeat us!
I-It's the Phoenix's Jolly Roger!
Dang, that was pathetic!
If you're gonna run from a fight,
you should give up being pirates!
Don't be so harsh.
It just goes to show how powerful
this Jolly Roger has grown.
Yeah!
Luffy!
Thank goodness!
Luffy-san...
Luffy!
I'm so glad you're okay!
It's great!
I'm so happy!
Here you are.
You still haven't caught them?
How is the Straw Hats' flag coming?
It should be here soon, Papa.
Please calm down.
Huh?
I am calm!
Really?
I'm glad to hear it.
Well, they say that you enjoy things more
if you have to wait for them, Papa.
Huh?
Did someone pass by just now?
No, I didn't notice anyone.
Have you had too much to drink?
I don't know...
At any rate, hurry up with the flag!
Uh-huh.
I'll see how it's coming along.
Hey!
Yes?
Also check on Straw Hat.
Certainly, Papa.
Where am I?
The best part of a game is the brawl!
A brawl?
I'm good at those, too.
Coup de Vent!
Game set...!
Super!
Oh?
And right when I ran outta cola!
What's with this place?
It's too cold!
It's kinda cramped in here, huh?
Sorry.
I kept you waiting, didn't I?
I wanted to lend you a hand
and tried pressing some buttons,
but nothing would turn on and it's cold...
What's wrong with it?
Jeez!
That pounding won't stop and
the temperature keeps dropping!
This isn't funny!
Pounding?
Uh-huh!
It couldn't be...!
I caught them alive!
Never let your guard down!
Click.
Huh?
What was that?
Uh-huh.
Two?
Oh, is that right?
Uh-huh.
Okay.
You got it.
Go, my kites, Uo!
Now then, let's resume our game.
What happened?
My third oldest brother
caught two of the bounties.
It was her and him.
C'mon, c'mon!
Hurry!
Let's play!
R-Right.
Why don't we play some more at your house?
Huh?
You'll come to my house to play?
Will you invite me over?
Sure!
Damn it!
Wh-What's going on?!
Why are there two of the same guy?
Wow!
Is he a Devil Fruit power holder?!
It's a clone technique!
That's so cool!
Hey, Chopper!
Let's give it a try.
Sure!
I've got no objections!
But how do we do it?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Stifling to the Max!
The Twins' Magnetic Power Looms"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!