Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Here's the thing about phoenixes:
No matter the hardship,
they always rise back up!
And they're reborn even stronger than before!
I...
Sorry, men! I was a foolish
captain who couldn't live up
to the trust my precious friend placed in me.
But... But I wanna let...
...Vigaro see it once more!
He has to see our flag flying
above the ocean where he's at rest!
Hey! Give back my flag!
It looks like Luffy is here.
He's come for our Jolly Roger.
That's right! We're finished!
No! We can still make it!
Indeed. I don't know how
Luffy learned about the flag,
but it's not as though he
witnessed it getting stolen.
Yep! Which means we've still got a chance!
I know where the Jolly Roger is.
You can leave it to me.
Sweet!
Way to go, Robin!
You're far more reliable
than that lame moss head.
Promise to become my big sister.
Do and I'll save you.
You've made a fool of the Accino Family!
So you're the one who stole
our Jolly Roger, Naked Balloon!
Hmph! So what if I did, whippersnapper?
I'm gonna kick your butt right
quick and get our flag back!
"The Super Hot-Hot Final Battle!
Luffy vs. the Scorching Hot Don"
Wow! So you're a Devil
Fruit power holder, huh?
It truly has been a long time
since I personally hunted a pirate.
You should be honored, Straw Hat!
Don Accino...
So he's the head of that
family of bounty hunters, huh?
What type of powers did he
get from the Hot-Hot Fruit...?
It's his fault that the temperature
has been going up and down!
You're going to kick my butt?
Thinking back, I've met countless
pirates who've made that same claim.
Do you know what happened to them?
--Each and every one...
--Gum-Gum...
You should let me finish talking!
...Pistol!
Hot! Hot!
I can melt... anything I touch.
Wha--?!
Still think you can win?
Gum-Gum...
...Battle Axe!
It burns!
Luffy's attacks aren't working!
He hasn't even touched the guy!
Bastard!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
You still don't get it, do you?
--He's hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
--Luffy!
You can't lay so much as a finger on me.
Damn it!
He's too hot to punch!
Lookie! Slip, slip, slip away!
Wh-What?!
I can even do stuff like this!
My entire body is suspended
by the tiny bit of steam
emitted from the ice melted
by the soles of my feet.
Awesome! That's so neat!
What's he doing?
Yay!
Slippity-slip!
Slip around like fools!
Check it out!
Heh heh!
--Wahoo!
--Screech!
Your Hot-Hot ability isn't all that bad after all!
Just what I should have expected
from a 300-million Berry bounty.
You're pretty good!
Good at what?!
But...
...the real fight has just begun!
Wh-What's that?
Hot Makeup!
What the--?!
I can't see a thing! What's he up to?
Hot-Fried Tofu!
Our flags are somewhere inside that house...!
Jiro, let's go!
Huh? But...
Luffy'll be fine!
All right!
Wait!
Uh...
I love children.
However...
...I only love my children!
That burns!
Chopper!
Hey, Naked Balloon!
Don't throw a hissy fit. I'll play with you now.
Huh?
Ready for the finishing move?
Steam...
...Iron!
L-Luffy!
Damn it! We can't afford to let
Papa's temper grow any hotter!
Papa is going to claim
Straw Hat's head, anyway.
At the very least, I need to
take out this 100-Berry-bounty,
so I can lift his spirits
back up as much as possible!
Sorry, but I can't hand my head
over to a lowly bounty hunter!
Puzzle, you may think you're
fighting on par with me,
but the tables are about to turn.
I'm frozen to the bone!
Cold!
Men, is this the best the
Phoenix Pirates can do?
I can't help it!
Now then, it's about time I took your head.
That hurt, dammit!
Y-You didn't take any damage?
I was burning hot at first, but luckily
the ice cooled me right off!
Is that right? This time I'll melt
your entire body in a flash...
...so I don't have to endure any
more of your insolent garbage!
Heat Level Up: 3,000 Degrees!
That's an impressive amount of smoke!
This isn't smoke!
I just can't touch you, right?
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
Yay! He went flying!
Amazing!
Luffy!
We don't have time to be rejoicing!
At this rate, Luffy will go after
the Jolly Roger in no time!
Crap! Crap! He'll find out that
they stole our flag for real!
What's holding Robin up?
Curse you, Straw Hat!
As soon as you lose the ability to manipulate
that vexing chain, you're finished!
These penguins plan on freezing us.
Then they'll come in for
the kill once we can't move.
--Damn it!
--The beasts!
Men, fall into a close formation
so we can share body heat!
Th-This is so wrong!
I'm working up a nasty sweat!
Moron! It's not like I want to do this!
Men, do you feel nice and warm?
I'd rather fight than keep this up!
I'm with him, Commander Stansen!
That's the spirit! Let's go!
Puzzle, prepare to die!
You're the one going down!
Where is our flag?!
Let's go!
Yeah!
You're the first man to ever bring me
to my hands and knees, Straw Hat.
Yeah? You've still got some fight left in you?
And you're also the first
to have truly made me mad!
Heat Level Up: 5,500 Degrees!
Hot Omelet Shots!
Don Accino...!
Straw Hat!
Robin-chan still hasn't given the sign,
which means we're stuck
reclaiming the flag ourselves!
Sure does! We've gotta beat Luffy to it!
I'll keep an eye on Luffy.
That's it for our strategy meeting!
We're all set!
Are you okay, Jiro?
Captain!
Sorry for making you worry about me.
I wasn't worried any!
That aside, we've gotta get our flag back!
Yeah! We're going to reclaim our--
the Phoenix Pirates'--pride!
--Uh-huh!
--Let's go!
Captain, it's horrible! Our ship pulled
away from the shore all on its own!
What?!
Please leave the ship to us!
Captain, you go with Jiro!
I'm counting on you, Stansen!
Let's go, Jiro!
Uh-huh!
You're one slippery brat!
But you're done for, Straw Hat!
Take this! Hot-Hot Gatling!
What?! That's my move!
No way!
H-He's fast!
But your shots are moving
at the same speed as earlier!
S-Stupid! Hurry and run for it, Luffy!
Luffy!
That startled me!
I don't care about your bounty anymore.
I'm going to melt you into nothing but steam!
Doesn't 300-million-Berry
steam sound luxurious?
Well, Straw Hat?
I'm not a sauna, Naked Balloon!
Evaporate off the face of the planet, Straw Hat!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
That burns!
It's all your fault.
Because of you, my darling
daughter and sons were...!
I'll never forgive you!
The temperature keeps climbing up!
Is his Hot-Hot Fruit to blame?
There might be more to it than that...
Huh? Sanji, Franky's missing!
Where the heck did he go?
Don't worry about him!
I'm sure he has plans of his own.
What?!
This must be the Savage Penguins' doing!
Dammit! They trashed our raiding dory,
so we can't go after them!
Are they retaliating for how
we took out their friends?
Just how messed up are these penguins?!
The captain and Jiro will
definitely get our Jolly Roger!
I couldn't bear to face them if they came back
and there wasn't a ship
on which to hoist the flag!
Commander Stansen!
Please, Big Sister Robin!
Stay here with me forever!
Promise that you won't go anywhere.
I can't do that, Lil.
Why not?
--Robin-chan!
--Robin!
Why won't you do as I say?
Is that kid controlling the plant?
In that case, I'll give her a good spanking!
You are strictly prohibited from
raising your hand against a lady.
You have a broad definition of the term...
Unhand Robin-chan, you stinking flower!
Here I come!
Why, you--! Take this!
Are your friends all that important to you?
Yes. I want to get our flag back.
The Straw Hat Crew's flag?
Papa enjoys collecting a bunch of Jolly Rogers,
but I don't care about those scraps of cloth...
Indeed, they may be nothing
more than scraps of cloth.
But to us pirates, our flag is
more important than life itself.
It's something we can't lose, no matter what!
Are they really all that important...?
Oh, no! Papa...!
He's really angry!
S-S-Save--!
I'm only saying this for your own good!
You'll get indigestion if you eat him!
--Lil!
--Special Attack! Exploding Star!
Lil!
You're okay now.
Big Sister Robin...!
If anything were to happen to you,
your big sister and brothers would be sad.
You're their cute, precious little sister!
Isn't that right?
You aren't alone.
Hold your family dear!
Are we on top of a...?
Second... Gear!
You're going to the New World?
Yeah. After I get our Jolly Roger back.
You'll never get there. Your destination
was set in stone a long time ago!
I've already decided that's where I'm headed.
I'm definitely going there after I kick your butt!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
Found it!
Hot!
Zoro!
Zoro...!
I won't let go, even if it kills me!
This is our pride as pirates!
Jiro!
C-Captain... I...
You did great, Jiro!
Surprisingly Hot Nose Jet!
Chopper!
Guys! I... I made sure to get it! Look!
So we made it in time.
We did it, Nami-san! Now Luffy
won't make fun of--whoa, wait!
Whoa! What's with that flag?!
What the heck?!
Why'd it turn out like this?
It looks like we get to start over from scratch...
Didn't Robin, Sanji-kun,
and the others make it in time?
I hope ours isn't amongst those...!
My beloved family...
My Lovely Land...
And now my prized collection!
I swear, I will personally take you out!
Hot-Hot powers, to the max!
Maximum Heat Level: 10,000 Degrees!
You can still heat up?
What the heck are those two up to?!
The ice is melting right and left!
It looks like they're going all out.
But I'm starting to get
concerned about our Log Pose.
They're unbelievable! I guess I'll go
pick them up in my super ship right quick!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"We'll Be Waiting in the New World!
Parting with the Courageous Pirates"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!