Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Okay! The Great Usopp
will be the first to jump off!
--Yay!
--Lookie!
Wow! That was awesome!
Hey, me next!
All right, go for it!
Almost there!
And here... I go!
You did it!
Ow!
"Absolutely No Entry"
Damn it! I thought I was doing her a favor!
Wh-What in the...? You didn't!
What're you doing in here?
Didn't see the writing that said to keep out?
I guess you can take a peek,
but I had planned on surprising
everyone all at once.
Don't tell the others about it yet.
Whatcha think? Feeling especially surprised?
It had a lackluster design,
not to mention boring features.
So I spruced it up a bit!
But I've never seen its power source before.
Where'd you get it?
Don't remodel stuff without permission!
What did you use as the motif?!
C-Can't you tell? It's a white hobby horse...
This is a hardcore waver
equipped with a Jet Dial!
And you had the nerve to
turn it into a hobby horse?!
Do you think I'm a kid?!
Uh, no...
It's done!
I know they won't complain
about the design now!
This is my trump card.
"Plunging into the Devil's Sea!
The Mysterious Skeleton Floating in the Fog!"
Yay! Luffy's next!
Go!
Wow! That's a new record!
Nami-san! Robin-chan! Sorry for the wait.
I know! This time let's jump off together!
--Okay!
--Hey, guys!
--Almost ready...!
--If you're goofing off,
could you grab those octopi you
threw in the aquarium yesterday?
Octopi?
Yeah.
We're having octopus rice
and octopus shabu.
I'll boil tomatoes to soft
perfection for a sauce
and make some colorful salpicon!
I figured I'd use all the
octopi in tonight's dinner.
Sounds good! Sanji, add fried
octopus to the menu!
Make a hundred!
Fine, you got it.
So go get 'em!
All right!
They're certainly lively.
Oh, perfect timing! I
have one for you, Robin.
--Thank you.
--Hurry! --Octopus!
Octopus! Octopus! Octopus!
Heave-ho!
I'll get them!
Darn it! They keep getting away!
I can't catch any.
All righty! Now it's my turn.
No, wait! If they pull you into the water,
you Devil Fruit power holders will drown!
Leave this to me.
Usopp?!
Damn! Where'd they wander off to?!
Found them!
The darn things are clinging onto each other!
But...
Prepare to meet your maker, octies!
In the end, you're no match
for the Great Usopp!
There's one!
Two and three!
Four, five, six...
Darn octopi don't know when to give up!
Usopp!
Well, that's no good!
Curse you!
Get off me!
What's going on? The
water turned pitch black!
Hey! Are you okay down there?
Usopp's in trouble!
The octopi latched onto him!
What?!
Usopp, grab on!
Usopp!
Are you okay?!
Let go, you little--
You little twerp!
It's no good! The water's so
dark I can't see where he is!
If I know where they are, I can...
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
He's alive!
What a relief.
Your punches nearly killed me!
All this over some measly octopi.
You're the one who said to go get them!
What were they doing?
Hey, something's floating on the water.
What? What?
Huh? Where is it?
Is that it?
"Offering of Treasure to the Sea God"
A barrel?
Doesn't it say "treasure" on it?
"Treasure"
You're right! Maybe a treasure
ship accidentally dropped it!
"Offering of Treasure to the Sea God"
Treasure?!
Hey, Luffy! Let's pull the thing up already!
Okay!
Treasure! Treasure!
A treasure of silver and gold!
Pieces nice and big! Nice and--
Nope!
That contains booze and rations.
How would you know if
you haven't looked inside?
Doesn't the banner say,
"Offering of Treasure to the Sea God"?
"Offering of Treasure to the Sea God"
It's called a "drifting barrel."
It means someone made an
offering to the god of the sea
in hopes of a safe voyage.
"Offering of Treasure"
means it's a gift to the god.
That bites! So we can't do anything with it?
Hey! Since we picked it up,
let's drink the booze!
Stupid! The god'll get angry at you!
You can drink it as long as you pray first.
I don't pray to any gods.
I've heard that booze is extra good
after it's been floating on the waves.
Then we've gotta try it out!
Sweet! Let's have a toast!
It's custom to refill the barrel with
fresh offerings after you've emptied it.
--Yeah?
--Let's open it! Hurry up and open it!
Hey, God! I'm taking your snacks. Heh, heh!
What's so great about "God"?
Didn't a certain someone beat the
crap out of that God on Sky Island?
Okay, I'm done praying.
Cool, it opened!
Something flew out!
What's that?
Red light...?
What was that? What does it mean?
The booze flew out, flashed, and vanished.
It was a flare.
A flare?
Don't you mean the Sea God's curse?
I hope someone did that as a
simple prank, but just maybe...
Just maybe?
Someone may come after our ship.
S-So that was a trap?!
"By opening the barrel, we just informed
someone of our location!" Like that?
Chopper, check the perimeter!
--I'm on it!
--More bounty hunters might come down on us!
I don't see anyone anywhere!
Same here!
Yeah, I don't see anyone...
But this air pressure...
And the clouds are moving quickly.
Everyone, take your stations!
We're escaping to the south-southeast!
A huge storm will be here in five minutes!
I don't see a storm, but if that's
what she says, I bet it'll suddenly hit!
Nami, where should I take us?
Head straight for 2 o'clock!
Th-There...
Damn! It started to rain
right after her warning!
Now we've got lightning!
Crap! We're getting hit by head winds!
They're going to push us back!
Hey! Is this ship really
that big of a pushover?
Oh, yeah!
Guys, take in the sails!
We're bringing out the paddle!
Oh, that?
I love how cool it is! Do it!
Are you all set?
The main sail is set, Nami-san!
I took in the foremast!
Franky, we're ready!
Great!
Soldier Dock System, Channel 0!
With its cola-powered engine,
it's the Paddle Ship Sunny!
Go!
Plow forward!
We survived!
Yeah. It's nice that we pulled through,
but what's with this sea?
It isn't night yet, but with this thick fog,
it's creepy how dark it is.
Do you think we stumbled into that one sea?
I'm not ready for this!
What? We're drawing up on Fishman Island?
Nope! First we have to cross haunted waters.
Yep! Don't let your guard down.
From the looks of it, we're already
caught in the infamous...
...Florian Triangle!
These are mysterious waters where
everything disappears without explanation.
I-It's h-ha-haunted...
These seas are haunted!
What the hell?! And you all knew about this?!
You never bothered to fill me in!
Zoro...
Granny Kokoro gave us the heads up.
There's a living skeleton!
A-A l-living skeleton?
Only in your imagination.
Don't scare him more than he already is.
Listen, Usopp.
In this sea, over 100 ships
mysteriously vanish every year.
And to top it off, I've heard ghost ships
carrying the dead wander these waters.
No! You shoulda warned me about this sooner!
What good would it have done?
I-I coulda prepared! I've gotta
cover myself in anti-evil stuff!
Usopp, please let me borrow some!
♪ Yo ho ho ho ♪
Where's that voice coming from?!
--♪ Yo ho ho ho ♪
--One appeared!
It's a ghost ship!
♪ Yo ho ho ho ♪
What's with that song?!
It's an evil spirit's sailor song!
Don't listen! Plug your ears!
It'll curse you!
Pretend you can't hear it if
a ghost tries to talk to you!
It'll drag you into the sea if you respond!
Evil spirits wanna drag you down with them!
No!
♪ Yo ho ho ho ♪
Is someone aboard that ship...?
If he's our foe, we'll take him out.
Something... is up there.
♪ We're on our way... ♪
♪ ...to deliver Bink's booze ♪
♪ Yo ho ho ho... ♪
Did you see that just now?
A skeleton was singing!
S-Stupid! Skeletons don't sing.
You're just hearing things!
Yep, yep!
But didn't you hear him?
C'mon! Let's go! Like right now!
There really is a living skeleton! Sweet!
Hold your horses!
Not so fast, Luffy.
Go on. We're going to draw to see
who goes aboard that ship with Luffy.
What?!
Why?! Send whoever actually wants to go!
Right! That's what we should do!
Do that!
Are you sure you're okay with that?
Okay, let's go!
Yay!
I hate this...
Please let me draw!
Whoa, Zoro-kun! Wait, wait!
Does everyone except the
three of us plan on going?
I'll draw! I'll draw! I'll take my chances!
I can go by myself, you know!
If we don't hurry, the ship's going to leave.
That isn't an option.
Just draw your sticks already.
Two people will go with him.
It'll be their job to make sure
he doesn't do anything stupid.
Why'd it have to be me?
I wanna go back...
Nami, you ready yet? Hurry on up!
No, no, no, no!
I said I was cool with going by myself...
Forget it! What if you did something
stupid that got our whole ship cursed?
My luck bites!
Nami-san, never fear!
I'll protect you, Nami-san!
How are you supposed to protect me...?
Nami, weren't you eager
to find a treasure ship?
There's no way this is a treasure ship!
Didn't you see that skeleton move around?!
I bet he's the treasure's guardian!
Let's go look for him.
H-Huh?
No!
Evil be gone! Evil be gone!
Luffy, rest in peace!
Huh?
Good day to you!
Sorry for earlier! Our eyes locked, but I
wasn't able to give a proper greeting.
You gave me quite a start!
How many decades have passed
since I saw people in the flesh?
Every ship I run across seems
to be a ghost ship! It's dreadful!
Come along! Feel free to come right inside.
Why don't we enjoy a nice,
leisurely conversation?
Look! He's talking!
The skeleton has an afro and he's talking!
I can't believe it...
My, my!
What a truly elegant lady! You're beautiful!
N-No, hardly!
My eyes follow the beautiful ladies.
But I'm a skeleton, so I don't have eyes!
May I see your panties?
No way!
My, my! You're harsh!
That made my bones rattle,
especially since I'm a skeleton!
Shut up!
How did a skeleton get a bump on his head?
Say, do you poop?
There are a boatload of questions
that should come before that!
Yes, I poop.
Don't take so long to answer
his question! And who cares?!
For starters, why are you alive and
talking when you're nothing but bones?
What the heck are you?
What are you doing here?
What happened on this ship?
What's the story behind this sea?!
Answer all of my questions!
Wait.
Putting that aside...
...join my crew!
Yeah, okay.
Hey!
Hello, everyone! Good day to you.
I am the dead and skeletonized Brook.
Who the heck is this, Luffy?
Isn't he funny? I added him to our crew.
No, you did not!
Really, don't get so worked up.
Let's have dinner.
That's not for you to decide!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Joy of Seeing People!
The Gentleman Skeleton's True Identity!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!