Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
W-What the hell...
are you guys doing?!
What do you mean?
We're here to get Nami.
Oh, yeah. Where are Usopp and Johnny?
Usopp! T-That's right!
There's no time to be
loafing around here!
What's wrong?!
That bastard's been caught by Arlong!
We gotta hurry before he's killed!
--He was killed!
--What?!
Big Bro Usopp is dead!
He was killed!
By Big Sis Nami!
"Everyone's Gathered!
Usopp Speaks the Truth About Nami"
Are you serious?!
Yeah. It's terrible!
She was a witch all along!
She's been winning Arlong's favor
so she could have the treasure buried
in Cocoyashi Village all to herself!
She'll calmly kill people for it, too!
She's scum, rotten to the core!
She had us all fooled the entire--
You!
Try saying that again! I'll kick your ass!
Stop, Luffy. This has
nothing to do with Johnny.
If you don't wanna
believe me, then don't!
But I saw it with my own two eyes!
She killed Big Bro Usopp--
Quit spouting nonsense!
Nami would never kill Usopp!
We're friends!
B-But, I...
Who're friends, Luffy?
Nami!
Why are you here?
What're you talking about?
You're our friend! We came to get you!
--You're a big problem.
--Nami?
Friends? Don't make me laugh!
You're just a pathetic bunch of
people cooperating with each other.
Damn you! You killed him!
I saw it with my own eyes!
How dare... How dare
you kill Big Bro Usopp?!
So what? Why not kill me
as revenge, then?
What?!
I'll tell you this much.
Right now, Arlong wants to kill
Roronoa Zoro and his men.
Because Zoro just had to be stupid.
No matter how monstrously
strong you guys are,
you're no match for real monsters.
If you hang around this island,
you will wind up being killed.
Not that it matters to me, though.
Her cool look is so enchanting, too!
Hi, Nami-san! It's me!
Do you remember me?!
Let's set sail together!
Shut up, you!
You're just complicating things!
Say what?! Love is always a hurricane!
Hey! Listen when people are talking!
Where's Usopp?
Bottom of the ocean.
Damn it! Cut the crap!
A swordsman would even
strike a lady, Roronoa Zoro?
What?! You don't even know
what's going on here! Back off!
I guess I'd be irritated too,
coming right off an insulting defeat.
Huh?!
Hey! Watch that mouth of yours!
Mind your own business,
you damn bastard!
Bros! This is no time for
you two to be going at it!
That's right!
If you're going to fight,
could you do it off the island?!
Don't butt any more into this
land's affairs, you outsiders!
Do you still not get it?
The one and only reason I got
close to you was for the money!
Now that you're flat broke,
you have no charm whatsoever!
You can have your ship back,
so just go find a navigator somewhere
and go into the Grand Line!
Go look for your One Piece or whatever!
Just get the hell out of here!
You're an eyesore!
Goodbye.
Nami...
Big Bro Luffy?!
--I'm going to sleep.
--Sleep?!
In this situation?! And right
in the middle of the road?!
I don't plan on leaving the island,
and I'm not interested in
what's happening on the island.
And I'm a little sleepy.
--I'm going to sleep.
--Huh?!
B-Big Bro...
Fine...
Fine, whatever!
Go ahead and die!
Na--
--Hurry! Hurry!
--What's the big deal?!
It's the navy! The navy's here!
Some survivors from Gosa managed
to contact the government!
The navy's come here to pick us up!
See?
We're saved!
We can finally escape this island!
So that's the infamous Arlong Park...
The world's on its last legs if
pirates can settle down so blatantly.
Listen, men!
Our mission today is to
successfully extract from the island
the survivors of the town of Gosa,
which was destroyed
by the Arlong Pirates!
But I am left to wonder...
Would our brand of justice
allow us to overlook the castle
of this unchecked pirate?!
It would not!
Our unit will now annihilate
Arlong and his men!
Prepare for battle at once!
Yes, sir!
Navy Branch ♪77?
Yes. That's what it said.
A newcomer.
Someone go there and negotiate
with the head honcho.
If two million isn't enough to keep
them from trying anything funny,
get rid of 'em!
They're suddenly opening fire!
Arlong-san! Look out!
--H-He crunched a cannonball!
--What terrifying jaws and teeth!
Arlong-san. The negotiations?
Canceled.
--Alright! Let's go!
--Time to fight!
It'll be a navy bloodbath!
Not so fast, guys.
There's no need to expend so much
energy just to take out the trash.
We'll go!
What foolish humans they are to pick
a fight with us in these waters.
Three of our leaders'll
make for a grand fight!
That ship won't last even three minutes!
That's odd...
Commodore! The cannonball
appears to have been a dud!
Fire another! This is a
signal of open hostility!
We're dealing with fishmen!
Don't let your guard down, men!
Yes, sir!
He's been hit!
It's one of Arlong's men!
Get him! Commence attack!
Stop! Remain calm!
One of Arlong's men, yes?
I am Commodore Purinpurin
of Navy Branch ♪77.
We are a somewhat
well-known elite naval unit!
If you do not wish for death,
I suggest you dutifully surrender--
Commodore!
--How dare you?!
--Kill him!
W-What's this shock?!
Don't tell me there's
fishmen under the ship?!
I'm sorry to bother you like this,
but we just took the liberty
of removing your ship's rudder.
--W-What?!
--Commodore! Are you all right?!
Don't worry.
I didn't hit any vital spots.
This is just hypothetical, Commodore,
but if one were to move a large reef
directly into a strong current,
what do you suppose
would happen to the ocean?
What?!
M-Moving a reef?!
That can't possibly be done!
Alright! Right around there, Hachi!
Right!
C-Commodore!
A giant whirlpool has
suddenly appeared ahead!
The rudder's not working!
What?!
I told you. We removed the rudder.
This rudderless ship is now headed...
...into the depths of the sea.
This can't be happening...
This is reality.
There's no way we can escape
from Arlong's control.
Sorry to make you work so hard!
Not at all. We know
everything about these waters,
from the winds to the
depths. It was a cinch.
With our top skills, we have
no one to fear in these seas!
And let's not forget Nami's sea charts.
I moved the reef after checking that!
It even tells the flow of
the currents and everything!
Those are some excellent
charts, all right!
If we have Nami draw up charts
of all the world's oceans,
we'll be the eternal kings of the sea!
Nami's definitely vital to have for
the creation of the Arlong Empire!
--It's a real shame!
--A shame?
He promised to let Nami
and Cocoyashi Village go
once she saves up 100 million Berries.
For reals, Arlong-san?!
You're really going to let Nami go?!
For reals, for reals?! That's a big waste!
It can't be helped.
That's what we agreed
to eight years ago.
I'm a man who'd die to keep
my money-related promises.
Hey, Big Bro Zoro!
What on earth are you thinking?!
Arlong is out to kill us!
So why aren't we running away?!
Now that we know
what Nami's really like,
there should be no reason
at all to stay on this island!
A reason for staying on
this island? There is one.
He's staying here.
Don't tell us you're still gonna try
to get her back too, Big Bro Zoro!
I have nothing to do with it.
He decides who we have as navigator.
Big Bro...
A-All right! Understood!
It was a short reunion,
but our role as guides ends here!
Same for me! I don't wanna
deliberately wind up killed!
Yeah. Take care.
Well, until we meet again!
Stay well, you guys!
You, too!
--Hey.
--Yeah?
Why do you suppose
Nami-san was crying?
She was crying?
Inside her heart.
You sure they weren't tears
of grief for killing Usopp?
Yeah, right. Are you serious?
Do you honestly believe
Nami-san killed Long-nose?
When she did that...!
It's for my business!
This was my only choice!
When she did that,
Nami stabbed her own hand to
make it look like she stabbed me!
If Nami hadn't done that for me,
Arlong would've killed me for sure!
What now?! Manly Usopp can't
just turn tail after being saved!
For now, I gotta hurry and find Zoro!
Is that... Zoro?!
It is! Yes!
Nami didn't kill him. Is that
what you're tryin' to say?
Am I wrong?
I wonder.
I did make her out to be a small fry
who can't even watch a guy die.
She might've done it out of frustration.
Whadya mean, "small fry"?!
What's so small about
Nami-san's chest?!
Is that all you can think--
He's alive!
No, I think he's dead now...
Usopp!
Did Nami do this to you?!
Sorry. Me and him did that.
You did it!
L-Luffy! You're here?!
Yeah. Just got here.
Oh, I came too!
Good to work with you!
Someday I'm gonna kill you!
--Oh! You're pretty alright after all!
--Shut up!
Speaking of which,
we heard Nami killed you.
--Eh?!
--That damn Johnny!
He was talking nonsense after all!
No... In a way, it's not a lie...
But it's actually the opposite!
Nami saved my life!
You really know how to trash a place.
What's wrong, Nami?
Nothing. I'm just here to rest a little.
Breaking glass and furniture
just to rest is a bit much.
You have that treasure map open
even though nothing's wrong?
Something happened to
make me mad, that's all!
Them, huh? Who are they?
You met them?!
Yeah. Some Captain
Something-or-Other.
He seemed kind of liar-ish, though.
I hear you smiled happily when
you were traveling with them.
Even though I haven't
seen you like that in years.
Talk to me! Who are those guys?
We agreed you could tell me
anything, remember?
I had planned to forget about them...
I thought I had erased
them from my mind.
Yes! I'm out!
Darn it! You win all
by yourself again?!
Wait, hold on, Luffy!
Why do you have so many cards?!
I get the feeling having more is better!
You idiot!
Learn the rules already!
Alright! Then let's say
the one with the most wins!
--Alright, it's decided!
--Quit deciding on your own!
--But the more I tried to erase them,
the more I remembered...
Oh, crap! We sprung a leak!
Hurry! Stop it!
Alright! Leave it to me!
Quit thrashing around!
The truth is, I once forgot
the fate I bear for a short while...
Who do you take your friends for?!
I honestly felt like always being
with them, if it were possible.
Now I see...
Yeah, that'd hit you hard.
To think that someone
really showed up for her...
Friends, huh?
The most painful word for her...
So that's how Nami pretended
to kill me and let me escape!
It looks to me like there's a reason
she's in a fishman pirate group!
Obviously.
So, what do we do?
Do we storm Arlong Park?
H-Hold on! We gotta find out what
the story with Nami is first!
It's no use, either way.
No matter what you guys do,
Arlong's rule won't come to an end.
Nojiko!
--Who's she?
--Nami's big sister.
N-Nami-san's older sister?!
No wonder she's so beautiful!
What do you mean it's no use?
Please, don't get any more
involved with this village.
Leave Nami alone.
--I'll explain the circumstances.
--Circumstances?
You mean why she
joined Arlong's group?
Yes. You'll feel like leaving
the island once you hear it.
Alright. Let's hear this
reason or whatever, then.
--I'll pass.
--H-Hey!
I don't care about her past.
--Where are you going, Luffy?
--For a walk.
A-A walk?! You're not
gonna listen to this?!
No. I'll pass.
Who's he?
Don't mind him.
That's just how he is.
We'll hear you out.
Though I don't think
it's gonna change anything.
Yeah! I'll listen, too!
I wanna know what's
happening on this island!
Me, too! I want to know
everything about Nami-san!
And now he's sleeping.
Don't sleep right after you say that!
I see. This is why Nami
had such a hard time.
There's a navy ship at the shore?!
It's Branch ♪16's ship!
Maybe Headquarters is taking action
after what happened to Branch ♪77?!
I am Colonel Nezumi of Navy Branch ♪16!
Bring me Genzo, the
representative of Cocoyashi Village!
I'm Genzo, Colonel.
You, huh? Lead me to the
house of the girl named Nami.
Nami? But what on earth for?!
You simply need to lead the way.
It all goes back to eight years ago...
To that day, when we
were still little children...
She was in this village.
Me and Nami will never forget
her as long as we live...
Her name was Bellemere.
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Bellemere! What a beautiful girl's name!
How I'd love to meet her!
Hey, are Bellemeres yummy?
It's not food! It's the person
Nami-san will never forget!
Meaning she could be Nami-san's...
Nami-san's... Nami-san's...!
Shut up! I can't sleep, Sanji!
Are you guys even serious
about listening to Nojiko?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Untold Past! Female Warrior Bellemere!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!