Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Anyway, we should try to stay put!
Luffy and the others are sure
to come save us. You hear me?
I'm with him! I don't wanna go outside again!
I'm not going back in the forest or graveyard!
Wha--?
Why, you--!
Someone's here?!
Hey, Nami? Is there a problem?
They're in the way...
Huh?
Caught ya!
Please let me go!
Guys, why don't you join my pirate--
Cut that out!
Hey, Absalom!
I was searching for my bride, Hogback.
That woman tickles my fancy.
I'm going to make her mine!
You're trembling. How adorable!
You're so cute...
I won't let you leave, children!
Chopper! Nami! Head for the door!
We're leaving the mansion!
What's keeping you, Nami?!
No!
D-Don't tell me...
It won't open! We're trapped in here!
What?!
Now you've made me mad!
--I won't let you escape!
--Now come on back!
No!
"The Zombie's Secret!
Hogback's Nightmarish Laboratory!"
Duck!
That was close!
Let's leave this room for now!
Try another room!
We won't let you escape!
No!
"Evil Be Gone"
No! No, no! Let go!
Wait!
We're in a fireplace!
No!
We're doomed! There's nowhere left to run!
No!!
Where is this?
Hey, they vanished!
They disappeared in the fireplace!
Crap! The entrance to the secret
passage must have opened!
Now they'll make their way
to Hogback-sama's laboratory!
After them!
It's no use! They're pushing
against the door on the other side.
H-Hey, Usopp! Put some muscle into it!
No!
No!!
No matter where they go, this mansion is
stuffed with fellow "Surprise Zombies."
Th-This is nuts!
Gyah!
No!
The hallways are out!
So are places with paintings!
We need to find a room somewhere!
That room!
"Evil Be Gone"
More paintings!
A-Are those photos?
What a relief!
These aren't zombies, are they?
Aren't these... of that one lady?
Cindry-chan, the lady who hates plates...
What is with this room?
Now that I really look at her, the servant
Cindry-chan is quite pretty, isn't she?
So do you think this is her room?
But would she hang a bunch of
photos of herself in her own room?
Her face and body were covered in stitches.
I don't see any on her in these photos, do you?
But I doubt they're of someone else,
so are they old photos?
Listen to this!
"Victoria Cindry."
Apparently she was a famous stage actress.
Look! All of these are articles on her.
Huh? A stage actress?
But didn't the doc say she used
to be a servant somewhere?
She got the boot after she broke some plates...
Going by this, that doesn't seem very likely...
She was originally born into nobility.
And she was popular since she was little...
What's wrong?
She fell from the stage...
Ten years ago, there was
an accident and she died!
Wh-Wh-What're you talking about?!
She was clearly alive!
She wasn't dead!
But if that obituary is legitimate,
that means she died and came back to life!
This island is filled with real zombies!
We saw deceased that truly were resurrected!
No!
Talk about messed up...
This place gets creepier by the second!
I wish I didn't know the truth!
What is it?!
Look at those, Usopp!
Aren't they treasure chests?
You were quick to adapt!
Oh, Usopp! Open it!
Open up that chest!
Uh, okay...
Sorry! This isn't where we store the treasure!
It's a jack-in-the-box!
You've come out!
Zombie Paintings!
"This isn't where we store the treasure."
I'm sure that's what the
Jack-in-the-Box Zombie said!
No!
Oh, Bodyguard!
I see some people have
gotten lost in the mansion.
Oh, it's you!
Not a problem! I shall catch them for you.
So like I said, stop jumping at the
chance to recruit these weirdoes!
As it is, we've already got
a raccoon dog and a robot!
Hey, I'm not a robot! I'm a cyborg, moron!
It's obvious you aren't human anymore!
At the core, I'm human!
At the core, you're a pervert!
Eh? Oh, well, as long as you understand...
Hey, that wasn't a compliment!
I wonder what will be next!
This is a blast!
Didn't we run into a treeman
and a unicorn earlier?
What about them?
All of the bizarre animals in this
forest seem to share these traits:
Bandages, stitches and numbers
tattooed onto their bodies.
Numbers? Yeah, he is numbered, isn't he?
Does that mean someone is overseeing them?
Yes, that's what I would assume.
Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!
--Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!
--Huh? I hear something.
Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!...
There's a ghost!
They're multiplying as they dance! Awesome!
That's one creepy cheer.
I'll catch them and keep them as pets!
They're spirits through and through!
All righty!
Fresh Fire!
Shoot! It didn't work.
That was an epic fail.
I'm such a loser this week.
Nothing I do works out.
I'm not sure I can live like this...
I can hear the whole world booing me!
Are you really that bummed out?!
Okay! I've got the punk!
If I could be reborn, I'd like to be a clam.
I suck! I wish there was a
hole for me to crawl into!
What the heck are you two doing?!
Do you think that perhaps touching
those ghosts weakened their will?
That's absurd!
Those two are pathetic! They're at
the mercy of those weird ghosts
because they aren't calm
and collected most of the time.
I'm sorry I was ever born.
That's enough!
Sheesh...
It looks like you were right, Robin-chan.
Not only do they lack physical bodies,
but they also break your
will if you touch them.
They would make for formidable foes.
Definitely.
What a fascinating island!
Gah! Those ghosts are gonna
pay the next time they pop up!
I don't want them as pets!
They must have a weakness! I'll wipe them out!
You put on quite the show!
Shuddup!
"Man, I'm sorry! Sorry I was ever born!"
Why, you...!
It looks like we can put the numbered
patchwork creatures into one category,
but those ghosts were a
completely different life form.
Didn't one of them appear on our ship?
The way they occasionally show up,
it's like they're keeping tabs on us.
The question is: Who is controlling them?
Wow, it's a big cemetery!
It's got character!
Hey, let's eat here!
Stupid! It'll ruin the food if we eat here!
No, we're eating here!
Nothing has ever once ruined a meal!
Only you think that!
Besides, we're in a hurry.
Here!
I'm not goin' back down! Are you stupid?!
A severely injured old man?
He's obviously a zombie!
How dare you make fun of zombies?!
Don't underestimate us!
Are zombies supposed to be this full of life?
Teach them just how
dangerous zombies can be!
What, you wanna fight?
We can teach you a thing or two
about how dangerous we are!
600 Million Berry Jackpot!
That's Hogback's laugh.
What is this room?
His laboratory!
It's almost done!
What a glorious mario!
Behold, Cindry-chan!
The work of a genius... is truly art!
I hope you fail right before completion.
How could you say that, Cindry-chan?!
I swear, I'm taken aback each time
you fling such cruel words at me!
I made dinner.
Oh, is that right? What are we having tonight?
Spaghetti soup.
The soup is vanishing right
before my eyes, Cindry-chan!
I wish plates would cease to exist.
Yeah, I get that!
But if that's how you feel,
why must you choose such bold dishes?
Aren't there plenty of other
things you could make instead?
--Cindry-chan is also in there...
--Let's see! There's fried soba noodles!
Or even fried udon noodles!
See? There's also fried pork cutlet!
I wonder if she's really the lady
who died in that accident...
I can't believe it...
I'm sick of these soupy dishes!
What about your spaghetti soup?
I-I-I'll eat it...!
I'll eat that! I'd like some!
What's on top of the table?
It's probably a human corpse.
Based on his complexion, he's no longer alive.
He's numbered, just like the
zombies in the graveyard!
He said that it's almost done.
That settles it!
He's clearly trying to turn that into a zombie.
Hogback revived all of
the zombies on the island.
That's the only possible explanation!
But medicine can only save
people before they die.
He can make the corpse as strong as he wants,
but it won't bring the person back to life!
We'll never figure this one out!
If we spy on him, we'll learn the
secret to how he revives people!
Good day to you!
If you're curious about
what's inside, you should go in.
"Yo ho ho"?!
B-Brook...?!
I never expected that man to be here!
Hey, Robin! Do you know him?
This man's bounty, Luffy,
used to surpass yours!
It used to...?
So he must be the man pulling the strings...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"His Name Is Moria! The Great
Shadow-Seizing Pirate's Trap!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!