Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Nami would never kill Usopp!
We're friends!
Who're friends, Luffy?
Don't make me laugh.
You're just a pathetic bunch of
people cooperating with each other.
Now I see...
Yeah, that'd hit you hard.
To think that someone
really showed up for her...
Friends, huh?
The most painful word for her...
So that's how Nami pretended
to kill me and let me escape!
It looks to me like there's a reason
she's in a fishman pirate group!
Please, don't get any more
involved with this village.
Leave Nami alone.
I'll explain the circumstances.
--I'll pass.
--H-Hey!
I don't care about her past.
--Where are you going, Luffy?!
--For a walk.
Who's he?
"Untold Past! Female Warrior Bellemere!"
What a shock!
I guess we really did see a
ship fall from the sky, huh?
It seems some unordinary humans
have stepped foot on this island.
Who could it be? And why?
Look! Who's that?!
He's not from this island!
Oh? So those are fishmen?
H-Hey! Wait! You!
Huh? You called?
W-Who are you?!
What are you doing on this island?!
What does it matter to you?
Y-Yeah. You have a point.
I'm Luffy. I'm taking a walk.
A walk?!
Have fun!
You! Where are you headed?
Heck if I know!
He seems like a funny guy!
Just who is he?
He walked right by us,
with no fear whatsoever.
He's a mysterious guy.
Bellemere?
And this person raised you and Nami?
Yeah, that's right.
How should I start to explain
about Bellemere-san?
I fell asleep?
Huh? Nojiko?
Where could she have gone?
Just a little more, Bellemere-san.
Just a little more,
and everything will return!
Cocoyashi Village,
the tangerine orchard,
and even my dream!
It took eight years...
All done...
All done!
Now I just need to check that book...
Oh! Nacchan!
What's wrong?
Nothing! Nothing at all!
Oh, my!
Damn it, Nami! Not again!
--Oh? Did it again, Nacchan?
--Let go!
--You just never learn!
--I'm not a cat!
You idiot!
How many times do I have to
tell you stealing is wrong?!
Bleh!
It's not my fault we're poor!
Cheapskate!
Bellemere!
Bellemere! Your no-good
cat's been at it again!
Whadya want? You're annoying!
Oh! Welcome home, Nami!
I'm back!
Look! This is the umpteenth time!
She's even famous in the village now!
So?
Surely even you've
shoplifted before, Gen-san?
This is why she acts this way!
I'm just kidding!
--Alright. You paid for her, right?
--B-Bellemere...
Thanks so much.
I don't have money right now.
I'll pay you later...
...with my body.
D-Don't be s-saying
things like that!
Look at you blush!
Oh? And why are you laughing?
Try that again and
you'll get 100 spankings!
I'm sorry!
But I really wanted this book!
If you wanted it,
why didn't you just tell me?
Because you wouldn't
buy it for me anyway...
Of course I would!
We do have some
money stashed away.
But the villagers said the
climate's been so good lately
that you can get tons of
tangerines from any old field,
and our tangerines won't sell good
'cause they don't go up in value.
They can mind their own business!
You're so dumb, Nami!
I would've stolen it way better!
I said no stealing!
I was just joking!
That hurts!
But you know,
there's one thing for sure!
The maps you draw are
really amazing, Nami!
First you learned how to draw
sea charts, and now land maps!
This is a map of this island, isn't it?!
No one would ever think
such a little kid drew this!
I'm studying navigation too now!
Navigation, too?!
It is Nami's dream!
Yeah!
I'm gonna use my navigation skills
to travel to all the world's oceans!
And then I'm gonna make a
world map of everything I see!
So your map of this island is your
first step toward your dream, then?
Yeah!
A map of the world, huh?
Nami! Someday, you will
make your dream come true!
I just know it!
Hey, Bellemere-san.
You haven't been eating meals lately...
I've been eating tangerines,
though. I'm on a diet!
I don't need any meals, either...
What're you taking interest in guys for?
Kids need to eat right!
You keep lying!
You don't have any food because
we don't have any money!
For reals?!
--You're suffering, so that we can...
--Diet!
You shouldn't underestimate
the beautifying power of tangerines!
They're the reason I still have
such lustrous skin at the age of 30!
But your hands are yellow.
Just shut up and eat!
Here you are, Nami! All done!
A super custom-made
Bellemere brand!
Another hand-me-down from Nojiko?
Here we go!
It looks great on you, Nami!
This lion used to be a sunflower!
It can't be helped!
You're two years younger
than me, you know!
Age has nothing to do with it!
I want new clothes too!
Mine are old clothes too, you know!
You get my stuff 'cause
you're my baby sister! Blehh!
But I'm not your real sister!
We're not related by blood!
Nami!
Bellemere-san!
So what if you're not
related by blood?!
Never say anything
stupid like that again!
W-Whatever...
You're not our real mother, either!
You'd be better off
without us, wouldn't you?!
That way, you could eat,
buy all the clothes
you want, and be free!
I wish...
I wish someone richer
had adopted me instead!
I-Is that so?
Fine, then! Do whatever!
If you hate this house that much,
then go leave for somewhere else!
Stop it, you two!
I will leave!
Nami!
Nami!!
Bellemere-san...
The three of us are a family!
I'm sure Nami feels the same way!
She didn't mean what she said!
You're a strong person, Nojiko.
That was real immature of me.
Could you go bring Nami back for me?
I'll have a super delicious
supper ready before you get back!
Okay!
Okay, Miss! I'll lower it to this much!
Eh? Lower it a little more!
Right over here!
Low prices! Low prices!
It wouldn't hurt to buy any of
these fresh fruits lined up here!
So, coming here from the outskirts
of the village is "running away"?
That's sure nice and convenient!
Here. Drink up before it gets cold!
Bellemere-san would be
happier if we were gone.
Why do you think that?
Having two children
costs lots of money...
And everyone in the village
hates her, because of me...
You're old enough to
consider others now, huh?
Don't worry.
She was a famous brat in this
village when she was your age, too.
Bellemere-san was?!
Even now, she's still quite
a brat in the villagers' eyes!
How shocked the village was
when that brat suddenly said
she was going to be a marine...
A marine?!
Bellemere-san was a marine?!
Yeah.
Pirates have to pay for
slaughtering innocent people...
With those words, she left the village.
She says she felt her time
to die had finally come...
Oh, well...
Your baby sister?
No. I don't know who she is.
You have no idea
how that makes me feel...
And that was you, Nami.
When she saw you, Bellemere
mustered up the will to live again.
It is a boat! I knew it!
On a stormy night like tonight?!
Who on earth could it be?!
Doctor! Call the doctor!
Bellemere? Is that you, Bellemere?!
--Bellemere!
--What is this?!
--Who are these children?!
--Doctor! They have terrible fevers!
They've been completely
worn out by the storm!
What?!
Alright! But we need to tend to
those nasty wounds of yours, too!
Just hurry!
Please! Don't let them die!
Save those kids' lives!
I beg of you!
What did you just say, girl ruffian?!
I'm going to be these kids' parent.
That's what I said.
You can't!
Don't do it! A punk like you
can't possibly raise children!
T-Take my advice! Give them
to a government institution!
I've already decided!
I'm an adult now, too.
I was even in the navy.
I think I'm a little
more upstanding now.
I'm going to take the responsibility
of raising these kids.
I'm going to raise them
to be wonderful people
who won't lose to the era we live in!
I'm going to live with these kids.
Nami and Nojiko gave me life.
You girls have a bond that goes
far deeper than a real family's.
Nami! I thought you'd be here!
N-Nojiko!
Bellemere-san is waiting for us!
She's making a yummy supper!
Okay!
I bet it's your favorite!
Omelets with tangerine sauce!
Yes!
Yay! Omelets!
How time flies...
Children once on the brink
of death, now so full of life...
Watching them grow up
is like a joy for all of us!
Yeah! We won't feel happy until
we see that family of three happy!
Right?!
Yay! Yay!
Pirates, everyone!
Pirates are coming!
Pirates! Everyone hide!
--It's the Arlong Pirates!
--Arlong?!
That can't be!
What are fishmen from
the Grand Line doing here?!
Was the rumor about a split in
the fishman pirate group true?!
Nami! Nojiko!
Gen-san!
It's dangerous here!
Hide in the back woods!
Eh? But...
Go! Now!
You seem to be in excellent
spirits, pathetic humans!
As of this moment, this village--
no, this island is now
under my control!
Listen up!
On this memorable day, you will
all buy your lives from me!
100,000 Berries per adult.
50,000 Berries per kid.
Those who can't pay... die!
What do we do, Nojiko?
We can't pay that much!
But they might not spot our house!
You can't see it from the village!
How much did we get, brother?
Just over 25 million, I'd say.
Excellent!
Sounds like we'll hafta pay
for our lives every month
at 100,000 Berries
per person from now on!
100,000?! We can't
make a living that way!
Endure it for now!
We should just be glad no
one in the village has died.
If money is all that's needed,
it's an easy price to pay.
I at least hope they'll leave
without noticing Bellemere's house.
With the two children, it would
come to 200,000 Berries...
I doubt she has that much saved up.
Alright! Time to go, brothers!
Arlong-san! There's smoke
coming from outside the village!
Okay!
Alright, let's see!
Too delicious!
Nothing's quite like Bellemere's
Special Tangerine Sauce!
Nami and Nojiko are gonna
leap out of their seats!
The smoke is coming from a house!
Oh? We almost missed it.
Damn!
Bellemere-san!
Let's go! Let's collect our money!
Whoa, this is bad! The pirates...
...are headed to Bellemere's house!
Hey! Nojiko and Nami are gone!
What?!
Ten more minutes for the duck in
the oven. And the stew is boiling.
This'll be a big blow
to our family budget.
But I guess I'll splurge, anyway!
Bellemere-san's gonna...
Bellemere-san's gonna be killed!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Oh! How cute Nami-san
was as a child!
Geez, were you even
listening to the story?!
Of course I was!
I'd listen to every single
word that's about Nami-san!
--Got that?!
--Yes, I'm sorry.
Wait, why am I apologizing?!
Is it over? Where's Luffy?
He was really sleeping?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Survive! Mother Bellemere
and Nami's Bond!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!