Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
This shadow will bring me one step closer
to becoming the King of the Pirates, Hogback!
It's been a decade since we first met.
I put all of my prowess into creating
No. 900 for a day such as this!
With that shadow in it,
I'm certain it'll become the
most powerful zombie in history!
It will be a great asset!
The day I become the world's
"King of the Grave" is close at hand!
I can practically see the day I turn
the cute critters of the world
into zombies and make them
serve me in my dream kingdom.
Heave, ho! Heave, ho! Heave, ho!
Heave, ho! Heave, ho!
--Luffy!
--Stupid! Don't pop out!
He won't die just because they took his shadow!
Remember Brook!
Uh-huh...
Here, guys, take this.
What is it?
The zombies' weakness!
This is their weakness? What exactly is it?
It's salt.
To reiterate, please stuff salt into
a zombie's mouth to defeat it!
That's the trick! Even for this
bag of bones, that's a snap!
--Snap! Snap! Snap!
--But Brook...
Why are you so knowledgeable
about the zombies and this island?
That has to do with when I lost
my shadow five years ago...
Naturally, they sent me back out to drift at sea.
Fortunately, I was able to
turn back by the time I awoke.
And thus I returned to the island and fought.
But in the end, I lost miserably.
Well, you'll have to pardon me.
I'm in a hurry. Take care!
Stop right there!
On top of everything you've told us,
answer this one question before you go.
I can't wait!
When I saw his corpse in the Land of Ice,
my body wouldn't stop trembling.
I had never dreamed I'd get to see
that legend with my own two eyes!
This is a zombie creator's--
Hey, Cindry-chan! Why are
you walking in front of me?
Yet another legend shall come back to life!
Long time no see, No. 900.
Now, it's time for him to awaken!
He is the only berserker to have
gone down in history as a "Devil."
Oars!
"Awakening After 500 Years!!
Oars Opens His Eyes!!"
Let's get this underway!
What is that? A-A giant's... corpse?
Even for a giant, it's freaking huge!
Don't make a sound, Chopper!
Be still, Straw Hat Luffy's shadow!
I am your new master.
I'm about to provide you with a voice and body
so that you may live as a zombie.
Forget all of your past relations
and become my obedient soldier!
We have a deal!
Wha...?
We should have made Cindry-chan
agree to forget her past, too.
Then I'd actually get to eat on plates.
I wish I could break your knee caps like plates.
Yikes! Cindry-chan, that threat was super scary!
Cindry doesn't show Hogback
any mercy, does she?
That was a Hog-smackdown...
Huh?
It's time! Awaken!
L-Luffy's shadow...!
Arise from 500 years of slumber!
Wh-What's happening?
Luffy's shadow...!
It went in!
No! Don't scream!
The corpse moved!
Who are they?
C-C-Crap! They found us!
I screamed out!
A demon has awoken!
Hey, Kumacy! Don't tell me
you've been sheltering the pirates!
My bride! What are you doing down here?
We won't let you escape!
Magnificent!
How truly overawing!
He's a piece of art! A real devil!
Meat!
Wh-What was that?
I'm hungry!
Kumacy, don't let go of me!
--Okay!
--What?!
--Now zoom!
--Yep!
--Uh-huh!
Hey! Where are the pirates?
Where did my bride go?
They ran as fast as their legs could carry them!
Boy, can they run!
Tch! I won't let them escape!
Sanji, feed me!
Huh? Sanji? Who's that?
What was that? What did we just witness?
The corpse started to move
after he inserted Luffy's shadow!
That's the deal behind these zombies.
This is how Dr. Hogback
brings people back to life...
That huge creep's ability probably stems from...
...a Devil Fruit!
Considering the first word out
of his mouth was "meat"...
...that monstrous giant clearly
has Luffy's personality, huh?
--Yeah...
--Then think back!
We ran into a penguin in the
breezeway who resembled Sanji-kun.
I won't kick a woman...
...even if it kills me!
Oh, yeah! So does that mean
he had Sanji's shadow?
I'm sure it does!
There was the samurai who hit
us with the back of his sword!
May I see your panties?
No way!
That was Brook's shadow! And we had no idea!
All of the strange things on this
island are starting to make sense!
He was just pretending to make zombies!
That man is making a mockery of human life!
How is this fulfilling "mankind's dream"?!
How is this "resurrecting the dead"?!
Dr. Hogback is a truly
wonderful man! I respect him!
He isn't the least bit
interested in saving people!
He's just a scumbag!
Chopper...
You don't have time to lament over that now!
Our pals fell victim to his
game of make-believe zombies!
Don't you see? We're the
only ones who can save them!
Let's hurry! They carried
Luffy's body down this way!
Right! The perv said to take him to the ship.
I wonder if he meant Sunny.
If Zoro and Sanji met the same fate,
we might find them there!
I swear, those guys...
...can be such a handful!
Usopp! Chopper!
Are you okay?
Wh-What?! Ow!
Hey, let go of me!
This freak... is really strong!
Care to say your last farewells?
This woman is going to marry me today!
Moron! If I can't protect a single woman...
...there was no point in being born a man!
Wow! Usopp, that weapon--!
Wh-Why does Usopp have it...?
Eat this!
Six Chamber Viper Star!
He's vanishing again!
Huh? I'm disappearing too?
Why?!
Nami vanished with him!
Nami!
Where are you?
What's that?
Some strong odor is masking his scent!
Save me, Usopp! Cho--
Hey, Nami! What happened?
Where are you?
Answer me, Nami!
Zombies, I'll let you take over from here!
Catch those two and bring
them before Moria-sama!
Shoot! Which direction
is his voice coming from?
Nami, where are you?
Usopp, behind you!
What's that?! A zombie in armor?!
A bunch of zombies are downstairs, too!
Wh-What now?
Hey, this looks bad!
We've got a bunch of zombies upstairs!
Hey, pirates! Hand over your shadows!
Ch-Chopper, don't get caught!
They'll take our shadows.
R-Right!
Shadows...!
Your shadows...!
Hand over your shadows!
There is even a zombie painting!
No!
Damn it! You guys play dirty!
You're immortal and get to
attack in numbers! It's no fair!
That's low! Aw, man!
All we want is your shadow, bro.
Crap! Let go! Shoot!
We can't let them catch us!
Wait!
There's more?!
Fork over your shadows!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Give us your shadows!
Grah! W-We... We're doomed...!
Save me!
Hey, someone else is here!
Our buddies are getting purified!
You'd better get your mitts...
...off my sworn little brothers, punks!
C-Certainly!
Who the heck are those guys?
They're rottin' bad!
Big Bro!
Robin!
Did we take too long? We're short one.
Usopp, Chopper, are you two all right?
If you're my shadow,
why don't you understand
how important this afro is?
There is a reason why I can't afford to lose!
Not my afro! Anything but the 'fro!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Belief Worth Begging to Live For!!
Brook Defends His Afro!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!