Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
They were merciless.
Wha--? M-M-Marriage?!
Don't be stupid! I won't let that happen!
He's got guts to marry Nami...
And there is a giant version of me?
That's how you make a zombie?
So we need to find a zombie in sandals,
Luffy's giant, and the cook's dogguin.
Our shadows will come back if we
throw salt in their mouths, right?
But honestly, I'm amazed you
discovered that weakness.
All of our info came from that bag of bones,
from how to defeat the zombies
to how to rescue you guys.
He...
He's a real man!
Didn't you say, "I got so
lonely that I wanted to die"?
If I were you, I would have
taken my own life ages ago.
You're doing all of this because
you want to keep a promise...
What exactly did you promise your crewmates?
It's quite simple.
Long ago, we left a member of my
crew behind at a certain location.
It was unavoidable, yet sad.
When we set sail, we vehemently
swore that we would return.
But then we were annihilated on these seas,
preventing us from keeping our promise.
I believe it has been... fifty years
now since the day we died.
Fifty years?! Hey, that was ages ago!
I wasn't even born yet!
Sorry, but I doubt he's been waiting that long!
What right do I have to decide
whether or not he's still waiting?
We swore to reunite with my crewmate
off some capes. His name is...
...Laboon!
I doubt he will forgive us for
irresponsibly dying on him...
We made a selfish promise
and died under a distant sky
where our voices couldn't reach him.
"I'm sorry we died" could never cut it!
We gave our word as men that we would return!
And that's why he's still alive...
Laboon...
Seriously?
It's him...
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Chopper wasn't there for this, huh?
We know him.
We know that whale.
"I Swear to Go See Him!!
Brook and the Cape of Promise!"
You know him?!
Why? How'd you meet?
Twin Capes is at the
entrance to the Grand Line.
A freakishly huge whale was there...
Nami-san! I see a mountain up ahead!
A mountain?! That can't be!
But it's really there!
Who cares?! Go!!
Hm?
Oh, crap!!
It's not a mountain!!
It's a black wall!!
No, it's not!!
Then what is it?!
I-I-It's a whale!!
Wh-Wh-What're we gonna do?!
--Shall we fight?
--Idiot! There's no way we can fight that!
B-B-But our path is blocked!
What're we gonna do?!
Oh, yeah! I've got an idea!
Luffy...? Hey, what're you doing?!
It doesn't work! The ship doesn't turn!
--Dammit!
--Don't give up!
Is this it...?!
Cannon?!
All right! Did it stop?
Ah... We're screwed...
This might be it...
My special seat...!
Let's get out of here before it's too late!!
What the heck is going on?!
Did he not notice the cannon attack
because his body's too big?!
Or is he just slow?!
Who knows?! Anyway,
let's get out of here now!
Ahhh! My ears hurt!
Paddle! Just paddle!!
We have to get away from him!
Luffy...?
You...! What the hell did
you do to my special seat?!
Dumbass!!
Wh-What?
--Luffy!
I'm not gonna die!!
Thanks to Luffy's silliness,
we got swallowed whole.
Th... The whale ate you?!
And that was Laboon, right?
Right. There was an ancient lighthouse
keeper who lived inside the whale.
What?!
Flower pops!
He had been treating Laboon from the inside.
The lighthouse keeper was treating him?
Supposedly he used to be
the medic on a pirate ship.
Yeah? But why did he
need treatment? Was he sick?
He was continually bashing his head
against the Red Line, which is
like a wall dividing our world.
He's been waiting fifty years for some
pirates who promised to come for him
after they traveled around the world.
But fifty years...? Those pirates sure
are making him wait a long time...
Idiot! This is the Grand Line.
They're dead.
No matter how long he waits,
they won't come back.
Yeah, it's true that fifty years ago
the Grand Line was an uncharted sea
more terrible and chaotic than it is now.
Why are you talking so hopeless?!
You don't know that for sure yet!
They might come back!
It's a very touching story!
A whale continues to believe in the
promise with his friends... Right, pops?!
Yeah... But reality is cruel.
I confirmed it using reliable information.
They ran away... from the Grand Line.
Can't be... Don't tell me...
they left without him?!
Even if they are alive,
they'll probably never come back here.
Seasons. Weather. Current. Wind direction.
They are all random. Common sense
is useless in the Grand Line.
The terror of the Grand Line takes
over weak minds in an instant.
They abandoned this whale?!
When he's been waiting for fifty years...?!
That's cruel!
If you know that, why haven't you told him?
That whale can understand
what people say, right?
I did tell him... everything.
Listen to me, Laboon! They're not gonna...
I understand you don't wanna accept it.
But you somehow have to accept it...
Laboon!
It's since then that he started
howling at Reverse Mountain
and that he started slamming
his body against the Red Line...
It's as if he's insisting that they'll come back
from the other side of that wall any time now...
What a whale...
When there's no point in waiting...
He refuses my words because if he accepts them,
it means that there is no point in waiting.
He's afraid of that more than anything.
He's from the West Blue.
There's no way of going back there now.
That's why those pirates he came here
with are his only buddies and hope.
Look at the scars on his forehead!
If he continues to hit his head hard
like that, he'll die without doubt.
It's a strange relationship, but
I've been with him for 50 long years.
I can't just stand by and watch him die now.
Hmph!
--Huh?
--What's that idiot doing?
When we looked away for a second...
Is he pretending he's mountain
climbing or something?
Gum-Gum...
...Flower Arrangement!
Isn't that a mast?
Yep. It's from our ship.
It's the main mast... Hey! Don't break the ship!
What the hell are you doing?!
Wha...?! Hey, kid!
Don't worry. He doesn't die
even when he's crushed!
Ha! Dummy!
What does he think he's doing?!
Luffy! What the hell are you trying to do?!
It's a draw!
I'm strong, aren't I?
You wanna defeat me, don't you?!
Our fight isn't over yet!
So we have to fight again.
Your buddies're dead,
but I'm your rival forever.
We definitely have to fight again
in order to decide who is stronger.
After going around the Grand Line,
we'll come back to see you again.
When I come back, let's fight again!
Hmmm. This is good.
This is the symbol of our
promise to fight again.
Until we come back, don't remove that
mark by hitting your head. Got that?!
All right!
See ya, flower pops! Thanks for the log pose!
Yeah. Have a safe trip!
See ya, whale! I'm leaving now!
To Whisky Peak...
...full speed ahead!!
Yeah!!
Luffy got him to stop killing himself
by hitting his head on the wall,
so he's still alive...
Even now, he's waiting for his
crewmates back at those capes.
It's an unbelievable story.
Both sides have been keeping
their promise for fifty years!
I had no idea one of the people
Laboon has been waiting for...
...was that skeleton!
I, too, have grown stronger
during these past five years!
We share the same thought patterns!
I see you still hold your afro dear.
You cannot possibly hope to
defend such a large weakness.
Silence!
Laboon, do you still remember us?
My heart grows tight
whenever I think about you.
Although I don't have a heart anymore!
We were not strong enough to face
the harsh cruelty of the Grand Line!
All of our friends have died!
As for me, I lost everything along with
my crewmates, including my face and body...
Even if we were to meet again,
you probably wouldn't recognize me
now that I've been reduced to a skeleton!
Don't! Don't!
Don't hurt my afro!
I have nothing left...
But I want to protect this hair,
which everyone said resembled you!
Seeing them like this, they look just alike!
Brook's hair really resembles Laboon!
Hey, Brother!
I will protect the last remnant of who I was!
I swear I will go see you!
So I'd like you to keep waiting...
...at the capes...
...where we made our promise.
I love that bag of bones
and that whale, dammit!
Shuddup!
Now I'm getting excited!
He's a musician, a talking skeleton,
has an afro, goes "Yo-ho ho!"
and was Laboon's pal!
He's coming aboard our ship,
even if I have to drag him.
He's joining our crew! Any objections, guys?
If there were, would you change your mind?
I wanna help him see Laboon again!
You've got my vote, dammit!
Same here, dummy!
I'm not afraid of that skeleton!
That's a given. I'm more concerned
about stopping Nami-san's marriage!
Hey, Zoro! Where are you going?
I'm going to raid the place. Don't we
have one more shadow to recover now?
Sweet! Guys, get ready for our counterattack!
We're gonna knock
Thriller Bark outta the water!
Yeah!
--Go!
--You're coming, stupid!
Unforgiveable! Who's trying
to marry Nami-san?!
Oh, I forgot to mention this,
but when Nami was in the bath,
that invisible man--
What did you just say?! Wh-Wh-What did
he do when she was in the bath?!
He looked her up and down.
The bastard!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Food, Nami, and Shadows!!
Luffy's Enraged Counterattack!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!