Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We swore to reunite with my crewmate
off some capes. His name is...
...Laboon!
Laboon...
Seriously?
It's him...
We know him.
We know that whale.
I had no idea one of the people
Laboon has been waiting for...
...was that skeleton!
I love that bag of bones
and that whale, dammit!
Shuddup!
Now I'm getting excited!
He's a musician, a talking skeleton,
has an afro, goes "Yo ho ho!"
and was Laboon's pal!
He's coming aboard our ship,
even if I have to drag him.
He's joining our crew! Any objections, guys?
If there were, would you change your mind?
I wanna help him see Laboon again!
You've got my vote, dammit!
Same here, dummy!
I'm not afraid of that skeleton!
That's a given. I'm more concerned
about stopping Nami-san's marriage!
Hey, Zoro! Where are you going?
I'm going to raid the place. Don't we
have one more shadow to recover now?
Sweet! Guys, get ready for our counterattack!
We're gonna knock
Thriller Bark outta the water!
Yeah!
"Food, Nami, and Shadows!!
Luffy's Enraged Counterattack!"
What's this pole?
I might as well see what's at the top.
Here I go!
That's strange. I coulda sworn
my arms could stretch...
Weird! Did I dream that up?
I wonder if my legs can stretch.
Wh-What's that?!
Is that an earthquake?!
Sheesh! He's a stinking zombie,
so why does Oars have such a free spirit?!
What the heck is he doing up there?
He's making a ruckus.
Looks like they don't stretch.
Well, darn. I'll just have to climb.
Man! Hunting down the
zombies with our shadows
sounds like it's gonna be a pain.
And Luffy's zombie is a real monster!
He's over twice the size of your average giant!
I'm not sure you guys can beat him!
Size isn't the only issue!
Luffy, he has your shadow!
Don't be such a baby!
Z-Zoro?
Size and strength mean nothing.
The only way to get Luffy's shadow
back is to take him down, right?
We don't need to search for the zombies.
Although I would like to see mine!
What's gotten into you?
If we stay like this, we'll never get to
walk under the light of the sun again!
But remember what that
grandpa zombie told us?
I saw what you just did!
You're terribly strong, aren't you?
So what did you wanna discuss?
There is a man I would like you to defeat.
I'm sure you could take him down!
He has created countless victims,
all of whom could be saved if you defeated him!
If we take out Gecko Moria,
everyone will get their shadow back!
Y-Yeah, that's what he said...
He's cutting to the heart
of the problem again...
And isn't Moria at the top of that staircase?
Whoa! He's dead on again!
So anyway, I'm gonna kick Moria's butt.
That way everyone will get their shadow back.
Sanji, you're in charge of rescuing Nami!
Yeah!
You'd better believe I am!
I don’t care if he’s an invisible
man or a dismissible sham!
I'll kick him to the ends of this fog!
I'll crash that wedding!
Oh, I forgot to mention this earlier,
but that invisible man
ogled at Nami in the bath.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
What?!
Curse him!
Don't fire him up any more.
I'm afraid he might transform into something.
Damn you, invisible man! You're gonna pay!
Awesome! He exploded!
I feel bad about letting Nami get
whisked away right before my eyes.
I'm going with Sanji!
Besides, I don't wanna run
into that Warlord again!
That skeleton's duel has me concerned.
I'm going after him.
If Straw Hat throttles Moria
before he gets to fight,
that will be the end of it.
But we'll have a problem on our hands
if his shadow trashes him first.
I'll join you, Franky.
What's the zombie of a legendary samurai
capable of? I'm dying to find out.
Nami-chan and the skeleton...
Simply put, they're the ones
who need immediate help.
Finally, subduing Moria
is key to claiming victory.
Guys, you're making this sound simple,
but he's one of the Seven Warlords!
Not a problem! So was Crocodile, remember?
And you don't see the problem?!
He nearly killed you!
I'm begging you! Please be careful!
I've already spelled this out loud
and clear, but your zombie is insane!
I get it, I get it!
I'm on my way, Nami-san!
These are for you. Guys, you each get a bag.
They contain my special
Zombie Ascension Salt Balls.
Oh, is this what you were making
back there? I should have known.
You guys have no sense of danger,
so let me make this perfectly clear!
Just because these waters
are shrouded in thick fog
doesn't guarantee safety from the sunlight!
You're only safe because it's night!
In other words, consider your drop-dead
time limit to be dawn, when the sun rises!
No matter what, you can't
forget about this time limit!
You're absolutely right! It'd suck
if I couldn't eat before dawn.
We're gonna make you rue the
day you picked a fight with us!
Gecko Moria, we're taking back
twice the amount of food you stole!
And before dawn!
Yeah!
Uh, no. That's not what I meant.
You have to recover your shadows by--
--Let's go!
--Yeah!
--Uh, no. I meant--
--Nami-san! Take my hand, honey!
Fine, ignore me!
This spells trouble! I need to
hurry and inform the master.
Awesome! This is a ship?
Neat! Too cool!
I can't see squat on these waters,
but I see a great future ahead of me!
That was a close one.
All righty! With this ship,
I'm gonna become King of the Pirates!
Where is Oars right now?
He has climbed to the top of the mast, Master.
Is that right?
Hey! Really now, Master!
We can't enjoy our Laidback Fever
with that massive, dream-filled
zombie wandering around the island!
That bastard is rottin' bad news!
Leave him be! It's just a matter of time.
He'll calm down before long.
With Oars on our side,
we'll be able to steal shadows
from stronger pirates!
We'll start creating
Special Zombies left and right!
I'm going to need stronger mario, Hogback!
Just leave that to me.
H-Hogback-sama!
B-Big news! The pirates are...!
What is the matter, Hildon?
The three pirates we just stole
shadows from awoke on their ship.
They're coming back with their crewmates!
What?!
The people we stole shadows from
couldn't possibly be awake!
I-It looks like their friends
whacked them awake!
They seem to have ties with
the Humming Swordsman!
I believe he must have tipped them off.
As proof, all of the pirates
know how to purify the zombies!
Th-They what?!
The zombies are afraid of the pirates.
As such, they are currently
running for their lives!
This is rottin' bad!
Run for it!
The Wild Zombies, Surprise Zombies,
and Soldier Zombies
didn't stand a chance against them
before they knew about salt.
Send the General Zombies after them!
They can defeat the pirates
without getting fed salt!
Come to think of it,
where the heck is Absalom?!
Uh, about that...
His wedding ceremony is about to start...
The majority of the General Zombies
are attending his wedding.
What is wrong with those idiots?!
Oh, yes! Hogback-sama, he'd like
you to get everyone pumped up
at the reception in an hour
with your belly dance.
I suppose I could. Wedding ceremonies
are memories that last a lifetime.
I should make it fun and exciting--
This isn't the time for that!
Make him cancel the wedding right this instant!
I-I am merely a zombie, so I can't
tell Absalom-sama what to do...
This incident doesn't call for that beast.
What?
If we weaken them with my ghosts,
the Soldier Zombies should be
fully capable of capturing them.
Don't freak out just because they
learned the zombies' weakness!
I will bring all of them here bound up,
so go prepare mario for the rest of the crew.
I'm going back to my room.
Come on, Kumacy.
Okay! I'm coming.
She has a point. She certainly is reliable.
I should have expected as much
from the Ghost Princess!
Yes?
You could learn a thing or two...
...from Kumacy.
What?!
A-At any rate, it looks like everything
will be all right, Moria-sama.
Oh, really? That's no fun.
Really, now! We all know
you weren't going to help...
I'm going to stay here for a while.
I want to play with Oars.
Then I have a favor to ask of you.
Since Absalom is currently preoccupied,
please give me command over two zombies.
Whatever. Pick out two
and take them with you.
Thank you very much!
In that case, I know just the two I want.
He's here!
--Where is Moria?!
--Stay away!
Get outta my way!
Give my food back!
Who's the bastard that peeped on
Nami-san when she was bathing?!
He's rottin' dangerous!
Show yourself!
They don't even need salt.
Their hearts are burning with anger.
Aren't they worried about their shadows?
"Moria's Dance Hall"
C-Captain! Five pirates are headed
straight for the dance hall!
"Gyaa!" "Waah!"
"Racing to the Dance Hall"
There are two on the lower bridge!
"Moria's Dance Hall"
"Perona's Room"
"Wonder Garden"
"Racing to the Dance Hall"
"Headed for Perona's Room"
All of them are too much for us!
Th-These guys are rottin' bad! Retreat for now!
--They're here!
--Run for it!
It ticks me off when I think about how
these weaklings managed to catch me!
If you're willing to adore me for setting ya free,
I'll let ya call me "Bro."
In your dreams!
Crap! I completely forgot!
What's wrong? What is it?
Ghosts!
I can't take it anymore! In my next life,
I hope I'm reborn as a mosquito larva.
I hope my eyebrows curl up
too much and I become an idiot.
Hey! Luffy! Sanji! What's gotten into you two?!
Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!
Robin, what just happened?
Those ghosts did it! They can
dishearten you with a touch.
As of right now, we don't
know how to counter them...
What?!
Sweet! I caught him!
We got this one!
--Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!
--Crap! They caught both of them!
Luffy! Sanji!
Shoot! Now that it's come to this--!
Lead Star!
Hurry!
If we lose heart like them, it's game over!
Our only hope is to carry them and run!
The ghosts are coming after us!
No! I don't want everyone to get caught!
This looks seriously bad!
S-Stay back!
Set sail! Set sail!
Huh?
We're falling!
Usopp! Sanji!
Wasn't that...? No, it couldn't be.
But I wasn't expecting that!
The stairs have completely vanished.
Wh-Wh-What was that? What happened?
A bunch of zombies, Usopp, and Sanji...
The whole lot of them fell
when the stairs gave out.
Forget about those two
who came hurtling down.
What the hell is that?
It came out of nowhere
and it's blocking our path!
What is this wall?!
Dammit! What just happened?
Ow, ow, ow... What was that...?
This isn't made out of stone...
Weapons Left!
What?! It wasn't effective?
No! What the heck are you two doing?!
See, this wall suddenly appeared in front of us.
Stupid! That's no wall!
That is Luffy's zombie!
What?!
This is...
Luffy's...
...z-zombie?!
"On the next episode, Oars' entry into
the fight suddenly changes everything!"
Now do you see just how
terrifying my ghosts are?
I'm going to wipe out your entire crew!
Wait! I won't let you wipe us out!
Anyone can talk big!
Negative Hollow!
"Nami, who has gone missing..."
You've made one terrible mistake.
"...is getting married?!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Usopp's the Strongest?
Leave Anything Negative to Him!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!