Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Negative Hollow!
What?!
My name is Captain Usopp.
Why?! Why aren't you falling to your knees?!
My ghost clearly hit you!
How did you counter it?
I didn't do anything to counter it.
I've always been negative!
What?!
"The General Zombies Are Down in a Flash!!
Oars Feels Like an Adventure!!"
The ghosts' negative powers
don't work on him!
What a formidable human!
My Negative Hollow is ineffective?
But that's impossible!
There is no such thing as a
human immune to that move!
D-Damn it...! I told them that
I couldn't defeat the zombies.
Why didn't they take out a single one?
Even if I defeat that woman,
it's obvious that they'll take me out!
Shoot! I'm gonna die like this.
It's hopeless! No matter
how I look at it, I'm doomed!
I must have made some sort
of mistake a second ago.
You're going to lose all will to
live when they strike at once.
Four times the negativity! Negative Hollows!
They got him!
All of them landed direct hits!
Sweet!
Ever since Thriller Bark got up and running,
no one has been able to
stand up to those ghosts!
He out-negatived the Negative Ghosts!
Kumacy, sorry I'm always so mean to you.
The effect has spread back to Perona-sama!
Is that man a sage or a saint?!
Listen... When it comes to thinking negatively...
...I'll have you know I'm unbeatable!
Wow! He's super confident in a bad way!
But why is it? For someone bursting
with confidence, he looks mighty small.
Isn't he trying to escape?
--Busted!
--Wait!
Crud! They saw through my plan.
Wild Shot: Salt Star!
Curse you! You've started to purify
my darling Wild Zombies yet again!
Stay away from me! Salt Star!
He's got salt! Be careful!
Covering your mouths is against the rules!
I wish I had kept that "Salt Star" part to myself!
I can't believe Usopp's
negative outlook came in handy!
If it weren't for him,
she could have wiped us out!
She's got one terrifying ability...
--Hey...
--Huh?
This is where our paths diverge.
I'm gonna head over to Nami-san!
Got it! Be sure to save her!
You bet! I'm the Will-o-the-wisp of Love!
Nami-san!
I won't let you get married!
He jumped...
Wasn't this pretty high up?
Well, supposedly an adrenaline rush
can dull a person's sense of pain.
Anyway, we need to reach
that mansion's top floor!
--Yeah!
--That's where we'll find the skeleton!
Are you quite finished yet?
Why don't you be a man and admit defeat?
You are like a phoenix... Or perhaps a zombie!
You shouldn't have the strength left to stand.
I am just about ready to fully immobilize you
so that you will never come
after your shadow again.
What shall I sever with my
special move, the Notch Slash?
You don't...
You don't know a darn thing...
Don't use that name!
I came from a certain kingdom's assault convoy.
The quick slash that I specialized in
was called "Requiem La Banderole."
The nickname my crewmates gave
that technique out of admiration was...
...Three-Pace Hum: Notch Slash!
You may share my personality and abilities,
but I don't want you to use that
name if you cannot remember
my past and the feelings I harbor!
If you feel that you are
the true master of this style,
prove as much by defeating my "fake" style.
This is your last chance.
Three-Pace Hum...
...Notch Slash!
Seeing them like this, they look just alike!
Brook's hair really resembles Laboon!
Hey, Brother!
Laboon!
More than anything,
I want to apologize to you...
I want to apologize for my endless bad luck...
Fifty years on the dark sea...
Time has passed so slowly...
I can't believe my life was in vain!
What a lonesome... life it's been!
I've been so lonely...
Now then, where should I begin cutting?
For starters, this afro must go.
What?! The mansion is shaking!
Hey, why is the mansion shaking?
Like I'd know! Maybe there's an earthquake.
Is that the lab?
There he is! Hey, Skeleton!
Dude! You took a royal beating,
but you're still with us, aren't you?
You're still alive, right?!
Wh-What are you doing here...?
I can't allow this! You should
not touch the loser in a duel!
Whoa, there!
Is it you?
Are you the legendary samurai who
supposedly killed a dragon a long time ago?
I've been wanting to see you!
What's going on up there?
The whole place is shaking!
The ship has probably gotten
caught in a weird current.
I think it's probably your fault, too!
So, what do you want? What brought you here?
Right. You had some nerve,
tearing off my shadow earlier.
I'll be taking my shadow back.
Right along with Zoro's, Sanji's, Brook's,
the grandpa zombie's, and everyone's!
You're one greedy bastard!
How are you going to get them back?
I'm gonna kick your butt!
Smooch! Smooch! Smooch! Smooch!
Smooch! Smooch!
Smooch! Smooch! Smooch!
Smooch! Smooch! Smooch!...
Just a second! Why is the ship shaking?!
I can't kiss my bride!
Absalom-sama!
What is it? Do you know what the deal is?
Our giant ship, Thriller Bark,
is caught in a strange current!
It's changing our course!
The entire island is shaking!
How did that happen?!
Well, it looks like that Special Zombie
is messing with the rudder.
What?!
It's moving! It's moving!
Take that!
Move!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
General Zombies, all of you are
to set out at once! Stop Oars!
Sir!
Move! Move! Move!
Oars!
Playtime is over, Special Zombie Oars.
Chop him down from the legs!
Where's Oars?
He vanished! Oars vanished!
But he's so big...
How could he be so quick?!
There he is! Look up!
Gum-Gum...
Actually, I'm not made of rubber.
Gatling!
Don't get in the way of my adventure!
Annihilated?! But they just left...
Uh, right. They're as flat as pancakes.
They composed the strongest
zombie army on the island!
They were General Zombies!
Right. They were out in a flash.
Absurd... Wasn't Oars on our side...?
Why is he going on a rampage?
Zombies have no choice but to obey our orders!
What will happen to Thriller Bark
if we let him run loose...?
Nami-san!
I came for you!
There she is!
He's part of the Straw Hat Crew!
Amazing...! He pushed Ryuma back.
Who is he?
He's a stinkin' aggressive pirate swordsman
who practices the Three-Sword Style.
He's damn strong!
If your pride will stand for it,
I bet he'd recover your shadow for you.
What do you say?
My shadow? Really? Oh, please do!
I'm begging you!
Please recover my shadow for--
Shut up! Keep quiet!
--Ploink!
--Hey! Skeleton!
You know, that looks like a good sword.
You have a good eye! This is in fact
one of the 21 O-Wazamono swords.
It has a black blade with a reversed saw.
This famous sword is called Shusui.
It's not the sort of thing you see every day.
So it's a sweet sword? Looks like
I've come across a nice find!
Of course, I figured you'd have something
halfway decent since you're a samurai...
All right! I'll be using that sword from now on.
You're too cool!
Ploink!
Nami-san! I will never
leave your side ever again!
--Right! I will always be with you!
--Bastard! We were in the middle
--No, for all eternity!
--of an important ceremony!
Listen to me!
Why do I have to listen to you?
Mincemeat is too good for the likes of you!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Blazing Knight Sanji!!
Kick Down the Fake Wedding!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!