Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Ow, ow, ow...
What's the hold-up?
Weren't you going to kick my
butt as many times as it takes?
Yeah! I will in just a sec, so hang tight!
Well, I don't mind the wait,
but he'll come back if you don't hurry.
"He"? Who are you talking about?
You!
That's right. I don't have
time to be goofing off.
I need to hurry back.
Oh, jeez. You're such a handful.
Don't! Robin is a lady!
A lady...?
What of it?!
Robin!
Unbelievable! Sanji actually kicked...
Golden...
No!
...Pound!
Sleep till dawn!
Didn't that samurai just say something?
Long story short, what just happened?
In short, the fight is apparently over.
I've never seen a duel like this before.
That samurai wasn't taking me
the least bit seriously!
"Slashes Dancing on the Rooftop!!
Showdown: Zoro vs. Ryuma!"
You think that you can steal
my black sword, Shusui?
To be precise, I'm going to take
the sword from beside your corpse.
I see. You are full of spirit!
I wouldn't provoke him if I were you...
I see you also carry three swords.
Yeah, but one is a broken blade.
I just carry it at my waist because
it doesn't feel right without it.
I'm a Three-Sword Style swordsman.
A Three-Sword Style swordsman?
I've never heard of such a thing.
Is it a circus act?
It's a pity I can't let you
see it in action right now.
I'd break that squat nose of yours!
I'm sure. You seem quite strong.
Emotions beyond my
recollection are surfacing.
I feel as though I am standing
face to face with a giant beast.
It is a strange, exhilarating sensation!
I feel as though I could start dancing.
What a shock!
Aubade Coup Droit!
H-He used a pistol?!
I-It was a thrust!
If I used that move,
it wouldn't be as impressive!
He shot a hole through the wall!
To shoot a thrust like that...
Just how strong is he?!
I'd say it's a draw.
Yep.
You nearly got me.
What the heck?!
When did that
Haramaki freak get in a counter attack?!
The attacks... were nearly simultaneous.
So he can throw his attacks as well.
The skirmish between them
just now truly did end in a draw.
The samurai zombie is currently
using my shadow to move,
but the samurai was probably an expert
swordsman when he was still alive.
I believe those two may possess
the same type of build as swordsmen.
Does it mean anything if
they share the same build?
It means their strengths
lie in the same areas.
I doubt this duel will last long.
Prelude Au Fer!
A sword-breaker assault?!
Two-Sword Style... Flash!
Demon Magma Bear!
Gavotte Bond en Avant!
Two-Sword Style Sword Draw...
...Rashomon!
He blocked my attack!
They slashed through the support beams!
Oh, crud! This floor is toast!
It's dangerous up here!
Man, hang on! We're gettin' outta here.
The whole roof's comin' down!
Seventy-two Pound Phoenix!
Polka Remise!
Weapons Left!
Dang, that was close!
Careful! You don't want to fall!
Falling...!
How can they fight with such poor footing...?
I'm afraid my swords will break
if this drags out much longer.
He truly has the body and
spirit needed to support the
strength of a legendary swordsman.
One-Sword Style!
Soaring Dragon...
Three-Pace Hum...
...Notch Slash!
...Blaze!
My wound is bursting into flames!
I have lost.
Once, a legendary samurai
wielded the great sword Shusui.
I am sure this katana would be
happy to have you as its master.
Didn't that samurai just say something?
Long story short, what just happened?
In short, the fight is apparently over.
I've never seen a duel like this before.
That samurai wasn't taking
me the least bit seriously!
Hey, Skeleton! What do you mean it's "over"?
It was an incredible duel...
It pains my samurai heart
that I must taste defeat...
The fact that you feel ashamed proves...
...that you are a swordsman
in both mind and body!
I wish we could have met
when you were still alive.
I-Isn't that...?
It sure is! It's my shadow,
which Moria snatched away
from me five years ago!
Look! It's copying whatever I do!
Isn't that a given? It's your shadow.
This might be hard for you to understand,
but I'm finally my old self again!
I'm touched! I'm moved!
These emotions are coursing through my veins!
Ah, not that I have any veins.
I guess they go "bone deep."
It's back! After five years,
I have a shadow again!
I'll take your sword, but I'll pretend
that our duel never happened...
...samurai of the Wano Kingdom!
I wonder if Sanji has already
found and rescued Nami.
And how are Luffy and the others doing?
At any rate, I've just gotta tell
everyone about how I beat
that Horo-Horo Chick when they
didn't stand a chance against her!
I can't wait to see their faces!
Perona-sama!
Do you think she's okay?
Of course! Captain Kumacy and Lieutenant
Gentleman Hippopotamus went after her!
By now, Mr. Negative Nose
is the one crying like a baby!
Phew, that was a close call!
All of my hard work would go down
the drain if I got taken down now.
There'd go my bragging rights.
Moving on! Sanji! Guys!
What happened here...?
Weren't they supposed to be
attending Absalom-sama's wedding?
The Special Zombie did this to them.
Absalom-sama ordered them
to forcibly stop Oars,
but he took them out in the blink of an eye.
Absurd! Even though he's a
Special Zombie, he's still a zombie!
Why would he attack his comrades?
Oars is rather new to his life as a zombie.
Apparently he still has
Straw Hat's personality.
Awesome! This is a ship?
All righty! With this ship,
I'm gonna become King of the Pirates!
Gum-Gum...
Actually, I'm not made of rubber.
Gatling!
Don't get in the way of my adventure!
I suspect it will take a while for him
to become an obedient zombie...
Wh-What?! He took out all of these
General Zombies in an instant?
That's right.
They must have let their guard down!
Otherwise this never would have happened.
If I were you, I'd start running!
Otherwise, Oars will do you in as well!
Silence, Hildon! Are you mocking us?!
The monster! How dare he kill our comrades?!
Since Absalom-sama gave those orders,
no one will mind if we
teach him a thing or two!
I swear by our title as the strongest
that we will let Oars know just how
powerful the General Zombies are!
--Ch-Charge!
--Yeah!
Don't get in my way!
Gum-Gum...
Oh, oops! That's right. I'd forgotten!
I need to hurry on back.
What happened to all of that
fire you had earlier, Straw Hat?
Damn it! Don't act so high-and-mighty
when you aren't fighting, Giant Shallot!
I've already told you:
I am the man who will let others
make me the King of the Pirates.
And it looks like the day I realize my
dream has gotten a whole lot closer!
I'll keep taking you down until
I recover all of the shadows!
Like I said, defeating me won't--
When ya get down to it, I just need
to defeat you and this shadow!
Gum-Gum Rocket!
I don't care what happens to you,
but as things stand, your future looks bleak.
A more powerful foe will be here
any minute now, you know?
Dr. Chopper, listen. The zombies are happy.
After all, they are given a second
chance to live amongst us as humans!
--You're wrong!
--I'm wrong? Like your medical knowhow--
Shut up! That isn't a medical procedure!
I'll never forgive you!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Chopper Is Furious!!
Hogback's Evil Medical Practices!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!