Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
One-Sword Style!
Soaring Dragon...
Three-Pace Hum...
...Notch Slash!
...Blaze!
I have lost.
Once, a legendary samurai
wielded the great sword Shusui.
I am sure this katana would be
happy to have you as its master.
I'll take your sword, but I'll pretend
that our duel never happened...
...samurai of the Wano Kingdom!
"Chopper Is Furious!!
Hogback's Evil Medical Practices!"
Tell me: How does it feel to be
subjugated by the might of your friends?
I can't believe you tried to stuff salt
down my throat with your weird powers!
They're strong!
Darn it! I never expected
Sanji to kick Robin.
He isn't Sanji anymore!
Who is that Sanji guy?
Don't make me kill you, jerk face.
I'm afraid they don't have a single
memory of your days as crewmates!
Occasionally fresh zombies retain
some of the shadow's feelings,
but these shadows have
fully settled into their bodies.
They've completely lost their human hearts.
They've become zombies that
will obey my every command!
As far as zombies are concerned,
their orders are absolute!
I'm actually happy... to see that
you're rotten to the core, Hogback!
In all actuality, you have
saved countless lives.
I really did respect you as a doctor.
The same goes for your zombie research.
Death can come suddenly...
I'm sure there are a lot
of things the deceased
and those they left behind
never got a chance to say.
I'm not asking for years. If they
could have just a few minutes!
If there was a way to bring back the dead...
...even if people cast stones,
calling it "evil medicine"...
...it would mean the world to those it saved!
So when you said that you were
researching how to "resurrect the dead,"
I thought that you truly
were an amazing doctor.
Fool! Why would I go to
such lengths for others?
You said that you respected how I used
to save lives, but it was the same deal!
I was simply a genius!
I conducted operations for money,
but there was no stopping
the unwanted flood of patients
that came from around
the world for treatment!
"Save my dad!"
"Save my child!"
"Save my beloved!"
It got old!
It was a pain!
The run-of-the-mill quack
couldn't save them, but I could.
Can you understand the hardships of a genius?
You're free to respect me if you want.
But your disappointment is uncalled for.
If you can't forgive me as a doctor
because I don't match your ideals,
then you never understood me
to begin with, stupid reindeer!
Are you going to start
lecturing me on medical ethics?!
I wouldn't dream of it!
I don't consider you a doctor!
What?!
The same goes for these zombies.
All you've done is reanimate the dead.
They aren't alive!
Don't take life so lightly!
You can be rather cruel.
They're moving right before your very eyes,
and you think they aren't alive?
Yeah, you heard me!
Dr. Chopper, the "dead" are being given
a second shot at life. It's a miracle!
Why would you want to reject these lives?
Behold!
Don't move.
Now start licking the floor, Cindry.
Okay, Hogback-sama.
Didn't you see that room, Dr. Chopper?
That is my room.
The numerous photos were of the stage
actress Victoria Cindry before she died.
I had been in love with
her for a very long time.
I wasn't the only one. Her beauty had
charmed men from across the country.
There!
You're all set, Doctor.
S-S-Sorry! I shouldn't make a
patient sew a button back on.
It's all right.
Thanks to you, I'll be
able to go back on stage.
Thank you very much.
Father! Mother! Sorry to
have kept you waiting.
Uh, excuse me...
Despite her popularity,
she was down to earth.
She was close to her family...
She was kind to everyone...
A truly wonderful woman.
But that woman...
...rejected my proposal,
when my renown as a doctor
had let me obtain anything I wanted.
She already had a fiancé.
And shortly thereafter, I caught wind
of some news that left me dumbfounded.
Cindry had died in an accident.
I felt drained.
I ultimately abandoned my work.
That is when he came.
A giant man appeared before me.
It was my master, Gecko Moria!
Dr. Hogback, lend me a hand!
And I boarded this ship under the condition
that he would use his miraculous
ability to resurrect Cindry!
I stole her body...
It was so easy to obtain the actress,
Cindry, and bend her to my will!
Cindry-chan!
I wish plates would cease to exist.
Plates?!
The personality of the woman who had
spurned me was of little consequence.
As long as she retained her beauty...
That is the zombie, Cindry-chan!
Of course I'm thrilled,
but I'm sure she is as well!
She gets to live in this
world as a human again.
How could you call her a human?
Make her stop licking the floor!
When a human's heart isn't linked
to her body, she is no longer human!
By using corpses that can't
stick up for themselves,
you're creating nothing but monsters!
For every zombie you create,
you're making a person miserable!
I figured that out, which is
why I can't forgive you guys!
Don't lecture me on life when you're
a mediocre doctor, pirate reindeer!
Cindry-chan, finish those two off!
Okay.
I'm going to turn you guys into marios!
Rejoice, Dr. Chopper! Once you are dead,
I will make you my assistant,
since you admire me so much.
Square Plate Blades!
One! Two! Three!
Stop it...!
Damn you!
Chopper!
Don't underestimate her
just because she's a woman!
I've enhanced her muscles for combat.
You don't have to listen to
that monster! Ow, ow, ow...
I will kill you!
You poor thing! And here you're already dead.
How would the family you left behind
feel if they knew about this?
Let go of me!
If your family saw you covered in stitches
and being used as an expendable soldier,
it would tear them apart!
Let go of me!
The heart you were born and
raised with is already dead,
but your body is being forced
to do the bidding of others.
What the hell?!
Are you questioning your eyes? Face facts!
This is mankind's eternal dream!
I've resurrected the dead!
The dead can come back to life!
Is the ability to move all that matters?
Humans are freer than that!
You're the one who treats them
like they aren't humans!
Robin, hurry and feed her salt!
Right!
Dogguin! Jigoro! Help Cindry out!
Take out the pests!
I failed! Chopper!
Three-Sword Style...
...108-Pound Phoenix!
Stop it, Zoro!
Doce Fleurs!
Not... her again!
Take out... the pests!
--Jerk!
--Huh?
Why did you attack me along
with them?! Don't be a pest!
Now you're asking for it!
That's how I feel!
The pests are supposed to get taken outside!
Then get going! He issued that order to me!
It was meant for me!
I just said he issued it to me!
Jerk!
Hey! What are you two doing?
Hey, knock it off! You
need to actually work--
--Robin!
--On it!
Isn't this turning out to be fascinating?
You ordered them to "take out the pests."
They are obediently trying to
obey that order even as I speak.
I wonder what would happen
if you didn't issue a new order.
Even without their memories,
those two are still like water and oil...
Unbelievable.
Isn't this a rather tall tower?
Huh?
Why don't you order the two
of us to jump out the window?
Robin...?
What's gotten into you?
I'll say that as many times as you like!
Jump! Jump! I want you to
jump out the window together!
--Sure.
--Huh?
No, not you! Wait!
Run faster! He wants us to jump out together.
Don't tell me what to do!
We don't want to.
I won't forget this!
You tricked me! You're horrible!
You're the scum of all mankind!
Luffy will purify all of the
zombies when he defeats Moria.
You're the one I want to throttle, Hogback!
C-C-Cindry! Buy me some time!
I'm gonna run for the hills!
Where is my answer? I'll give you
another shadow if they take you out.
Don't worry about dying!
What the--?!
I cannot...
move.
C-Cindry!
He's here! He's here!
Well, now you get to meet him...
...Straw Hat.
He's huge! This is my shadow?
So he has finally decided to submit to me!
Tell me: Who is your master?
My master is Moria-sama.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Oars Roars! Come Out, Straw Hat Crew!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!