Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Don't take life so lightly!
You can be rather cruel.
They're moving right before your very eyes,
and you think they aren't alive?
Behold!
Now start licking the floor, Cindry.
Okay, Hogback-sama.
When a human's heart isn't linked
to her body, she is no longer human!
By using corpses that can't
stick up for themselves,
you're creating nothing but monsters!
For every zombie you create,
you're making a person miserable!
Don't lecture me on life when you're
a mediocre doctor, pirate reindeer!
Cindry-chan, finish those two off!
One! Two! Three!
You don't have to listen to
that monster! Ow, ow, ow...
I will kill you!
Is the ability to move all that matters?
Humans are freer than that!
You're the one who treats them
like they aren't humans!
Dogguin! Jigoro! Help Cindry out!
Take out the pests!
Three-Sword Style...
...108-Pound Phoenix!
Why did you attack me along with them?!
Jump! Jump! I want you to
jump out the window together!
I cannot...
move.
C-Cindry!
He's here! He's here!
Wh-Who's here?
Well, now you get to meet him,
Straw Hat.
"Oars Roars! Come Out, Straw Hat Crew!"
Hey, what's gotten into you, Cindry-chan?
Come on, Cindry-chan!
Cindry-chan! Earth to Cindry-chan!
Hey, what's the matter?
I...
cannot move.
I cannot stop crying.
You can't move? What the
heck are you talking about?
And dry those crocodile tears!
Do you realize who gave you a body
that can move as long as you have a soul?!
You exist to serve your master!
That is how zombies find
meaning in their existence!
It looks like the owner of
her body is trying to resist him.
She died ten years ago.
Could the body still have a
will even if the soul has left?
Even if we scoured every library in the world,
I doubt we could find an answer.
I will kill those two.
Atta girl! You've finally returned
to your senses, Cindry-chan!
Be sure to buy lots of time!
Enough for me to get away.
What a pity. I was hoping
for some kind of miracle.
Doce Fleurs!
Tsk!
Wait!
Like I'm gonna wait!
Wh-Why is the room shaking?!
Damn it! You're a pirate reindeer
just pretending to be human!
How dare you side with a bunch of corpses?!
You aren't even human, you stinking monster!
A monster, a cyborg, a pervert,
a guy with a long nose,
and a moss head follow my captain!
Unlike you guys, he doesn't
have to boss around corpses
that can't speak for themselves!
Let go, freak!
Robin!
All right! I'm on it.
Pierna Fleurs!
Huh? What's going on?
What? What? What?!
W-W-Wait, Dr. Chopper! If I fall
from this height and hit my head,
my genius noggin that is a gift
to the world will crack open!
Are you okay with that?
I don't care!
The zombies are less rotten
than the stuff between your ears!
Why don't you calm down a bit, Dr. Chopper?
Eat this! Robi-Cho Suplex!
He's twice the size of a giant.
So this is my zombie?
I've been waiting for you, Oars!
It looks like your shadow has
finally settled into your body.
Have you become an obedient zombie?
Tell me! Who is your master?
My master is Moria-sama.
What?!
Hey, how could you say that?!
Are you really my shadow?
Don't listen to this jerk!
Who are you, punk in the straw hat?
Let me present your
commemorative first mission.
Look at the wanted posters
attached to your arm!
Those ruffians are currently
running amok on Thriller Bark.
They are the Straw Hat Crew!
Crush them mercilessly and
toss them onto their ship!
I don't care if any of them die.
Those worth over 100 million
won't die if you squash them anyway.
Cut loose! Let me see
the extent of your power.
Okay, Moria-sama.
Ah, there's one! It's Straw Hat!
Goodbye, Straw Hat!
You're running away?! You jerk!
Gum-Gum...
H-H-Hey, wait! That's dangerous!
...Bell!
What?!
What's that?
L-Luffy's zombie...!
Oars!
The floor is collapsing!
Chopper, come over here!
Okay!
Huh?!
Ouch!
That was a close call.
This... is Luffy...
Hogback and Cindry fell down a floor.
Crap! This is heavy.
Cindry-chan, get this stone slab off of me!
C-Cindry-chan, hurry! Save me on the double!
Look! Oars is coming.
I... I can't get stepped
on when I'm a genius!
Hey! Why are you just standing there?
I'm your master!
I... cannot move.
What?!
You're repeating that nonsense again?!
Your sense of loyalty is
the only will zombies have!
Now save me already!
Your looks are all you
have, you crappy corpse!
Hey! Hurry it up, Cindry!
Oars is coming!
Oars, look down! You imbecile!
It's me, you wretched ingrate!
I'm the one who modified your
body so that you could move!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What gives?! What gives?!
That last quake was way worse
than any of the ones before it!
L-L-L... Luffy's zombie!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What is making everything shake?!
What gives?!
No way! Is that Luffy's zombie?!
Crap!
Nami-san, seriously! This isn't
the time to get your beauty sleep!
Screw it! I'm gonna have to run for now.
Huh? Nami-san?
Nami-san?
Wh-What?!
Nami-san vanished...
It couldn't be...!
It looks like the tables are turned.
Jerk! You're still alive?
Beast Man, show yourself!
It looks like we finally
have control of this devil.
I've won! This time she will be my bride!
Damn it! Give Nami-san back!
Where the hell are you?!
Have him play with you!
Enjoy the ultimate zombie!
Hey, did you feel that just now?
Yes, I did. It was so ominous
that it made my hair stand on end.
Oh! But since I'm a skeleton,
I don't have any hair!
Ah! I do have hair!
Punk! That's your precious afro!
Don't forget about it!
Maybe you'd rather have
a pompadour hairstyle!
--Uh, pass!
--Come over here!
No, don't! Don't cut it!
What is that?
I'm getting goose bumps!
Oh! I'm a skeleton, so--
Gah! Something just popped out!
What is that?!
Th-That's... a zombie!
It's Luffy's zombie.
Look over there!
Didn't Curly Cook come out with him?
Damn it!
Nami-san...
What is that stupid cook doing?
Wait!
Moria!
Are you going to chase
after me no matter what?
I'm worried about that huge zombie,
but taking you down is the only way
to recover everyone's shadows.
I won't let you escape!
Look! I am the last one laughing!
She sure is sound asleep.
Let's go elsewhere... and hold
the ceremony... one more time,
my quiet bride!
Is Perona-sama all right?
She's unconscious!
I don't see any injuries.
Captain Kumacy and the Lieutenant
were taken out! Curse Long Nose!
Get her out of here!
This mansion is rottin' dangerous!
The Special Zombie will avenge them!
Things look rottin' bad!
Get away from the mansion!
The Special Zombie is fighting!
Get rottin' far!
H-He's huge! I can see
his head over the mansion.
Oh, crap!
Usopp!
Chopper! Robin!
W-W-We've got a problem!
O-O-Our wanted posters are
a-attached to Zombie Luffy's arm!
I-I'm sure of it!
He is totally...
...coming after us!
Come out, Straw Hat Crew!
The freak! Is he trying to get in our way?
Darn it, Luffy! Are you going
to crush your own crew?
Someone must have issued the order.
I hope the real Luffy is all right.
What is that?!
Can we take that monster down?
This should be fun.
Sanji!
He's insanely fast for someone so huge!
If he lands a solid hit,
it could do serious damage!
Crap! What is he going to do to Sanji?
Hey, get back!
Don't underestimate me, monster!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy Is the Enemy! The Ultimate
Zombie vs. the Straw Hat Crew!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!