Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
What's wrong, girlie?
Do you want me to return
the village that badly?
Then how's this?
Let's make an agreement.
Agreement?
That's right.
Gather up 100 million
Berries and bring it here.
Do so and I'll let the village
go and give you freedom.
--Honest?!
--Honest!
I'd die before I break an
agreement concerning money.
It doesn't matter how
many years it takes.
I'll honor our agreement.
I absolutely will save up
100 million Berries!
Bellemere-san! I will do it!
No matter how much time it takes!
"Luffy Rises!
Result of the Broken Promise!"
Gen-san? And the navy?
Are you the girl thief known as Nami?
Our information has it you've hidden
treasure you stole from pirates.
The government hereby confiscates
all the property you have stolen!
What's the matter?
Did you not hear me?
The government
hereby takes possession
of everything you
stole from the pirates.
My, my. You're very passionate
about your duties, I see.
You're not brave enough
to stand up to pirates,
so you deal with sneak thieves
instead to earn brownie points.
Talk about superb!
Here's a warning for you.
I'm a leader of the Arlong Pirates.
Mess with me, and Arlong
won't sit by quietly!
Silly girl. Do you think you're
dealing with me on equal footing?
Find the stolen goods!
Wait!
Stop!
Is this what the navy
should be doing right now?!
The Arlong Pirates have killed people,
and even destroyed towns!
You know that!
He's ruling over this island and
trampling all over people's lives!
Is ignoring that major problem
and raking in stolen goods from a thief
what the government stands for?!
Don't talk all big.
Continue your search!
People all over the island've been
waiting for your help for years now!
How dare you just pass
them by and come here!
Colonel! This tangerine
orchard seems suspicious!
Dig it up!
Keep your filthy hands off of
Bellemere-san's tangerine orchard!
I won't let you have my money!
That money's for...
This girl's money is meant
to save Cocoyashi Village!
What gives you the right
to take it away, navy man?!
Oh? A lowly village representative,
talking down to a navy colonel?
Gen-san... How do you know about that?
I've always known, Nami.
--I'm... joining...
--Eh?
I'm joining... the Arlong Pirates...
Nami!
You...
Nami...
I couldn't believe
what you'd done then,
so I confronted Nojiko later.
Everyone in the village
has known since then
that you stayed with the Arlong
Pirates so you could save the village.
But we pretended we didn't know.
Because our hopes would keep you
from running away from Arlong
if you ever decided to.
You can't be serious...
What on earth are you talking about?
You're saying all the
villagers are thieves,
and we should arrest them?
He's saying that each and every
one of us is fighting to live!
But only because we can't rely
on any of you government people!
If you're not gonna save our village,
then get the hell out of here!
Dilly-dally and Arlong'll
go after your ship, too!
Mr. Arlong will?
I wouldn't be so sure...
You still haven't found it?!
We're looking for 100 million
Berries here! Not a grain of rice!
Hey, you! How do you
know how much there is?!
Oh, the 100 million?
I just got the feeling
there's that much.
Don't tell me he...
Don't tell me Arlong sent you here!
Who knows?
We're simply dealing with theft
as any government workers would.
What rotten scum!
I can't believe the navy would
stoop to being pirate cronies!
Arlong!
I found it!
This is incredible!
I'm impressed you could
gather this much, girl!
It's all ragged and stained with blood...
No matter! Money is money!
Thirty percent of this is all mine!
Don't touch that...
Don't touch that... Don't touch that...
Nami...
Don't touch that!
Nami!
Nojiko!
Nojiko!!
A pinwheel, huh?
Man, that was so cool!
I thought up a good move!
Doctor! Doctor!
What is it, Gen-san?!
--Nojiko's been shot!
--By who?!
--The navy!
--The navy?
Nojiko!
I'm fine...
Arlong's been working with the navy.
What?!
He's lied to Nami
for the last eight years.
He never intended to
honor their agreement!
--What?!
--Oh, no! Then...
That bastard!
He lied to our Nacchan!
Nacchan!
Nami...
Heya, Nami! What's up?
Need help with anything?
Are you still here?!
This has nothing to do with you!
Leave the damn island already!
Arlong... Arlong...!
Arlong!
I'd die before I break an
agreement concerning money.
It doesn't matter how
many years it takes.
I'll honor our agreement.
Arlong!
What's her problem?
Oh? What's wrong,
skilled surveyor of ours?
Why the angry look?
The navy men you have under
your control stole all my money!
What happened to dying before
breaking promises about money?!
Why?!
When did I break our promise?
Don't play dumb!
You teamed up with the navy to--
When did I break our
promise? Let's hear it!
Damn you... Damn you! Damn you!
I see! So your money's been stolen?
How unfortunate.
But an agreement is an agreement.
If you can't gather up
100 million Berries for me to see,
I'm afraid I can't give
you the village back.
Scum!
It's only 100 million Berries!
Just start saving up again!
Or are you gonna run out on me?
But if you do run away, I'll kill
everyone in Cocoyashi Village.
Nami...
We pretended we didn't know.
Because our hopes would keep you
from running away from Arlong
if you ever decided to.
Oh? Finally running away, huh?
Shouldn't we chase after her?
Chase? What for? She won't run away.
She could never abandon
the lives of the villagers.
You certainly do know
how to play dirty...
No way would I let such an exceptional
surveyor as Nami go so easily.
But I'm not a heartless devil.
Once she's done surveying
all of the world's seas,
I'll give her her freedom!
That's like decades from now!
Not even a hundred years'd be enough!
Alright! Let's meet up with Luffy ASAP!
Hey, Sanji. What're you doing?
Appreciating happiness.
What're you talking about?
Nami-san's lived with many times
the suffering of a normal person.
I'm going to take away
that suffering of hers.
Is there any happiness
greater than this?
Your ulterior motive's
way obvious, Love Cook.
I'm fighting for a beautiful person.
What's wrong with that?
That's not what this is for!
It's for Nami and the villagers!
Shaddup.
Quit your jabbering and let's go!
No more of this!
Take up your weapons!
Let's fight!
Gen-san! Everyone!
Please! Don't be hasty!
You can't die! It'll all be over!
You have to survive,
or everything will end!
Eight years ago, we swore
not to throw away our lives!
No matter how painful and insulting
it was to be ruled by them,
we swore to fight the patient fight
as long as Nami was cheerful!
But this is their answer!
Now that our village's chance for
freedom is gone, we have no hope!
More than that,
we must make those fishmen pay
for toying with that girl's kindness!
Any objections?!
Of course not! Let's go!
We were always fully ready
to fight at any time!
I refuse to let them
rule over me any more!
Wait, everyone!
Nami!
Just a little more!
Just wait a little more!
I'll work hard again!
I'll save up the money again!
It'll be easy this time!
I'm used to it! I'll be fine!
There's no need to worry at all!
This is nothing
compared to back then!
Please, no more dying!
Everyone! I'm fine! I'm just fine!
You can stop now... Even you
know there's no point now...
You fought very well, carrying our
lives on your back all this time...
Joining them must've been
even more painful for you
than being cut through the heart...
You fought very well.
Gen-san...
Leave the village now.
Gen-san?!
Do it, Nami.
W-What?!
--Nacchan...
--Nami...
You're crafty, and you have a dream.
Nojiko! Everyone!
I won't let you go!
Stop it, everyone!
I don't want to see anyone
else get hurt by them!
You'll die, you know!
We know.
It's no use!
We've made up our minds!
Get out of our way, Nami!
Let's go, everyone!
Even if we can't win, let's
show 'em what we're made of!
Arlong!
Arlong! Arlong!
Arlong! Arlong! Arlong!
Arl--
Luffy...
What do you want?!
You don't even know anything!
You don't even know what's happened
on this island the past 8 years!
Yeah. I don't know.
This has nothing to do with you!
I told you, leave the
damn island already!
Yeah. You told me.
Leave! I don't need you!
Leave! Leave! Leave! Leave!
Leave! Leave! Leave!
Leave!
Luffy...
Help me...
Of course I will!
Don't touch my treasure!
Luffy...
Let's go.
Yeah!
Hey! Are you guys alright?!
Did Arlong do this to you?!
Move aside.
We have business with the fishmen.
Now that we know the
truth about Big Sis Nami,
we felt the only thing
we can do was defeat Arlong.
So we challenged him...
But we lost by a hair.
Sorry, but we're not letting
you through this door,
seeing as you have no hope for victory!
What?!
We're waiting for certain
men to arrive here, you see!
Certain men?
I'd bet my life on it. They will come!
Here they come!
It's them...
Just who are they?
If they can't handle them,
then there's no hope
for not only this island,
but for the future of
the entire East Blue!
The faces of those four men
who're here to change destiny...
Burn their images into your eyes!
Move aside.
Hey, do you think those two
idiots were part of Zoro's group?
Zoro's? They seemed too weak for that.
They're not even worth killing.
That's for sure!
What the...?
Which one of you is Arlong?!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
You just had to run ahead by yourself!
I said don't hog all the prey!
Really?
--Huh?
--What's wrong?!
Yeah, that's the thing!
I'm kind of in trouble! Hear me out!
Oh, crap! That guy
plans to do something!
What do I do?
What do I do?! What do I do?!
Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy in Big Trouble!
Fishmen vs. the Luffy Pirates"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!