Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
The sky is unexpectedly clear tonight.
M-Moria! It's Moria!
Where?! Where is he?!
The sun will be rising soon.
Should you really be farting around?
Why is he here?
Huh? I can hear Master's voice!
Usopp!
Huh? What?!
Crap!
Usopp!
Shit! Oars is acting intelligently
now that Moria is with him!
Usopp!
Where are you?! Answer me!
He's okay!
I thought that you might need salt,
so I gathered it in bulk!
Brook!
You're a lifesaver!
"The Secret Plan to Turn the Tables!
Nightmare Luffy Makes His Appearance!"
Brook, you can move?
You seem to be doing really great.
I owe ya one. Thank you!
Indeed, I was severely injured!
I dragged my battered body
to the kitchen in search of salt.
Upon stumbling across some milk, I happily
drank away and look what happened!
Wait, just how regenerative is calcium?!
Doesn't milk help mend broken bones?
Don't lie!
Whatever the case may be,
we got a massive
amount of salt just in the nick of time.
The path to the kitchen has been cut off.
Brook's salt is our last hope.
We're running out of time. We must fight!
If we can stuff the salt
down that monster's throat
and kick Moria's butt before dawn, we win!
I'm freaking scared!
I'm horribly scared as well.
I still can't believe he has a cockpit.
I thought that freak had a normal body.
You should be grateful that
I have decided to join the fray!
And I'd be extremely careful if I were you.
I'm not simply a passenger here!
I will show you the ultimate nightmare!
I shall fight in this battle as well!
I will give it my all!
I could never begin to repay the debt
I owe you guys for recovering my shadow,
but I'll fight to the fullest!
--I'm stiff!
--Don't push yourself!
Stay on top of the salt!
--Let's go, Chopper!
--Yeah!
I'll give you a taste of
my anti-monster shells!
Victory goes to those
who take the initiative!
Apparently it wasn't big enough last time!
Franky, I'm counting on you!
Special Attack! Special Oil Star!
Okay! Now we're talking!
Transform!
Super Size!
Fire Bird Star!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Hot! Hot, hot, hot!
Hot! Hot, hot!
Sweet! Serves you right!
Okay, now get that one contraption ready.
Huh? Oh, okay.
Hot! Hot, hot! Hot!
Pathetic! Don't shrink back, Oars!
You only think things "hurt"
or "feel hot" because
of the time you spent as a human.
Things of this nature do not work
on you now that you are a zombie.
Calm down and put out the fire!
Now that you mention it,
this doesn't feel the least bit hot.
Now, Zoro!
Okay!
Oomph!
Three-Sword Style...
...Great Buddha Slayer!
Eat this! Jenga Cannon!
Have seconds! Thirds!
Fourths! Fifths! And sixths!
Stinking jerk!
The tower is flying straight at us!
Oh, no!
Huh?
Veinte Fleurs!
Oh, thanks!
Stop it, you idiots!
Oops! He used them against us!
Hey, you guys okay?
H-Here's my new weapon, Kuwagata!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, and whoosh!
Hah! Super!
Uh, drop the super pose...
Holding this back is killing me.
So are you all set, Usopp?
Y-Yeah, but I only made this to look cool!
I have no idea how it will actually work!
Don't worry about it!
I'm extra super this week.
Then get on!
All right! Aim for the
center of that lug's gut!
Go! Special Attack! Iron Man Comet!
This is going super!
Say your prayers!
I use this trench mortar
against sea monsters and Sea Kings!
I'm gonna fill ya full of holes!
Eat this, Moria!
He's so agile!
Sometimes I forget that he's Luffy!
Tch!
Franky!
You're not done yet, Oars.
He's still hanging on by a thread.
Finish him off!
Okay!
Shoot! Isn't he going to stop there?!
Stop it! He can't move anymore!
Franky!
Thunderbolt...
Huh? That cloud...!
...Tempo!
Damn it! Who did that?!
What did they do?!
It worked! Oars fell to his knees!
Lightning! That attack
could only come from...!
Clima Takt! Nami-san, are you all right?
He just sparked!
Lightning? Out of nowhere?
Oars summoned lightning! I'm sure of it!
There you are!
It's Nami-san!
Nami-san! Nami-san! Nami-san! Nami-san!
Nami-san!
Hey! Quit yelling my name!
What if he notices me?!
Thank goodness! What a relief!
I'm so glad Nami-san is okay!
Thank God! Please forgive me for failing you!
--Nami-san, I'm sorry!
--What a loudmouth.
--Woman!
--See?
How dare you take us so lightly?!
Oars, show them your true power!
Gum-Gum...
Wh-What? What? What?! Can he stretch?
He can't reach her from there, can he?
Now's our chance! Get Franky somewhere safe!
'Kay!
...Pistol!
What?!
H-His arm extended?! Why?!
It stretched. That feels
more like how it should.
But that's impossible!
--Nami!
--Nami-san!
No!
I see her! Nami is okay!
Phew! Robin saved her.
I wasn't expecting that.
Are you all right, Nami?
Thank you. I'm okay, thanks to you.
Something seriously bad just happened!
Why was he able to stretch his arm?
There is only one rubber man in the world!
It's Moria! He must have done something.
The bastard!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
It's like we're fighting a
monster version of Luffy!
What is keeping Luffy?!
I need to hurry back!
I'm awful! I intentionally held
my leg out to trip you! Teehee!
What's your problem?! I'm in a hurry!
What do you want?!
Yeah, we know! We totally
get that you're in a hurry.
Please give us a minute!
You're our only hope!
--We've been searching for you this whole time.
--Huh?
We're the Risky Brothers,
members of the Rolling Pirates led by
Captain "Marriage Proposal" Lola.
Don't you want to defeat that Gecko Moria
guy who lives in the mansion? Well?
So? What's your deal?
We know the secret behind Moria's powers.
We'll give incredible power to you,
so please! Take him down!
Secret? Power?
C'mon!
Like I said, what's your deal?!
Allow me to introduce the Rolling
Pirates' captain, Marriage Proposal Lola.
She has currently proposed 4,443 times!
My! I like you. Please marry me.
No.
Rejected! That was her 4,444th rejection!
So everyone here has lost their shadow
and joined the Victim Association
that wanders these forests.
I'm in a hurry, since my
shadow was also taken!
Aren't you Straw Hat Luffy?
Bluntly put, today is the first day
Thriller Bark has rocked and shaken like this!
The Three Phantoms who serve Moria
have been defeated one after the next.
The mansion is already halfway demolished!
Yeah! You've filled us with non-stop
excitement ever since you arrived.
But your enemy is no pushover!
He has already awoken the Special Zombie!
Don't look so surprised!
We use the Victim Network to stay
up-to-date on the situation!
We've gone three whole
years without our shadows!
I don't want to spend
the rest of my life like this!
If you defeat Moria,
everyone will get their shadows back!
That's what we thought, but jeez!
Do you even know where Moria is right now?
In its belly! The belly of that monster!
What?! Did he get eaten?!
No! He climbed inside
of the monster's stomach.
In other words, you can't touch Moria
if you don't defeat the Special
Zombie that has your shadow!
Your friends are fighting the zombie
in the mansion courtyard right now!
They're what?! Damn it!
I don't have time for this!
We need you to hold your horses!
Ow!
Jeez! We'll skip the circular explanations!
It'll be faster if he sees it for himself!
Show him the secret behind
the shadows that we discovered!
Okay! Move, move! Coming through!
Huh? A shadow?
Right, it's a shadow.
When we feed salt to a zombie,
we can catch the shadow that comes out!
Ready, go!
Wh-What are you doing?!
--The shadow is stabbing me!
--Sit still!
Knock it off! I'm feeling lightheaded!
Great! It went in.
Well? Are you still yourself?
Yeah...
Can you use a sword?
Nope, not at all.
Give him a sword!
Here!
Geh! What's going on?!
The shadow we just put inside of you
belonged to a skilled Navy swordsman.
A Navy swordsman?
All of the shadow's combat abilities
will be added to your own.
And we can put in as many shadows
as you can mentally handle!
Well? Isn't it amazing?
We can use Moria's powers to
boost your strength several fold!
We still have a bunch
of shadows we've caught!
But if you have weak
willpower, you'll pass out.
All of our hard work will go up in smoke!
Why do you have so many shadows?
We desperately went around purifying
zombies in search of our own shadows.
Wouldn't it tick you off if you released
some random stranger's shadow?
So that's how we began our shadow collection.
Listen, you need to remember this!
When a shadow enters a corpse,
it turns into a zombie.
But it won't stick around if there
is already a soul in the body.
Your power-up will only
last ten minutes at most.
After that, the shadow will pop out
and return to its true master.
Got that? You must finish
the fight in ten minutes.
We will give you all of the shadows
that we risked our lives to obtain!
Geh! That many?!
Now that the fog has cleared up,
we only have twenty minutes of
night left to get our work done!
You must hurry!
Don't forget who you are!
I am sure you can handle
twenty or thirty shadows!
Although we could only handle two or three.
Huh?
--Do it!
--Okay!
Whoa! W-W-Wait!
I didn't say I'd go along with...!
J-Just how strong... is this man's willpower?
He's amazing! I've never
heard of anything like this!
W-We put in all 100 shadows!
Incredible! Just what I'd expect
from our Star of Hope!
H-Hey, did you lose your mind?
Are you still you, Straw Hat Luffy?
Yeah, I'm me.
Power is surging through me. I can't stop it!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!...
Take this, Straw Hat!
You know, man... It's like you're
a completely different person now.
Weren't you a little bit shorter before?
I wonder how strong he has become.
I am itching... for a fight!
He'll do just great!
Go on! There isn't much time!
Go give Moria a nightmare,
our Star of Hope, Nightmare Luffy!
Just you wait, Moria!
Wait! The mansion isn't that way!
No way! Why does Oars'
body stretch and contract?
You're mistaken. Oars' body isn't stretching.
Huh? What do you mean?
It looks like Oars' body is changing to
match the movements of his shadow.
In that case, this is another
one of Moria's powers.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Straw Hat Crew Gets Wiped Out!
The Shadow-Shadow's Powers in Full Swing!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!