Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
H-Here's my new weapon, Kuwagata!
So are you all set, Usopp?
Y-Yeah, but I only made this to look cool!
I have no idea how it will actually work!
All right! Aim for the
center of that lug's gut!
Go! Special Attack! Iron Man Comet!
Eat this, Moria!
Tch!
Franky!
You're not done yet, Oars.
He's still hanging on by a thread.
Finish him off!
Okay!
Thunderbolt...
Huh? That cloud...!
...Tempo!
Damn it! Who did that?!
What did they do?!
Nami-san!
Hey! Quit yelling my name!
What if he notices me?!
Gum-Gum...
Wh-What? What? What?! Can he stretch?
...Pistol!
What?!
H-His arm extended?! Why?!
It stretched. That feels
more like how it should.
"The Straw Hat Crew Gets Wiped Out!
The Shadow-Shadow's Powers in Full Swing!"
Gum-Gum...
Incoming!
...Bell!
I'm in the groove now that my body stretches.
Gum-Gum...
Here comes another attack!
...Spear!
Damn it! What is going on here?
His attack power has skyrocketed!
How come Oars can stretch
when he isn't a power holder?
What did Moria do?
Good guess! I'm making you live this
nightmare with my Shadow-Shadow power...
...Shadow Revolution!
R-Revolution?
Shadows copy whatever your body does.
That's common knowledge!
Your body and shadow are always
mirror images of each other.
That is a hard-and-fast rule.
Oars' shadow is supposed to obey him,
but I usurped control by
slipping my shadow inside of it.
Do you know what that means?
I can freely alter the shape of Oars' shadow.
But his shadow and body
must take the same form.
Since the shadow stops
matching the shape of his body,
his body transforms to match his shadow.
That is how Shadow Revolution works!
In other words, it's the
opposite of common sense.
Moria made the arms and legs
in Oars' shadow extend,
so his body stretched to match.
So instead of becoming a rubber man,
Oars' body can transform into anything?
Give me a break. He's too big for that.
Yeah. I can't get near him like this.
This is far worse than rubber!
If I make his shadow round...
Oars will turn into a ball!
No way...!
What... is he doing?!
Ow, ow, ow!
I-Is this for real?
Oars Ball!
Eat this!
Whoa...
Run for it!
Hey, now! Just a sec, Master.
Keep out of my fight!
My bad! I didn't mean to interfere.
I'm just here to offer assistance.
Go on, Oars! Crush each
and every one of them!
By the way, where is Luffy?
Moria must have tricked him
into going somewhere!
There is no way he got his butt kicked!
Seriously? I swear, he is such an idiot!
What should I do? Should I tell everyone?
We're already in a tight spot...
Do they need to know
that there is another Warlord
on this island right now?
So does this mean everyone
won't get their shadows back
unless we defeat both Zombie Luffy and Moria?
Yeah, that sounds about right.
No way! It's almost dawn!
That's part of the enemy's plan!
We just have to thwart it!
--Excuse me!
--What?
Skeleton, you're here?
Please...
Please grant me this one request!
Huh?
You shouldn't get near him, Zoro!
Thank you so much, everyone!
This is nothing.
Have you lost your mind, Brook?
Didn't you see what happened to Franky?
Don't blame me for what happens!
This packs a wallop, so get ready!
Dark Cloud Tempo!
Go ahead! Please do your thing!
I didn't think I'd use Kuwagata again!
There is no greater pain than
being unable to repay a favor!
I shall put in backbreaking effort!
Okay! Then off you go!
I'm off!
Slalom Vine!
The electricity is so strong
you can see my bones!
But I was nothing but bones to begin with!
It's show time! I'm like a lightning arrow!
Lightning Bone Sword...
Gavotte Bond en Avant!
Awesome! He drilled through.
He went through my body!
He made an opening! Keep the attacks going!
Mission: Complete...
Well done, Bones!
Two-Sword Style... Nigiri...
...Tower Climb!
Why, you--no, first I'm going
to finish off that skeleton.
Gum-Gum...
H-He wouldn't...!
...Battle Axe!
Brook...!
Brook!
Special Attack! Atlas Comet!
That won't work!
--Crap!
--Usopp, fight!
"Fight"? Eh? Hey! Whoa, wait!
You're up next, Long Nose!
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
I'm dead!
Huh? Huh?
My arm isn't stretching! Why not?
Ochenta Fleurs Cuatro Mano!
Where did these arms come from?!
They're annoying!
Could you stop manipulating
his shadow for the time being?
What?!
Hold!
G-Gak! C-Can't breathe!
Keep it up, Robin!
Do you think this will
keep me out of the fight?
Your plan doesn't amuse me in the least!
Brick Bat.
Robin-chan!
Veinte Fleurs!
Calendula!
Robin!
What do you think you're
doing to Robin-chan?!
Moria's shadow?!
Let's see who is the more powerful
long-distance power holder!
Your hold hurts pretty darn bad!
Don't get distracted by his shadow!
If we take out his body,
the shadow will disappear as well.
Cuatro Mano!
H-Hey!
What are you doing?! Stop it!
Clutch!
No!
--Sweet!
--You're amazing, Robin!
Hey, Robin! Watch out
for the shadow behind you!
Huh? What is Moria doing down here?
You were close! It's such a pity.
Doppelman and I can switch
places at any given minute.
They switched places?
Huh? Then the one inside Oars is...?
My Shadow Substitute that
has no joints to dislocate!
That's right! It's the shadow that
was here until just a second ago.
Robin-chan!
That's three down!
Now he's got Robin's shadow!
I don't have anything to put it in,
but I might as well take it.
Diable Jambe!
You damn bastard!
Give Robin-chan's shadow back!
Extra Haché!
Brick Bat!
He switched places with his shadow again!
If he switched with his shadow...
Moria is back inside Oars' stomach!
And everything has returned to how it was.
Gosh darn it, Master!
This is supposed to be my fight!
I'm sorry, Oars. I had a bit
too much fun with them.
Huh?
I'll finish off that woman.
Gum-Gum...
His arms can stretch out again!
Shoot! He's going to attack
Robin when she's out cold!
Sanji! Robin! Run for it!
...Bazooka!
Diable Jambe!
Frit Assorti!
Huh?
You repelled him!
Now's your chance!
Get Robin-chan away from here.
You can count on me!
Hey! Sanji! Zoro!
Chopper, what are you doing up there?
I've been searching for what
caused Oars to die 500 years ago!
His cause of death?
Go after his right arm!
This isn't his real arm!
Hogback reconstructed it, but there are signs
of horrible frostbite around the stitches.
I can't say for certain, but I suspect
he froze to death 500 years ago!
Even a monster like this is
no match for the elements.
He died while wandering the Land of Ice!
Even 500 years ago,
I'd wager Oars went around...
...mostly naked!
I don't wanna lose to someone that stupid!
Zombies may not feel pain,
but they still take damage.
All of the attacks we've
landed are accumulating!
If we can render this arm nonfunctional,
it will halve his offensive power!
Long story short, focus on this one arm!
Why are you talking up a storm...
...while standing on my shoulder?!
Chopper!
Huh?
He's gone!
Since you're a zombie,
you have no idea how badly
you just hurt your own body
with that punch, do you?
Huh? Oh, you went inside my fist!
Heh! I'm tiny, so the crevices
in your fist are like caves!
Rumble!
Jumping Point!
Arm Point!
Chopper!
Glad you dodged that!
I'll lend you a hand!
Sanji, please do!
Armée de l'Air...
Cloven...
Roseo Shoot!
You jerks!
Stop hitting me in the same spot!
Those attacks aren't going to work.
They'll work! Pain is a signal
meant to protect the body!
Lacking pain doesn't make you strong!
Chopper!
Save your fuzzy logic!
Hey! That looks bad, guys!
Get away from there!
Gum-Gum...
Now we're in for it.
Shoot!
...Gatling!
Sanji! Chopper!
There go another two...
He's taking everyone out...
Darn it!
Four down! Five down!
Three to go!
I have no idea who you are,
but thanks for rescuing me!
So who the heck are you?!
Monkey D. Luffy.
Don't lie!
It really is me.
What the heck happened to you?!
And you're stinking strong now!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Incredible Battle
Starts! Luffy vs. Luffy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!