Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
"Hot Water"
--Catch!
--That was too high!
Here I go!
I'd like a Rainbow Rock.
I'll get right on it.
Yeah, I'd like to give it a shot.
This is awesome!
It's hard to believe this resort was
just outside the Florian Triangle.
I know!
I am honored that you
are enjoying yourselves.
Spa Island has twelve heated pools.
--You're lovely!
--There are three lazy rivers...
Incoming!
...and a pool dedicated to diving.
We also have waterfalls for
meditation and fifty baths,
including a cola bath and a milk bath.
"Milk Bath"
"Women" "Men"
Furthermore, we have water ping pong
and a floating casino for those
who would like to play games.
You can enjoy exquisite cuisine prepared
by master chefs at several restaurants.
As your host, nothing could make me happier
than to melt away the fatigue
from your long voyage.
Some lucky visitors may even get to
see a circular rainbow and candy rain.
Oh, aren't circular rainbows
a rare natural phenomenon
called the "ocean's treasure"?
But I've heard there hasn't
been a sighting in years.
As I said, "some lucky
visitors" may see them.
Is something the matter?
We might see some candy rain in just a bit.
Eh?!
Surely you jest!
I'm sure it must be difficult
to run a resort on these waters.
Since our opening, we've earned
10 billion Berries a year.
We're endorsed by the World Government,
so we haven't run into any problems.
Our security is rock solid.
I'm confident that our
regular guests have nothing to
fear as they kick back and relax.
10 billion Berries a year?!
Naturally, that applies to pirates as well.
Thanks for your hospitality.
I'm sorry if that spoiled your mood.
As long as you're a paying customer,
I don't care if you're a pirate or
part of the Revolutionary Army.
You two are rather similar.
10 billion Berries! Berry, Berry, Berry!
"The Slow-Slow Menace!
'Silver Fox' Foxy Returns!"
Ready, go!
Boo-yah!
--Whoopee!
--Yeah!
Huh? What are those things?
Candy! It's raining candy!
Candy ball raindrops!
And they're only raining here.
Talk about lucky!
We're super lucky! Lucky!
Candy too heavy!
Stupid!
You guys are so stupid!
Huh?
What is that?
This is the ocean raccoon dog, Nukki.
He can transform into anything!
Wow, awesome!
He said that this girl is called Rina.
The raccoon dog talked!
I'm not a raccoon dog! I'm a reindeer!
Eh?
"Eh?" Be nice!
Are you hungry?
Yeah...
Want my lunch? But it's not a pirate lunch.
Huh? You're pirates?
Honest?
I'm Luffy, the man who will
become King of the Pirates!
I'm the ship doctor, Chopper!
I'm Captain Usopp, the sniper.
Wow! I didn't know there were
funny pirates like you guys.
Thank you! Now to chow do--
Huh? What's wrong?
I forgot about my big sister.
Your sister?
Big Sis Sayo!
You're eating up a storm!
This guy will eat anything.
Ocean raccoon dogs are omnivores.
Think he'll eat this?
Of course not!
What is that?!
What?! He can transform into anything?
Pretty much.
A babe! Please transform
into the hottest babe ever!
Ah, if only I was better with words!
Transform into Nami-san!
Please turn into Nami-san!
You're puny!
I am a stinking idiot!
But even if you're puny,
Nami-san is still Nami-san!
Nami-san!
Jerk!
See? Aren't they goofy?
Are you going already?
Uh-huh.
Thank you for the feast!
Oh, are you leaving?
Yes. Thank you for the meal.
Are you all right?
I had a blast! Thank you, Luffy.
Aw! Is the ocean raccoon dog leaving already?
That's who you'll miss?!
I've been looking for you two.
This is getting old!
I didn't expect you to get this far.
Your drive is impressive.
I'd love to catch you here and now,
but that'll have to wait.
I've run into some rather familiar faces.
You're doomed now that
I've run into you, Straw Hat!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Who are you?
He doesn't know who I am...
He doesn't remember!
Oh, no! Boss! Don't let it get to you!
By any chance, are you...
...the guy that Zoro and Sanji beat up?
He's doing it on purpose!
It has to be intentional!
Boss!
Hey! Straw Hat, you jerk!
You tarnished my undefeated legacy
"Fox"
and stole our pride--our Jolly Roger!
Don't tell me that you've forgotten!
Ah! Now I remember.
You're Split-Head Fox!
I'm "Silver Fox" Foxy!
Luffy, be careful. As I recall,
he can shoot a weird beam.
Really?
Hey, he isn't much of a threat
if we know what's up his sleeve.
Don't expect me to rely
on the same tricks forever!
Look!
A mirror?
High-Speed Rotation Mirror Ball Amplifier!
Thousand-Armed Kannon, Slow-Slow Beam!
--Shoot!
--That's against the rules!
Darn... it...
I... told... you... so!
Anything struck by my beam is
slow for thirty seconds afterward.
I'll be taking this.
Now do you remember me, Straw Hat?
You'll start to fall in ten seconds!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
What a lovely bath.
It made my skin so smooth. It's great!
But I'm a skeleton, so I don't have any skin.
What are you guys up to?
Franky! Brook! Beat them up!
Weapons Left!
What's going on?!
Luffy?!
Cien Fleurs!
Thank you, Robin-chan!
I owe ya!
Is everyone okay? Gosh, you scared me.
You're amazing, Luffy!
Yeah, I'm a rubber man. I won't
let that Slip-Head defeat me!
Damn it! You've added new
members to your crew, Straw Hat!
B-Boss, they have a skeleton!
Shoot! Let's try again!
Victory is mine as long as
I have this mirror ball.
Stupid! What are you doing?
Shut the door already.
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
I swear I'll get him!
Please remain calm!
"Hot Water"
Why is everyone leaving?
I'd like to ask you two something.
Wh-What?
It's about that notebook.
Foxy and his goons are after it, aren't they?
Foxy?
The pirates from earlier.
Sure, we have a history with them,
but I'd say they were more
interested in your notebook.
I called it, didn't I?
This notebook explains how to create jewels!
How to create jewels?!
--Rina!
--It's okay. Leave this to me.
Huh?
It's true that they're pirates, but they
seem trustworthy. Plus they're strong!
If we try to deal with this on our own,
we may never reach our goal.
You see, this notebook
belonged to our father.
Oh, wow! It's full of numbers!
Our father is an inventor, and those
formulas explain how to make jewels.
You can read this?
Big Sis Sayo can. It goes right over my head.
Really? You're something else, Sayo-chan!
What about this? He included
a nautical chart...
It has a hot water mark and an "X."
That's his secret message.
We think it's a hint regarding
how to make jewels.
Huh? This?
The formula for making
them is about 99% complete.
And he hid the remaining 1% in this clue.
Right.
Could the hot water mark
mean a hot springs...?
In which case, the "X" might mean Spa Island.
Yep. We reached the same
conclusion and snuck aboard.
Impressive!
But despite all of our searching,
we can't find anything to indicate
we're on the right track.
I doubt that notebook alone could
tell you how to make jewels...
But the Foxy Crew has come this
far in pursuit of that notebook!
It might be legit.
It might be fake.
Huh?
Rina!
I'm sure it's fake.
There is no way you can make jewels!
What?
My father is a stupid liar!
He is really stupid!
I hate my father!
"Rina and Sayo's Village
-Three Years Ago-"
Dad!
Welcome home.
Sayo! Rina! This is horrible!
What is?
It's a golden beetle!
L-Legend says that our village
will perish when one appears!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
Dad...
The paint is coming off.
He fell for it!
What an idiot!
Scram!
I can't believe them!
What a relief! Thank goodness!
Huh?
Well, isn't this great?
The village isn't doomed.
Isn't it wonderful that it was a prank?
Our father loved our village.
He loved it because that was
where our mother was born.
My research can save the entire village.
Everyone will be able to live in comfort.
What type of research
are you conducting, Dad?
Jewels! How to create jewels!
Jewels...? Those aren't
something you make, Dad!
Your dad sounds neat!
He isn't the least bit neat!
He's a horrible father!
Three years ago, he went on a journey
for his research and never came back.
He abandoned us!
It's been just the two of us ever since.
We've had to grit our teeth
as everyone made fun of us.
"I don't have a dad. He's dead!"
That's what I've told myself.
But then a month ago...
Nukki suddenly came back
with this notebook in his mouth.
There was a letter in the notebook.
What do you think it said?
"Dear daughters.
Please complete my research."
Can you believe him?
He was so busy with his research that
he forgot about us for three years!
Why must we risk our lives and
travel to these dangerous waters?!
He's stupid! Stupid!
I don't believe a word he says.
He's fudging over his lies about
the jewels with this picture.
Why did he give us this quiz at the end?!
Your dad really is neat!
Huh?
I wanna see those jewels.
Did you pay attention to a word I said?!
Ah, there you are!
You're late, Zoro!
Hey!
But didn't you come to
search for the treasure?
I didn't--my sister did!
I'm her bodyguard.
Her bodyguard?
My sister was insistent
about searching for the secret,
so I came to protect her.
What are you guys doing?
I am certain that there
is a way to make jewels!
I believe in him.
Big Sis Sayo...
Everyone, please help--
Big Sis Sayo!
I've got the girl. If you want
her back, do as I say!
Doran?!
Who is that?
The ship's host.
What?!
I'd like you to uncover the secret
behind that notebook.
I'll return the girl in
exchange for the answer.
Shoot! Foxy wasn't our only enemy!
What should we do, Luffy?
Please, Rina! Finish the research.
Don't let Dad's dream fall
into the hands of that jerk!
Dad's research was nothing but lies.
I can’t believe Sayo got caught
because of his notebook!
Please, Luffy! Save Sayo!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Great Scramble for Treasure!
Collapse! Spa Island!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!