Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
On the voyage to their next destination,
Luffy and crew drop by
the resort ship, Spa Island.
While enjoying their vacation,
they meet the sisters Sayo and Rina.
This is the ocean raccoon dog, Nukki.
Big Sis Sayo!
You're doomed now that
I've run into you, Straw Hat!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
It's about that notebook.
Foxy and his goons are after it, aren't they?
This notebook explains how to create jewels!
Everyone, please help--
Luffy and crew managed
to repel the Foxy Crew,
which was after the sisters' notebook.
It held the secret to their father's
research on making jewels.
But now Sayo has been taken hostage
by the mastermind, Doran!
"The Great Scramble for Treasure!
Collapse! Spa Island!"
Big Sis Sayo!
Dang! This ship is loaded with traps.
Boss, hang in there!
That was pathetic, "Silver Fox" Foxy.
They won despite your trickery.
Oh, well. Now I simply have to wait for
them to solve the secret of the jewels.
This just isn't enough to go by!
Didn't you search all over the ship?
Wasn't there a large "X" mark?
No... What should I do?
This notebook really is full of lies.
And now my sister is...
--Luffy!
--Huh?
Please save... Big Sis Sayo.
Sure.
Huh? You're sure? Really?
Yeah, I wanna see those jewels.
Even though this notebook could be lying?
But how are we going to save her, Luffy?
Let's see... Why don't we destroy this ship?
Whaaat?!
What?!
Where did that come from?!
Hey, man! Are you thinking straight?
What about Sayo?
We'll find her if we destroy the ship.
And the hint about the jewels?
It'll be easier to look for if we destroy the ship!
Let's get started.
Zoro?
There is no point worrying about something
that might not be on this ship, anyway.
I swear, you guys don't
have a shred of delicacy!
Nami-san, the idea of meekly obeying
that dastardly mustache irks me to no end.
I don't care if we sink this ship.
Gah! Not you too, Robin!
Isn't someone going to stop them?
Those were the Captain's orders.
Oh, you're quick on the uptake!
Franky!
Please look after Sunny.
You've got it.
Super!
There goes the resort...
All right! Destroy this ship!
108-Pound Phoenix!
Concasser!
Gum-Gum Whip!
Tabasco Star!
Hoofprint Roseo!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Clutch!
Three-Pace Hum... Notch Slash!
Everyone is strong!
Give Sayo back!
Outta my way! Move! Move! Move!
Like those puny bullets can hurt me.
Wh-What?!
He repelled the bullets?
Owie!
Jerks! Now I'm ticked!
Weapons Left!
Hey! Come on and give Sayo back!
Curse you!
What is that?!
Is that a cannon?! I thought it was a chimney!
Big Sis!
Rina!
Damn it! He's taken her hostage.
How dare you wreak havoc on my ship?!
Do you realize how much
it cost to build Spa Island?
Damn that rotten mustached jerk!
Sayo!
Big Sis!
Big Sis Sayo!
Next I'm gonna blow that brat sky high!
Stop it!
I had originally wanted you to
solve the puzzle in that notebook,
but forget it! I'll be taking that notebook.
I'll give her back after you hand it over.
You can have the notebook,
so give Big Sis Sayo back!
Don't!
Don't give it to him!
Big Sis Sayo...?
Rina, solve the secret in the notebook
and finish Dad's research!
No! Why should I?
Believe in Dad, Rina!
Don't give Dad's research to that jerk!
Dad was working to make his
dream come true for you, me, and everyone in the village.
Please! For my sake,
don't throw away Dad's dream!
You're lying! Dad is just
a self-absorbed researcher.
Rina...
I mean... I mean, he was
always in his own world!
"For Dad"
--It's done!
Do you think Dad will like his birthday cake?
Yep!
He isn't coming home!
I'm sure he must have found something again.
I'm going to bed!
Okay.
"For Dad"
A cake? Oh, yeah.
They must have baked a cake for me...
Dad...?
Did I wake you up?
What are these?
Cast-off Thirty Year Cicada shells.
I can probably use them in my research.
There was a big outbreak of them
for the first time in thirty years!
Is that right? Ah! But last night...
A cake! That cake looks delicious!
But that cake...!
We made that yesterday.
It may have gone bad. It is summer and all...
Doctor... Get a doctor...
He already saw you and left!
I don't care about him!
He doesn't know a thing about us!
He doesn't think about us!
Hey, this isn't the time to get in a fight...
Don't butt in.
This is their problem.
Rina, you're mistaken! Listen to me! Dad...
I'm sorry about the cake.
Dad...
You were looking forward to having
a birthday party, weren't you?
Yeah...
I need the materials in the
cast-off Thirty Year Cicada shells to make the jewels.
If I didn't get them now, I'd have
to wait another thirty years...
I had to go.
Uh-huh.
You aren't angry?
No...
I see. But I bet Rina is mad at me.
You are just like your mother,
but Rina takes after me.
She's a handful when she gets upset!
After I make some jewels,
let's eat a cake that's this big!
Yeah!
Let's get one that Rina could hide in.
Nukki says that it's all true.
And he said that your father
left home to protect you and Sayo
from some bad guys who
were after his jewel research.
Oh, no...
What's this...?
I can't find one...
You have to work to find a four-leaf clover.
But Big Sis found three of them!
That's because she believed with all
of her heart that she would find them.
--She believed?
--Right!
Conducting research and searching
for four-leaf clovers are similar.
If you never stop believing and work hard,
it will pay off in the end.
Really? Then I'm going to find a five-leaf clover!
Huh? Five leaves...?
That'd be amazing!
I found one!
I found a five-leaf clover!
Th-That's... Rina!
You were right! I believed I could find one.
That's right, Rina! That's amazing!
Yay!
All right, Rina! I'm gonna
succeed with my research!
Yeah... I had forgotten all about that...
I used to believe he could pull it off.
This is Dad's dream! It has to come true.
Rina!
I've changed my mind! You can't
have the notebook after all.
Wh-What?!
It's show time!
Don't play games with me!
Seis Fleurs!
Tabasco Star Onslaught! Star! Star!
Nami, get on.
Uh-huh.
Sayo-chan!
Hurry! Untie her.
What is that?
A lock?!
Where did you come from?
Wait! What are you going to do?
Please wait!
Three-Sword Style...
...Great Buddha Slayer!
They're doing a great job.
Hey, you need to do a great job!
Curse you!
What's that?
The jerk! He released all
of the steam in the ship!
That's better!
Now die!
Let's go, Rina!
Yeah!
Third Gear!
Bone Balloon!
Giant Axe!
Boss!
What on earth is going on...?
What the heck?!
Later!
Stupid! Don't forget about
everyone who has to abandon ship!
Luffy, you're amazing!
Oops! I forgot that I shrink
when I use that move.
Huh?
Sheesh! Think ahead a little, will you?
A giant "X."
We did it!
Serves the jerk right!
An "X"! And it's huge.
Yep! Dad was referring to that
underwater volcano on the map.
Doran built his ship right above
the treasure he was searching for.
The doof didn't realize the key
to the secret was right under him.
Amazing!
That's... a circular rainbow!
I've never seen a round rainbow before.
Same here.
It's a mysterious rainbow! Awesome!
W-Wait a sec! Is that the treasure?
Huh?
Come to think of it, circular rainbows
are referred to as the "ocean's treasure."
What?!
Oh, man!
Th-That's it?
You better not tell me that this is the treasure.
Don't underestimate us!
Uh, well...
You can have all of the treasure!
Don't give us that!
Huh? That rainbow looks weird...
The order of the colors is inversed.
The order...?
What's wrong?
Just maybe...
"-Several Days Later-"
I think that might be...
You're the monster raccoon dog
from the other day!
No, it's an ocean raccoon dog.
A letter?
It looks like Sayo-chan's guess
was dead on back there!
"Dear Luffy and friends. Are you well?
My big sister and I went straight
home and tested out her idea."
We followed my father's formulas
and made seven different medications.
When we mixed them together in
the order of the circular rainbow...
It worked!
She says it created a jewel!
Yay! We did it! We did it!
Sayo... Rina...!
Is this it?
Cool!
That's a sign of their gratitude.
They say, "Thank you, guys."
Let me get a better look at it, Luffy.
--I wanna see it! Lemme see!
--Huh? Let's see it.
Wait! Just a sec.
Hey, guys! This isn't a toy.
What's going on?
It's candy rain! Ow, ow!
It's yummy!
Oops. I dropped the jewel.
--Which one is it?!
--Beats me.
Find it! Find it fast!
You guys had better find it!
Okay!
Why are you so excited, Brook?
After learning about the great feats
you've accomplished on your voyage,
I've realized I must work
to become a true comrade!
"A true comrade"? That's not
something you work toward.
Oh, dear!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Brook's Great Struggle! Is the Path to
Becoming a True Comrade Rigorous?"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!