Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
On the way to their next
destination, Fishman Island,
Luffy and friends helped save
Camie's friend, Hatchin.
The Straw Hats fought a hard battle against
the kidnapping gang, the Flying Fish Riders.
That's when they saw the true identity of
Duval, who held a burning hatred for Sanji.
Stop screwing around!
Unleash the Sunny's Super Secret
Weapon, the Gaon Cannon!
That face... Is that even possible?
Incredible...
There's actually someone who looks just
like that scribble on Sanji's wanted flyer!
"Black Foot" Sanji, it's all your fault!
Hey, Sanji! Where are you going?
Do you know how scared I was when
people suddenly wanted me dead?
Why? Why did I have to be chased
all the way to Navy HQ?!
Why do I have to be nearly killed
by famous bounty hunters?!
Why?!
Sanji?
All because you made a name
for yourself as a pirate,
I've had to live every day in
fear, running around and hiding!
What did I even do?!
Give me my life back!
"Black Foot" Sanji!
What do I care?!
Head!
How can you not care?!
Who else could be responsible
for this but you?!
Shut up! I'm the one who's
pissed about that wanted flyer!
I know how the poor guy feels...
But Sanji was really upset
about that wanted flyer, too.
Who is this?
Are you gonna be depressed forever?
Shut up! Why is mine the
only hand-drawn one?!
That's all you're worth.
Speak in actual words, would you?
They'll laugh...
All the ladies in the
world will laugh at me...
I never knew stuff like this could happen...
What a shocker. The world
sure is a big place.
Sanji must've been born
under a star of miracles.
He's going to have such an
interesting death someday.
I feel so sorry for that Duval guy...
Hey, they look just like each other!
Two peas in a pod.
Brook! I'm gonna pound you later!
Okay, Sanji, we're going on ahead.
You think this is my fault?!
If you don't want to look like the
flyer, cut your hair or grow a beard!
There are plenty of things you could change!
Oh! I never thought of that!
Are you just stupid to the core?!
I'm not stupid!
You know, Black Foot, we...
We...
...used to be plain old mafia
guys out in the country.
Hey, kid! What did you do to our leader?
Are you her dad?
I-I'm sorry!
Please forgive us!
Honey!
Daddy!
How are you gonna pay me back for this?
Huh?!
Daddy!
Honey!
We went around tormenting
the village folk every day.
It was a happy life, in its own way.
But then, all of a sudden, tragedy
fell upon my peaceful life...
What did he do?
That's a ton of money.
Shouldn't we report him to the Navy?
Here he comes!
It's dangerous to be around him!
We'll get in trouble, too!
Run!
What? Why'd everyone run away?
Ah!
At the time, I thought I had finally
been recognized throughout the village.
But then...
We never expected you to escape
this far to the countryside.
We're locking you up!
Why's the Navy after me?
Just do as we say,
"Black Foot" Sanji!
What?!
No way! There's a price on my head?!
A bounty of 77,000,000
Berries... and "Sanji"?!
Apprehend him!
I'm not him! I'm not Sanji, I tell you!
Stop!
I'm gonna be killed!
Do you understand, Black Foot?
I've never done anything
worse than shakedowns,
and suddenly I had a price of
77,000,000 Berries on my head...
The terror of having Navy guys on a totally
different power level chasing me around...
I finally ended up with
a huge wound on my back,
and donned an iron mask so my
face would never be seen again.
My life was ruined because of you!
I will chase you to the ends of Hell itself!
If you don't want that,
then kill me here and now!
I'm gonna be killed!
Why did Nami-san and Robin-chan have
to be put in danger just for your
stupid baseless accusations?!
That's the ship that allowed you to
make a name for yourself as a pirate.
That means its crew is included
in my hatred for you, too!
You can all die!
Poison harpoons!
Assume formation!
Huh? Pervert?
I'm gonna skewer you, Black Foot!
Die!
That's enough, all of you.
You took the bait, Black Foot!
Crap!
Sanji-kun!
They're gonna drag him underwater!
Sanji! Break the net!
Damn it! An iron net?!
Suffer and drown to death!
Sanji!
Damn it! I'm coming to save you!
You can't, you idiot! I'll go!
Wait! Humans are too slow to catch them!
Leave this to me!
Fool! Even if you're a fishman,
you'll never catch them!
Flying fish are among the
fastest creatures in the sea.
And their riders are equipped
with oxygen tanks,
so they can stay under as long as they like!
He's gonna suffocate and die for sure!
The next time Black Foot
appears on the surface,
it'll be as a pathetic drowned corpse!
What'd you say?!
Feel the Head's wrath, Black Foot!
Can't breathe...
Don't worry!
Camie?!
Hey, cowboy, I think you
forgot about someone.
It's true that flying fish
are faster than fishmen.
They're among the top of their class.
But the race that sits at
the very top of that class
is mermaids!
There's nothing in all this world's oceans
that can match a mermaid's swimming speed!
It'll be okay!
I'll save you, Sanji-chin!
She's that amazing?
They're not a race that can be caught unless
they're completely spacing out, really.
Oh, okay!
Camie! Take care of Sanji!
What is that?!
A giant ship anchor? That's too huge!
Aim for the Straw Hats' pirate ship!
Hit it smack in the middle and sink it!
Some of them have powers! If we fight
them underwater, victory is ours!
This is bad! We're gonna go down in one shot!
Dodge it! Use Burst or the
paddle wheels! Is there time?!
No, it's too late!
Come with me, Usopp! Hurry!
O-Okay!
Stand by at the bow!
G-Got it!
We're using our emergency secret weapon!
Secret weapon?
The Sunny's in trouble!
This is very bad!
Drop it!
No way!
It'll be a direct hit from there.
Sink!
It's coming down!
Drop it!
The Sunny's in trouble!
This is very bad!
Have faith in this ship!
Whoa! Its mane is spinning!
Sink!
It's coming down!
Emergency escape secret
weapon: Chicken Voyage!
What?! They dodged it?!
No way!
I've never heard of a ship that can back up!
Usopp, get inside the bow!
Inside the bow?
Oh, you can go in!
Franky even made all this?
Don't think it's over just
because we dodged that!
There's still more to this ship's strength!
Awesome!
Pour in the cola energy!
What now?
Charge complete!
Hey! What do I do now?
Get as much of them in the circle as you can?
The circle?
You mean this?
Got 'em!
Lock on with the button on the
handle and pull the lever!
So this... and this!
What's that?
Gaon Cannon...
Fire!
Amazing!
You're too moved!
Did ya see what the Sunny can do?!
That took down almost all of the flying fish!
That was all Usopp's skill.
Excellent for a first try!
What awesome power!
Sunny!
The lion is so amazing! I thought
my eyes were about to pop out!
Not that I have any eyes to pop out!
To keep the ship from blowing out
of the water with three barrels
of cola energy sent to the bow,
we pump two barrels of Coup de Burst
into the stern at the same time.
This baby burns through
cola, so I rarely use it.
I'm stuck in the net!
Damn that agile mermaid!
I'm almost there, Sanji-chin! Hang on!
Camie!
Thank goodness! Is Sanji okay?!
Everyone, it looks bad!
Sanji-chin lost a lot of blood!
What?
They got him?
I thought I'd saved him, but then a
bunch of blood flew from his nose...
Wha— A nosebleed?
Forget it. Just let him die there.
Yeah. He looks happy, anyway.
Hang in there, Sanji-chin!
Am I in heaven?
Damn... That bastard is alive?
You've lost a lot of men now.
Curse you!
Then I'll show you what makes
Motobalo so terrifying!
To this day, countless men have
fallen victim to these tough horns.
These horns even tore a
hole in the village dam!
Put him in a cage, and he'll bust out!
It was thanks to his horns that I managed
to escape my Navy pursuers with my life!
People call them "Heart-smashing Horns"!
All right. I'll stop him.
Go, Motobalo!
Look out, Luffy!
The horns had nothing to do with it!
Fighting you is a waste of time!
Hey... What's wrong, Motobalo?
His cow's acting weird.
What?
It fainted?
What happened?
Luffy, what did you do?
I didn't do anything!
Motobalo! How could this be, damn it?!
Luffy didn't shoot anything at him.
It looked like he just intimidated him.
What does that mean? He
won by pure intensity?
That giant thing just passed out!
Is that possible?
Curse you Straw Hats!
Wait just a minute, Luffy.
Sanji, I'm glad you're okay.
This all happened because
of false accusations.
I'll finish it.
Finish it?
Black Foot, so long as you live as a pirate,
I will never live in peace!
I've had enough of being
persecuted for nothing!
Shut up.
I never wanted to see the
scribble on that wanted flyer.
It wasn't supposed to exist in real life!
Then you should die!
Œil!
Nez!
Joue! Bouche! Dents!
Menton!
P-Please, no more!
Parage...
Shot!
Enjoy the fine flavors produced
by a weave of supreme techniques,
you bastard.
Attention!
I'll teach you clueless people
how to get to Fishman Island!
First, you have to get a coating
on this ship at a certain island!
That island is—
Look! That's the island!
Cool! A bubble!
Hey, I was still talking...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Landing on the Way to Fishman
Island! The Sabaody Archipelago!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!