Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Having defeated
Duval's Flying Fish Riders,
Straw Hat Luffy and company
now head for Fish-Man Island.
So, umm...
What do you say, Nami?
This doesn't mean
you're suddenly somehow forgiven.
No! Of course not!
That's not what I meant!
I was just wondering how it tastes!
It's really good!
Really?! It is?!
First, there are actually two routes
that lead to the New World!
But for outlaws like you guys,
there's really only one.
Just maintain course
for the route you'll use,
which is known as Fish-Man Island's
"Sea Floor Route"!
The Red Line is a large barrier
that stretches all around the world,
but there is one small hole
in one part of it,
and that's where Fish-Man Island is!
In order to make their ship
capable of submerging to the sea floor,
Luffy and company
needed to visit a certain island first.
This is it!
Sabaody Archipelago!
Awesome!
Oh! It came outta the ground!
Neat!
I'm riding it!
That looks fun!
Say, Hachi.
What's our purpose
on this island, anyway?
Oh, we're going to see
a coating craftsman
and have him cover your ship in resin.
Simply put, that'll make it
so your ship can go underwater.
Are you serious?!
And so Luffy and company landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago
to find a coating craftsman Hachi knows.
"Tyranny! The Rulers of Sabaody,
the Celestial Dragons"
Everyone's gone into town.
You guys aren't going?
Nah, we used up all the cola
in that last sea battle.
The ship's maintenance is my job!
And I'm stayin' behind
because I wanna help, of course!
Let's all three of us
go when we're done!
This island looks like fun!
No,
I'm gonna wait for someone to come back
and then go shopping.
Huh? How come?
Actually, you see...
It's because my beloved
Nami-san said this...
Whatever will I do?
The ship is so full
of treasure right now...
I wish there was a knight somewhere
who could protect it for me...
Tadah!
It's me!
You sure know how to fall
right into Nami's hands.
I'm a slave of love!
Admitting it yourself saves me trouble.
Hey! Zoro!
Earth to Zoro-kun!
Where are you going all by yourself?!
Just for a walk...
Stop!
Don't you dare, you damn bastard!
You always get lost!
This is an archipelago, you know!
We'll never be able to find you!
I ain't gonna get lost!
As if anyone could get lost on such
straightforward islands as these!
All the trees are numbered!
Worst case, even a kid could make
it back by asking for directions!
Oh!
I never expected you
to have such street-smarts!
We underestimated you!
Sorry! Take care!
Make sure to ask for directions!
Don't trust yourself!
I dunno what the hell
they're talking about!
I just need to remember
this tree's number.
#1. Okay.
They can mock me all they want;
I'll never get lost on these islands!
Unlike some other guy
with no sense of direction!
The World Nobles are also known
as the Celestial Dragons.
They act so high and mighty
that they wear masks
to keep from breathing
the same air as common people.
Whatever you do, don't defy them!
That's one thing you have to promise!
Sure!
There are a couple other things
to watch out for, too.
Like I mentioned before,
people heading for the New World
gather on these islands.
There are infamous
pirates like you here,
as well as marines and bounty hunters
who are out to catch them.
Not to mention kidnappers!
There's no law here at all
against buying and selling pirates.
Do anything to stand out
and they'll set their sights on you,
so be very careful what you do!
The marines here
aren't pushovers, either.
Navy Headquarters is in
nearby waters, you see.
Which is why the bounty hunters
are all just as ferocious.
And one other thing!
Oh, come on!
There are too many things
to watch out for!
Hey, when did you get hurt there?
Oh, this? Don't worry about it.
Camie and I aren't merfolk
or fish-men here.
Treat us like we're human
on these islands.
Huh? How come?
It'll make things a lot simpler.
When in a city,
do as its citizens do, Luffy.
Let's do as Mr. Octopus says.
Harder! And push into it slowly!
I'm inside!
Neat!
How curious!
I can get in! I can get in!
It's not leaking at all!
All right, then!
Put this inside.
Like this?
Is that high enough for ya?
You'll go forward now if you peddle.
Oh! It's going forward!
Awesome!
This is fun!
Yahoo!
It really doesn't pop!
Convenient, huh?
They're Sabaody Archipelago's
famous Bubble Bikes!
I wanna ride too!
Whadya say?
It's 500 Berries a day to rent one,
or 10,000 Berries to buy one!
Pretty cheap, huh?
I think we'll rent--
I want it!
I'll buy this one
with my spending money!
Me, too! Me, too!
Forget it!
Let's just rent.
There's no point in buying one.
Why do you get to decide?!
Yeah!
Urgh! I'll explain later!
We'll rent two more, mister!
Huh? You're from around these parts?
What a bummer...
This feels so nice!
Doesn't it, though?!
They even have different kinds.
It makes me want to sing now!
I think I'm gonna buy
a Bubble Bike after all!
Straw Hat.
You know how you first went up
into the sky on those bubbles?
Why did you come falling down?
Oh! Actually, I went
past the tops of the trees
and wondered if I could
go any higher up...
...when all the bubbles
around me disappeared
and the bubble I was on
suddenly popped too...
Then I fell.
You must have left
Sabaody Archipelago's climate area, then.
This place has a suitable climate
for Hustle Mustle Mangroves to grow.
Outside that area,
the resin components in the bubbles
lose a lot of their capabilities.
I see.
Then that means the bubbles
can't be ridden outside of these islands?
That's right.
Newcomers here often buy Bubble Bikes
and take them with them.
That's a dirty business.
Renting Bubble Bikes is all you need.
No! I'm buying one!
'Cause I can't agree
with that explanation!
You just don't understand it!
Basically, the bubbles will pop
outside of these islands,
mysteriously enough!
What?! They pop mysteriously?!
Why didn't you say so sooner!
We have been trying to tell you!
But you can use it on
Fish-Man Island, Luffy-chin!
There's a bubble civilization
on the sea floor, too!
I wanna go to Fish-Man Island
right away!
I can't wait!
Then you should meet
the Mermaid Princess!
She's a girl of matchless beauty!
I'm a panderer; shall I hook you up?!
That sounds splendid!
I love having an eyeful
of beautiful girls!
Though I lack eyes,
due to being a skeleton.
Wait, are you even listening?
Ooh, that smells good!
What's a "Grand-Bun"?
"Grand-Bun" "GR Famous Food"
"GR Famous Grand-choco!!"
"GR Famous Grand-Bun!!"
Grand Line Manju buns!
Commonly called Grand-Buns!
How about a taste test?
See how they say
"Grandline First Half" here?
They're very popular as souvenirs
for going into the New World!
They last for three whole months,
so you can rest easy!
These are delicious!
Could I ask you to open the next box?
Are you planning to pay?!
Grove #35.
There seem to be a lot of hotels here.
They're for the sailors who're waiting
for their passes from Marie Jois.
Building hotels is easy, you know!
See, look over there!
Paint a giant bubble with a metal alloy
and you have your foundation!
That's how round buildings are made!
Oh?
Robin!
Look! Is that a shopping mall?!
Come again!
Grand-cracker! Grand-choco!
Keychain!
Pennant!
You guys are all about the memories!
You really bought a lot!
It'd be tough to lug all that around.
Have 'im bubble pack it for you.
Bubble pack?
It's so light!
You don't need strength
to carry stuff on these islands!
Upsy-daisy...
Huh? Where are Nami and Robin?
They went to the shopping mall
in Grove #30.
They left us in charge
of getting the ship coated.
Oh? They did?
Okay! Leave it to us!
Where are we headed again?
Grove #13.
It's still a ways away,
even by Bubble Bike.
Let's go!
Camie-chan didn't come along
when we invited her...
Yeah.
She's been a bit reserved
ever since we landed on these islands.
I wonder what's up with her...
Who knows, perhaps this island
has a bad history...
Bad history?
Yahoo!
It's so fast!
Huh? Where's Straw Hat?
Over here!
Straw Hat!
I'm in the lead now!
You won't beat me!
We still have a long way to go!
Go, Hatchin!
What?!
When did this suddenly
turn into a race?!
I'm sorry!
U-uhh, umm...
I-I'm sorry!
Please stop!
Take it off!
Please! Take...
Take this off!
I...
I'm...
...going back home now!
What's all that noise?
Please! Hey!
I beg of you!
Anyone will do!
Just lend me an axe or a saw
or anything!
Please!
I'm just going to break this collar!
I won't hurt anyone!
Please let me go!
I don't want to die!
I've given up on the New World!
I have a wife and kid back home!
Come on! Please!
Help me out!
I wanna go home!
My kid was just a baby back then!
The bugger still doesn't
even know what I look like!
I'm begging you!
Who's that?
I wanna go home! Please!
I beg of you!
Don't get involved, now.
He's probably a pirate who was caught
by kidnappers and then sold!
His owners brought him to this island,
and then he ran away!
Even though he surely knows
there's no escape!
W-What's that sound?
Damn this collar!
If only... If only it wasn't for this!
Damn it! No!
No! Stop!
I... I...!
Damn it!
Slaves always have leashes
around their necks
that are set to explode if the slaves
try to remove them and escape.
I'm gonna buy souvenirs and go home...
I'm giving up the pirate business...
It's an escaped slave!
Get away!
Don't get involved with him!
H-Hey! We need to help that person!
You idiot!
You promised not to get involved,
no matter what happens!
What's with this town?!
Hatchin! What should we do?!
There are Celestial Dragons nearby!
It's okay.
Just stay calm, Camie.
Straw Hat.
Come down from the Bubble Bike.
How come?
Just hurry!
Okay... Got it.
Here they come!
That's a Celestial Dra--?
You kneel down, too!
What's the big idea?!
Whoever comes,
don't look them in the eyes!
Same for you guys, too!
Right!
Oh, my! How disgraceful, Saruu!
Is that them?
Yeah.
Dear me, Father.
Another one has broken down.
Did you remember to give it
a sedative every day?
I most certainly did.
It has no effect on the poor fool.
Please buy me a new one.
Honestly, now!
You're terrible at taking care of them!
You keep breaking everything
in my ship captain collection...
It's this thing's fault.
A grown man, always crying
about family this, family that!
When he's nothing but a mere human!
Honestly, now!
He's not doing anything now...!
You make me sick.
--She's--!
--Stop! Please!
I think I would like
a giant for a slave next.
No, you will start with a human child.
I don't like such weak ones!
Please! Just endure it!
It's the navy!
Outta the way!
We need to get out of here for now!
Would you like some tea?
It will help you relax.
I don't feel very good now...
That guy...
Do you think he'll survive?
Even if he does,
he'll probably go to prison,
seeing that he's a pirate.
That pirate could've easily
beaten that old man and lady!
So why...?!
Harm a Celestial Dragon
and a Navy HQ admiral
will lead an entire army here!
An admiral?!
Aokiji?!
It could even be Akainu or Kizaru...
There's no way of knowing.
Navy Headquarters
is very close by, you see.
What makes them so high and mighty?!
They share the Creators' blood!
Creators?
The twenty kings who created the huge
World Government organization
800 years ago!
Their descendents are
the Celestial Dragons.
With each passing generation,
they grow more reckless with power,
which is why they act like that now.
Celestial Dragons...
That him?
Yeah.
No doubt about it.
Straw Hat Luffy.
300 million Berries!
Shakky's Rip-Off Bar?!
Monkey-chan, is it? Welcome.
You know about me?!
Of course, I would know of the 300 million Berries, Luffy.
However, there are currently,
people with higher bounties than you.
Higher than Luffy?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
New Rivals Gather! The 11 Supernovas
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!