Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Luffy and company, realizing that
the Sunny will need to be coated
in order to reach Fish-Man Island
, their next destination,
stopped off at the Sabaody Archipelago.
This is it!
Sabaody Archipelago!
At the seemingly enjoyable archipelago,
Luffy and company searched
for a coating craftsman...
...but they encountered world
nobles known as Celestial Dragons
and were witness to their
domineering behavior.
Damn it!
If only... If only it wasn't for this!
Honestly, now!
You're terrible at taking care of them!
You make me sick.
She's...!
Stop! Please!
Please! Just endure it!
That pirate could've easily
beaten that old man and lady!
So why...?!
Harm a Celestial Dragon
and a Navy HQ admiral will
lead an entire army here!
They share the Creators' blood!
Creators?
The twenty kings who created
the huge World Government organization
800 years ago!
Their descendents are
the Celestial Dragons.
And then a dark shadow
loomed toward Luffy and company...
Straw Hat Luffy.
300 million Berries.
"New Rivals Gather! The 11 Supernovas"
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
What's with this skeleton freak?!
Time to die!
Why, you!
Gavotte Bon en Avant!
Gotcha!
Watch out! He's quick as a monkey!
Damn! The others are strong, too!
In that case...
...I'll just take her hostage!
Oh no! Camie! Pappagu!
Alright! C'mere!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
Alright! You okay?
Thanks, Straw Hat.
Thanks, Luffy-chin!
Yeah!
Are you done beating yours up, too?
Indeed!
You guys really are amazing!
I'm full!
I could take those guys
on any time and never lose!
Damn!
He's too strong!
300 million is too much
to handle after all!
There are so many big shots
on these islands right now, too...
Damn... Can't we bag at least one?
No, wait...
I think that girl might be a...
I just had a good idea!
What on earth is going on?
All these bounty hunters
suddenly appearing out of nowhere...
That makes three surprise attacks now!
I don't see any more taste-testing--
"Navy Keep Out"
I mean, souvenir shops, either.
It's almost strange seeing shops
and streets without anyone around...
It's hard to believe
there's a coating craftsman here!
This is a big archipelago,
so there are always places
outside the government's watchful eye.
Marines can't go very far
into the interior, either.
Look here.
A map?
It shows all the different areas here,
divided into 10-grove sections.
None of it's set in stone or anything.
It's just how they are generally.
For example,
the area we've come through...
Your ship is docked at #40,
a tourism area filled
with souvenir shops.
And #30 is an amusement park area
centered around Sabaody Park.
Oh! #60 is a naval post
where the government comes and goes!
Yeah, #60 is like the front door,
you could say.
Then what area is this place?
Here?
We're in Grove #16 right now.
Most of #1 through #29
is a lawless area!
That's why there are
so many bounty hunters.
Couldn't you have told us sooner?!
And then Zoro and Sanji
could've come instead!
It's okay!
We're headed for #13, the next one over!
Chopper-chin!
You and Skeleton-chin were really cool!
That doesn't make me happy, you dumbass!
I'm blushing so much
that my ears are red!
Though I have no ears,
because I'm a skeleton.
"Sabaody Archipelago - Grove #13"
All right! We're here!
We finally made it...
It's the shop on top of that root.
Is it still in business?
It's been 10 years now...
Hey, is the coating craftsman
a fish-man too?
Oh, Pappagu and I don't know him.
We heard he's incredible, though.
Oh? Really?
Well, we'll find out when we meet 'im!
"Shakky's Rip-Off Bar"
Shakky's Rip-Off Bar!
Hachi.
It really sounds like they intend
to rip you off at this place...
This craftsman isn't super-violent
by any chance, is he?
Don't worry!
They're nice people!
I've known 'em since I was little!
Hey, why are we going to a bar?!
Looks like they're still in business.
Rayleigh? Shakky?
"Bar Owner & Former Pirate
Shakuyaku (Shakky)"
Come on in.
What'll it be?
Oh?
Is that you, Hatchan?
Long time, no see!
It's good to see you again, Shakky!
Yes.
How long has it been? 10 years?
Have a seat for a second.
I was in the middle
of ripping these kiddos off
for an excessive amount.
Take your time.
It won't take long.
Oh?
You gave up being a pirate, Hatchan?
Yeah, a lot happened...
But that's okay.
After all, an honest
life is the best life.
Say, it's rare for merfolk
to be above water.
Are you Hatchan's girlfriend,
Camie-chan?
Eh?!
M-M-Me, Hatchan's wife?
I-I-It's too s-s-soon for...!
Jumpy much?
We run a takoyaki shop together.
Oh, really?
Oh, right.
Let me get you some drinks--
Shakky-san.
These boiled beans are delicious.
They're raiding the fridge!
Luffy! Brook! She's gonna rip you off!
It's okay. Go ahead.
Here, I have something you'll like.
Here.
Cotton candy!
Sweet! Yum!
Okay, that'll be 100,000 Berries.
I... I... don't have that much...
I'm sorry. I was only teasing.
I can't charge friends of Hatchan.
Really?!
Lady.
How do you know what Chopper likes?
You're Monkey-chan's group, correct?
You know about me?!
Of course.
Everyone's talking about you.
Plus I stay well-informed.
Wow!
You're famous, Luffy-chin!
But I had no idea
you had a skeleton on your crew
or that skeletons could
even move about, though.
Oh, pardon my late introduction.
I am the dead and skeletonized Brook.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, look at how much you've dropped...
Shakky-san...
What a delightful person!
What color are your panties?
Why're you asking that?!
Let me think... I believe today's are...
Don't tell him!
Oh, my! How incredible!
My nosebleed won't stop!
I have no nose, though! Kaboom!
Here you are!
Thanks!
I read your news stories.
How much of the Enies Lobby
incident is true?
Is it true you picked a fight
with the government?
Forget about that.
It's too much of a pain to explain.
You're not going to brag?
You really are a big-shot...
That reminds me...
You have the same name
as someone in the navy named Garp.
Yeah. He's my grandpa.
I thought so.
Garp once chased me a long time ago.
How come?
Shakky used to be a pirate.
Really?
I washed my hands of it
40 years ago, though.
Wait! How old are you, lady?!
Nowadays I have fun
cheering on rookies like you.
Anyway, Shakky...
No, don't say it.
I know. I know everything.
You guys came all this way by land
to help Monkey-chan's group
get their ship coated here, right?
That was good!
Here you go!
So basically,
you have a coating job for Rayleigh?
That's right.
He isn't here, though.
Eh?!
The craftsman isn't here?!
We wanna go to Fish-Man Island!
Well, seeing as he wouldn't
leave this archipelago,
why don't you check around
some pubs or gambling houses?
We'll just wait 'til he gets back, then.
Yes, he'll be back eventually.
He's been gone half a year now, though.
Half a year?!
He's probably shacked up
with some girls he's picked up,
so I'm not worried about his wellbeing.
Maybe it's the former pirate in him
that keeps him away for
so long once he leaves.
The old craftsman guy
was a pirate, too?!
That's right.
This is a real problem for us, though.
If he's not here, then our only option
is to go look for him.
Do you know where he might be?
Hmm...
He's probably somewhere in #1 to #29,
if I had to guess...
Groves #1 through #29...
That's the lawless territory!
He's notorious, too.
He can't relax with the
navy keeping watch...
And let's see...
Another area he's fond of
is Sabaody Park.
The amusement park?!
Alright! Let's look there!
--Yahoo!
--Yay! Amusement park!
Camie! Stop that!
Amusement park! Amusement park!
In any case, be careful,
wherever you end up looking.
According to my information network,
including you, there are now 11 people
on the Sabaody Archipelago
whose bounties exceed
100 million Berries.
11 people with bounties
over 100 million?!
Amusement park! Amusement park!
In any case, be careful,
wherever you end up looking.
According to my information network,
including you, there are now 11 people
on the Sabaody Archipelago
whose bounties exceed
100 million Berries.
11 people with bounties
over 100 million?!
Yes.
Excluding Monkey-chan and Roronoa-chan,
that still leaves nine.
When you entered the Grand Line,
you chose one of seven routes
and followed your Log all the way here.
Yeah.
So, naturally, there are others
who took one of the six other routes
and had to overcome many difficulties
similar to yours to get here.
All routes run into the Red Line,
so everyone gathers on this
archipelago to cross that wall.
Understand?
It's not every day
that so many of the world's rookies
all show up at the same time, though...
Especially Kid, Luffy,
Hawkins, Drake, Law...
These names showed up
in newspapers all the time.
I don't read newspapers.
Information is a weapon.
Shouldn't you at least learn
the names of your rivals?
Let's see... Kid, Hawkins, and...
Drake, was it?
In terms of bounty amounts...
you'd be #2.
There's someone worth more than Luffy?!
On these islands?!
"Grove #24 - Restaurant"
Look at her eat!
Where does all the food go?!
Bring more food!
Vulgar woman...
She's ruining my meal.
Go shut her up.
That's not a good idea, Father!
Navy Headquarters is just
a stone's throw away!
If we were to cause a scene now...!
"From West Blue Captain
of the Firetank Pirates"
Capone "Gang" Bege.
A 138 million Berry bounty.
Where's my seconds?!
Bring it now!
T-They said they're working
as hard as they can, Captain.
It's not fast enough!
More pizzas!
"From South Blue Captain
of the Bonney Pirates"
Jewelry Bonney, the "Glutton".
A 140 million Berry bounty.
I'll bring it right away!
I-I'm very sorry!
Why, you little...!
Stop.
Why, Captain?!
He got spaghetti all over my clothes!
Such was the fate of those clothes.
I apologize for scaring you.
Taking a life on this particular day
will only diminish fortuity.
"From North Blue Captain
of the Hawkins Pirates"
Basil Hawkins, the "Magician."
A 249 million Berry bounty.
Who's the guy with the stupid face?
Oh, that'd be Sea Roar.
Boss!
What's going on?! A fight?!
If you want a fight,
let's save it for the other side!
Or do you not know how strong I am?
"From Grand Line (Longarm Tribe)
Captain of On Air Pirates"
Scratchmen Apoo, the "Sea Roar."
A 198 million Berry bounty.
Then quit yer damn starin'.
Boss! Don't!
Damn, you're one creepy bastard.
I can get rid of you
right now, if you'd like!
"From South Blue
Captain of the Kid Pirates"
Eustass "Captain" Kid.
A 315 million Berry bounty.
The Mad Monk's on a rampage!
We gotta get outta here, quick!
If you wanna go wild...
...do it in the New World!
"From North Blue
Captain of the Drake Pirates"
"Red Flag" X. Drake.
A 222 million Berry bounty.
I see.
Drake, the fallen navy officer...
"From Sky Island
Captain of the Fallen Monk Pirates"
"Mad Monk" Urouge.
A 180 million Berry bounty.
You're lucky to be alive, masked fellow.
"From South Blue
Combat Crewman for the Kid Pirates"
Killer, the "Massacre Soldier."
A 162 million Berry bounty.
Things were just getting good, too...
Drake-ya...
How many people have you killed?
"From North Blue
Captain of the Heart Pirates"
Trafalgar Law, the Surgeon of Death.
A 200 million Berry bounty.
A countless number of pirates
have entered the Grand Line,
but only a countable few
have made it this far.
The Grand Line is a lot like
an enormous survival tournament.
Those pirates who've made it
this far through each route alive
are truly the cream of the crop.
One of them
might even usher
in the next generation of pirates.
In any case,
with so many rookies here
all at the same time,
things are going to get ugly
in the New World.
Also, as for why Captain Kid's
bounty is higher than yours...
It's because he causes
serious harm to civilians.
Not very charming, is he?
That's why I'm behind you guys 100%.
Well, for now...
I just wanna have fun!
But I'm worried about
the old craftsman guy,
if he's in such a rough town.
My husband will be fine.
After all, he's 100 times
stronger than you kids...
100...
...times?
Right! We're gonna go find the old coating guy!
Yeah!
Oh! It's the Sabaody Park!
Let's try looking here for him!
Yeah! He might be hiding in the ferris wheel!
Alright, let's have fun!
You're not trying to find him!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Target is Camie!! The Looming
Clutches of a Professional Kidnapper"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!