Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
In search of a coating craftsman
to help them reach Fish-Man Island,
the Straw Hat crew
visited the Sabaody Archipelago
along with Hachi and Camie's group.
However, Camie was abducted,
and is about to be sold
as a slave at a human auction!
"Time Limit
-- The Human Auction Begins"
"Navy Headquarters"
"Dark King" Silvers Rayleigh, huh...
Apparently, no one around him
recognizes him,
so he's being sold
as a regular old man...
The Dark King,
being sold at a human auction?
It is hard to believe something like this
would happen to the real one.
My men aren't 100% sure
it's really him, either...
Tea!
Oh, thank you.
What should we do, Vice-Admiral?
Shall we report this
to Fleet Admiral Sengoku?
No, I'll handle this myself.
Don't tell anyone about it, now.
Not even Sengoku!
Give your men a convenient story!
But, what if it really is him?
It's him, all right.
I'm sure of it.
I hear reports of him
being seen on occasion.
If I had to guess,
I'd say he probably lost
while gambling and sold himself.
He may be an old soldier,
but if we take Rayleigh on foolishly,
our forces will lose an
unthinkable number of men.
Now is an especially bad time.
Are you suggesting the navy
take on two "legends" at once?!
Okay, ladies and gentlemen!
It's the moment you've been waiting for!
Grove #1's monthly
Great Human Auction is about to begin!
And your emcee, of course, is this man!
Sometimes known as the
Walking Super Bazaar...
...Mr. Disco!
Hello, everyone!
I have some great-quality
slaves again for you today!
You're lucky!
We even have a super-great
showcase item for sale today!
I pray from the bottom of my heart
that you'll get to take home
the slaves of your choice!
What are you planning to purchase today?
The last human slave I bought
didn't even last 10 days
before it broke down.
So I'm hoping to procure a young
and durable male giant today.
I'm considering buying two
or three young girls for eye candy.
Oh, you certainly do love those!
I can't wait to see what
cuties they'll have today!
Oh, you!
Well, then!
Let's get this auction started!
Get #2 and #3 ready.
Right!
Entry #1!
From Troa in West Blue!
A proud pirate from a
long line of musicians
and versatile with musical instruments!
Give him an instrument, and he'll play
any background music you request!
He's a human music box!
He's also a great cleaner!
Give him a mop, and he won't
miss a single speck of dust!
In addition,
he's skilled at making wine!
A hard-working 25 year old male human!
192 centimeters and 130 kilograms!
Goes by the name of Byron!
Bidding will start at the special
offer price of 480,000 Berries!
Okay! Raise your bidding paddles
and name your price!
Well, 480,000 is a steal!
#7 bids 480,000!
Any other bidders?!
500,000!
#82 has just bid 500,000 Berries!
520,000!
Yes! #105 bids 520,000 Berries!
I have 520,000!
This is a great value, you know!
He can play music, perform housework,
and as a pirate,
he'll make a great guard-dog!
Are there any other bidders?!
Any other bidders?!
530,000!
550,000!
600,000!
#7 bids 600,000!
Any other bids?!
Sold, for 600,000 Berries!
Using by-bidders to enliven the place
and raise prices to their limits...
This is the pro technique and skill
of Mr. Disco-sama,
the Walking Super Bazaar!
Okay! There are many more
great deals to come!
Be sure not to miss your chance,
ladies and gentlemen!
Now, then!
Let's move on to the next item!
"Human Buying and Selling"
What is this disgusting list, Duval?!
They're market prices!
Market prices?
The general minimum value
of humans is 500,000 Berries...
Male giants are worth
50 million Berries...
What?!
Female mermaids are worth
70 million Berries?!
Now do you see why everyone
wants to catch mermaids?
They're in a class of their own!
Once you buy one,
you're free to have it do whatever you want,
but most are used by rich people
as decorations.
They spend the rest of their lives
in cramped fish tanks as eye candy.
What the hell are you trying to say?!
Oh, it's just that when I think about it,
that's not living at all.
If you feel that way,
then find her already!
This is Fish #20!
I've checked all the kidnapping groups here!
There's no word in this area
about a mermaid being abducted!
No mermaid info here, either!
Damn!
No leads at all here, either!
Hurry up already!
Gimme a break!
It ain't a bird!
It needs a running start!
Camie! Where are you?!
It pisses me off!
I mean seriously, it's a giant!
Catching one that was asleep
was nice and all,
but it took so much work
just to haul the thing here!
You'd normally think our item
would be the main event, right?!
But then some guy brought in a mermaid
just before the auctions started!
So how can I not drink now?!
H-Hold on! Who was this guy?!
This is Fish #5!
Attention, all Rosy Life Riders!
Do you read me?
It was Peterman who
kidnapped the mermaid!
He sold her to the
auction house on Grove #1!
Peterman?!
Do you know where that is?!
Yeah! Let's step on it!
This is a bit fast!
It's frightening!
Don't tell me she's been
sold to someone already?!
Hurry!
Grove #1 is right nearby!
Leave it to me!
Our destination is the auction house!
We know where she is?!
Thank goodness!
Camie!
Hurry!
I'm tryin' to get back to my ship.
Do you know where the #1 trees are?
Sure, I'll tell you!
Oh? I appreciate it.
Listen!
You ain't going back anywhere now...
...Pirate Hunter Zoro-san!
Your 120 million Berry bounty is mine!
U-Uhh, let me think! Grove #1 is...!
Okay! Let's move on!
Next up is Entry #6!
A 10-pack of male human laborers!
Head here!
Attention all units!
Check today's auction schedule!
It starts at 4:00,
so it's been going for 30 minutes now!
Hey, are we gonna make it?!
Don't worry.
Mermaids are always the
big showcase items,
so they won't auction her off
until the last half!
We'll make it in time!
Just take the shortest distance!
You're slower than the flying fish!
Just stay calm, Young Master Black Leg!
I am the head of the team!
Have I changed course
after hearing where the mermaid is?!
No...
That's because
I've been heading for Grove #1
from the very start!
Look ahead! That's Grove #1!
Crashing the place first goes to show
why I'm head of the team!
Seriously?!
Was it "colleague's intuition"
or something?!
We're here, Mr. Reindeer!
Yes! Thanks!
Oh, Sanji!
You didn't make it here first!
Sanji-kun! Chopper!
Nami-swan!
Hey! Everyone!
Camie!
Be careful!
Yeah! Thanks!
Who's this guy?!
Two million berries!
Any other bids?
Sold!
This the place?!
Why can't you give her back?!
You have no business selling Camie-chan!
You're the one who has no business here!
If you keep pestering us,
we'll take legal action against you
for obstruction of business!
Damn them...!
Business my ass, you damn bastard!
A business like this has
no place in this world!
An outlaw pirate has no business
lecturing me about being humane!
Buying and selling people
is taboo throughout the world!
How much are you paying the government?!
That's not a very nice thing to say.
But, yes...!
Even when people from the government
or navy talk with us,
they apparently have a hard time
hearing the phrase "human trafficking"
so it's as if they don't know
about the existence of this industry at all!
What a load of crap!
You're all in this together!
I can't believe the
government quietly allows this!
How can this be happening?!
This is horrible!
That's just the way it is.
There's nothing you can do about it.
Which is why you're also--
This is annoying!
If we're sure the mermaid's here,
then this is all we need to do!
Weapons...!
No!
There are Celestial Dragons inside,
and if Camie is being held here,
then she must have a collar on by now!
Eh?!
Those ones that explode?!
We can't just go
and take her out of there then!
Please, feel free to leave!
Damn you!
No, we can't do that, Sanji!
Let go, Chopper!
No, Sanji!
Dammit...!
There's no getting through to you!
Hey, girl!
Where are you going?!
Calm down, Sanji!
Nami-san?!
If we can't use force,
then we'll get Camie back
using their rules!
Bring out #15 and #16.
Right!
No!
Stop!
I don't want this!
I'd much rather stay locked up!
I don't want to be a slave!
Help me! Help me!
Sedate him!
Call the navy! Please!
Please don't sell me to someone!
Hatchin... Save me...
Boss.
Isn't that the Straw Hat crew?
The Straw Hat captain ain't with 'em.
I was hoping to see just how much
of a crazy bastard he is, but...
Now, then! Next up is Entry #14!
This item is a female human!
Aside from housekeeping,
she's also an expert in games,
ranging from cards to chess!
She'll be great to have
when you want to pass the time!
Let's start the bidding
at 600,000 Berries!
Oh, this could be an excellent bargain!
Drat!
I used up my entire budget
on the female human I just bid on!
This one is clearly much better, too!
That's a shame!
But I do believe I'll bid on this one!
700,000 Berries!
900,000 Berries!
1 million 200 thousand!
1 million 500 thousand!
2 million!
Bastards...
3 million!
#51 has bid 3 million Berries!
Are there any other bids?!
Any other bids?!
Sold to #51 for 3 million Berries!
Is Camie going to wind up
like this, too?
We will get her back! Just you watch!
But, in this situation, how...?!
We have quite a lot of treasure
on our ship right now.
Altogether, I think it's
worth at least 200 million.
What's the market price for mermaids?
That should be more than enough,
but I can't pay you back!
What're you talking about, Hachi?
Are you Camie's guardian or something?
It's not like that!
If it's to get our friend back,
then I don't care how much it costs!
You guys okay with that?!
Of course we are!
This isn't about money!
Guys... Thank you!
I'll never forget this
for the rest of my life!
I love Nami-san when she's like that!
Shut up. Come on.
Extra! Extra!
Is the World Government crazy?!
Is this for real?! If they do that...!
Captain! This is bad!
So that's why?
What is it, Captain Drake?!
It finally makes sense.
I wondered why there were
so few marines on these islands,
despite being so close
to Navy Headquarters...
What's happened?!
Whitebeard's second division commander,
Fire Fist Ace, is being
given a public execution!
But won't Whitebeard
take action if they do that?!
There's going to be a war!
Okay!
Things are really picking up
here at the Great Human Auction!
Next up is another
highly-recommended item!
Entry #15 is an unbelievably
beautiful female slave!
Just look at these
miraculous proportions!
This is Pashia, a 20 year old dancer!
The sight of Pashia--
one of our showcase items today--
is guaranteed to beguile
and lead you to heaven!
800,000!
Already, bidding for the beautiful
dancer Pashia is at 800,000!
1 million!
1 million 500 thousand!
3 million!
Bidding has jumped straight
to 3 million Berries!
Are there any other bids?!
What the hell?!
What do all these people
take ladies for?!
We will save her!
I refuse to let Camie
get sold to the likes of them!
Hurry!
I know!
Hurry to Grove #1!
This is Grove #2...
The next one must be it.
And you call yourself
a member of the Straw Hats?!
You've been doing nothing
but scream this whole time!
I can't help it;
it's even more frightening
than the rides at Sabaody Park!
It's like my heart
is about to fly out...
I don't have a heart, though!
Geez!
Your face is a whole lot scarier,
if you ask me!
I wonder if everyone's already there?!
We will save you!
Hang on, Camie!
Get #17 ready!
Camie's auction has started!
It's ok!
We've got 200 million berries, after all!
The Celestial Dragons!
Are they planning to buy Camie, too?
My friend's about to be bought and taken away.
I can't let that happen!
I'm not gonna lose!
I'll get Camie back, no matter what!
On the next episode of One Piece!
The Fist Explodes! Destroy the Auction
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!