Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
The Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago
to search for a ship coating craftsman
to help them reach Fish-Man Island.
During the adventure, Camie, a mermaid
who was with them, was kidnapped.
After determining her location,
Nami and company attempted
to win her in an auction.
All the way from Fish-Man
Island, the mermaid Camie!
Camie!
They're selling Camie now!
Alright! We're gonna get her
back! We have 200 million here!
However, Nami's plan failed
in an unforeseen manner.
I'll buy it for 500 million Berries!
So suddenly?! We don't have that much!
We can't let this happen!
We can't let our friend get
bought and taken away like this!
Just then...
Luffy!
Luffy-chin!
Camie! We've been looking
everywhere! What a relief!
Hold on, Straw Hat! What are you doing?!
Hachi tried to hold Luffy back as
he went to rescue Camie, but...
He's a fish-man!
Hachi was then gunned down
by a Celestial Dragon!
Don't... Don't be mad...
You promised not to defy
the Celestial Dragons,
even if you saw someone get shot...!
You lousy fish, still blabbering
on even though I shot you!
You annoy me!
What's with that look, you?!
You guys'll get in huge trouble too!
Straw Hat-ya...?
Is he serious?!
You annoy me, too!
"Major Panic! Desperate
Struggle at the Auction House"
S-Saint Charloss...
Ch-Charloss!
Sorry, guys.
Punching this guy means a navy admiral
is gonna come here with a warship...
I missed my chance to cut him down
because you beat him up first.
Hachi! Hang on!
You're all in big trouble now...!
We can't help it! That's just how Luffy is!
Alright, then...
Guess that makes it clear
what we gotta do now.
I think the key to Camie's collar
is probably somewhere backstage!
I need to tend to Hachi's
injury! You get the key!
Guys...!
Charloss...!
Brother Charloss! Not even
Father has ever struck you!
Curse you!
How dare you, a commoner,
lay a hand on my son!
Th-They've made the Celestial Dragons mad!
Run! Get outside!
Leave! Quick!
Quit pushing!
I'll teach you what happens
when you assault us,
the descendants of this world's Creators!
Hell if we care, you bastard!
How dare you strike Saint Roswald!
Joue!
Concasser!
Go, Franky! Free Camie-chan!
Alright! Super leave it to me!
Guards! Get them! Seize the pirates!
They just keep coming!
What?!
What a ruckus. Sounds like
something's happened...
All out...
Well, then...
Old man...
Only a fool would protect a lousy fish!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
Gotcha!
Tatsu...
...Maki!
Strong Right!
...And Fresh Fire!
Outta the way, outta the way!
Such violence!
Curse you all...!
Halt!
Stay away!
Watch out for thunderclouds!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
So sorry!
Yeah!
You intend to defy us to
the very end, do you?!
Gum-Gum...
...Battle-Axe!
Camie isn't for sale!
Call for a navy admiral and a warship!
Let them see who's boss!
When are we gonna get there?!
Soon! We're in Grove #1 now!
Straw Hat, the busty girl, the
young master, the swordsman,
the panties guy, and the
reindeer have already arrived!
Huh? That means the only ones
who are late are Robin, Brook...
...and me?!
Oh! How could this happen
to the great Usopp-sama?!
Hurry! Go!
Quit thrashing around! That's dangerous!
Come on! Faster!
Go!
Oh, what a beautiful sky!
Wait, huh?!
Whew, I owe you one...
You know better than to jump off early!
You're the one who shook me off!
You were going too fast. Bye.
We'll be going on ahead!
Wait for me, guys!
A pirate struck a Celestial Dragon!
Navy Headquarters is going
to send a warship now!
"Justice"
I can't believe this! I should have
just paid for my slave and left!
Watch it, you!
It would be a waste to
use that to buy someone.
I think I'll use it in a
more productive way instead.
There's no end to 'em!
That's for sure! I'm gonna wear
down my heels at this rate!
Say your prayers!
Duck!
36 Pound Cannon!
Are you trying to kill us?!
I did warn you.
We couldn't hear you!
Camie!
Hatchin!
Are you okay?! They didn't do
anything bad to you, did they?!
I'm fine! But you've been hurt!
Don't worry! Who do you take me for?!
I'm Hachi, the takoyaki seller!
Just hang on a little
longer! Wait right there!
Yeah! Hatchin! Everyone!
Just like the rumors said...
Yeah. He's one crazy bastard.
Straw Hat-ya Luffy...
A 300 million Berry bounty, huh...
An uproar is already underway. There's
a flood of people at the entrance.
Our only choice is to jump into the
fray! Just crash into it, if you would!
Understood!
Huh?! I-I need to prepare myself first!
Here we go!
My "can't go to auction houses" disease...!
More flying fish!
Thank you!
Take care!
Cien Fleurs!
Wing!
Alright! Good luck!
Off I go!
Clutch!
I just cracked my back...!
Brook.
Oh, that's right! Milk heals
me since I'm nothing but bones!
I'm nothing but bones
and bones! Viva calcium!
Now, then! Pardon my late entrance!
Damn pirate!
Clutch!
Damn! Guard the mermaid at all costs!
500 million! She sold for 500 million!
Exterminate them at once!
Sorry to keep you waiting, folks!
There's nothing to fear now
that Usopp-sama is here!
The hero is always the
last to make an entrance!
I am the headliner here, after all!
S-So high up!
Since I'm here, maybe I'll
just fret for a little longer!
Get going already!
I actually would've preferred
to do it at my own pace!
I'll punish these cretins by
stuffing and preserving the women
and making the men slaves and starving them!
Father!
Oww, oww...!
Wait, that didn't hurt that much...
Sorry, mister!
S-Saint Roswald, too?!
You just repeated your crime, pirate!
Usopp! Robin! Brook!
Looks like everyone's here!
Luffy! Where's Camie?!
Over there! We'll run away as soon
as the bomb around her neck is off!
We have to hurry before the
warship and admiral get here!
Eh?!
The navy's already here, Straw Hat-ya.
Who're you?
What's with that bear?
They've had the place surrounded
before the auctions even began.
Navy Headquarters has a post
on this archipelago, you see.
Please leave the area immediately!
It's all right! We're here!
How's it look inside?!
We've finished evacuating the patrons!
The three Celestial Dragons are still inside!
Bring them out at once!
You damn pirates! Don't think
you'll get out of here unhurt!
I dunno who they wanted to catch,
but I doubt they expected anyone
would beat up the Celestial Dragons.
That was an interesting show
you gave, Straw Hat-ya crew.
You must be Trafalgar Law.
Luffy. He's a pirate.
Huh?! The bear, too?
And the man over there...
Eustass Captain Kid.
Eh?! That's the one with a
higher bounty than Luffy-san?!
This is unforgivable!
In which case, I'll kill this
mermaid that they're after!
The 500 million Berries!
P-P-Please wait, Saint Shalria!
That item hasn't been paid for yet!
Please wait, Saint Shalria! Saint Shalria!
Quiet, commoner!
All right, fish! This is
the end, once and for all!
Crap! Camie-chan's in trouble!
Quit your squirming!
Damn...!
Now you die!
Camie!
Oh no! We can't stop her in time!
S-Saint Shalria!
See, Mr. Giant?
The place is in a real uproar.
I'd say the auction's over.
I've stolen some money now,
so guess I'll head back
to the gambling houses...
You're one disagreeable old man.
You were only here to get some money?
I was hoping for a chance to steal
from whoever bought me too...
But I guess it wasn't meant to be.
Oh, right. I'm all out.
First thing is more alcohol.
Think about it.
I don't know about you, but I wouldn't
want an old man like me for a slave.
Oh? Looks like we've
garnered some attention...
Who's that old man and that giant?!
Those are today's merchandise! How
did they get out of their cell?!
They don't have collars!
How did they unlock them?!
What do we do?
What do you mean? Catching people is
outside of our field of expertise!
We can't hold back an unshackled giant!
R-Rayleigh!
You mean Rayleigh, the coating craftsman?!
Which one is he?!
Oh! Is that you, Hachi?! It is!
It's good to see you again!
What are you doing here?!
How did you get that injury?!
No, that's okay, you needn't say a thing!
In short... I see. I understand
the situation now.
You sure got yourself into
a heap of trouble, Hachi.
And you folks saved him?
Well, then...
Is he...
It couldn't be!
Huh?! How?! What did you just do?!
Who is this old guy?!
That straw hat suits dauntless men very well.
I've been wanting to meet you...
...Monkey D. Luffy.
That brat again?
He's always causing problems,
one after another!
Given that World Nobles are the victims
here, we will need to take action, Sengoku-san.
Kizaru...
Allow me to go.
Rest easy.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Admiral Kizaru Takes Action!
Sabaody Archipelago Thrown into Chaos"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!