Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
The Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago
to search for a ship coating craftsman
to help them reach Fish-Man Island.
During the adventure, Camie, a mermaid
who was with them, was kidnapped
and about to be sold as a slave.
Luffy, after storming the
auction house to save her...
Quit your squirming!
Damn...!
Now you die!
I've been wanting to meet you...
...Monkey D. Luffy.
"Admiral Kizaru Takes Action! Sabaody
Archipelago Thrown into Chaos"
This is bad! This town-- this
whole archipelago-- is in danger!
Straw Hat Luffy supposedly kicked
a Celestial Dragon's ass!
At the auction house on Grove #1!
What?!
Apparently Kid and Law are there, too!
That Straw Hat bastard!
What was he thinking?!
Doesn't he know that an admiral
from Navy Headquarters
will bring a warship here if
anyone hurts a Celestial Dragon?!
Has our ship been coated?!
It was completed yesterday!
We set sail for Fish-Man Island immediately!
We can't just sit around
while an admiral shows up!
Yes, sir!
Captain! Let's get out of here!
There's no point in staying here!
Guess that dumbass's captain
is an even bigger dumbass!
If I ever run into 'em in the
New World... I'll destroy 'em!
Causing trouble with Navy Headquarters
with the New World right in sight...
What a truly troublesome lot they are...
Focus on getting ready to set sail.
Yes, sir! Right away, Captain Drake!
Now, then. Who's going to show up?
Given the situation, I somehow doubt
this is an all-out arrest plot.
It's Straw Hat Luffy they're after, right?
I think I'd like to see what
an admiral is actually like.
You can't be serious, Apoo-san!
Let's just get out of here!
Captain Hawkins! It's dangerous
here! Let's set sail immediately!
Calm down.
I am not destined to die today.
"Holy Land of Marie Jois"
That brat again?! It's one
thing after the other!
What's with that entire family's bloodline?!
Reports indicate the presence
of the Straw Hat crew,
Eustass Captain Kid and his crew,
and Trafalgar Law and his crew.
Thirteen people with bounties
have been confirmed!
Of them, five are rookies
worth over 100 million each!
Naturally, the key offender
appears to be Monkey D. Luffy,
who assaulted the Celestial Dragons!
We've lost contact with the
guards at the Human Shop--
oh, I mean Employment Office.
I believe they may have all been subdued...
In any case, this act of taking
three Celestial Dragons hostage
is a vile and unprecedented transgression!
Have they made any demands?
No, none at the moment...
Whatever the case may be, Sengoku-san,
we'll need to take action
given that World Nobles are the victims here.
Kizaru...
Allow me to go. Rest easy; I won't be long.
"Justice"
This is no laughing matter!
This is your shop, you know!
Mister Doflamingo...!
Where are you right now?!
The shop has lost all credibility, and
then there's Roswald's family too!
They're definitely going to lash out at us!
Do something to fix things!
Seriously... Human trafficking
is so old-fashioned, you idiot.
It's all about smiles now! Smiles!
Disco, I'm giving the shop to you.
So don't be callin' me anymore!
What?! You're abandoning us during
the worst crisis we've ever had?!
Quiet, you annoying bastard!
While you sit there blaming
me for your own misfortune
a "New Era" draws ever closer, Disco-kun.
The navy has given orders forcing
me-- no, us-- into active duty!
Knowing this, what do you see
on the horizon, Disco-kun?
The Whitebeard Pirates versus
the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Please evacuate as far away as you can!
No watching, please! These
are dangerous people!
The slave I bought is still inside!
Have the mortars arrived yet?
Yes, most of them! We're
hurrying to set them up!
Has HQ said anything?
That Admiral Kizaru is coming, but
the vanguard will consist of...
Of them?! They're coming here?!
Yes, sir! That's what they said...
I'm going to remove your collar
now. Are you ready, girl?
Hold on, old man! Don't
be crazy! It'll explode!
We've seen a slave's collar explode before!
That's a bad idea! A very bad idea!
Are you sure about this, Luffy?!
W-Wait! Franky is looking
for the key as we speak!
We should really wait until he
finds it and brings it back!
Yeah! Stop him, Straw Hat!
Damn! Not here, either!
Dammit!
It'll be all right. Just stay still.
I dunno what kind of power he used...
...but the one thing for sure is
that he's no ordinary old man!
And that somehow means it's okay
to leave Camie-chan in his hands?!
Dammit! What's Franky doing?!
I'm telling you, it's too dangerous!
It won't come off without the key!
It's ringing! What're we gonna do?!
Stop! Stop it!
Camie!
Hold on! I'm coming!
What?!
Hey! What was that?!
See, I told you! Now Camie's...!
What's all this now?!
Don't scare me like that!
Your collar and handcuffs are already off!
It came off...
C-Camie!
Camie! Thank goodness!
What the hell?! I finally manage
to find 'em, but then...!
Oh! You found them? Well done!
But we no longer need them.
Here, you carry this girl.
U-Umm... Th-Thanks!
What in the hell's going on
here?! Who are you, anyway?!
Huh? What did he do?
That geezer did something mysterious again!
Just who is that old guy?!
Stop! Stop it!
He took the collar off barehanded?!
Hey, almost-slaves!
All the buyers took off! You
should scram while you can, too!
Here!
If that geezer took out these
guards all at once too,
then he must know how to use
magic or some type of sorcery!
He's got powers or something!
He said something about
your straw hat, though...
That straw hat suits dauntless men very well.
I've been wanting to meet you...
...Monkey D. Luffy.
How do you know him, Luffy?!
I don't know him! Really!
I think he used what's called "Haki."
I don't know much about it either, though...
Sorry about that, fellows. I didn't
realize other pirates were watching.
You must be quite strong to have
withstood that with no problem at all.
I never expected to meet
such a big-shot here...
"Dark King" Silvers Rayleigh...
No doubt about it. What's a legendary
man doing in a place like this?
On these islands I'm Ray-san,
the coating craftsman.
Don't go calling me that other name.
I'm an old soldier now. I just
want to live in peace and quiet.
I take it you'll survive, Hachi?
After I told you all those times
not to walk around these islands...
I'm sorry...
Thanks for saving my friend, fellows.
So, what's this about wanting
to meet me, old guy?
Yes, let's save that for later.
We first need to get out of here.
They have the place completely
surrounded, Boss.
Alright, you criminals! Release
the Roswald family at once!
An admiral will be arriving shortly!
I recommend immediate surrender!
Don't blame us for whatever
happens, you rookies!
We're not only caught up in this, we're
being treated as accomplices now.
I got a good glimpse of the insanity
that makes Straw Hat Luffy so notorious.
I have no complaints, but I'd rather not
run into an admiral now if I can avoid it!
Oh, I'd prefer not to use that power of
mine anymore, so I leave this to you!
It'll be hard for me to stay settled
down if the navy discovers who I am.
I have no intention of helping
out a senior citizen!
The longer we stay here, the
more troops there'll be!
I think I'll go on ahead!
While I'm at it, I'll help you guys out too!
I'll clean things up outside, so don't worry!
I told you, I'll do it!
Shut up!
I'm gonna do it!
Get outta here!
Shut up, you guys!
I'm going to do it.
What're you talking about?!
I told you, leave it to me!
No! I'm gonna do it!
Don't tell me what to do!
You guys just don't get it!
You're the one who doesn't get it!
Alright!
You guys can go back inside!
Hey! Are you even listening?!
I told you two to stay back!
Tell me what to do again and I'll start
by getting rid of you, Eustass-ya!
Get ready!
All three of them are captains!
They're spearheading the attack!
Monkey D. Luffy, worth 300 million!
I'm going!
Eustass Captain Kid, worth 315 million!
Let me handle it.
Trafalgar Law, worth 200 million!
You can stay here and
bicker all you want. I...
...can handle this all by myself!
All three of them have bounties
well over 100 million!
Geez, they're so simpleminded!
Hey! There's gonna an all-out brawl!
Let's use that chance to escape! We
can't just sit around here anyway!
Hatchin...
Thanks... I'm sorry for
causing you trouble...!
Never mind me! I'm just
glad you're all right!
Camie! It's my fault this happened to you!
I shouldn't have let you
go to the amusement park!
No, I'll always cherish the memory
of going to the amusement park!
There's no reason to apologize, Pappagu!
Straw Hat said the same thing, actually...
Eh?
What're you guys talking about?
There isn't one thing you
guys should be sorry for!
All three of you are my friends now!
We will rescue Camie, no matter what!
So stop crying!
Luffy-chin...
Let's follow them. We're going
to break through in one go.
All right, then.
Let us meet up on Grove #13, should
we find ourselves separated.
Grove #13? Got it!
You don't "got it" at all!
What will you do, Mr. Giant?!
We were all on the verge of becoming slaves.
I'm going to flee somewhere
with these people!
I see! Be careful not to
draw attention to yourself!
Old man! Straw Hat's friends!
I will repay this favor if we
ever meet again! Thank you!
Thanks so much!
Thank you!
Sure, no problem!
You're taking credit?!
Mortars! Fire!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Repel!
Room.
Wh-What's this circle?!
Shambles.
I've been killed!
Wait... Huh?!
Watch out! All three of 'em have powers!
Leave enough people to rescue the
hostages, and gather all our men here!
Mortars, too!
Ready! Aim!
W-Wait! Please wait!
Don't either of you do anything!
You'll just get in the way!
I already told you! Tell me what to do and--
Leave it to me!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Gum-Gum Finger Net!
He can stretch?!
What kind of weird power is that?
What are you doing?!
I thought I was a goner!
Sorry!
Straw Hat! You really are
screwed up in the head!
Start with Straw Hat Luffy! Charge!
Damn, you! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Now! Stay sharp! Go! Go!
Gum-Gum Whip!
Don't falter! Fire!
Oh no!
That was close...!
Now! Get him!
Huh?
Toward himself?!
Does he want to die?!
Repel!
This can't be! Are these
guys really rookies?!
Has Admiral Kizaru arrived yet?!
No, sir! But I think he'll be here shortly!
Reinforcements from the navy
post have arrived, though!
H-Hold on! What's going on?! Help me!
Yeesh. There's a lot more than I expected...
You guys sure got weird powers!
I'd say yours is the weirdest.
Really?
What?! Swords are flying toward him?!
Amazing! Marines are flying through
the air, whirling, twirling...
There are guns and even cannons
flying! What's going on?!
I don't believe my eyes!
And I don't even have eyes!
I didn't know Kid-san and Law-san had powers!
It's getting interesting now!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Break Through the Siege! The
Navy vs. the Three Captains"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!