Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Sabaody Archipelago!
Realizing that their ship needs to be
coated in order to reach Fish-Man Island,
the Straw Hat crew and Hachi's group
stopped by the Sabaody Archipelago.
It's time for the unveiling!
Take a good look!
However, Camie, a mermaid accompanying them,
found herself kidnapped and auctioned off.
500 million!
I'll buy it for 500 million Berries!
Stop, Straw! You guys'll
get in huge trouble too!
You annoy me, too!
Quit your squirming!
It'll be all right. Just stay still.
Stop! Stop it!
Camie!
He took the collar off barehanded?!
Thanks to the help of Rayleigh, a coating
craftsman who suddenly appeared,
Luffy and company succeeded
in rescuing Camie.
However...
Alright, you criminals! Release
the Roswald family at once!
An admiral will be arriving shortly!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Repel!
Room.
Wh-What's this circle?!
Shambles.
Watch out! All three of 'em have powers!
"Break Through the Siege! The
Navy vs. the Three Captains"
Rescue team has arrived at the back
entrance! Now entering the building!
The rescue team has made it inside!
All soldiers will commence attack
as soon as the hostages are secured!
Yes, sir!
Hurry! On the double!
Rescue team has reached the stage!
There they are! Should we capture them?!
No, we can't! Our orders
are to secure the hostages!
The Celestial Dragons' lives
take precedence over all else!
We need to ascertain their well-being first!
I can't believe mortars don't
work on any of them...!
They really do live up
to their notorious names!
This is no time to be impressed!
Hold out until the admiral arrives!
Like we can really wait that long.
A head!
Hey! Don't drop me!
How are you talking?!
I dunno! My body feels
hot for some reason, too!
Body?! What are you talking about?!
This guy's body is burning up over there!
It's burning up! My body's burning up!
Huh?! You can feel it?!
Oww! Oww! Hot!
Someone! Pour water on it, hurry!
I thought I was a goner...!
Watch out, guys!
That guy! Don't enter the circles he makes!
Room.
Y-You mean this?
Yeah, just like this!
We've been cut!
What in the world's going on?!
Make yourselves comfortable.
This'll be over before you know it.
Third Gear!
Bone Balloon!
This is the arm of a giant!
Don't be scared! Ready your
weapons! Fire! Fire like crazy!
But, Brigadier General! Our weapons...
...are flying away!
Wh-What?!
What the...?!
What's going on?!
What is this?!
What in the...?
What is that guy?!
This is no time to be admiring people.
Wh-What the...?!
Hey! Those are my legs!
Then whose are those?!
You have too many chests!
Don't look at me!
Giant Pistol!
Eat this!
Whoa, now! This, already?!
Amazing! I don't believe my eyes!
You sure know how to go berserk, Captain...
They're quite reliable, indeed!
What an impatient bunch.
What's with that, Straw Hat-ya?
That's not a very good finish...
Really?
Their formations don't amount to crap now.
Brigadier General! It appears all the
pirates have exited the auction house!
They intend to escape! Don't let
these runts make mockeries of us!
We have plenty more reinforcements!
The three hostages have been
secured at the back entrance!
Aim the mortars at those without powers!
Firing squads to the rear! We're
now commencing our all-out attack!
Take those pirates down!
Here we go. They got no plan at
all. It's a free-for-all now.
Oh! I'm back to normal!
Alright, Straw Hat...
I'm glad I got a chance to meet you.
But next time we meet,
I won't show any mercy.
But I'm going to find the One Piece!
Hey, Kid! What're you
just standing there for?!
You know, Killer...
On our journey up to this point,
we've been laughed at and ridiculed
whenever we mentioned getting
our hands on the One Piece.
And each time that happened, I
slaughtered everyone who laughed.
But what lies ahead is a sea of death
for those who don't got
the guts to mention it.
Let's meet again in the New World!
Let's go, men!
Yeah!
Trafalgar Law!
How dare you toy with my comrades earlier!
Bepo.
Huh? You're going back inside, Captain?
Hey, Luffy!
Oh! There you are!
Alright! It's time for us to go, too!
Let's do it!
Alright! Bring it on!
Oh, Sanji!
Luffy! Look over there!
Hey! Young Master and friends!
Flying Fish!
Hey!
Eh? Did you just say "handsome"?
No. I didn't. Not at all.
Anyway, we're all set to escape! Right, men?!
Yes! Life is rosy!
I wasn't expecting help from them again,
but I guess we are in a hurry...
Alright! Let's go!
Guess I have no choice...!
Straw Hat's getting away!
Lullaby Flanc!
Escape while you can, you two!
Yeah!
Quit sleepin'!
Are you guys with those pirates?!
N-No, not us! We aren't pirates!
Nueve Fleurs!
Huh?
Twist!
Oh, that was scary...!
Head!
You have trauma from nearly being killed
by Navy Headquarters, and yet...!
You endured it anyway!
What a fantastic person!
Q-Quiet! This is no time to talk
about trauma or anything else!
We owe the young master our lives! We
hafta help him out of this trouble!
Multi-shot! Flame Star! Flame Star!
Colonnade Rose!
Old man! Franky! Go on ahead!
Right! I appreciate it!
Don't let 'em escape! After 'em!
How many of these guys are there?!
This is certainly exciting!
You're one lively old geezer!
Hey! Hurry, you three!
Yeah!
Don't let the Straw Hat crew escape!
They're the main criminals!
Fire! Fire!
What the...?!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Why?
He just freed Saint Roswald's slave!
How did he uncuff him?!
Will you come along with me,
pirate captain Jean Bart?
It's been a long time since
I've been called that name.
If it means I can be free
from the Celestial Dragons...
...I'll gladly serve under you!
Give half of your thanks to Straw Hat-ya.
Don't let 'em get away! After 'em!
After 'em!
Alright! It's up to you now!
Leave it to us!
Yahoo!
Don't let them escape! Fire! Fire!
Damn! Can't this slowpoke cow go any faster?!
Actually...
...this is his top speed...
They've caught up?
Can't we speed this thing up somehow?!
They fled that way!
Don't let them get away!
They're still chasing us, even
after we demolished the bridge!
Of course they are. There should
be soldiers back in town, too.
Let's get the hell off these islands.
Kid!
Boss!
There.
Is that...?!
What's...
he doing on these islands?!
What an agile bear! He's too much to handle!
How is it even talking?!
I'm sorry...
He's weak-hearted!
Hurry, Bepo!
Crap! They destroyed the bridge!
You're a new guy, which
means you rank under me.
As long as I'm not a slave,
anything's fine with me!
Did we manage to lose them?!
Alright! Let's go straight
to the amusement park now!
Are you crazy?!
Yahoo!
How pleasant!
You're quite skilled to be able to
remodel it in such a short time!
That's for sure! You're
amazing! It's so fast now!
I do what I can!
This is where Peterman's hideout is...
Peterman?
Captain! Look!
Eustass-ya and...
That's...!
What is a Warlord of the Sea doing here?
Trafalgar Law...
You know my name?
Captain!
We're right next to Navy
Headquarters and Marie Jois!
Just about anyone can show up here!
Marines are coming up the rear!
This guy acts at random!
Trafalgar! Stay out of my way!
Do you want to be destroyed? I told
you not to tell me what to do.
We're running into unexpected
big-shots today.
I'd rather not add an admiral to that list...
...so you will let us pass...
...Bartholomew Kuma!
You were on the Pirate King's ship?!
But the Pirate King was
caught. How did you survive?
We weren't caught.
Roger turned himself in.
Huh?!
Would you like to know the whole story?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Roger and Rayleigh
-- The King of the Pirates and His Right Hand Man"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!