Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After being ejected from the Sabaody
Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma,
Luffy was separated from his
friends and arrived alone
at the female-only empire of Amazon Lily.
Sentenced to death,
Luffy was forced to fight
Snake Princess Hancock's sisters
in a combat arena.
I can't wait to see Marigold-sama's
"Salamander" with my own eyes!
And Sandersonia-sama's
"Eight-Headed Serpent"!
There!
You're not cracked, are you?
Wait here, you guys!
Sorry you got turned
into stone because of me!
Alright, then...
So I just gotta kick your asses now, right?!
What a joke!
What did he just say?!
He intends to beat the younger sisters!
Hilarious! Making people laugh
after being sentenced to death!
Men really are hilarious!
Kill him, Sandersonia! Marigold!
Through combat, give him
the ultimate punishment
for the great crime of sneaking onto
our maiden island and offending me!
What the...?!
Poison?! That was close!
Gum-Gum
Stamp!
It bounced off!
That hurts!
How...?! I'm made of rubber!
Gum-Gum...
--...Gatling!
--Snake Dance.
What's going on?!
She's guessing my every move!
Snake Stick!
Ouch!
Hey! What're you doing?! Don't touch them!
What if she breaks?!
She saved my life, you know!
We are going to break her.
Stop it!
I said stop!
The warriors are fainting!
That was the Conqueror's Spirit just now...!
This can't be real!
Only one out of a million
people can master that Haki!
Only a chosen few can use it!
I've never seen any person who
can use it other than our big sister!
This boy has the "qualities of a conqueror"
to stand above others!
He has the Conqueror's Spirit, just as I do?!
How can this be?!
Is he no mere boy after all?!
Alright!
You showed me you're strong!
Now let's get on with the duel!
"All-Out Special Power Battle!!
Gum-Gum vs. Snake-Snake"
What are you hesitating for?!
Men are undeserving of fear!
Sonia-sama! Mari-sama!
Beat that man up!
Yes.
There's nothing to fear, Mari...
If he can't control his enormous Haki,
then it's nothing but zeal!
But first...
If we're gonna go all out, we
better move her outta the way.
I wouldn't want to break her.
Oh, you sound quite confident.
It seems you still don't
understand the position you're in.
Who cares about that lousy statue?!
Margaret!
Why do you insist on protecting the statue,
even at the expense of being hit yourself?!
She has nothing to do with it...
She has nothing to do with this fight!
Very well. Let him move the statue.
Big Sis!
Let the man fight to his heart's content.
And then beat him completely senseless
and teach him just how insignificant men are!
Right!
Wait here just a little longer.
I'll figure something out once I beat 'em up.
Okay! All set!
Oh, you're already ready?
Ready for us to beat you to a pulp?
I already told you.
You're the ones who're gonna get beat up.
You're still as insolent as ever!
Ouch! Damn!
That attack doesn't scare me
if you can't hit me with it!
Gum-Gum...
What is this smoke...?!
My poison dissolves whatever it touches.
But that's not all...
Marigold-sama's poison attack!
The man fell for it so easily!
Heh. This is nothing at all.
H-Huh?
What the...?!
I feel kinda woozy!
I won't take you lightly anymore.
You're my prey.
I'll weaken you with poison, corner you,
and then kill you for sure!
Just one whiff of my poison
will dull one's consciousness!
That hurts, dammit!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Gum-Gum Pistol!!
What's the matter?
You can't even scratch us!
You seem to be at a real loss...
No matter how tough you may be,
if you can't control your power,
you're no different from a puny rat!
Just give it up!
Yes! He fell into the pit of blades!
I can see right!
I'm healed! The poison's gone!
His hand! It's the man's hand!
Look at that!
He just won't give up!
Mari-sama! Sonia-sama!
The man is still alive!
But what do I do about that poison smoke?
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Go flying!
Alright! That's much better!
All the poison and smoke is gone now!
Now I can fight with an easy mind!
The man used his breath to
send the poison flying away!
Unbelievable!
Men are so mysterious!
Aren't they, though?!
You can fight with an easy mind, you say?
After being beaten so horribly,
you still spout such insolence?!
Alright...
Now it's my turn to go full-power too.
Second Gear!
What is that?!
Smoke's coming from his body!
Is that how men are?!
What kind of creatures are they?!
Smoke! He's giving off smoke!
Full power?
Meaning you weren't at
full power this entire time?
So what if there's smoke
coming from your body?!
Have you forgotten that we
can read your every move
and that your attacks have no effect on us?
I'm gonna try anyway.
Gum-Gum Jet...
It's no use!
...Pistol!
Big Sis Sonia!
It looks like you weren't bluffing
about going full-power...
In that case, I'll bite you to death
with all the power I have too!
Medusa Hair...
...Eight-Headed Serpent!
Go!
Sandersonia-sama!
The fence around the arena!
The giant serpents are actually her hair,
yet it's like they have fangs of iron!
Why can't I hit him?!
I'm reading his every move ahead of time,
but I can't keep up!
Big Sis Sonia!
Gum-Gum...
It's no use!
Your attacks bounce right off,
as I showed you before!
As long as I can surpass your speed,
your brute strength attacks
cannot defeat my defense!
...Jet...
...Bazooka!
Sonia! Mari!
What are you two playing around for?!
B-Big Sis...!
Don't tell me you've forgotten
that man's transgressions!
S-Sorry, Big Sis!
We'll finish him at once!
Medusa Hair...
...Eight-Headed Serpent!
She's on fire!
Medusa Hair...
...Salamander!
We won't give you anywhere to run!
He's surrounded!
There's no escape now,
no matter how nimble he is!
There's no better attack than this!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Gatling!
Oh no!
Big Sis Sonia! Get away, quickly!
What?! I'm being dragged!
Our tails! When did he...?!
It's hot! It's hot! Help!
Wait, Big Sis! Don't pull me!
Big Sis Sonia! Watch out!
That's the pit of blades!
Hold on to the stands!
Th-That was close...
S-Sandersonia-sama?!
How pathetic!
Sonia's back...!
If...!
If the citizens should see it...!
Ouch! Hot!
That man!
He's kicking her when she's down!
He's inhuman!
He's going to knock Sonia-sama
Ninto the pit and skewer her!
Damn you, man!
Don't move!
Even if you guys wanna kill me,
I don't wanna kill you!
You insolent little...!
Mari! Use this chance to kill him!
What are you doing, Mari?!
I can't, Big Sis Sonia...!
Because...
he's protecting us right now...!
Look! Sandersonia-sama's
clothing burned off
and her back is showing!
If that man gets off her,
her Gorgon Eyes will be exposed!
Oh no!
Everyone who sees them
will be turned to stone!
My back...!
You guys said so earlier!
He saw my back.
Then he'll have to die.
Huh?! H-How come?! I only saw her back!
We would rather die
than let anyone see what you saw on my back!
You'd rather die than let
people see this, right?!
So don't move!
The combat is over!
Everyone leave the arena at once
before you're exposed to the Gorgon Eyes!
Oh no! We gotta get outside!
We'll be petrified!
Hurry! Hurry!
The Gorgon's curse!
I was fighting you just moments ago.
Why are you protecting me?
Our fight and the thing you don't
want seen are two separate things.
You now owe your lives to
the man you tried to execute.
Maybe you can fool the country,
but you cannot fool yourself
forever, Snake Princess.
The thing etched onto the
backs of you three sisters is...
After Luffy saves the
sisters from a tight spot,
they reveal their secret to him.
Hancock suppresses the fear
rising from deep within her
as she reveals the wounds in her heart.
It turns out a wicked shadow
lurks in her past...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hancock's Confession
The Sister's Abhorrent Past"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!