Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
After realizing the purity of his heart
and hearing about his fight
against the Celestial Dragons,
Hancock finally came to trust Luffy.
"Saving Ace! The Next Stop:
the Great Prison!"
Are you really gonna give me a ride?!
Don't worry. I wouldn't lie.
That's great! It doesn't have to be
a great boat as long as it sails.
Departure will be tomorrow morning.
The Kuja Pirates will give you a
ride to the Sabaody Archipelago.
--What?! By our pirate ship?
--Sorry to be a pain!
Rest well tonight to prepare for tomorrow.
I can't wait to get off this island tomorrow!
I really wanna see everybody soon!
Really. What a strange man.
Sonia! Mari!
Invite Luffy to tonight's banquet!
--A man to our banquet?!
--Big Sis, that's too...
--Didn't you understand what I said?
--Y-Yes...
What banquet?
It's a banquet to celebrate the Kuja
Pirates' safe return with a big haul.
You got any food at this banquet?
I haven't been to one in
a while! Yes!! A banquet!
Are you gonna come, too?
No, I'm a little tired.
I'll go to bed early.
Okay. You'll give me a ride and food.
I can't hardly believe it!
Doesn't he mean he can hardly believe it?
Banquet! Banquet! Banquet!
I didn't think that Snake Princess
would trust him this much.
I like you!
It's dinner time!! A banquet!!
I'm gonna eat!!
This tastes great!
This one's good, too!
There's a lot of good food!
Aren't you gonna eat anything?
Then, I'll eat yours,
alright? Oh, you guys, too.
That man saved our lives.
I heard he'll leave tomorrow morning.
Men's bodies are strange as the rumors said.
I saw it at the arena. They can
stretch their legs really long!
I wanna get my hands on Luffy-sama
to see how much he can stretch.
--"Luffy-sama"?
--That's his name.
Oh, Luffy-sama!
Watch your mouth!
It's unthinkable to address
a man in such a way.
Don't forget the rule of Amazon Lily!
Then, why is Luffy-sama here?
Right?
Why is a man who once got the
death sentence here, Ran?
And of all places, our celebration!
I can't believe that Snake
Princess has forgiven him.
Maybe, it's...
...a trap laid by Snake Princess.
A trap?
He surprised them at the arena by putting
up a fight so she wants him to eat a lot
and catch him off guard and give him hell.
So it's our role to give him hell, right?
Are you ready?
Let's take care of the man!
Wait!
He's starting to act strange.
Oh, no! Did he notice?
Hey! Screw you people!!
That's enough!!
He sensed the trap!
Maybe he wants to fight us
with the pan and the ladle.
That sounds like something
that stupid man would do.
Don't get beaten!
Why aren't you singing?!
What are you doing?
Look, you people! This is
how you have a banquet!
Yo ho ho ho… Yo ho ho ho…
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
Sea wind blows to where, who knows?
The waves will be our guide!
O'er across the ocean's tide,
the sunset is goin' wild
See the sky! Birds singing
in circles passing by!
--What's that?
--Men are funny!
It's funnier than Sweetpea's drunk dance!
I hate to admit it, but I can't top this.
Sailing out on our journey
to the ends of the sea!
Hey! Yo ho ho ho… Yo ho ho ho…
Yo ho ho ho…
Why can't you get it? It's like this!
Like this! This!
This!
Is it like this?
That's so funny, Luffy-sama!
Men stick chopsticks in their nasal cavities
to their mouth
and hold baskets in their hand...
What a classless dance!
Gum-Gum Belly-talk!
Here! This is the specialty of Maiden Island!
What? Specialty?
Penne gorgonzola with Sea King meat.
I often eat Sea King meat
but this is different!
It really does stretch!
It's soft like gum!
Your time's up!
--What? One more time!
--No, then you won't stop!
Wow, this Sea King meat is
very good! It's hard to eat...
W-W-What are you doing - picking
and stretching my body?!
We can't help it! You'll
leave tomorrow, right?
There are a lot of people who
want to touch you just one time.
--It's taking too long! I wanna touch him now!
--Me, too!
"20 gol per touch"
--You're so popular!
--Luffy-chan!
You can't do business using
me without asking me!!
Come on, Luffy-chan! Tonight is
our only chance to touch a man!
Hey! S-Stop, you people!
I can't eat! Hey! Hey!
Where's Margaret?
--Where did Luffy-sama go?
--No! He ran away!
He can't have gotten too far!
Let's find him and touch him!
What's the matter with them?
Keep hiding!
This is only food that I could bring.
It's great that you can
return to your friends!
Yeah. Well, I'm sorry that
I got you into some trouble.
I worried when you turned into stone!
But you protected us, right?
I heard what happened.
Thank you, Luffy!
What's wrong with Big Sis?
She hasn't eaten anything and while she
said she's tired, she also can't sleep.
The forcing assemble thing
is maybe bothering her.
Tomorrow morning...
Big Sis!
--Granny Nyon!
--What's the matter, Margaret?
Luffy's been chased by girls of the village.
No wonder. They don't see men often.
Hey, Granny Bean!
This part of the village is
secluded. Stay here for a while.
And my name's not Bean!!
He has something to eat, so just
bring him tea or something.
Okay.
Granny, you like to read newspapers, huh?
Coo News isn't delivered to a Calm Belt
so it's hard to get it but since our
empress is a Warlord of the Sea,
I have to know what's going
on in the world at least.
Who's a Warlord of the Sea?
Snake Princess.
Wh...
What?!
She's a Warlord of the Sea?
Does that mean she's
really strong in a fight?
You are a pirate.
Didn't you notice it?
N-No, I didn't.
Don't you read newspapers?
No, I don't read them.
Oh, what a shock!
Snake Princess became
empress of this country
and a captain of the
Kuja Pirates 11 years ago.
She was young but
they put a price of 80 million on
her head after her first expedition.
Just one?
It had to do with the bad reputation
Kuja had even before her.
The World Government became
cautious about her from the start
and they suggested that she become
one of the Seven Warlords.
But now, that title is about to be revoked.
Because...
W-What?!
The Seven Warlords and Navy Headquarters
are gonna fight
the Whitebeard Pirates?!
What's that?! What'll happen?!
W-W-W-W-Wait a minute!
T-This is too much to hear at once!
What a foolish man!
You don't know anything.
I must say, that was just a prediction.
But the battle will probably happen.
The World Government has made a move.
Whitebeard is a man who would never
allow his mates to be killed.
Even though they know this, they
announced the public execution of...
...Portgaz D. Ace, a great
commander of Whitebeard's.
They announced the public execution of...
...Portgaz D. Ace, a great
commander of Whitebeard's.
What's wrong?
Of who?
Ace. "Fire Fist" Ace.
Ace... is gonna get executed?
I heard a pirate called Blackbeard...
...became a Warlord by
defeating "Fire Fist" Ace.
Blackbeard...
The World Government will take full
advantage of this big fish they've caught,
--a pirate named Ace...
--Granny...
Granny!!
That's my brother!
Ace is my older brother!
What?!
Is that true?! He's your brother?!
I didn't know that he was captured.
And he's gonna be executed?!
Then, there's no chance for him to escape!
If Whitebeard wins this battle,
there will be a chance for him.
What should I do? Where are
they gonna execute him?
It'll take place Marinford's town square,
where Navy Headquarters stands.
It says "in one week," which
means 6 days from today.
What?! That's too soon!
How long will it take to get to
Sabaody Archipelago from here?
It will take more than a week.
If it takes that long, then Ace will
be finished before I meet my crew!
Then how long will it take
to get to where Ace is?
Impel Down is where he locked, and
it'll take a week by a pirate ship
and 4 days by a navy ship.
Why?! Navy ships are that fast?
There's a current used exclusively
by the World Government.
Enies Lobby.
Impel Down.
Navy Headquarters.
There's a giant whirlpool which
connects those three facilities.
When you open the Gate of Justice
at any of the three facilities,
the current runs inside
allowing you to enter.
That means if the gates aren't open,
you'd just keep drifting on the current.
Pirate ships would rather avoid the current
by going a long way round.
What should I do?
What do you want to do?
Don't tell me that's your
brother's Vivre Card!
Oh, is it the sheet that moves
around that you care about so much?
That's a different one.
This is the one that Ace gave to me.
That's also known as a paper of life.
It tells you a direction in which the
person is and about their vital energy.
So, if it's that small, it means...
When I got it, it was ten times bigger.
Ace has his own adventure...
I wanted you to have it. Here.
Always hang on to that.
Huh? It's just a scrap of paper.
That scrap of paper will bring you
and me together again sometime.
You don't want it?
No, I'll keep it.
It's natural for a big brother to worry...
...about his bungling kid brother.
Ace won't like me rescuing him
since he's stronger.
But...
I'm sorry, everybody.
I'm gonna take a little side trip.
I wanna go and rescue Ace!
Do you know for sure
how reckless it would be and how
big this battle is going to be?
You'll be like an ant blown into a storm.
You can just be flicked away
without even having done anything.
I don't care what's gonna
happen! I just wanna go!
I can't just sit by calmly on the
sidelines and let this happen!
I see.
So you're going to rescue the most
infamous prisoner in the world now.
If there is a chance in a million,
you better go to the Great
Prison where he's being held.
When they move him to the
execution ground in Marinford,
the navy admirals and the Seven
Warlords will be keeping a close eye.
However, because your brother is now
the most important prisoner they have,
there is no doubt that they're guarding the
prison with the military's full strength.
So it's impossible to enter.
I care more about getting there in
time than what happens after.
I got to get there while Ace is there.
Just give me a big oar,
and I'll paddle myself...
Wait a second! You can't
get there on will alone.
This is a slim chance, too, but...
Snake Princess refuses to follow the order to
force the Seven Warlords of the Sea to assemble.
If only she obeys the order,
we can take advantage of it
and let you on their ship.
Their ship? There's a navy ship here?!
Then I'm gonna go and ask her!
Granny Nyon!
What's wrong, Enishida? Why
are you in such a hurry?
Thank god. I was going to come get you.
What happened?
Well...
...Snake Princess...
...has come down with an unknown illness.
--She's sick?!
--Oh my god!
Big Sis!
Am I...
...going to die?
Hancock has fallen ill.
Granny Nyon tells the whole gang
about this terrifying illness,
which has killed previous
empresses of Amazon Lily.
What could this illness be?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Love is a Hurricane!
Love-Love Hancock!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!