Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy was ejected from the Sabaody
Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma, a Warlord of the Sea.
Separated from his friends,
he arrived alone at the female-only
empire of Amazon Lily!
He gained the favor of
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock
and was granted a ride to
the Sabaody Archipelago
in a Kuja pirate ship due
to leave the next day.
Granny Nyon!
What's wrong, Enishida? Why
are you in such a hurry?
Snake Princess...
...has come down with an unknown illness.
Curse the Pirate Empress!
Are you really not going to obey these
strict orders from the World Government?
If they revoke your title
of Warlord of the Sea,
you know what will happen to your country.
"Love is a Hurricane! Love-Love Hancock!"
Big Sis! Hang in there!
Big Sis!
I heard Snake Princess is sick.
Oh, Granny Nyon!
You, wait outside for a while.
What?! But I have to hurry!
I know that!
I can't breathe.
The way she's clutching her chest,
I think there's something
wrong with her heart.
But I can't figure out what it is.
I've never seen symptoms like these, so
I don't know what to prescribe.
Snake Princess seems to be in a lot of pain.
She didn't eat a thing.
I can't wait to get off this island tomorrow!
I really wanna see everybody soon!
Tomorrow morning...
This can't be happening!
Mon...
Lu...
--Snake Princess!
--Granny Nyon, stop fooling around with her!
She's in agony!
I'm not fooling around!
Oh my god!
I can't believe this!
What an untimely virus!
--A virus?
--Do you know what it is?
Granny Nyon... I can't breathe!
Am I... going to die?
Yes, you are.
--What're you saying?!
--Stop making stupid jokes, Granny Nyon!
The former empress died
from the same illness.
I heard the empress before
that died from this, too.
I caught it, too, but left this country
and survived.
Snake Princess, Monkey
D. Luffy is here with me.
Hey, Granny Nyon!
He wants to ask you a favor.
Can you at least listen to him?
--Big Sis is suffering!
--What are you thinking?!
She's standing!
Alright. I'd like to hear it.
How lucky he is, Monkey D. Luffy!
Will he move this mountain
that no one could move?!
Do you want something? Luffy?
I gotta ask you something!
Are you alright?
No sickness can overtake me.
There's a Whitebeard pirate named Ace who's
waiting to be executed. He's my brother!
I want to rescue Ace!
But I heard a pirate ship
can't make it in time!
Your brother is... that Whitebeard pirate?
Can you board the navy ship
and take me to Ace's prison?!
How self-centered can
you be? Straw Hat Luffy!
You know Big Sis's pain but you still
ask her to go to that abhorrent place?!
--How cruel you are!
--We showed you mercy and then you become arrogant!
This is why we hate men! Big Sis's
patience is wearing very thin!
Turn him to stone and
throw him over the edge!
So you want me to follow their order for
the Seven Warlords of the Sea to convene.
--Big Sis!
--Kill him!
If you want me to...
I'll go anywhere!
Good! Thank you! This way I can
make it before the execution!
S-Snake Princess decided to
go to the World Government HQ!
What happened to her, Granny Nyon?!
The Snake Princess is
suffering from lovesickness!
The former empresses died
from being burnt by love!
There is a saying around the East Blue:
"Love is always..."
"...a hurricane!"
What's happening to me?!
I don't think I can turn
down any request from Luffy.
I said I'd go without even thinking.
And I don't have any regrets.
That's what we call love!
Love?
The pain of thinking about
someone that you can't see
drags you down and leads
eventually to your death.
The former empresses fell
in love with some men but
because they were empresses,
they had to bottle up their feelings
and stay on this island.
In time, the pain was too much for them
and and in the end,
that's what took their lives.
But the decision you made to go
with him will save your life.
If you go to the World Government HQ and
keep your title of Warlord of the Sea,
it will save this country and help
Monkey D. Luffy at the same time.
What a weird fate he has brought with him.
Normally, there is only one way for
a pirate to get to the Great Prison
and that is to just get caught.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring, clank!
It's me.
Boa... Hancock?!
I decided to follow the orders to convene.
However, there is one condition.
If you can't accept that condition...
All right, let me hear it - this
condition that you're talking about.
Luffy!
I thought that he was gonna leave tomorrow.
I heard that they changed
where they are heading.
He'll get on a navy ship with Snake Princess.
--Luffy!
--You guys! Thank you for everything!
I'll be back with my friends!
Your friends?
Yes! I'll have Sanji cook for you.
He's a great cook!
You'll be surprised!
And there's a skeleton who's a musician!
A skeleton?
His name is Brook and when he sees a
girl, he always tries to see her panties!
Panties?
What's so great about them?
And there is a reindeer called Chopper and...
Oh, but is it possible?
Nami and Robin are
okay but this country prohibits men...
They'll make an exception for your friends.
Snake Princess seems to favor you.
We'll look forward to seeing them!
She's here!
Who put these things here? They're in my way!
A puppy and...
...a baby seal!
It's Snake Princess!
There's no end to her sexual allure!
I don't know why but her beauty
is even more striking than usual!
I am deeply sorry! I am
responsible for the animals!
Please be careful.
Hey, sorry to put you on such short notice!
Snake lady, I wanna leave
as soon as possible!
Don't look at his eyes!
No, Luffy! It's rude to call her that!
Call her Snake Princess!
You can call me Hancock.
Snake Princess!
Alright, I got you, Hammock!
It's Hancock.
S-Snake Princess is smiling!
How many karats is that sparkle?!
It's too dazzling...
A woman in love! I was once like that...
What's wrong, Granny Nyon?!
That face is so creepy.
Shut up!
Have a good trip, Snake Princess!
--We'll see you, Luffy!
--Luffy-chan!
See you!
Cut that out!
Come see us, really!
We're all looking forward
to seeing you again!
It's done!
I had no obligation to save you!
Oh, I'm so relieved!
I was worried that you were going to die.
Gum-Gum Belly-talk!
Luffy! I hope you can see your friends!
Yeah!
Granny Nyon.
Snake Princess has no problem but can
Luffy get on a navy ship for sure?
Managing to get a 3 hundred million
berries price on his head,
and then causing a serious incident
on the Sabaody Archipelago,
Monkey D. Luffy is a sworn enemy of the navy.
Is he planning to hide behind cargo?
Don't worry.
I gave Snake Princess a good strategy.
I've been waiting for you, Boa Hancock.
I told you about my condition
through the Transponder Snail.
I managed to get my superior's approval to
stop by at Impel Down, the Great Prison.
Is it only you and that snake
who'll get on this ship?
Even though you're a Warlord, pirates
are not allowed in that area.
We've made an exception for you
but we don't have time,
so we can't stay there that long.
I know.
Big Sis, please return safe.
Please come home alive, Big Sis!
We'll wish your good luck
in battle, Snake Princess!
Take care, Luf...
I'm going now. I'll leave the country
in your hands while I'm gone.
Yes!
It was worth the wait.
It seems like I can fulfill my duty now.
Anyway, you were so adamant about not
wanting to assemble, what made you change your...?
People may fear you as a pirate empress
but after all, you're just human.
When you are hungry, your stomach growls.
Silence! As an empress, I have
better manners than that...
--Then, what was that...
--That was me!
Luffy!
Sorry. I couldn't eat enough at the banquet
since I was being chased by all those girls.
If we get caught now, it's all over.
I will ask for food later.
Be patient for a while!
Alright!
And it's getting hard to walk like
this. Can you climb up higher?
Like this?
Do you have a fever? You're flushed.
It's nothing.
Then, first of all, can you revert
my crew that you turned to stone?
We can't go back to Navy Headquarters
in this ungainly state.
Are they dead?
--What was that? It sounded like a man's...
--I-It was me!
The night wind is not good for your
body. I may have caught a cold.
Sorry, your hair tickled my nose!
It seems like he didn't notice.
I'm not so sure but
you're not up to something, are you?
What do you mean by that?
You seem different than when
I saw you a few hours ago.
Did he notice?
I swear that both my body and soul are pure.
But if you have a doubt, why don't you
search my body with your own hands?
I'll allow it.
I'll let you.
What're you saying? That's too risky!
No. If you say so, I must believe you.
Take care of my crew.
Not only can we not make it to Impel Down,
but we can't even run the ship like this.
Wake up!
...cock-sama!
What happened?
Get underway, you idiots!
Y-Yes, sir! Right away!
Before we return to Marinford,
we'll stop at Impel Down!
"Navy Headquarters"
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
We heard from Vice Admiral Momonga!
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock finally gave in
and they are heading here now.
Finally!
I hope she can make it.
That woman is strong.
Six of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea will be here.
Hawk-Eye Mihawk.
Bartholomew Kuma.
Don Quixote Doflamingo.
Gecko Moria.
Marshall D. Teech.
And Boa Hancock.
What about the last one
who was put in the prison?
Did he cool off?
No, sir. He seems like he is
still rigidly opposing battle.
He said he is ready for his title
of Warlord of the Sea to be revoked!
I assumed that he would be the most
cooperative and fight with us.
But he caused a commotion at the last minute!
Damn, Jimbei!
I have an announcement. Fleet Admiral!
The 500 pirates
Admiral Kizaru captured in revenge
for the Sabaody Archipelago incident...
they said they can't hold them at Impel Down.
Put them on labor!
Don't bring me any problems other
than ones related to Whitebeard!
And Saint Roswald, the World Noble, is...
Let the Admirals handle it!
Where's Garp?
Vice Admiral Garp headed
to Impel Down while ago.
What is that man doing?
Coming and going as he wishes
at a time like this!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
It's an emergency! Whitebeard is moving!
Here they come! Is that from
one of the guard ships?
Put it through! I wanna hear directly.
No, but...
All 23 Navy ships which were guarding
against Whitebeard's main ship Moby Dick,
we lost contact with them
all a few minutes ago.
What?! What did you say?
I heard there was some worrying activity
by other pirate ships in New World, too.
If nothing is done,
we won't have any intel on how many
ships they have or when they're coming!
I already made arrangements for guard
ships to move in as replacements.
They've caught us off guard!
I didn't realize that they
were already on the move.
We don't know where they will strike.
Spread the word:
As long as Ace is there, a battle
may break out on Impel Down!
Yes, sir!
It's this way, Vice Admiral Garp.
Please be careful!
All right.
Oh no... this is a horrible sight.
Are you still breathing?
Ace?
Kuma's power has sent the friends far away.
Nami ends up on an island
populated by mysterious old men.
What is it that this
island's inhabitants study?
Meanwhile, Franky ends up on a different
island, where his body undergoes a change...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Friends' Whereabouts! The Science
of Weather and the Mechanical Island!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!