Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
What's the terrifying
difference between you and me?
Nose.
Jaw?
Webs!
Species!!
Such a fool! He hurt
himself by biting on a rock!
Now his teeth're brok...
He crushed the stone
pillar with his teeth!!
Ahh! That's scary!
"Explosion! Fishman Arlong's
Fierce Assault From the Sea!"
Did you see...
...the inherent power of a fishman?
Heaven created you humans as
creatures that bow before fishmen.
You humans are inferior creatures.
We were on a different level
from the moment we were born.
I'll show you... the real
difference between you and me...
Yeah, why don't you?
No way I'll lose
against someone like you.
I am the man who'll be
King of the Pirates!
King of the Pirates?
Don't make me laugh.
Can you inferior humans do something
like crush a pillar with your teeth?
It's true that humans can't crush
that thick pillar using their teeth.
If that jaw gets you,
it won't just give you bite marks...
It'll bite clear through your bones!
So what?!
Stop...
...bragging over stuff like that!!
It's not like biting is the
only way to break stone.
All right, Big Bro Luffy!
You sure told him!
That's right!
The outcome is the same!
Th-That's besides the point!
A stupid and weak species...
That's what humans are.
What can you do when you can't
even pull yourself out of the water?!
Nothing! That's why I need help!
Hm? He can also use swords?
--Take that... and that... and that!
--What're you doing?
It looks like you're just
swinging swords around.
If you're just playing around,
I'm not going to join your little game.
Enough of this nonsense...
Clench your teeth!!
Wha?! He shattered
Arlong's teeth!!
I don't know how to use
swords, you bastard!!
Huh? What's he saying that now for?
I don't know how to sail the oceans.
I can't cook...
I can't lie, either...
Hey...
I'm confident that
I can't live without help!
Fully admitting how pathetic you are...
You sure are honest.
I bet your crew is bothered by having
such an incompetent captain like you.
I wonder why your crew tried
so desperately to save you...
Someone like you without any pride
has the caliber to be a captain?
What on earth can you do?
I can defeat you!
Of course, you damn idiot!
If he dies, I'm gonna kill him!
I've got your back!
All right, Gum-Gum!!
Get him, Big Bro Luffy!
Go for it by a hair!
Go ahead and babble,
you inferior species!
Ugh! He's got new teeth!
I'm a shark. New teeth
grow one after another.
And they're stronger
than the previous ones.
As many times as needed...
Whoa!
As many times...
This is a distinctive
quality that heaven gave us.
Amazing!!
Are you starting to realize what a
superior species the fishmen are?
Tooth Attack!
Huh?
Stop!
Big Bro Luffy!!
A-Arlong-san...
That hurt...
Wha! B-Brother!
Phew...
You damn rubber man!
How dare you use
my brother as a shield!
What're you saying?
You're the one who attacked me.
Phew... Was I scared...
Don't move...
...you damn rubber man!
Oh, yeah! I've got an interesting idea.
An interesting idea?
What on earth will he...?
Did he come up with a
secret scheme or something?
Tooth Attack!
There we go!
You...
There's no point in crushing
my teeth repeatedly...
You still don't get it?!
B-Big Bro Luffy...
You surely don't mean
your interesting idea is...
Look! I've got fangs, too!
S... So there wasn't any secret scheme?
I thought as much...
How long are you going to...
...keep fooling around?!
I got bitten by a shark!!
That's because
you're playing around!!
It's not like I'm playing around.
Tooth Attack!
He got bit!!
How do you like your own teeth?!
Even if it's my teeth that you used,
it's your weak jaw after all.
Listen up.
Shark teeth become useful
when they come with a strong jaw
that can bite off the meat!
Ahh!! Big Bro's arm's
gonna get bitten off!!
Luffy!!
Is his arm okay?
If he backed off even a step,
it would've been bitten off!
In his case, it's not that he thought
about how animal's fangs work, though.
Is Big Bro's arm okay?
Oh...?
Where'd he go?
--Luffy! The sea!
--The sea?
There's a shark!
That's Arlong!
Huh? Did he dive in?
This isn't good!
His ability doubles in the water.
No one can stop me once my
speed accelerates in the water.
This is precisely an ability
that is given only to fishmen.
Did he run away?
Shark... Darts!!
What was that?!
A torpedo?!
Something flew out from the sea!
Ow... Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Wow, I'm impressed you dodged it.
But the more you dodge it,
the longer your hell continues.
Shark... Darts!!
Wha...! What kind of bones
does that damn shark have?!
His nose crushed the ground...!
Shark... Darts!!
Hey, Luffy, hide!
Arlong went into the sea again!
Big Bro! Please hurry up and hide!
He'll target you again!
Get out of there!!
N... No...
Don't be stupid! Are you knowingly
going to become a target?! Hide!
I don't want to!
I'll catch him and break his nose!
Come on! Shark!
You've got some nerve.
Or have you realized that
it's useless to run away?
Didn't you hear us saying
you should hide, Luffy?!
You barely dodged his attacks
and they all grazed you!
If you take a direct hit,
you'll die instantly!!
Gum-Gum... Shield!!
What's that position?
Surely he isn't going to
stop the attack like that?
This is double the acceleration
distance from earlier.
I'll pierce your heart!
Shark Darts!!
He got hit!!
What?! Did he get hit?!
No! He flung himself off!
You lose.
That attack won't work any more.
Shark Darts!!
You bastard!
That was by instinct, wasn't it?!
This is the final blow!
You won't hit me!
Gum-Gum... Finger Net!!
Fishing! Fishing!
And...!
Spear!!
Whoa!!
Hm...? Did he die?
The look in Arlong's eyes changed!
They look the same as the eyes
that Sea Kings show when they snap.
He must've snapped
with Luffy's last attack!
I've never seen
Arlong's eyes like that...
You inferior human!
What did you do...
...to me, a fishman?!
Boy, was I stunned!
It doesn't hurt, but I can
see he's really mad.
What the heck is that?
Shark Saw!!
It's a giant saw!!
--Big Bro Luffy!!
--Hang in there, Luffy!
--Run!! Watch out!!
--The attack won't stop...
He's getting cornered...!
He escaped into the building!
The left window on the top floor...
That room is...
That was close...
You can no longer escape.
This is the top floor of Arlong Park.
Looks like your final
moment is finally here.
What's this room?
Full of papers...
These're not just ordinary papers.
This is a room where I make that
woman continue to draw sea charts.
The survey room!!
Nami's room...
These're all sea charts that Nami drew.
Aren't they great?
They're my treasure, one that I
made her draw for eight years.
To us, getting data about
the oceans is very simple,
but it's a different story when we
have to create sea charts based on it.
We need a talented surveyor.
That's why I had my eye on that woman.
She's good. She draws
quite accurate sea charts.
She's too good for
you inferior humans.
In the past as well as in the future,
her talent should be
used for us fishmen!
Hm?
Nami is our friend.
Friend?
So don't interfere any more...
...you damn rubber man!
What's that look in your eyes?!
She is...
Nami is...
Hm?
...our navigator!!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Amazing! What a fierce battle this is!
I finally figured out how to save her!
Show us your determination,
you damn rubber man!
I'll completely destroy the room
that she wants to be free of!
Go! Get Arlong!
Luffy... Thank you...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"End of the Fishmen Empire!
Nami's My Friend!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!