Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Impel Down - the great prison that holds
villainous prisoners from all over the world.
The world's greatest prison - so heavily
guarded - has just been breached!
He has come to rescue his brother "Fire
Fist" Ace who will soon be executed.
He is Straw Hat Luffy.
However...
twenty years ago...
there was a man who had broken
out of the iron-tight Impel Down!
This can't be real! He cut off his own legs!
This legendary person is...
"Golden Lion"
...the captain of the Flying Pirates,
Shiki the Golden Lion!
This is a story of what
happened several days ago...
...before Shiki the Golden Lion
faced Luffy and his friends!
"A Special Presentation Related to the Movie!
A Gold Lion's Ambition on the Move!"
Captain! Colt-san!
Ah? What?
We have word from Big Boss Shiki!
Well, finally! We've waited so long!
Bring a Transponder Snail here!
Yes! Right away!
Big Bro, we did it! If we
can join Shiki's party,
it's gonna be our chance
to become successful!
B-Big Bro? Why are you crying?
Amore! My beloved brother Colt!
I am very sad!
If the plan of senor
Shiki is put into action,
the world will be filled with sorrow.
When I think about hearing
thousands of despairing voices,
it makes me very very sad...
Here is a Transponder Snail!
Good! Put him through!
Are you the captain of
Amigo Pirates - Mr. Largo?
No, I'm a vice captain Colt.
Tell me what you want.
All right.
I called to let you know that we have decided
to welcome Mr. Largo to Big
Boss Shiki's assembly...
...as our 51st pirate captain.
--No surprise there!
--However...
...there is a condition to
your attending the assembly
and we need to ask you to fulfill that first.
Conditions?
Nothing so far...
No good at all...
I'm hungry...
You look pretty full to me.
We've been having banquets
every night these days.
So our stomachs have expanded and
we have to eat more to be satisfied.
You're right! It feels like my
bones are bigger these days...
Yeah, in your dreams.
How's it going? Catch something?
Not good! Not even a nibble!
We're totally out of food!
If you can't catch anything,
it'll be no food for you guys!
What?!
Don't "what?!" me!
I told you it was a bad idea
to have a banquet before
we got to the next island!
But you guys were...
Banquet! Banquet!
Is that how we were?
Don't even remember?!
A bite! I've got something!
Here it comes!
Way to go, Brook!
It's a big one!
Great! We're gonna have
another banquet tonight!
Catch that fish even if it kills you!
--Banquet!
--Hang on! It's coming!
Looks like they're having fun.
It's coming! It's coming!
You gotta be kidding me!
What the hell is that?!
I-It's a...
...Beetle!
Our fish...
...He ate it!
Awesome!
It's...
...a pirate ship!
What shameless bastards!
Boss! Get them!
I-It's coming back!
That's a big beetle!
I wanna ride on it!
What?! Are you nuts, Luffy?!
Hey, Usopp! Let's catch it!
Alright!
Where the hell did you get that net?!
I'm not gonna let it destroy our ship!
Coup de Vent!
Franky's attack didn't work?!
Can't be true!
Leave it to me!
Alright, come on, you giant beetle!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
They blew Boss away!
That beetle breathes fire!
He's gonna roast our ship!
Luffy! You alright?!
That beetle isn't just
huge - he breathes fire...
How cool is that?
Huh?
He looks just fine.
Okay! I'm gonna make him one of us!
What?! No! Wait a minute, Luffy!
Alright, you giant beetle! Join my...
I got you!
This can't be true!
What is he doing there?
They're coming this way...
Yeah, they seem to be getting bigger...
He's aiming at us!
Help... Help...
Help me!
--Oh no, Usopp!
--Damn it! You idiot!
He's flying away!
What were they thinking?!
Hey, look! An island!
Is that where the beetle came from?
Boss!
Watch out, Boss!
H-Hey! We're gonna hit the wall!
You can't get away now, you giant beetle!
Just give up and become one of my crew!
I don't take "no" for an answer!
My boss...
...will never become...
...a pirate!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow! What is this place?
I didn't know there was an island like this.
And for that matter...
...What the hell is going on?
Yoko! What happened?!
Be careful! He's a pirate!
A pirate?! No!
Show us mercy!
Stop doing that!
You people are Straw Hats, aren't you?
Yes, we are.
Oh yeah! He's a Straw Hat!
Ah! He's "Pirate Hunter" Zoro!
And he's "Black Foot" Sanji!
And then he's...
Who are you?
Let me go! He tried to steal Boss from me!
I'm gonna bite you to death!
Yoko! Stop!
Shut up and just let me go!
Who are these people?
Ouch! You are the owner of this beetle?
The owner?! No way! Boss is my friend!
Friend?
Oh, you're already on someone else's team?
Is there any way that you'd let me have him?
Of course not! Over my dead body!
Alright! I give him up!
Huh?!
Here we go!
Hey! What're you doing?!
Boss!
I'm sorry if I hurt you.
You think that you defeated him?!
No, I didn't mean it like that.
Boss!
--Hey!
--Stay away!
These wounds mean nothing to him!
They'll heal up overnight while
he's sleeping underground.
Wow! That's amazing!
Not only that! Tomorrow he will molt!
He'll become bigger and stronger!
Huh? Do they continue doing that
even as full grown beetles?
Boss is different. He sheds
his skin once a month.
That's why he's so big.
You're gonna be stronger than you are now?
Yes, he is! What do you say to that?!
That's cool!
Alright! Then, let's have
this fight again tomorrow!
Let's make it clear which
one of us is stronger!
That's so silly... Oh?
Alright! So I have your word, then!
He is an interesting young man as they say!
Boss?
This way!
What a big cave! What is it for?!
This is an escape route.
Escape route?
This cave is like a maze.
We can escape through this
cave when pirates come.
We are world champions at
running away and groveling!
Y-You're proud of it?
That's how we survive in the Grand Line.
We don't have a military
and it's a remote island
so the Navy always leaves
us on a back burner.
Speaking about the Navy, that
girl was wearing a Navy coat.
Is there any reason for that?
She wears it in memory of her father.
He was a good man.
He couldn't stand by and see us
repeatedly attacked by pirates
so he stayed on this island separated from
other marines in order to protect us.
You said "in memory of" so I assume...
It was exactly five years ago...
he was fighting against some
pirates alone and died.
Three years later,
Boss came to us out of nowhere.
He bonded with Yoko right away and became
the guardian angel of this island.
Maybe, Boss reminds her of her
late father who was strong.
Is it okay for us to be here?
We're pirates.
You people are different! Now, we are here!
Wow! A windmill! It's gigantic!
It's so high!
Oh! I thought that it was just a
crag but it's beautiful in the back!
But then...
How can I say this? The buildings
here are all different in style...
It's a strange town!
Can't you see?
It was a deserted island when we first
got here and that was just the beginning.
Since then, for some reason, people
are coming here from the same ocean.
That's what made this town.
Welcome, Straw Hats!
This is Kansorn Island where people
from the East Blue live together!
It also known as Little East Blue!
Yeah! I didn't expect to see the rookie
of great promise in the East Blue!
Zoro-san! You're from
Frost Moon Village, right?
We have a training hall for
people who came from there!
Come and see it!
A training hall?!
Sanji-san, you grew up on The Baratie, right?
Try the food at the local Baratie!
It's pretty good!
You have The Baratie here?!
Anyone from Syrup Village?!
I think Luigia is from there.
Luigia?!
Yeah. She's living in the most
luxurious mansion in this town!
Mansion? The only mansion in
Syrup Village is Kaya's mansion.
Humph! Everybody's so caught up in them!
Pirates are all the same!
I wonder how they're doing...
Don't worry, Chopper! They'll call us soon!
You think?
We better get an insect cage fixed for them.
You're right. If the beetle
joins us, we will need it.
See? It's them!
Hey, it's me! Is Nami there?
Usopp? It's me! What's
wrong? Did you catch it?
No no no, it's...
Shut up! Calm down!
I got it!
Um... I'm wondering - can you come over here?
Huh?
There's a town on the
other side of the island!
They say that they really wanna see you!
Call her "Nami-sama"!
What's going on?
Anyway, just come over here! I beg you!
Huh? Wait, Usopp!
He hung up!
Why do they want just Nami?
I don't know.
Okay! Let's just go!
I'll leave the ship to you!
Yeah! Count on us!
There she goes...
Is this it?!
It's a rockbound and there
are reefs all around it
so regular ships can't approach the island.
Well, reefs are no problem with this ship.
Alright! Let's go hunting!
We're gonna get the big beetle that
took off from Shiki's hide-out!
Let's go, guys!
Yeah!
The Straw Hats arrive at the island
where immigrants from East Blue live.
The scenery looks so much like
their homeland that they
can't help but reminisce.
But the Amigo Pirates are also heading
toward the island in pursuit
of the giant beetle!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Special Presentation Related to the Movie!
Little East Blue in Danger!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!