Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
In order to become brothers
of the legendary pirate Shiki,
the Amigo Pirates came to the
island to catch the big beetle!
If you don't wanna get killed,
let us have the beetle!
The giant beetle doesn't want to join
a pirate crew! Just give up on him!
You got me wrong, stupid!
I'm here to catch him!
Mucho Needle Net!
Ow, ow, ow... Ouch!
Luffy!
Even if you are a rubberman, I will
not let you get away with it, senor!
"A Special Presentation Related to the Movie!
The Fierce Onslaught of the Amigo Pirates!"
I can't believe this!
There's no way to defeat her!
You won sixty-nine out of sixty-nine...
Robin-san, you're so good at it.
Hmm... I don't think that it's
possible to make such a clean sweep!
Oh? Are you suspecting that I
cheated? Do you have any proof?
Well...
What was that?!
It must be from behind the mountain.
Do you think Nami-san and others are okay?
Maybe they're having a hard
time catching the beetle.
Let's go help them!
"Big Bro"?
Are they related?
Ow!
Augh! What is this?! It's all tangled up!
Damn you!
There's no use in doing that.
The more you struggle,
the tighter the net gets.
Choking to death like that at your age...
...makes me think how
cruel this world can be...
You're the vice captain of
the Amigo Pirates, right?
How would you explain
this shameful situation?
Oh, I'm sorry! I heard the big beetle
is the guardian of this island
so we tried to give them a scare
and make them bring out the beetle
but then that guy stepped in!
A big beetle? Oh, I thought
we're here for a stag beetle.
You never pay attention! How many
times do I have to tell you?!
It's a beetle! A big beetle!
Yeah?
Then maybe the beetle that
I saw on the way here
was the one you're talking about...
Whaaat?!
Oh, shoot!
You have to keep moving!
Boss! Can you hear me? Boss!
Where did you see it, Big Bro?!
Hmmm... I think it was around there.
Alright then, let's just...
We can catch that crappy beetle any time.
So...
Let's give them an ultimatum: either let
have the beetle or face extermination.
That was a good idea which is rare for you.
Let's just go with it!
I didn't say "extermination"...
Ah, in addition to that,
we should get rid of those two who're
having been glaring at us so rudely.
You two! How would you like to
die by my Net-Net Fruit power
which has a capture rate of 120%?
Oh no! Really?
Alright, bring it on, swordsman!
Hundred-and-Eight Pound Phoenix!
You bastard!
A flying sword attack! Now I'm wide-awake!
Mucho Sticky Net!
I can't cut it!
Not done yet!
Sticky Net Network!
W-What the...?!
What's this?! It's so sticky!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Oh, shit!
What're you doing, stupid?!
Next up, what do you do for living?
I'm a good cook, you crappy net geek!
Well then, how about something
boiling hot? Colt.
Okay!
Aak! Ow, ow, ow...!
What a fool! You think drinking
hot water will help you?!
Whew, that was hot.
Okay, let's do it!
Million Boiling Net!
You bastard! Stop messing around
with those stupid attacks!
Let my friends go!
That kind of friendship gets me choked up.
You know that you can't beat me...
Mucho Iron Net!
What's this?!
This is crap!
Damn it!
He got all three! These
guys are the real deal!
I told you!
What the swordsman got was the
basic sticky net and there is...
...iron, hot water,
and then here is fire!
Aak! Ow, ow, ow, ouch!
I can turn everything that I ingest to nets
and capture something with a 120%
success rate that is my Net-Net power!
But you still challenged me...
It's so sad to see someone
who doesn't know his limits!
Now, it's your turn!
I wanna see you do your very worst.
You can count on it!
Alright, you guys! I heard that...
...you are all from the East Blue.
I'm gonna tell you weak
sea idiots once again!
Let us have the beetle!
I'm gonna picking you off
one by one from the end!
If you don't wanna die,
just tell me where it is!
Stop it!
Yoko! Don't be fool!
I'll fight you!
A Navy coat?! Is she a brand new recruit?!
Oh, senorita!
You stand against us with a
bamboo sword? Are you nuts?
Shut up! This is all I need...
...to beat you guys!
Oh no!
--Shoot her!
--Yes!
Yoko!
Boss!
So that must be the Shiki's big beetle!
Yeah, it is very big!
Oh no, it was just about to get exciting...
--Here he comes!
--Go, Boss!
Beat them up, Boss!
Yes! Get them!
Giant Beetle!
Shoot it! Shoot it!
Nice!
Boss!
Big Bro, the nets! Please!
No fun... This is no fun at all...
I was about to see a mucho mucho beautiful
inferno colored by despair and screams...
Big Bro, hurry!
Oh, he's so annoying. Doesn't
he know that he's just a pest?
Mucho Burning Net!
Now, shoot!
Boss!
We got it!
I can't believe that Boss got beat!
Fabre-san, there is no other way!
To save this island, we
should let them have Boss!
Make a decision! You're the mayor!
Yoko, I...
Dad, what should I do?!
To save this island...
Boss?
Boss?! Where are you going?!
Oh, you...
No, it's not like that, Boss!
No!
Boss!
Hey, Fabre! What is Boss doing?!
He heard everyone's inner voices and
he's trying to save this island
by sacrificing himself!
Boss!
It's okay. Don't be afraid.
You're covered with cuts and bruises.
Don't worry.
Stay still.
I'll fix you up.
Trust me.
No!
Saying goodbye is always hard to do.
I understand you, senorita!
That was too easy but it's okay.
Now, come in and make yourself at home!
With this beetle in our hands,
we can finally become members
of the Big Boss' crew!
Hey, you!
Wait!
I said "wait!"
Can't you hear what I'm saying!
I'm not gonna let you go with...
...these bastards!
Giant Beetle! You still
haven't fought with me!
We promised and I know that you remember!
Pirate!
W-What're you doing?!
Can't you see that Boss was trying
to sacrifice himself for the island?
Shut up! I don't care!
I just wanna fight him!
Is that it?!
He's so hopeless!
Do you have something to say?!
I want to...
...be with Boss forever!
Yoko!
I want to...
...be with Boss...
...on this island!
Hearing that makes me realize
something. Let me down!
You're completely right!
I'm sorry that I gave you a hard time, Yoko!
Before I thought that we
better let them have Boss...
...And I'm ashamed of myself!
We love Boss...
...As well as this island!
W-W-We won't let...
...People like you...
...Have him!
--Yeah!
You people are really manipulated
by what that stupid kid said!
It's like a sappy drama! It makes me sick!
They choose to be exterminated.
Underdogs will always perish.
That's the way of the world.
Oh, that's...
Oh, he starts to shed his skin!
Awesome!
How funny! Now they're starting
to fight amongst themselves!
Boss!
--Boss!
Oh no! It was too soon to
shed his skin as I thought!
I don't know about the structure of your body
but it seems like that was
an incomplete transformation.
You should be disappointed.
I feel sorry for you!
Crying or screaming won't help anymore!
We got your guardian angel as you see!
It's not over yet!
We won't let his last breath...
...be wasted.
Thank you, Giant Beetle!
Now, it's showtime!
To recover the beetle and
protect Little East Blue,
the islanders travel through
the caves according
to Nami's secret plan.
Meanwhile, Luffy pursues
Largo, but the power of the
Net-Net Fruit traps him inside Largo's body.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Special Presentation Related to the Movie!
Luffy vs. Largo The Battle is on!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!