Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Bon Clay who was saved by
Ivankov of New Kama Land...
...has just learned that Luffy's
treatment has already begun!
Don't underestimate miracles!
"Believe in Miracles!
Bon Clay's Cries from the Heart!"
M-Miracles?
Yeah!
But it will take a tremendous miracle
for Straw boy to survive!
I believe in Straw-chan's spirit!
I believe that miracles can happen!
B-Because it's Straw-chan!
I believe that he can do it!
Then, stop panicking!
We have to trust him and wait!
So I ate the Horm-Horm Fruit
and now I can control people's hormones
and change their sex, body temperatures,
skin colors, growth and emotions!
I can remodel people from the inside,
I'm like an engineer of the human body!
I can feel that you're
like the candies here...
...except they've all
transcended sex completely!
Some men you see could have been women...
...and some women could have been men!
That's some kind of miracle!
That's some kind of miracle-able!
That's right!
He changed that man to a
woman by injecting hormones!
Umm... But I still can't believe
there's a place like this in a prison!
I must be dreaming!
It's not a dream!
It's a dream land!
All of these candies were lost
prisoners who made it here by luck!
You see--there are entrances to
this New Kama Land on every floor!
There's one at the bloody mountain of needles,
and in the lair of wild beasts!
Or in the burning hellfire!
Even in the mortuary.
We use those passages to
get everything we need!
Jailers would never think that
there was a paradise like this in hell.
But we always know what's going on out there!
Because we've got a Transponder Snail
which is the same as the ones the jailers use.
So we can get all information
inside the prison!
And we steal newspapers from garbage cans
so we know what's going on outside, too!
We enjoyed watching the adventures
of the first invader--Straw boy...
...as well as you and the others!
We had so much fun!
Where are we in the prison?!
How did you find a space like this?!
Oh, this place wasn't always here.
I heard that there was a prisoner
with a hole-digging ability
and with that candy in the lead,
they built this prisoners' paradise long ago!
This place is like an ant farm that's been
created by digging tunnels in the rock.
It's right in the middle of level 5 and level 6!
Wait a minute! Level 6?!
There is such a floor?!
Well, it's not widely known but...
...there is level 6 where true villains are kept!
Every one of them is condemned
to a lifetime without parole!
That's level 6--Eternal Hell!
Exceedingly cruel crimes are often
covered up by the government.
As are incidents that'd harm
the reputation of the government.
For example, you guys
rampaged all the way to level 4
but if you'd tried that a little while ago,
it wouldn't have been so easy.
Because there was another
threat in this prison!
He was the Jail Manager of Impel Down -
Shiryu of the Rain!
He's as strong as Warden Magellan.
If you think about how little
Magellan actually works,
Shiryu was twice as troublesome.
S-Strong as Warden Magellan?!
Impel Down was iron-tight with those two!
Jail Manager Shiryu of the Rain...
What do you think you're doing, Shiryu?!
What do you mean?
The prisoners are not here
for your amusement!
No one cares whether or not these vermin die!
I can't overlook your actions any longer!
If anyone finds out what you've done here,
it will disgrace Impel Down!
Now I must exercise my authority
and put you under arrest!
He put prisoners to the sword as he wanted
and was out of control
so they hold him in level 6
now as a security risk.
I've never heard of this!
Even though it happened before I got here...
There are also pirates like
the world's most dangerous woman--
Catalina Devon,
"Great Battleship" San Juan Wolf,
"Heavy Drinker" Vasco Shot!
These are names that'd make
anyone shiver with fright!
There are wretched criminals,
whose crimes were so cruel
even papers refused to mention them...
...all down there in level 6.
Your former boss is there, too!
He's just as crazy as the others!
What?! 0-chan?! Crocodile?!
You guys were enemies of
Straw boy at Alabasta, right?
It's interesting!
It goes to show that anyone
can become friends!
You're right!
There is also a Warlord of the Sea
- "First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
And the guy that Straw boy snuck in here for.
He's the second division commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates--
Portgaz D. Ace!
I heard it over the radio!
They are brothers, right?!
Yes, Straw-chan said that the only reason
he came here was to rescue him!
It's miraculous that he snuck in.
But he's going to have to give it up!
He has to save himself first!
Today's the day that Ace boy
will be executed--at 3pm!
I think that they're gonna take him
to Navy Headquarters in the morning.
That means Ace boy will be taken
out of Impel Down in 7 or 8 hours!
Straw boy's treatment will take 2 more days!
Even if he survives,
he'd need 3 days of sleep
to restore his strength!
So when he wakes up, everything will be over!
But can he even take 2 more days of that?!
I told you that the possibility is low
and that he needs a miracle to make it!
You need to rest, too!
Eat something nutritious and go back to bed!
I'll offer you a quiet room to sleep in.
I'll stay with Straw-chan!
Hey, don't bother! He's...
There's little hope!
What are you gonna do?!
S-Straw-chan!
Hang in there!
Straw-chan!
I wonder how he's doing.
All he can do is wait.
Hang in there!
Hang in there! Straw-chan!
Hang in there! Hang...
Hang in there! Hang in there!
He's been doing it all this time?!
That's so stupid! That won't do anything!
You're right! Let's go!
Hang... Hang in...
Hang... Hang in there!
Can't you find...
...even one queer?!
Look for him again!
He's not back yet.
Is he still doing it?
He must have given up already
and probably went to sleep!
I'll go check!
I'll go!
Me, too!
I can't hear it anymore.
See, I told you!
He gave up and...
Hang... Hang in there!
Hang in there!
Hang... in... there!
How long will he keep wasting time like that?!
Hang... Hang in...
S-Straw-chan...
That fool!
Hey, you alright?!
Take care of yourself first!
We gotta treat him!
Keep your hands to yourselves!
Let him do what he wants!
But...
Bon boy wants to struggle
and fight alongside Straw boy!
Even if there's only a ghost of a chance,
he believes in Straw boy
and puts his life on the line
and shouts himself hoarse!
S-Straw-chan!
They're both beyond their
capacities already but...
...they're trying to create a miracle!
For more than 10 hours,
S-Straw-chan has been fighting against
his own destiny for his life in this way!
Then I... I...
I shouldn't give in, either!
Hang... Hang in there!
Hang in there!
Hang in there, Straw-chan!
Straw-chan!
You have to live!
Hang in there!
--Straw-chan!
--Hang in there!
Hang in there!
Hang in there-able!
Straw-chan!
Hang in there!
WARDEN'S OFFICE
Warden!
I just heard from the canteen staff on level 5
and they said that Straw Hat Luffy has...
...disappeared!
What?!
V-Vice Warden Hannyabal!
What are you doing here?!
Hang in there!
Hang in there! Straw-chan!
Ace-san, I don't know anything
about that woman but...
...I think that you better
assume she's lying.
So you're saying that she came
all the way to here just to lie to me?!
Well, I'm sorry.
But, to tell you the truth, Jimbei.
My brother would do something like that!
He does stupid things!
Since we were kids,
he always made me worry, that fool!
Finally, the day has come!
I hope that we can get
rid of him successfully!
I don't want any wars in Impel Down!
Warden Magellan will be here any minute.
I-It's blood!
No more screams...
But the treatment is excruciating!
So the fact that we can't
hear him anymore means...
It's too bad!
But he did his best for 20 hours!
Straw-chan...
What... What?!
Food!
S... Straw-chan!
Yeah!
Straw boy! I...
I can't believe this!
How can this be true?!
It didn't even take a day!
Warden! Warden Magellan!
Good morning!
I've got very bad diarrhea...
Please hurry.
It's time to move the
condemned prisoner - Portgaz D. Ace
Bring more food here!
Keep it coming! Cooked or not!
The amount is what matters!
Hurry up! Just leave it close to him!
Wow! He's taking in food like a sand pit trap!
How long will he keep eating?!
He's been eating for
30 minutes at a steady pace!
He ate several days worth of
the food supply for Kama Land!
What an amazing vital force!
He's coming out!
What kind of creature is that?!
That's not the form of human being!
I'm...
...recovered!
Thanks to Ivankov's treatment, Luffy has miraculously recovered
and intends to save Ace by himself.
Once Ivan-san learns that Luffy is the son of the revolutionary--Dragon,
he decides to lend Luffy his strength.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy's Back!
Ivan-san Begins the Breakout Plan!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!