Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has broken out of the great prison Impel Down
and is headed to the Navy Headquarters in order to rescue his brother, Ace!
"A Special Retrospective Before Marineford! The Vow of the Brotherhood!"
That must be Ace-san's Vivre Card.
Yeah.
I heard a lot about you from Ace.
He told me that you two always used to run through the fields together.
Yeah! Ace and I were always together!
Wait! Ace!
I'm gonna beat you this time!
Eating together...
Sleeping together...
Spending all your spare time honing your skills...
You're still far from defeating me.
That's how it used to be -
Ace-san told me nostalgically.
Ace went out to sea 3 years before me.
He hadn't even eaten the devil fruit at that time but I couldn't beat him even once.
You hadn't seen him after he left?
No, I saw him in Alabasta once.
Sheesh! I guess my letting you escape was pretty much pointless.
Yo!
Ace!
Haven't seen you in a while, Luffy!
This brings back memories!
I'm just in these waters on minor business,
so I thought I might look you up.
Minor business?
I'm a member of the Whitebeard Pirates now.
Whitebeard Pirates?
This is the mark of the Whitebeard Pirates. It's my pride.
Oh?
Luffy. Won't you join the Whitebeard Pirates?
Your friends can come too, of course.
No.
I figured not. Just thought I'd ask.
Whitebeard is the greatest pirate I know.
I wanna help him to be King of the Pirates...
...And not you, Luffy.
That's fine! Then we'll just have to fight!
Cheers!
Who said I was joining you?
Ace! Are you sure you won't join us?
I'm chasing a certain man.
His name's Blackbeard.
He used to be a member of the 2nd Division of the Whitebeard Pirates,
one of my men.
But he committed the worst possible sin on a pirate ship:
he killed a crewmember and jumped ship.
So, as the commander, I gotta find and get rid of him.
I wanted to give this to you. Here.
Hold onto it, always.
It's just a paper.
Yes, but that paper will lead us to one another.
You don't want it?
No, I want it!
Older brothers can't help worrying...
...if their younger brother is weak.
I know that he'll be a handful
but please look after him.
Huh? Are you leaving already?
Luffy! I'll see you at the top of the pirates' world!
Blackbeard...
I met him before in Mock Town.
--Hey, pops!
--Hey, buddy!
Hm? What's wrong?
--This cherry pie tastes extremely bad! Hm?
--This cherry pie tastes extremely good! Hm?
You bastard! Wanna fight?!
What the hell are you fighting about?!
Are you a pirate?
Yeah, that's right.
What's the bounty for you?
30 million!
30 million? For you?
Can't be true! It's gotta be a lie!
I'm not lying! That's the truth!
Stop it!
Whoa! They're gonna take Bellamy on!
Go for it!
Luffy, wait!
Hey, Mister! We want to go to the sky island!
Do you know anything about it?
She said "sky island!"
Give me a break!
Hey, you got me there.
You guys believe in such an ancient legend... that there's an island in the sky?
Just which era are you from?
Listen. The era where pirates dream about things is over
When I see idiots chasing after dreams like that, I get disgusted!
Luffy!
Zoro...
Don't take them on, no matter what happens.
The sky island exists.
You're that guy...
The new era they're talking about is crap!
The era where pirates have dreams will be over, they say?! Huh?!
People's dreams... have no end!!
Isn't that right?!
I still can't believe that somebody was able to beat Ace.
W-What?!
The Warlords and the Navy are gonna fight against the Whitebeards?!
What's that?! What's gonna happen?! W-W-W-W-Wait a minute!
T-This is too much to hear at once!
What a foolish man! You don't know anything.
I must say, that was just a prediction.
But the battle will probably happen.
The World Government has made a move.
Whitebeard is a man who would never allow his mates to be killed.
Even though they know this, they announced the public execution of...
...Portgaz D. Ace, a great commander of Whitebeard's.
What's wrong?
Ace... is gonna get executed?
I heard a pirate called Blackbeard...
...became a Warlord by defeating "Fire Fist" Ace.
That's my brother!
Ace is my older brother!
What?!
I wanna go and rescue Ace!
When I heard the news, I couldn't believe it either.
But... I didn't know that you already met Teech.
I remember that that's the way he talks.
Blackbeard!
So you're...
You're...
...Blackbeard?!
Huh? Oh yeah, I never gave you my name.
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
I was surprised, too, when I heard that you were the brother of my commander!
Are you sure you want to be here? You're gonna miss it!
Your brother's public execution!
I found out later that the former Warlord right there...
...Crocodile was defeated by you, Straw Hat Luffy!
At that time, I was trying to take his place as a Warlord so...
...killing you was the most effective way to show my ability to the Government!
But fate has saved you instead!
Pay your respects at his grave!
If it weren't for him, you'd be the one who...
...would've been killed, Straw Hat!
The guy that he killed was...
...called Thatch--the commander of the 4th Division of the Whitebeards.
He was a good-hearted man.
I wanted to help good old Whitebeard whom I owe so much
so I often visited the ship at that time,
but I didn't notice what Teech was up to!
And then,
Ace-san sailed out to sea alone.
As the commander of the 2nd Division of the Whitebeards,
he needed to get rid of Teech!
To all soldiers!
Report to the gulf!
Get ready for the public execution of Portgaz D. Ace!
I repeat!
All soldiers, report to the gulf!
Get ready to set sail! We've got a lot to do!
Hey! Wait, Teech!
I've been looking for you.
Ace! Commander!
Quit calling me "commander."
People who use that term usually respect others.
You can't fool me.
I got it. But let me say just one thing.
Ace! Why don't you join my crew?!
Let's dominate the world together! The way is all planned out
Whitebeard's reign is over! I'll become the next Pirate King!
For starters, I'm gonna kill Straw Hat Luffy who is in the Water Seven...
...as a gift to the Government!
Luffy? What did you just say?
Oh! You know him?!
Another reason I can't let you go free!
He's my brother!
And of course...
...I'm not gonna become one of...
...your crew.
Fire Fist!
I know what you want, Ace. You want to kill me.
No wonder. Killing a crewmember is the worst crime.
Yes, I killed Thatch - the commander of the 4th Division!
According to the ship's rules, the one who finds it can eat it.
I remembered how they looked from seeing all the fruit in a book.
I noticed this was the one I'd been looking for.
That's why you killed Thatch? To steal it?
Well, it wasn't for no reason.
The power chose me, Ace!
With that fruit, I've become the world's strongest man, Ace.
Look! This one is different from all the other Logia type.
Ace, your body is made out of fire, right?
Mine's made out of darkness!
Firefly! Fiery Doll!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
Ouch!
But it's odd.
If it was a Logia type fruit, you could fend off these attacks.
I told you. Darkness will drag in everything.
Bullets, blades, blows, fire, even thunder!
So I can't fend off attacks like you do.
My body will absorb even pain more than a normal person's.
But, in return for these risks, there's another thing that my darkness drags in!
Vortex!
The gravity of the darkness will pull in Devil Fruit eaters...
The gravity?!
...And my body will...
How's this? You get it already, don't you?
Ace!
No way!
You haven't been hit by somebody for long time, have you?
Ace.
I think that you got it when I grabbed you!
Another thing that my darkness drags in is...
...Devil Fruit powers!
That means as long as I touch them, Devil Fruit eaters can't use any of their powers!
Logia, Zoan, Paramecia...
All the Devil Fruit eaters in this world who put too much confidence in their powers...
...can't protect themselves from my striking power!
Then I won't let you touch me!
Vortex!
St. Elmo's Fire!
Ace!
Nothing can compete against darkness.
Even your strength.
But your power is such a valuable one.
Ace! You got to join my crew!
If I yield to power, there's no point in being born a man.
I'll never leave anything to be regretted later in my life!
Do you understand, stupid?
This world is worthless if you can't survive.
What a shame, Ace!
Die in the darkness!
Flame Commandment!
Flame Emperor!
The sun or the darkness - there'll be only one winner!
I'm gonna make Whitebeard the king!
Three hours before Ace's exectution at the Navy HQ,
all seven Warlords assemble and await Whitebeard's arrival.
At the same time, the three Admirals gather...
Tension keeps rising before the inevitable battle!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Special Retrospective Before Marineford! The Three Navy Admirals Come Together!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!