Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Raise the anchor!
Set the sails!
--Bring the ship forward!
--You idiot!
--Don't shake things, Sanji!
--Full speed ahead to the Grand Line!
Shut up. If you're scared, then go
down and sleep like a good li'l boy.
D-D-Don't be stupid!
Of course I'm not scared!
--Sanji! Breakfast!
--Yeah, yeah!
I'll get started on it. Hold on.
Good morning, Nami-san!
Good morning, Sanji-kun.
Hey. Hey, Zoro. Let's play tag.
Huh?!
What, what?! Tag?!
Let's play, let's play!
Are you guys stupid?!
You're pathetic, playing at your age!
I'm gonna get some more
sleep before breakfast.
Oh?! 'Cause you
don't like losing, huh?!
What did you say?!
I don't give a damn about that!
--See! You're suddenly mad!
--What?!
Hold it, you guys!
But it's the truth, isn't it?! Bleehhh!
Stop right there!
Does that mean you'll
join our crew now?!
But I'm only teaming up
with you, just so you know!
Always remember that!
--I'm over here! Come get me!
--C'mon, Zoro! Chase me, too!
I'm not playing here!
Nami-san! Your meal's ready!
Hey, guys! Food's on!
Yeah!
Hold it! I'm not done with you!
Even after he said all that...
Huh? What, Nami-san?
No, it's nothing!
Whew, I'm hungry!
Food! Food! Food!
This looks yum!
Say, what do you suppose
happened to Buggy after that?
Buggy? Oh, that Buggy?
Who knows? Maybe he's
at the bottom of the ocean.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Pirates are a stubborn lot,
every last one of 'em.
Yeah?
You're the one who kept
chasing me stubbornly! Oww...
I hunted pirates for years. I can tell.
Not that it matters,
but your food's gone, Usopp.
--Here you are, Nami-san!
--Luffy!
--A Special Yogurt Dessert!
--You stole my food again!
--Oh! Thank you, Sanji-kun!
--Give it back, you idiot!
Alright!
I've finally finished my flashy raft!
Just you watch!
I, the great and world-renowned
pirate, Buggy the Clown-sama...
...will get my crew back together
and get my super flashy revenge!
No matter what obstacles lie in my path!
The score must be settled!
You damn flashy
rubber man! Just you wait!
I absolutely will beat you senseless
and make you cry uncle!
Go! Set sail!
Stuff like this already?!
I refuse to lose! Damn you!
"Chase Straw Hat!
Little Buggy's Big Adventure"
I managed to make it...
to the next island...
Damn it! Don't scare me like that!
I'm not some kind of exhibit, dammit!
Why, you...! Are you mocking me?!
You got some real guts, ridiculing me!
I'm gonna eatcha!
I was just feeling hungry, too!
You've made me mad!
You're done for now!
I'm gonna eat you flashily,
so just give yourself up!
Chop-Chop Cannon!
Quit your flailing!
Just accept your fate!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
Forgive me!
C'mon! C'mon!
My plan is flawless!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
I caught him!
I got caught?! Huh?!
How did things turn out this way?!
Stop! Stop! No!
Is this the end already?! This sucks!
Why, you...! Am I that bad-tasting?!
That's a little bit of a shock!
Hey, look! A hermit crab!
I wonder when he got on
board. At Nami's village?
Probably. That, or maybe
at Usopp's village?
If so, that's incredible!
That'd mean he's been
traveling with us this whole time!
Dammit! Why does this happen to me?!
--Did you just say something?
--Huh? Me? I didn't say anything.
Nuh-uh.
That's weird. Must've
been my imagination.
--Hey, Luffy! Quit slackin' off!
--Oh! Sorry! Sorry!
There we go...
Where am I now?
Leave!
Who's there?!
I am this island's protective god!
Leave this island at once
if you value your life!
Protective god?!
Hey, you! You're one of those, uhh...
...weird creatures!
I'm gonna kick your ass, you moron!
Listen! Just try taking
another step into the forest!
The instant you do, will you
receive my divine punishment
and meet your doom?!
How should I know, you flashy idiot?!
Why're you asking me?!
What are these things?
The animals of this forest.
Don't mess with them,
unless you want to die!
Oh? These are some
flashily interesting animals...
I told you not to go any further!
Blast it! He suddenly shot at me!
Damn! I missed!
There you are!
What is this?!
Gotcha!
--Come out!
--Oww! Oww! Oww!
Dammit! You have a Devil Fruit power!
So what if I do?! You're nothing--
You're--
What are you?
Are you a boxed and sheltered son?
Yeah. I've been overly pampered
since I was just a little boy...
Of course I'm not!
Don't do stupid gags!
Damn you! Don't get cocky!
I don't show mercy to anyone
who messes with them!
Oh? You wanna fight me?
I commend your bravery,
but don't blame me after you die!
Gotcha!
Blast you!
Flying weapons are unfair!
Then what's this thing here?!
Don't talk so selfishly!
Say your prayers!
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
Oww!
--How dare you?! Blast it! Oww!
--How dare I what?! Huh?!
I've had enough!
Don't move!
Too bad! Anyone who messes
with the animals has to pay!
They're this island's treasure!
Those weird animals are treasures?
Treasure refers to gold, silver,
and jewels, you flashy idiot!
Don't play stupid! You came to
this island to get these animals!
Why would I do that?! I didn't
come here 'cause I wanted to!
You mean you're not a poacher?
Don't be stupid! I might not
look it, but I'm a great pirate!
I'm Buggy the Clown-sama!
I'd never do anything as mean as that!
Pirate? You're a pirate?!
Huh?
Me, too! I used to be a
pirate a long time ago!
Oh, my bad! My bad!
So you're a pirate, too!
Whadya think? Good, huh?!
It's my own unrefined sake!
Yeah, this is the best! How many
days it's been since I last drank...
You can have as many refills
as you want! Drink up and up!
But I'm really sorry about earlier!
I just assumed you were a poacher
who came to get these animals!
That was some horrible stuff you did!
But it doesn't matter now!
Plus you let me have
this delicious booze, too!
The only things in this world that
interest me are treasure and alcohol!
I'm likin' you even more!
You're a pirate, all right!
You're a real stout-hearted guy!
Tell me, why are you on this island?
Oh. I originally came here
in search of treasure, too.
What?! There's treasure on this island?!
Calm down. If there was, I wouldn't
be hanging around here, either.
O-Oh. You have a point.
Anyways, some stuff happened
and my crew left me behind.
So I've been calling this island
home for the past 20 years now.
20 years?!
You've really had it rough!
It's not so bad, really.
These guys are here with me.
This way of life is actually pretty
nice once you get used to it!
I dunno. I'd much rather be living
the pirate life with my crew.
True, pirate life is nice! It's great!
Even I would gladly risk my life to
go on treasure-hunting adventures!
Right?! It's like, "Hurray for pirates!"
What do you say? When I get my
pirate crew back, won't you join us?!
Eh?!
I greatly welcome guys like you!
After all, you have the pirate spirit!
Well? Whadya say?!
You're... inviting me?!
I appreciate the thought,
but these guys are my friends.
When you live with them for
20 years, they rub off on you,
even if they are weird creatures.
I can't leave them now.
What? What's so funny?!
No, I was just
remembering a young pirate
who asked me to be a pirate
again just like you did.
Don't be so upset, old guy!
It's a good thing we came after 20 years!
30 years later and you
might've been dead!
Straw Hat...
He was such an incredibly nice guy.
I'm sure you and him'd be good friends!
I see. So there are
youngsters out there like that...
Not me, though.
I ran into this one horrible kid!
Assemble! Chop-Chop Parts!
Tadah!
Looking for these?!
My parts!
Way to go, thief!
S-Stop!
Go flying, Buggy! Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
And that's how I wound up
on a wandering journey...
Just thinking about it now
makes me boil with rage!
I see. Sorry to hear what happened...
But it just goes to show there are
all kinds of youngsters out there.
In any case, let's have fun tonight!
We don't want this
night to go to waste!
Yeah, huh?
--To pirates!
--And to us meeting!
Cheers!
Sorry for asking you
to help make a raft, too.
Not at all. It was my pleasure.
So you're really going to stay?
Yeah. With all my friends here.
I see...
Alright! Take care of yourself!
You, too!
Farewell, friend! Take care!
Yeah...
You, too!
Set sail!
Alright!
Buggy...
There are many strange
creatures in these waters.
Be ever careful on your way!
Wait, I forgot to tell him that!
R-Run, Buggy!
Ahh! Look out! Run! Get out of there!
W-What's that?
Pretty...
Who's that?!
She's super pretty!
Well, at least it looks like he's saved!
He had me sweating bullets there!
In any case, take care of yourself!
Thanks for the help! I flashily
thought I was a goner there!
There's no need to thank me.
You're Buggy the Clown, right?
How do you know that?! Who are you?
I'm looking for a certain man.
You know him, right?
Damn rubber man!
Damn you! Someday, I will settle
the score with you! Just you wait!
This is the guy you're looking for?
Come. I have a meal ready.
I see. So that's why you helped me...
That's right.
So, what do you say?
Will you team up with me?
Sure, why not?
We both have the same goal.
Let's be friends.
That's great. Then cheers!
Cheers!
Sanji... Food...
You just ate... Gimme a break...
Shut up, you guys... I can't sleep...
You sleep too much... Help out
with work sometimes... Sheesh...
I'm amazed they can hold
conversations in their sleep.
Talk about skillful...
Well, I guess I'll hit the hay, too!
Good night.
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Oh, yeah! Buggy's
henchmen were neat, too!
Yeah, you mean like the
unicycle guy and the lion guy?
--Cabaji and Mohji, was it?
--He had animals, too?!
Are they really pirates?!
Who do you think is their captain now?
Cabaji or Mohji, obviously.
Who knows? Maybe it's that lion!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Wait is Over!
The Return of Captain Buggy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!