ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
Oh
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who is waiting to be executed.
No way!
I think he'll appear from
where we least expect.
Maybe we got the wrong lineup.
I see a shadow in the bay!
I get it now!
They got all their ships...
...coated and approached from underwater!
Here comes Moby Dick!
"The Beginning of the War!
Ace and Whitebeard's Past!"
No way!
There's more?
Th-There are 3 more Whitebeard Pirates ships!
They've infiltrated the bay!
Th-That's the...
...1st division commander--Marco!
14 commanders--
they're all here!
It's been awhile, Sengoku.
Whitebeard.
You better tell me that my beloved son...
...is all right.
I can't believe that
we let them get this close!
We made it through the gate but...
...what I'm concerned about is
whether your father is here or not.
"Your?"
I don't think that Dragon
would let them kill his own son...
Oh, my dad and Ace's are not the same.
My dad is Dragon
but Ace's dad is Gold Roger.
He got a great father but he never met him.
He'd get mad every time I mentioned it.
Oh, I shouldn't have said that.
Give me a second, Ace.
Pops!
Wh-What is that?!
He cracked the air?
Where's that explosion coming from?!
No good! The water surface is too high!
A seaquake! He's distorting the sea!
The other side, too!
This is the power of Whitebeard!
I'm heading out first!
Take care, Ace!
Yeah. See you, Luffy!
Uh-huh!
I'll be a lot stronger when
I leave here in 3 years!
You bet!
Ace!
We'll show them how it's done!
That bastard! He became a pirate!
It's a pirate ship! I never seen their flag!
This is a pirate whose become
very powerful rapidly recently.
"D?" Where is he from?
We can't quite figure that out
but even as a rookie,
he has the power of Logia.
Such a dashing young man in the Grand Line.
He refused the offer to join the Warlords.
How long have they been at this?
They're still young.
They shouldn't rush.
Are you serious, Captain?!
I have to see him...
..."Red-Haired" Shanks.
Spade Pirates?
The infamous super rookie
came to say hello to me?
It's not what you're thinking.
My brother was always talking
about you as his lifesaver
so I came to say thank you.
You're Luffy's brother?
I didn't know that he had a brother.
Great, I'm glad to meet you!
Tell me all about yourself!
Let's have a banquet!
So he's still talking about
becoming the King of the pirates?
I guess that's his favorite phrase.
I feel sorry for him because...
I'm the one who'll become the next King.
Yeah? You think?
First, I'll let the whole world
know the power I have.
Oh? How'll you do that?
By beating the strongest man in this world!
You mean Whitebeard?
Hey, big guy, I wanna see the
guy who goes by Whitebeard.
I cannot introduce a sharp
young man like you to the old man!
Captain, that's Jimbei!
Oh, the Warlord?
Then I'd gain prestige if I beat him.
I'm not on the crew of the Whitebeard Pirates
but I owe him, so I'll fight you!
It's been 5 days since they started fighting.
They're both gonna die!
Ace!
What is that?!
Which one of you wants to kill me?
I'm gonna fight you as you wish.
Whitebeard Pirates!
I'm gonna fight you people single-handedly.
Guys!
Flame Fence!
Captain!
Captain Ace, what are you doing?!
Run, guys!
Captain!
What's the matter?
Are you backing away after all?
Let my crew get way. Instead...
...I'm staying!
You snot-nosed brat!
How cheeky you are!
So this is the guy who contended
for supremacy with him.
I won't...
Still some fight left in you?
You are too valuable to let die now, boy.
If you still wanna run wild,
run as wild as you want
on the sea under my name.
Become my son!
Screw you!
Hey!
I'm the 4th division commander.
My name is Thatch.
If you're gonna join us,
we should become friends!
Shut up!
So you're grumpy when you wake up?
Oh yeah, you wanna know what
happened after you passed out?
Your crew came to get you back
so we beat the hell out of them.
But they're not dead.
They're on this ship, too.
Don't you have to put
me in cuffs or shackles?
Shackles? We don't need them!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Do you know what time it is?
Guys, he fell overboard!
He can't swim.
Somebody, help him.
He's been at it every day.
How gutsy he is.
Must be more than 100 times now?
I guess.
Why...
...do you people call him Pops?
Because he calls us "sons."
We are all hated by the world.
So it makes us happy.
I know it's just a word.
But it still makes us happy.
Are you gonna keep doing this
after your life has been saved?
You got to make up your mind.
You're not capable of killing him.
It's either get off of this ship
and start over again...
...or stay here and...
...wear the Whitebeard logo on your back!
Are you Doma?
Ace did it again!
He made Doma and his crew
surrender  by himself!
You want me to command 2nd division?
It's been a vacant post for a
long time. If you took it...
...Nobody would complain.
You're one of the originals, right?
Don't you mind it at all?
I'm okay, don't worry.
I've got no such ambition.
Do it for us! Commander Ace!
Pops, you got a minute?
Well, that was surprising.
I didn't know that.
Your character is nothing like Roger's.
He was your enemy, right?
Don't you wanna kick me out?
You said that it's important
but it's such a small matter.
No matter who your father is,
we are all children of the sea.
Ace will be our 2nd division commander!
You're a star, don't look dazed. Here!
Here!
Hey, the food's not leaving so don't rush.
And you're the star of this banquet so...
He falls asleep!
Whitebeard got a powerful newbie again.
I heard that he's insanely strong!
2nd division come to cover us!
Ace!
Thatch, you okay?
Yeah. Thank you!
Your bounty will rise again!
Maybe.
Ace, I found something interesting.
Oh, is it a devil fruit?
I don't know what fruit it is yet.
Come on, Ace, just calm down!
Pops said that this is an exception.
You don't have to go after Teech!
Let me go! I am his commander!
If I don't do anything about it,
Thatch's spirit can't rest!
Ace.
It's okay. This is an exception.
I have a bad feeling about this.
He killed his crewmate and ran away!
He had been beholden to you for decades
and then he threw dirt in your face!
And above all, he disgraced my father's name
and I can't allow that.
I'll take care of this!
Hey, wait! Come back, Ace!
Is it over?
What caused that quake?
Pops.
Everybody.
I ignored your advice and took off!
Why didn't you just give up on me?!
I'm the one who caused all of this!
No.
I'm the one who told you to go.
Son.
All of the cast has assembled.
Whitebeard's tremendous
power brings a huge tsunami
that threatens to swallow up
all the brave men of Marineford, as
well as the peace and justice there.
A battle crossing generations begins at last!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Force That Could Destroy the World!
The Power of the Tremor-Tremor Fruit!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!