ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
Oh
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who is waiting to be executed.
Meanwhile, the world's
greatest pirate – Whitebeard
has finally appeared...
...at the Navy HQ in Marineford!
He cracked the air?
A seaquake! He's distorting the sea!
I won't...
Still some fight left in you?
You are too valuable to let die now, boy.
If you still wanna run wild,
run as wild as you want
on the sea under my name.
Become my son!
Screw you!
Why...
...do you people call him Pops?
Because he calls us "sons."
We are all hated by the world.
So it makes us happy.
I know it's just a word.
But it still makes us happy.
"The Force That Could Destroy the World!
The Power of the Tremor-Tremor Fruit!"
That's a lie! Cut it out!
You told me not to go but I...
I'm the one who told you to go.
I'm the one who told him to go.
Isn't that right, Marco?
Yes, that's what I heard.
I'm sorry that we put you
through so much, Ace.
Everybody in this world knows.
What will happen to someone
who messes with...
...our crewmate!
We won't let anybody who
hurts you get away with it, Ace!
Count on us! We will save you!
Prepare yourselves, Navy HQ!
We brought this upon ourselves.
It's too late to say such a thing.
That's so hideous.
On this side, we, The Warlords,
the Navy's greatest powers--3 admirals
and a hundred thousand elite soldiers!
On that side, there are
the Whitebeard Pirates
and more than 40 allied ships!
Now, how do you wanna do it, Whitebeard?!
It's so exciting!
Do you wanna be on the sideline as always?
I know that you just came to kill some time.
So be it.
There are rowdy men everywhere
and I can't stand it.
He is also a man but he is an exception.
I'm praying for you, Luffy!
H-Hey!
What's wrong?
The water is receding!
What does it mean?
What's going on?!
The ship is flying backwards!
Is this for real?!
It was really smooth just two minutes ago!
Why all of the sudden...
Oh no! My waterworks!
We've gotta keep moving!
What's going on here?
This must be...
F-Finally it stopped!
What was that all about?
We went back a good distance.
I wonder when we can get
to Marineford like this.
Ow, ow, ow...
Wh-What was it?
Hey, Jimbei!
Can you hurry up? Please!
I gotta get there before Ace's execution!
Don't worry, Luffy-kun. We'll make it!
Okay.
Hey, hey!
How can you be so sure?
Roll-y roll-y.
You think your Fish-Man Karate can help?
Or are you gonna call out
whale sharks to help again?!
My power is not enough.
Then, who are you depending on?
He said we'll make it! So we'll make it!
"He said we'll make it! So we'll make it!"
Fine! Whatever!
That's nonsense.
I'm gonna take a nap.
We can't stick around here any longer!
What happened to your dream to
become the King, Captain Buggy?
Well...
If the time is right,
I'm sure that there'll be a miracle.
But if it's too early,
then I'll just wait for the right timing.
Y-You're gonna just give up?
I'm disappointed in you!
Can't you see it?!
I mean, can't you see his
magnificent confidence?!
No... It doesn't look like that to me.
This is what they call "perfect composure!"
He's got the regal presence
to become the King!
Now that you mention it, I see it!
How great!
I can't see it at all...
I know that miracles don't happen that often.
But there is nothing I can do but wait.
Dammit!
The tide has changed!
We're going forward!
Did you do something?
I was just steering.
It's speeding up!
C-Could this be...?!
Ouch! What? What happened?!
Captain Buggy!
The miracle that  you were
talking about is about to happen!
I don't think so.
I don't know what's happening
but this is it! Go!
Do you see it, guys?!
The time is calling me now!
Saying "come and become the King!"
You're so great! Like no other!
Yeah! Captain Buggy!
Great! It seems like we can make it!
H-Hey! Look at that!
Wh-What a hell is that?!
They've quieted down all of the sudden.
Are they waiting for Whitebeard's command?
I can hardly breathe!
The water level is rising again!
Wh-What's that?!
I can hear the ground rumbling!
Now it's coming!
The seaquake that he set up before!
Coming in the form of tsunami!
The Tremor-Tremor Fruit
made him a quake man!
Edward Newgate aka Whitebeard!
Look! What is that?!
It's a giant tsunami!
Don't think that our superior forces
will guarantee us victory.
We could well fail.
Because that man has...
...the power to destroy the world!
It's beginning! The war!
Let's go!
The invaders: a fleet of 47 ships
from the New World led by Whitebeard.
The defenders: the 2 greatest
forces of the Government--
Navy HQ and The Seven Warlords.
No matter who wins and who loses,
the times will change!
It's a tsunami!
What power!
He certainly is the legendary monster!
Ice Age!
Aokiji!
You young squirt!
I-It's frozen!
Th-That was close!
Admiral Kuzan did it!
Partisan!
Uh-oh.
The whole bay is frozen!
The ships can't move now!
W-We have the greatest force of the
Navy HQ--the admirals--on our side!
Th-That's right!
There's no reason to be
afraid of the Whitebeards!
Fire! Destroy the Moby Dick!
Let's go!
We've got a good foothold now!
Show them what we're capable of!
The commanders came out, too!
Don't stop firing!
Mount a counter-offensive!
Yes!
He must be the 5th division
commander - Flower Sword Vista!
Stay alert, Tashigi!
They're all mighty soldiers -
not just the commanders!
Don't forget it!
I-I got it, Smoker-san!
It's nice to have ice in the water!
Because my blood is burning!
Let's shoot them up and invade the island!
It's not that easy, huh?
Here come the vice admirals of the Navy HQ!
It's so rare to see all of them
together at the same place!
It's like when they have
the Buster Call. But...
...when it comes to Pops and us,
it won't work that way!
Tsuru-san, why don't you stand back?
Leave it up to us
and have some tea or something
from a comfortable distance.
Don't talk smart to me, fledglings!
There is no safe place even if
I back up to the end of the sea!
Bring the ship to the ice gorge!
Trounce them all and get to the land!
Go!
We'd be happy to give our lives for Pops!
We're not scared of the Navy HQ!
Let's go, Squard Pirates!
It finally started!
Dracule Mihawk!
Is the Warlord on the move?!
That's very unusual!
The capricious "Hawk-Eye"
seems like he's willing to fight.
What? Do you wanna fight?
I just want to figure
out the true distance...
...between us and that man who
seems like right in front of us.
Even very skilled soldiers would
tremble and freeze from fear
just by looking into his eyes.
He is truly a "Hawk-Eye" as he is called.
I've always wanted to see him.
It's every swordsman's dream
to cross swords with him.
Because he is assumed to be
the strongest in the world.
That's the instinct of swordsmen!
So that's the Black Sword
that everybody's talking about.
To be precise...
...it's Black Sword "Night!"
It's one of the 12 highest
grade swords in the world.
And its dark blade edge has an irregular
temper line and a double clove pattern.
It's a noted sword suitable
for the greatest swordsman.
"Hawk-Eye!"
Mihawk and Kizaru launch
their attacks on Whitebeard.
In response, the Whitebeard commanders
fight back using their own powers.
As the unpredictable battle rages,
Admiral Akainu finally unleashes
his incredible power!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An All-Consuming Inferno!!
Admiral Akainu's Power!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!