ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
Oh
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ
to rescue his brother, Ace!
Meanwhile, at the Navy HQ,
with Ace's execution at hand,
the Whitebeard Pirates suddenly appear!
You better tell me that my beloved son...
...is all right.
Pops!
Finally, the war has begun!
I can hear the ground rumbling!
Now it's coming!
The seaquake that he set up before!
Coming in the form of a tsunami!
It's a tsunami!
Ice Age!
What? Do you wanna fight?
I just want to figure
out the true distance...
...between us and that man who
seems like right in front of us.
"An All-Consuming Inferno!!
Admiral Akainu's Power!"
Oh no!
Run!
Pops!
He deflected the blow of
the world's greatest swordsman!
H-H-He must be...!
...3rd division commander--Diamond Jozu!
You better keep your wits about you!
Guys! Let's keep advancing!
Fight them back!
What fools!
They want to break through from the front!
Artillery unit!
Fire at the enemy ships
and approaching pirates!
Yes, sir!
Forward units, don't allow
them access to this plaza!
Yes, sir!
Oh boy...
The commanders of the Whitebeards
are true to their reputation.
They are all pretty much like monsters.
To finish this with minimum damage,
we just have to cut off
their head nice and quick.
I-It's bright!
Wh-What is it?!
I-It's Kizaru!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
Hey, that's so bright.
He warded off the admiral's attack!
What's that?
He's engulfed in a blue flame!
Blue flame?
You can't reach...
...the king...
...so easily!
So fearsome, these Whitebeard Pirates.
What's with his body?!
He took Kizaru-san's attack
directly but didn't fall!
So he has this power as they say?!
It's even rarer than Logia.
Zoan type--Mythical Creature.
Look! His wounds are disappearing!
I-I can't believe it! It didn't hurt him?!
It did.
Don't lie.
So he's the 1st division commander...
No matter what kind of attack he absorbs,
he recovers by flames...
Marco the Phoenix!
I have never seen a bird like that.
How painful.
Don't lie!
Kizaru-san got blown away!
I can't believe it! Kizaru-san!
I knew that you wouldn't let me...
...strike your head that easily.
Giant unit, you better pay
attention to the sky, too.
Yes, sir!
Here come the giants!
Attack their feet! Let's topple them!
All of you! Stand back!
Jozu!
What power!
Withdraw for now!
What is he doing?!
Stop this if you can!
It's a block of ice!
It's gigantic!
Damn! Those two...
They shouldn't leave their
positions like that.
If all three of us left our positions...
...who would cover them?!
Akainu-san!
Great Eruption!
That gigantic block of ice disappeared...
...into thin air!
No...
Get away!
Volcanic rocks!
Too many of them!
Dammit!
One of our ships has been hit!
Get away from the ship!
This is like watching the end of the world!
He lit up the place too brightly.
Why don't you light up birthday
cakes instead, you magma squirt!
Don't you want an illuminated
funeral for yourself, Whitebeard?
There're 3 more!
Keep firing! Don't fall back!
Don't be afraid!
Get to the plaza!
Stop the commanders!
Don't let them get ashore!
Sink the Moby Dick and kill Whitebeard!
Th-Th-They are pirates...
And this is a real battlefield!
Oh no!
I feel weak at the knees
and I can barely move!
It's impossible...
We have nothing on these guys!
Don't you think so?
They are all monsters.
There's no role to play
for fledglings like us!
Let's get away from here. Okay?
Okay?
But...
Are you nuts?
If we try to fight this battle,
we won't last even a second
and you know that!
Don't you wanna become an admiral?!
I'll become a Navy...
...ad...
...admiral someday!
You wanna fight me, right?
Then, of course you have to
become a big deal like that!
D-Don't take this the wrong way!
That's why, that's why...
...neither of us can die here!
Our place to die is still far away!
But I promised Luffy-san so...
Wh-What is it this time?!
Here he comes!
Get him! Get him!
Break the artillery defense
of the Navy ships!
Ace-kun!
Nice! Get them!
Little Oars Jr.!
He must be a descendent of
the Continent Puller Oars.
He's big!
He's way bigger than common Giants!
Don't let him invade the island!
It'll give them the advantage!
I didn't know that the descendant
of Oars was allied with Whitebeard!
I want it!
I want his dead body!
He makes me tingle!
Oars!
Ace-kun is a nice person!
I won't let him...
...die!
In the past, the Straw Hats suffered
at the hands of the beast, Oars.
Now, to save Ace, an ally
of the Whitebeard Pirates,
the descendant of Oars
breaks through to the bay.
How will the Navy deal with
an attacker whose power
overwhelms even the Giants?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Descendent of the Beast!
Little Oars Jr.--Full Speed Ahead!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!