ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
Inside the bay, Luffy and the Whitebeards
are trying to get to the scaffold
but the Navy stands in their
way. The battle is heating up!
Why did any of them come?!
I deserve this! They don't have
to risk their lives for me!
Don't do this!
Everyone! Why are you doing
this for a guy like me?!
I'm your brother!
Kuma! Kuma, that's enough!
It's me! Did you forget my face?!
If you don't stop, I'm gonna fight
back although I'm a gentle person!
I don't know how you know him
but you may as well give up!
It's no use talking to him, Emporio Ivankov,
commander of the Revolutionaries army!
You...! What do you mean?!
What's wrong with him?!
You're a friend of
Bartholomew Kuma I suppose.
He was once called Tyrant
Kuma and now he is...
...dead.
Your power is not enough to beat me!
Damn! Get your jutte off of me!
You! Leave him alone!
She got me although my body is smoke!
Th-That's...! The pirate
empress saved Straw Hat!
Hancock! What are you doing?!
Are you gonna resign from The Warlords, too?!
Shut up! I'm deafened by my own anger!
How could you hit and pin down my beloved?!
I won't let you survive! I have
never felt this much anger before!
I'm gonna cut you up and feed you to beasts!
That's the Haki of Kuja!
"Kuma's Transformation!
Ivan-san's Blow of Anger!"
Wh-What's going on here?
Why did the pirate empress save Straw Hat?
No, she didn't save him! She's
gonna turn Straw Hat to stone!
I always believed that
you'd make it here alive.
Take this.
It's your brother's handcuff key.
What?!
That's how diabolical the empress is!
Straw Hat can't move now!
Has he turned into stone?
Hancock!
You just said my name again!
Luffy's hands... Luffy's hands touched mine!
Hancock!
Yeah!
You're so...! You're so...!
Thank you! I mean it!
N-No... No problem...! Never
mind me, you've got to...
You've got to keep going, Luffy!
You're right!
Thanks!
No way! He beat the pirate empress?!
He must've fought back and thrown
his weight high into her!
See? She looks so tortured!
He beat The Warlord so easily!
How strong, Straw Hat Luffy!
Like that! Like that!
Like that!
I wasn't expect him to hold
me so tight like that!
I can still feel Luffy's body
in my arms and on my chest!
Is this...
Is this what they call...
...marriage?!
Snake Princess-sama!
Congratulation, Big Sis!
So beautiful!
Best wishes to you!
Luffy!
Hancock. You look very beautiful.
H-A-P-P-Y!
I'll make you happy for
the rest of your life.
Honey.
Yes!
Honey...
Honey!
Luffy! I see it! I can see it!
A string that links us together!
A string that no one can ever cut!
It's a thick red string
of fate like a big snake!
Luffy!
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat!
Perfume Femur!
You outrageous fool, stand back!
I won't let you pass through here!
Look! She's really looking down on him!
Looking down too much makes her leaning back!
Do you know what's
gonna happen to you
after messing with the Navy?!
I can do whatever I want!
Because I'm beautiful!
This is great. She helped me out again.
Wait for me, Ace!
What did you say?! Kuma is dead?!
Then, who is this right here?!
He's alive! Stop talking nonsense!
Ivan-chan! Ah?!
That's the bear guy!
Be careful, Ivan-chan! If
you get blown away by him...
I'm okay. Now, Kuma, move out of my way!
Ivan-chan, do you know him?
Yeah, sort of. But he's acting strange.
Seems like you both have memories of Kuma.
But the Kuma that you both knew
and this one are not the same!
N-Not the same? What is he talking about?
That can't be true!
I'm absolutely sure that he's
the Paw-Paw Fruit eater--Kuma!
Say something, Kuma!
He's pissing me off! Although
he has always been quiet.
I told you that it's no use talking to him.
It was just days ago...
The Government scientist--Dr. Vegapunk
modified him for the last time
and he turned into a complete
human weapon at last!
To be precise, he's the
former Bartholomew Kuma!
Modified? Weapon? What
are you talking about?!
In fact, he volunteered to be a guinea pig
for a study to build a human weapon...
...run by the Government.
First, his hands. Second, his legs.
While his mind worked, they
modified his body piece by piece.
Stop lying! Kuma hates the Government!
He wouldn't sacrifice his life for them.
I know that he wouldn't do that!
Stop yelling.
I don't know what kind of deal
he had with the Government.
Only a few days ago,
he still had his personality.
But now, he doesn't even remember
that he was born human so
he is no better than dead.
He is a monster who fights
as the Government tells him.
He is Pacifista PX-0!
So you better forget about the past!
Kuma! What's happened to you
over these past several years?!
Now I remember him saying...
We will never meet again.
Farewell...
...At that time.
What's wrong, Kuma?! It's me! Ivankov!
Wh-Where'd he go?!
Watch out, you guys! Heads up!
Pad Cannon.
Kuma, you bastard!
Face...
...Spectrum!
I'm watching you!
Galaxy Wink!
Heehaw!
How could you attack  my sweet candy boys?!
I'm not gonna go easy on you anymore!
Here!
Kick!
That's how strong he is!
Among all people that I've met...
My face!
No one has ever forgotten
my face in my entire life!
Oh, uh, hmmm.
But...
...even if you've lost your memory,
if you can't remember how scary I am,
I'm gonna beat it into your body!
Be ready for it!
He's recovered, so quick!
I'll take it from here!
You guys, go ahead and back Straw boy up!
Roger!
Okay, let's go, Straw Hat!
Thanks, Ivan-chan!
Get to the scaffold!
They suddenly disappeared in ice!
It doesn't seem like Admiral
Aokiji used Ice Age again...
Where did they...?
This ice is not cold!
What's wrong?
Alright, guys.
Listen carefully.
Blah-blah-blah... Buggy is great.
Dah-dah-dah... Buggy is genius.
Right? That's how we want it.
That's nice!
And we want the world to be shaken
by the arrival of the new hero.
That's a perfect plan!
Y-You sure?
Let's go, guys!
How annoying, Straw Hat!
Don't fall behind! The plan is called
"Take Captain Buggy to Fame!"
Now is the time to proceed it!
When we succeed, the whole
world will be stunned!
All of you, do as we planned
and watch what you're doing!
Are you sure about that plan?
Crocodile!
There're too many!
I'm too far away from him.
I won't let you get near Pops!
Don't stand in my...
...way!
What a pain in the ass.
He's still messing around.
Brilliant Punk!
He's giant but so fast! How can I avoid him?
The 3rd division commander--Diamond Jozu!
How did you get out of the prison, gator guy?
Did you like the Pool of Blood?
Doflamingo, mind your own business.
Or I'm gonna kill you!
You have a dirty mouth. He-he.
Hey, why don't you team up with me?
Stop here!
Don't get in his way!
Keep going, Straw Hat!
Thanks!
Ace!
I'm sorry, "Red-Haired."
I will not hold back my power.
That's...
..."Hawk-Eye!"
Now, I wonder if fate...
...will end the life of the child
of the next generation here.
Or, if it will save him
from this Black Sword!
Dracule Mihawk,
one of the Seven Warlords of
the Sea, stands before Luffy.
A single slash by the
world's strongest swordsman
easily splits a massive wall of ice in two.
How will Luffy fight back
against such immense strength?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Great Swordsman Mihawk!
Luffy Comes Under the Attack
of the Black Sword!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!