ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
Oh
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
Inside the bay, the Whitebeards
are trying to get to the scaffold
but the Navy stands in their way.
And at the bay head,
the Pacifistas began to attack
the allies of the Whitebeards
to exterminate them!
Squard!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Yeah, barely.
I see. I was calling for you a while ago.
How is it at the bay head now?
Your allies were beaten badly.
I made it here because
I found the way out luckily.
Sengoku has no mercy.
He's using all the forces he has
in order to defeat us.
Pops, did you notice what the Navy was up to?
I've known Sengoku for a long time.
Squard? Why is he up there?
There are 43 allied captains here
and we are all in your debt beyond words!
We risk our lives for the Whitebeard Pirates!
"Akainu's Plot!
Whitebeard Entrapped!"
L-Look! Whitebeard has...
Whitebeard has...
Whitebeard has been stabbed!
Old man!
Wh-Who stabbed him?!
I think he is...!
Yes! But the man who did it is a
captain from among the allies...
...from the New World - Whirl Spider...
Squard!
Why did you do that?! Answer me, Squard!
S-Shut up! You guys made me do it!
What do you mean?!
Do you know what you've done...?
Pops! Don't push yourself! Your health is...
Old buddy!
Stop perpetrating this farce, Whitebeard!
I know about your deal with the Navy!
You have their assurance that the
Whitebeards and Ace will remain safe!
What is he talking about?
What's going on here?!
Everyone, listen very closely!
We've all been trapped!
You never told me...
...that Ace was a son of
that hateful Gold Roger!
When you first found me, I was all alone...
Squard is out of control again!
He's dangerous! Stay away!
Again?! Please!
We can't do anything
about it  when it starts!
Isn't there any strong man?!
Hey! Bring it on!
Bring Gold Roger here!
What? Are you all scared?
What are you waiting for, guys?
You know why I was all alone.
Because Roger killed all my precious crew
who had fought alongside me for so long.
I despise Roger and...
...you know it!!
Then you should have told me
that Ace was Roger's son
and you want to make him
the next King of the Pirates!
Don't mind the Whitebeards!
Back down to the plaza immediately!
The old man wants Ace to be the King?
Whitebeard is the greatest pirate I know.
I wanna help him to be King of the Pirates...
You were already betraying me at that time!
But I didn't know. I even befriended Ace!
I must've looked so stupid!
And then, your dearest son Ace got caught!
With the Whitebeard Pirates
all inside the bay
and we allied pirates on the outside.
You have sold the 43 captains
of the allied pirates to the Navy...
...in exchange for Ace's life!
The allied pirates will be vanquished
and the Whitebeards and Ace will be safe.
That's your deal with Sengoku, isn't it?!
Ace is Roger's son?!
Yes and our superiors have an agreement
over how they're gonna end this war.
That's a lie! I can't believe that crap!
Whether you like or not,
there's only one truth
and you all will die in vain.
Silence! I won't fall for your line!
Can't you see it?
Soon you will know that I'm not lying.
Look closely and see
the outcome for yourself!
Our converging attack will start soon
and only you--the allied
pirates--will be attacked.
The Navy won't even touch
the Whitebeard Pirates.
We didn't know anything about it
and we followed you here sacrificing
our lives to save Ace and help you
and this is what happens!
In fact, we're the ones who
have been attacked by the Navy!
Those monsters approach from the back
and the ice is blocking us on both sides
and we have no way out now!
Big buggy, is he telling the truth?!
Say that he's lying, old buddy!
It's a miracle that I could stab you once.
I'm prepared for it! Kill me!
The wall of ice is blocking us!
There's no place to go!
Is this it?!
When I come to think of it,
they're attacking just us!
Run!
Old buddy, did you really trade us...
...For Ace's life?!
Please say something, old buddy!
Old buddy!
It can't be true!
Whitebeard wouldn't sell out to the Navy.
He sold his allies?
No way, Whitebeard wouldn't do that!
Whitebeard and the Navy made a deal?
Then the pirates who trusted
and followed Whitebeard...
...Are betrayed and will
be killed by the Navy?!
I didn't wanna believe it,
I couldn't believe it!
I never thought that
old buddy would betray us!
You fool!
You've been deceived, Squard!
Why couldn't you trust Pops?!
Don't play innocent, Marco!
You're the 1st division commander,
I know that you knew about Ace
and the deal with the Navy!
It's true that Ace is Roger's son.
They used that to their advantage,
tricking the one man who would
be most angered by that fact.
Their strategy was a notch above us.
I don't want any delay. Aokiji!
He's coming towards us?!
This war was a setup?!
Everything up to now meant nothing?!
There'll be no win or lose?!
Turned off!
What's wrong?
Is it broken?
Activate the encircling walls!
That bastard!
How could he let his own
allies stab him that easily?
Shame on you, Whitebeard!
I've no recollection of being
beaten by such a weakling!
Croco boy...
Crocodile.
It's true,
he could've fended off that attack
if he was the same guy he used to be.
Even if it was a surprise attack or
the attacker was one of his fellows,
he could've avoid it!
That's the problem!
Are you telling me to draw their
sympathy by putting these on?
Pops!
He allows himself to get out of shape!
You know what you have done, right, Squard?
You thrust a sword into your father's body.
You're such a stupid son!
But I love you, son, even if you are a fool.
Cut the crap...
You sold our lives to...
Who pulled your upright and
loyal heart into the darkness?
Tell me.
He's an insurgent in the Navy.
I'm opposed to this plan.
People who don't know the truth
are calling him a legendary
pirate and honoring him
but that's not true.
He's just a scumbag who
offered a secret deal to the Navy
just to protect his own interests
and betrays and sells out his allies.
They made up all his legends.
The one that we have to
kill in this war is Whitebeard!
It's absolutely unthinkable not to!
If you're gonna help me,
I'll save you all--the allied pirates.
Stab Whitebeard.
He said he would save us
allied pirates if I slew you.
So that's what Akainu told you.
I know how much you hate Roger...
...so much so that I can feel your pain.
But, Squard,
it's ridiculous to lay the blame on
a child for the sins of his father.
Did Ace do something to you?
You and Ace have weathered
agony, joy and pain together...
...so many times along with
the others, isn't it right?
I don't give a damn who Ace's father is.
We all met each other
on this wide sea by chance!
Not only the two of you but
all of you, I take as my sons!
So, Squard, treat him kindly.
I don't love him any more than any other.
You are all family to me!
Anyway...
...he has never...
...changed at all, Sengoku.
He shook us up very well.
How ridiculous to say that I sold my sons!
He gave the pirates the way out.
I should never underestimate that guy.
The wall of ice has broken down.
This Navy ship is in good condition!
We can get away at any time!
If you are a pirate, you pick what
you want to believe on your own!
I knew that it was a lie!
That was the Navy's plan!
Damn! They fooled us!
Old buddy would never betray us!
I'm sorry! I will never lose
trust in you, old buddy!
Me too, old buddy! I'm so sorry!
I'll follow you to the end!
Old buddy!
Did you call me a weakling?
Please, Croco brat.
I'm just a human with one heart.
People would call me a devil or a monster
but I can't continue to
be the strongest forever.
If I can save this one young man's life,
I will earn my right to
retire from the world.
Those of you who'll follow me,
lay down your life for it!
Be ready! He's gonna run wild!
He's the strongest man in the world!
Let's go!!
The world's strongest pirate, Whitebeard,
has joined the battle himself.
Unleashing his Tremor-Tremor
fruit powers to the max,
he decimates the Navy's
forces one after another.
In response, Sengoku finally enacts
the greatest counterattack plan
in Navy history!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Encircling Walls Activated!
The Whitebeard Pirates backed into a corner!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!