The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Wow! What a huge town!
The place used to be full of pirates
on their way to the Grand Line.
It has everything you could ever need!
Alright! I'm gonna go get equipment
for our upcoming great adventure!
Looks like I can get
some good ingredients here.
Good women, too!
I got something I wanna buy, too.
Oh? How are you gonna do that?
You're flat broke, as I recall!
Alright! I'm gonna check
out the execution platform!
Huh?
I'm gonna see where the King
of the Pirates was executed!
Hey, wait! We still haven't
decided where to meet up at!
Man, that guy...
The King of the Pirates was
born here and died here!
He might've even walked
down this very street!
Yahoo!
"The Town of the Beginning and End;
Landfall at Loguetown"
--How's this?
--Oh! You look wonderful, Miss!
--You look so elegant, Miss!
--How's this?
--Elemental, Miss!
--Electrical!
--How's this?
--Elegy!
Will you be purchasing all of these?
No, I don't want 'em.
I want something that's rougher.
Come again!
Oh! A top-quality aperitif!
Oh! Two Poinderine
champagne-like beauties!
The whole town is brimming with
the finest ingredients around!
Damn, I can't decide
what to go after first!
I just found the main dish!
"Love-Love Pirates"
Awesome! What is this place?!
Everything here is a collector's dream!
Welcome!
Everything here once belonged to pirates
who returned alive from the Grand Line!
They are especially valuable goods.
Then these are all items that went
on adventures in the Grand Line?!
That's absolutely correct!
We only do business
with warriors of the sea here,
so we warmly welcome
gentlemen such as yourself!
What do you say? This was the
favorite gun of the Gold Roger!
What?! Gold Roger's?!
Yes!
How about it, sir?
S-Show me more!
Thanks! Come again!
Captain Smoker! Terrible news!
A message from Headquarters!
They've received word that a
Monkey D. Luffy and his pirate crew
are headed here, to Loguetown!
He just earned a 30 million
Berry bounty in the East Blue!
30 million...
That's worthy of congratulation.
He's an incredibly evil villain
who even defeated Don Krieg
and Arlong the fishman!
Quiet!
Damn your shouting.
You made it fall apart.
I'm sorry, sir!
It's not good to be tense.
I got my own pace I do things at.
Isn't that right?
Y-Yes, sir!
So... What, now?
Right! A pirate group!
Word has it they may
show up in town today, yes!
What're you so flustered for?
Have any pirates who've set
foot into this town ever escaped
since I took charge here?
N-No, sir...
Then calm the hell down.
You're gonna screw up my pace.
Yes, sir...
Reporting, sir! We have word that
pirates have appeared at the port!
Please go there at once!
It must be Luffy's group!
They've definitely set foot into town!
30 million, huh? I pray he
puts up at least a bit of a fight.
Sir?
Just talking to myself. Forget it.
You're not going to look at this?!
"Justice"
Captain! Please give
each unit their orders!
No need.
But you need to
consider how powerful he is!
You're annoying me.
Don't tell me what to do!
My apologies, sir!
Never mind that. Where's Tashigi?
Y-Yes. She mentioned she
would be gone this morning,
but that she'd show up for training.
That dumb girl.
Where the hell'd she go?
Yay! A triple-scoop ice cream!
Hold on, now!
You'll drop them if you run!
C-Captain Smoker!
M-My ice cream...
I-I'm very sorry about my daughter!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Sorry 'bout that.
My pants ate your ice cream.
Here, buy yourself five scoops.
--Let's go.
--Yes, sir!
T-Thank you!
Thanks!
Loot everything there is!
Don't leave a single potato behind!
I, Gally the Crescent-sama,
will use these vital food supplies
on my way to becoming
King of the Pirates!
Hand it all over thankfully!
Hey.
Who's in charge here?
What do you want?!
So you're Monkey D. Luffy?
I'll test you and see if you're
worthy of setting foot into my town.
Don't give me your crap!
Get 'im!
Captain Smoker?
Yeah. He's one of the toughest
guys from Navy Headquarters.
This town used to be a hangout
for pirates headed for the Grand Line.
But ever since he took over, every
single pirate who's come into town
has wound up in the slammer.
His strength is extraordinary.
He's a monster.
They even say he has
Devil Fruit powers...
Devil Fruit powers?!
Incredible, Captain! You captured
Luffy's crew in no time flat!
Are your eyes just for decoration?
This guy obviously isn't Luffy.
Eh?
The world'd be ending if this
shabby fly were worth 30 million.
T-Then, where is Luffy?
He'll show up soon enough.
The fun is just getting started.
Huh?
How did I wind up at the port? How?
Hey!
Is he one of these guys?
I don't know. I don't think so...
Perfect timing! Do you know how
to get to the execution platform?
The execution platform?
I got lost on my way...
I've never seen you around before.
Yeah! I just landed on this island!
This town sure is huge!
It's way different from Fusha Village!
Why are you looking for
the execution platform?
I wanna see the place where
the King of the Pirates died!
You don't know where? Aww...
Wait. Follow the smoke.
Oh! That way?! Thanks!
Damn, these are expensive!
Too expensive!
Lend you money? Sure!
But including interest, you'll hafta
pay me 300% of what you borrow!
I can't afford to borrow
any more from that girl...
But I can't go into the Grand Line
stuck with just one sword...
--What do I do?
-- "Monster"?! How rude!
Aww, shut up! Our boss is
behind bars all thanks to him!
Have you still not learned your lesson?!
Nope! We ain't happy
with things as they are!
We're gonna bring
your corpse to him to see!
Very well. I will fight you.
--You will, girlie?!
--Don't make us laugh!
What can a girl possibly do?!
--Die!
--Yeah!
--She did it!
--You're strong, lady!
You're amazing!
Oww!
--I can't tell if she's strong or weak!
--Glasses! Glasses! Glasses!
--Glasses...
--Hey. Are these them?
S-Sorry to bother you!
Thank you!
--My glasses!
--I-I didn't mean to!
Those were expensive! How could
you do something so horrible?!
I told you, I didn't mean to--!
Pay me back for them!
Oh, man.
I was trying to get to
the execution platform,
but now I'm somewhere else completely.
Oh, well. I'll get
there sooner or later.
Is it this way?
Let's see...
Gold... Roger?
Do you work here, old guy?
It said "Gold Roger"
on the sign outside...
Is that this place's name?
Scram.
This ain't a place for a runt like you.
Besides, we're closed
for good as of today.
It went under?
It didn't go under!
I'm shutting it down myself!
Now get lost!
I was just curious about
the name, that's all.
I'm lost. I was wanting
to go the execution platform...
Can you tell me how to get there?
What's that on your table?
Oh! A skull?! It's huge!
This is what became of a guy
once known as Killer Giant.
A villain who sent hundreds
of pirates to the afterlife.
But Gold Roger sent him to
his grave with just one blow.
Gold Roger did?!
With truly lightning speed!
This guy was famous for the
absurdly huge blade he used,
but their fight ended
in the blink of an eye!
And this is the wound he received!
But he was an infamous scoundrel himself!
With his dying breath, he muttered,
"Roger... My hat's off to you...
May you have honor
as the Eternal Pirate..."
So awesome! So cool!
Eric Down,
the man known as King...
Silver Silver,
the world's greatest gunman...
The giant Gowns Brothers...
They were all tough men
who were as feared as demons.
But for Gold Roger,
they were as weak as infants.
Would ya like to hear more?
Yeah!
Very few people these days
believe this story, you know...
That's okay! Just tell me!
Hold your horses.
Gold Roger...
In those days...
no, even still, I guess...
...he was the one and only man
who didn't fear the Grand Line.
Back then, the Grand Line
was an unknown area,
from which not a single boat ever
returned after being swallowed up.
It was a sea of evil that people
feared and which few approached!
Old man. Give me more rum.
The whole bottle'll do.
You sure are drinking happily, Roger.
Of course I am. I'm just about to take
a little stroll into the Grand Line.
I'm excited beyond belief.
Whoa! You're going there?!
Into that sea of evil?!
What? Is there something
wrong with that?
No, not exactly, but...
Take my advice.
Forget about going there.
No one's ever come back!
That's why I'm going.
Now, then. Give me more rum.
A whole barrel'll do.
After saying that,
he drank the whole place dry,
then set sail all too
casually the next morning.
When I heard he had conquered
the Grand Line a bit later,
I was more happy
than I was surprised--
I was more excited than
I should have been at my age!
And then, 22 years ago today,
Roger died on the execution platform.
Ever since that day, everyone
proud of their great strength
has tossed their hat
into the pirate ring.
It marked the beginning
of the Great Pirate Era!
But now look! The town's full of
nothing but cowards and scum now!
Men crazy enough to challenge that
sea of evil are all but gone now!
That's why this bar is
closing down for good today.
I'm going to the Grand Line, too!
Huh?!
Gold Roger's so cool...
He's how a pirate should be!
That's why I set out to sea.
I'm gonna go to the Grand Line,
get the One Piece,
and be King of the Pirates!
Those're some mighty big words!
And in this bar, of all places!
I only said what I meant.
Kiddo! If there're still
patrons like you out there,
maybe I'll hold off on closing this place!
How should I know if there are?!
You're right!
Of course you wouldn't know!
I haven't been in such
a good mood since then!
I'll treat you to a drink!
I don't drink alcohol.
Right! Then have this!
Let's have a toast!
To the Eternal King of the Pirates!
You?!
That's certainly a warm hello...
...for a regular patron of yours.
Cut the crap! You're tryin'
to shut the place down!
It's wrong of you to
hold a grudge against me.
I only come here as a loyal customer.
It's the pirates' fault that
they're all cowards these days.
You had a customer? How rare.
I'd like a drink of rum...
There is no alcohol for you here!
Don't be so iron-hearted.
Today's a special day.
Wouldn't you agree?
That's the stuff...
Even now, I remember that day clearly...
How Roger looked at the very end...
This is Main Street!
Did Gold Roger walk through here, too?!
Yes...
It was a humid afternoon,
just like today...
His hands were shackled as
he was led down the main street
toward the town square,
where the execution platform stood...
Yet, he walked like
a triumphant general.
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger had attained everything
the world has to offer...
Even though he was
walking toward death,
he was literally
a king of great pride...
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
Do you have any last words?!
Take this off for me.
It's itchy beyond belief.
I can't do that!
Do you think I would run away?
You sure know how
to make a guy feel lonely.
All right, let's get
this over with quickly.
Hey, Pirate King!
Where did you hide
all the treasure you found?!
Is it in the Grand Line?!
You got it, didn't you?!
That legendary treasure!
--Shut up, you!
--That great treasure!
The One Piece!
My treasure?
Don't speak without permission!
If you want it, you can have it!
--Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
--Execution!
That's how it all began...
Hey!
A new wanted poster!
Put it up somewhere noticeable!
C-Captain Smoker!
Sorry for the rudeness, sir!
U-Umm...
That Straw Hat...
It was Monkey D. Luffy!
There it is...
So this is where the King
of the Pirates was executed...
The place where the
greatest pirate in history died...
The place where it began...
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Ahh! This is a town
for meeting pretty women!
Pretty women, indeed...
We can't relax! The marines
here are supposedly tough!
We just got here!
How about you?
Did you buy your swords?
That's the problem. In any case,
I gotta get me two more swords.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Kitetsu III and Yubashiri! Zoro's New
Swords and the Woman Sergeant Major"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!