ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
Blackbeard who acquired Whitebeard's
power now is in a standoff
with the Navy at the plaza!
Meanwhile, Luffy has collapsed
after Ace's death and...
...Jimbei rushes to the bay head
in order to help him escape!
Let's start with sinking
Marineford into water!
Shock Wave!
A building can easily be rebuilt!
But the island of Marineford is located
virtually in the center of the world!
To protect the people of the world who
are threatened by rampaging villains,
it is important to them that we are here!
Justice that comes from
humanity will never perish!
Don't claim to be able to
sink this place so lightly,
you little punk!
Well, then:
defend this place--if you can!
Destroy them!
Destroy them!!
What's this?!
I'll have an advantage once we
get to the sea! I can outrun him!
Oh no! It's frozen!
Sables!
You gotta protect the one you wanna protect!
Don't let them have their way!
What is that?! The ship came out of water!
That's a submarine!
Whose ship is that?
Put Straw Hat-ya on my ship!
"Straw Hat-ya"? That's really
a strange way to call somebody!
Who the hell are you, brat?!
I'm gonna help him get out of here.
Let me take care of him for now!
W-What?!
I'm a doctor!
"The Desperate Scream! Courageous
Moments that Will Change the Future"
Are you kidding me?! Doctors
don't carry swords!
Do you visit your patients by submarine?!
What's wrong?! Who is it?!
Trafalgar Law, a rookie from the North Blue!
What?!
That rookie must be Straw
Hat Luffy's accomplice whom
we weren't able to catch when
they had trouble with...
...the Celestial Dragons
in Sabaody Archipelago!
He came to save Luffy by submarine!
You're too slow! Hand him over already!
I said who the hell are you!?
Captain Law! Navy ships are
approaching off the stern!
Hurry up! Put those two on this ship!
I said "move out of my way"!
It's amazing that such rascal
pirates like you guys are...
...risking your lives to protect the son of
the worst criminal - the revolutionary, Dragon!
Stop undermining the wheels of justice!
Hound Blaze!
Stop Akainu here!
I won't let him lay a finger
on Ace's brother again!
Listen all Navy soldiers!
Split in two to go after the Whitebeards
and fight the Blackbeards!
Navy soldiers are coming
out from underground!
There were tunnels?!
We have backup! Great!
Let's get them at once!
Hey, Coby?! Aren't you feeling well?!
You're acting weird!
Only the man who reigns over
the Navy could do that!
"Buddha" Sengoku, very powerful.
But that's not enough to
defend the island against me!
Shut your big mouth already!
And be gone from Marineford!
--B-Blackbeard has...
--...Stopped the shock wave of Fleet Admiral!
Let me give you a hand, Captain!
W-What was that?!
Garp!
I'm a Navy soldier, too.
I have a duty to defend Marineford!
You washed-up old farts!
Take a good look!
Captain, we'll soon be in
range of the Navy ships!
Do something, Bepo!
What?! You're not Captain, you're a newcomer!
They're coming on this side too!
Finish them off with a barrage!
Fire! Fire!
Wh-What is this?!
This is...!
Blackbeard is using the
Tremor-Tremor Fruit power again!
The one he acquired from Whitebeard!
But it's way more powerful than before
when he destroyed the HQ building!
Not only the ground! The sky and
the sea... Everything is shaking!
What wonderful power!
I won't let you get away!
You can't go any further!
Not again!
Stop the Navy soldiers here! Let as many
of our people get away as possible!
No way! We won't let
even one of you get away!
You just put on another great show!
But I can't control the power very well yet!
Hey, Captain! If you aren't careful, we'll
lose the ground we're standing on, too!
Blackbeard, you bastard!
Whitebeard would be horrified to
know this punk is using his power!
How was it, "Buddha"
Sengoku?! Garp the hero?!
Do you think you can stop me?!
Your time ended with Whitebeard's death!
What will Blackbeard do next?!
--I'm scared!
--He's terrifying!
Urgent! After the earthquake
that hit Marineford,
a tsunami warning has issued for the
south shore of Sabaody Archipelago.
In order to avoid widespread panic, please
remain calm before taking any action.
Run!
Please evacuate to the north side -
the elevated area of Grove 40, 50.
Move! What are you doing?!
I'm a nobleman! I'll pay
you to let me go first!
Everybody, please stay cool.
The Pacifistas are getting
over the crack in the plaza!
Follow the Pacifistas! Don't
let the pirates get away! Go!
H-Hey!
You guys should go ahead and get on the ship!
But...
Did you forget Pops' order?!
We gotta get back to the New World
with as many alive as we can!
I got it!
Alright, stay with me!
We won't let you go! None of you can survive!
Pops, I'm sorry! I'm gonna disobey
your order for the first time!
I'm gonna die here!
Me, too! I'm gonna follow Pops to heaven!
Finally, it stopped shaking!
What's the matter with you?!
I don't know! I feel sad!
Sad?!
The voices disappear one by one in my head!
Huh? The voices?
--We'll show you the justice of the Navy!
--Is this what you call "justice"?!
Stop the Navy soldiers here!
No way! Destroy the pirates!
That's for my friend who
got killed in the war!
Damn pirates! Go to hell...
Let's teach them!
We're the ones that will conquer
the world, not the pirates!
I got one!
What are you talking about?!
Are you losing your mind?!
Get ahold of yourself!
H-Help me!
Run!
Coby! H-Hey! Where are you going?!
Let as many of our people escape as possible!
Stay with me! He's alive!
Let's get him treated!
I-I don't wanna die!
Forget about him! The war is not over yet.
But...
Now is our chance to show them
the power of our justice!
There's no time to help the wounded! Go!
Y-Yes, sir!
Corner the pirates! Destroy
them--to the last man!
Somebody, give me a hand! Somebody!
Destroy all the damn pirates!
The Navy soldiers are still motivated
even though we achieved the goal!
Guns don't work!
--Run!
--Chase them!
--Damn villains!
Something is not right! With either side!
We're not satisfied even though we won!
Damn!
Listen, guys!
As long as you're a Navy soldier, you
can't forgive those thugs, the pirates!
Curiel!
Admiral Sakazuki!
Hey, are you alright?!
H-Hey!
No one can stop me! I'm gonna
destroy and devour everything!
B-Blackbeard! He's pretty scary!
I gotta leave here as soon as possible!
Why don't you leave Straw Hat Luffy here?
Ugh! It's...!
--It's Kizaru!
--Get them on the ship!
Alright, I leave them
to you, Whoever You Are!
Do the best you can!
Catch them, Jean Bart!
Yeah, that's it!
Submerge!
How dare you get away from
us at Sabaody, Trafalgar Law?
He's severely wounded! Is he alive?!
Let's run!
Dammit!
Give it up!
That's enough!
A Navy soldier?
Coby!
Let's end this now!
Let's not fight anymore!
What is he doing?
S-Somebody...
H-Help me!
We're wasting people's lives!
Every single soldier has a family
that's waiting for him to come home!
We accomplished the purpose already
but we're still chasing the pirates
who have no will to fight!
We could stop but we're coveting more!
We're giving up on our soldiers
who could survive if we
treated them right away!
On top of that, we keep multiplying
the number of victims!
Soldiers who're gonna go down after this...
Is that Coby?
They're no more than fools!
Who are you, you fool?!
You've wasted my time!
We have no use for a soldier
who doesn't believe in justice!
Oh no, I'm dead! But I
said what I wanted to say!
I have no regret!
Coby!
Good job, you young Navy soldier.
The courageous moments that you
created by risking your life
just now have changed...
...the future of the world
tremendously - for better or worse.
Hurry up! Bring him inside!
Not a chance!
Don't do anything, Kizaru!
Oops, you're Benn Beckman!
Huh? That's...! The ship is...!
Let's go!
Why is one of The Four Emperors
from the New World here?!
"Red-Haired" Shanks!
I'm here to...
...end this war!
The "Red-Haired" Pirates have
appeared out of the blue!
Law tries to give Luffy a chance to escape
while the Navy catches their breath,
but the three admirals attack relentlessly.
Then Shanks reveals his real reason
for appearing on the battlefield...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Here Comes Shanks! The War
of the Best is Finally Over!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!