ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
Blackbeard who acquired Whitebeard's
power now is in a standoff with
the Navy at the plaza!
Meanwhile, Jimbei rushed to the bay
head carrying the unconscious Luffy
but they got attacked by Admiral Akainu!
Good job, you young Navy soldier.
The courageous moments that you
created by risking your life
just now have changed...
...the future of the world
tremendously - for better or worse.
I'm here to...
...end this war!
"Here Comes Shanks! The War
of the Best is Finally Over!"
"Red-Haired"! He is the one who
motivated Luffy to become a pirate!
There he is!
It's the Red Hair Pirates!
Prepare for surgery! Both of them
are bleeding uncontrollably!
We need to prepare for transfusions!
Captain, it's dangerous!
Sure, you can't often see The Four
Emperors but close the door already!
No way!
"Red-Haired" had a run-in with Kaido,
another one of The Four Emperors,
just yesterday in the New World!
And he made it here already?!
Sh... Shanks?!
Why the hell are you here?!
Buggy!
The straw hat?!
Give it back to Luffy!
Why should I?!
I refuse! I was just trying hard to fade out!
I don't wanna draw their attention anymore!
Oh no! That's too bad!
There's a treasure map
that I wanted to give you!
Really?!
Yes and it's a great one!
Yeah, right! Don't think that
I'm gonna fall for a deal
that is too good to be true!
Okay, then I gotta ask somebody else...
Al-Alright, hang on! I'm
gonna go give it to him!
Boss!
You haven't seen Luffy for 10 years.
Don't you wanna see him?
Yeah, maybe...
He got you good, boss!
Why are you laughing?!
That was so uncool! Why
didn't you fight them?!
No matter how many there are
or how strong they seem,
you're not men--or pirates - if you
laugh after something like that!
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
But... Shanks...!
Your arm!
It's only an arm. It's no big deal.
I'm just glad you're alright...
Yeah, I wanna see him.
Captain! Captain!
They're gonna attack us
if we don't submerge soon!
Please close the door!
Okay.
--Wait a minute!
--I can't wait anymore!
Oh no!
This was left behind! Here, catch it!
He threw something.
--This is...
--Captain, hurry up, hurry up!
Okay.
I wanna see him but...
I'll leave this hat with you.
Come bring it back to me someday!
Once you've become a great pirate!
That's our promise, Luffy!
If I see you now,
it means I fail to keep the
promise, doesn't it, Luffy?
Alright, let's do this.
This one's been shot through his
stomach and he's barely alive.
Straw Hat-ya is severely injured too but I
think there are more problems deep inside.
Do they need anesthesia?
No, they don't.
They're both so seriously
hurt that they can't feel any pain.
They don't have the energy to complain
no matter how drastic the remedy will be.
It's gonna be a fun operation!
"Red-Haired", you bastard! You
let Dragon's son get away!
Ice Age!
He's after the submarine!
The sea is gonna be frozen!
His pulse is steadying.
What's that?
It's an emergency! The water
is starting to turn into ice!
Oh no! Oh no!
If nothing is done, we're
gonna get caught, Captain!
Do something!
We'll submerge rapidly!
Did I lose him?
W-We made it!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
What is it this time?!
Let's go deeper--to the bottom of the sea!
It's gonna hit us! I'm sure
that it's gonna hit us!
Hurry up! At full speed!
Luffy!
--Damn! They're so persistent!
--It didn't hit them, did it?!
Ace's brother! Jimbei!
Luffy...
If they're still alive after this,
we have no choice but to let
them go and count them lucky!
Why is that Navy ship taking off on its own?
Hurry up! Go after the submarine!
But they went underwater
and I don't think that they could've
escaped the attacks from the admirals!
No, I'm sure that they're alive!
Listen to me!
Tell the Navy that, being a Warlord,
I will catch  and kill Straw
Hat Luffy at any cost!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
--But I don't know where we should go...
--Shut up and advance!
She's reckless but beautiful!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh...
What did you just say?!
You lied about the treasure map?!
Y-You bastard!
I just said that on the
spur of the moment, Buggy!
It's been awhile, huh?
Cut the "It's been awhile, huh?" crap!
Don't forget that I have a reason
to be mad at you, Shanks!
--What's that?
--Don't forget about it!
If you didn't surprise me at that time,
I wouldn't have lost the treasure
map and become a Devil Fruit eater!
Is that what happened?
Thank you for that great reaction.
I always hated that about you!
How could you made me work for
free as soon as we met again!
You said you were here to
stop the war or something
but I can start a war with
you right now if you want!
--Did you see that?
--Yes, I did.
He has such sass, even against
"Red-Haired" of The Four Emperors...
Captain Buggy!
We will follow you for the rest of our lives!
I understand so just relax.
Say what?!
But, wait a minute!
If I stay with them, I can
get off this island safely!
"Red-Haired"...
Marco.
Stop fighting back. Just
back out nice and easy.
"Hawk-Eye", where are you going?
I agreed to fight Whitebeard
but fighting "Red-Haired"
is not in the agreement.
It's time to quit.
If you continue desiring more and more,
it will just increase the damage
on both sides purposelessly.
Those of you who only want to fight more...
Bring it on! We're happy to fight you!
What do you think, Teach?
I mean, Blackbeard!
You're more handsome than ever, "Red-Haired".
Those scars look good on you.
Let's stop this, then!
I already got what I wanted.
And we're not ready to fight you guys yet.
Let's go, guys!
Everybody.
For now,
you need to do as I say!
Looks like our coverage of
the war will soon be over!
Whitebeard, Ace...
Let us handle the burial of those two.
The war was broadcast to the world.
I won't let you dishonor their
death in public any longer!
That's ridiculous!
We raise a shout of victory by exposing
their dead bodies to public view!
Vice Admiral is right!
Are you trying to bring
disgrace to our victory?!
We're not gonna listen to a pirate!
I agree!
Fleet Admiral-dono!
Only because it's you, I
allow it, "Red-Haired"!
But...!
I will take the blame on myself!
Thanks.
Treat the injured now!
This war is...
...over!
Those of you who are able, help the medics!
Carry for the seriously injured ones first!
Don't let anyone else die here!
Thus, the biggest war since the
beginning of the Great Pirate Era -
the War of the Best in Marineford has ended
and so it will be recorded in history.
The "War of the Best" has shattered
the balance of the world.
The end of the war becomes the sign
for the pirates to set out
upon the wave of a new era.
With the menace that was Whitebeard gone,
the seas are growing rough again.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Mighty Leaders Face Each Other
Down! Heralding the 'New Era'!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!