The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
What a huge town!
The place used to be full of pirates
on their way to the Grand Line.
I'm gonna go get some equipment!
Looks like I can get some nice
ingredients in a town this big.
Nice women, too!
I got something I wanna buy, too.
Oh? How're you gonna do that, Zoro?
--Alright! I'm gonna check
out the execution platform!
--Huh?
--Die!
--Yeah!
--Glasses... Glasses...
--Hey. Are these them?
Sorry to bother you!
Pay me back for those!
Perfect timing! Do you know how
to get to the execution platform?
Follow the smoke.
Let's have a toast!
To the Eternal King of the Pirates!
That Straw Hat...
It was Monkey D. Luffy!
The place where the
greatest pirate in history died...
And the place where
the pirate age began...
I'm gonna see the view the King
of the Pirates saw before he died!
Alright! Time to go up!
"Kitetsu III and Yubashiri! Zoro's New
Swords and the Woman Sergeant Major"
Captain Smoker!
Where are you going?!
The execution platform.
I wanna see the place where
the King of the Pirates died!
He will be there!
You mean the Monkey D. Luffy?!
We can mobilize
100 men immediately, sir!
And the entire battalion afterward!
You guys just don't get it.
I'm more than enough on my own.
Man, that's dangerous...
Hey.
Hey, boy.
What do you want?
I'm busy right now!
Are you the guy with the
biggest bounty in the East Blue?
I'm Luffy. Do you need something?
I'm Captain Smoker of the Navy.
I'm in charge of Loguetown.
You're under arrest.
Huh? Arrest? Forget it!
I'm just about to go into the Grand
Line and be King of the Pirates!
King of the Pirates?
I refuse to get arrested
in a place like this!
Then you'll have to beat me first.
You don't get into the Grand
Line unless you can beat me.
That's the rule of this town.
That's assuming you're brave
enough to fight me, of course.
I can't get into the Grand
Line unless I beat you?
Then I'll beat you!
Go ahead and try.
Gum-Gum...
He's made out of rubber?!
Darn it! My legs are tangled!
Just what the hell are you doing?!
I'm not doing this 'cause
I wanna! It's my legs...!
I'm unstuck!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Too slow!
Someone as pathetic as you,
worth 30 million Berries?
I don't even need to use
my Devil Fruit power.
My fists are more than enough!
Here I come!
22 years ago, I saw his execution.
His proud final moments were
worthy of the King of the Pirates...
You, King of the Pirates?
Don't make me laugh!
You can't even enter the Grand Line!
There's no point in getting back up.
There's no way to
know that unless I try!
Here goes! Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
U-Uh oh!
I really messed that up!
What's with that boy?
There you are,
my beloved mademoiselle!
Huh?
My damn mistake.
Please come again...
Huh?
Man, was she beautiful...
--Thank you!
--Sure!
Huh?!
--Oh! I'll take this, too!
--Thank you, sir!
What are they doing?
I knew it. The cards say that
detestable runt is already in this town.
The time for revenge
has flashily come at last!
So? Do you successfully take his life?
Obviously.
The one who dies is...
Oh. It's you!
Bonk!
Captain! W-We just saw--!
I sure flew a long way...
What was with that guy?
Now what do I do?
Guess I'll sleep for now!
--Hey, are you okay?
--Do you suppose he's dead?
You think?
Where exactly are we going?!
You broke my glasses.
I told you.
I'll pay you back... somehow.
You don't look like you
would have any money!
Something about you just seems off!
T-True, I don't have any money, but...
Those wrinkles between your eyes!
That look of having
eaten nothing for days!
Do you have a sick mother?!
Did your wife run out on you and
leave you with five babies to nurse?!
L-Look, you!
I won't ask for details!
Just come with me!
T-The navy?
Here.
The cleaning man just quit his job.
If you work for the navy, you'll
never need to worry about money!
You're a very lucky person!
Screw that! Why should
I work for the navy?!
You're just going to run off?!
You're insulting a person's kindness!
Maybe your poor spirit's more of
an issue than your money problem?!
Look, you!
Sergeant Major! It's time for training!
Bye! Please work hard, okay?
Sergeant Major?!
I bought a lot!
Maybe I'll hit another store!
The navy?
Dammit, how'd I get stuck doing this?!
Zoro's... working for the navy?
Just pretend you didn't see anything...
Damn it!
I'm gettin' nowhere like this!
Guess even three brushes is best!
Let me try again!
You! What are you doing here?!
I knew it! You are Pirate Hunter Zoro!
Why the hell are you in here cleaning?!
Intel has it you've teamed up
with Monkey D. Luffy's crew!
You're under arrest!
Well... now what?
What happened here?!
It seems someone attacked them!
There's no trace of whoever did it!
"For your glasses."
Man, that freaked me out...
Dammit! She looks
way too much like Kuina!
Not to mention she's
a swordsman, of all things...
The world sure is a big place.
But I doubt I'll ever see her again.
I'd like some swords.
Yes, yes! Welcome!
Have a look at anything you'd like!
Our shop's been in business
for 200 years, you see!
I got 100,000 Berries.
Sell me two swords.
Eh? Two swords for 100,000 Berries?
Damn, he has no money.
50,000 a sword'll only
get you some dull blades.
I'll make do with whatever.
I just don't got any money.
You'll make do with whatever?
Hmph! What an amateur!
That sword on his waist!
Could it be?!
O-Oh, h-h-hold on. L-L-Lemme
see that sword of y-y-yours!
What're you all fidgety for?!
J-Just let me see it!
Weirdo.
T-This really is it!
C-Calm down! This is your chance!
An absolute amateur waltzed
right in here with a legendary sword!
You need to act cool!
Wow, that's not a bad sword!
What do you say? I'll buy this
from you for 200,000 Berries.
Then you'll have 300,000 Berries total!
You could get three good
swords at 100,000 apiece!
Huh?! What're you talking about?!
A-Alright! I-I can make it
250,000! No, 300,000!
500,000?
Look. Raise the price all
you want, this sword isn't--
Alright, then! I'll buy it
from you for 650,000 Berries!
Fine, you damn professional!
How does 800,000 Berries sound?!
Hello!
Did you finish polishing my Shigure?
Thank goodness! You're all right!
Someone went on a rampage
at the navy outpost earlier.
You were gone too, so I was worried!
--She's a royal-class dimwit...
--Thank goodness! What a relief...
But the fact that you're
here safe and sound...
...means you actually scoffed
at my kindness and ran off!
Here's your money back.
I can't accept money from
someone who's heartless.
Besides, I bought some new glasses!
Is this sword the Wado Ichimonji?!
It is the Wado Ichimonji!
Wado?!
Don't say it! Don't say it!
What a beautiful straight temper line!
I believe it's one of the 21
O-Wazamono swords!
See! Look at this! It's worth
no less than 10 million Berries!
But what are you doing
with such a legendary sword?
Curse you! You just
had to blurt it all out!
I'm suing for obstruction of business!
O-Obstruction of business?
I'm sorry! Did I say something wrong?
You're here for your Shigure,
right?! I'm done polishing it!
Take it and get the hell out!
Why did you run straight into those?!
I-I'm sorry.
That dumb girl saved you!
It's true, that sword's
so legendary it'd be a waste
for a guy who doesn't know
its value to walk around with it.
All the swords in that barrel
are 50,000 Berries apiece!
Just take whatever two you want!
What's he so mad about?
You must really like swords,
carrying three of them around!
That's almost like this one
bounty hunter out there!
Bounty hunter, huh?
He's famous! His name is Roronoa!
I hear the name a lot.
Yes. He's a famous swordsman
all throughout the East Blue,
but he's a notorious person!
Using swords as bounty-hunting
tools is unforgivable!
Why is evil so strong in this era?
All the famous sword masters
are pirates or bounty hunters...
And almost all of the world's
legendary swords are in their hands.
It's a real shame...
I dunno, maybe everyone has
their own circumstances and stuff?
All jobs need to keep up
with the times somehow.
In any case, with my Shigure,
I'm going to polish
my skills as a swordsman
and someday gather
all the legendary swords
that are in the hands of
criminals throughout the world!
The 21 Top O-Wazamonos,
the 21 O-Wazamonos,
and the 50 Ryo-Wazamonos...
I'll risk my life for them!
You gonna take this sword, too?
The Wado Ichimonji, was it?
No, it's not that I want
legendary swords...
I'm just saying I don't like
them being in criminals' hands!
This sword...
That sword! I think it's...
I thought so! Kitetsu III!
It's the Kitetsu III!
Its predecessor, the Kitetsu II,
is an O-Wazamono sword,
and the Kitetsu I before that is
listed as a Top O-Wazamono sword!
Mister! Is this sword
really 50,000 Berries?!
Y-Yeah...
Incredible! It's a respectable
Wazamono, you know!
That one! You have to choose that one!
It normally goes for one million Berries!
You absolutely have to choose it!
N-No! I can't sell it!
Yeah! Selling this for
50,000 Berries is clearly strange!
No, that's not what I mean!
A cursed sword, huh?
You knew?!
No. I can just tell.
Starting with the very first one,
all the Kitetsu have been superior
swords, but every last one is cursed!
Many famous master
swordsmen have met tragic deaths
after taking up Kitetsu swords.
These days, there ain't a single
person who uses a Kitetsu.
Because you'll leave this world
even if you use them unknowingly!
Even I wanna get rid of that thing,
but I'm afraid it'll curse me...
I-I'm sorry! I had no idea it
was such a terrifying sword!
I should've minded my own business!
I like it! I'll take it!
A-Are you a fool?! I can't sell it!
If you die because of it, then
it'd be like I killed you myself!
You're the fool!
Just sell the stupid thing off!
Honey!
Then let's do this.
My luck, and this thing's curse...
Let's see which one's stronger.
You can't be serious!
Stop! Its sharpness is the real deal!
It'll take your whole arm off!
I'll take it.
Hey. Could you choose me another one?
S-Sure...
H-Hold it!
The make is black lacquer...
...and the blade's
temper pattern uneven!
The Ryo-Wazamono "Yubashiri"!
My shop may not be much,
but this is the finest sword I have!
I can't buy that. I already
told you, I got no money.
Forget the money. And I don't
need any for the Kitetsu, either.
I'm sorry for trying to cheat you earlier.
It's been a while since I've
seen a good swordsman's eyes.
They say the sword chooses the owner.
I pray for your good fortune!
I definitely feel more
relaxed with three swords.
Oh, what's this?
I can't believe a big skinflint like
you gave the family treasure away!
What's wrong with one man
entrusting a dream to another?!
Now take out the damn trash!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I was so frightened...
that I still can't stand up...
What a nice nap!
Alright! Time to go
to the execution platform!
--Found him?!
--No, not yet!
Are you sure it was
Straw Hat you saw?!
Yes! We're sure!
Alright! Scour the place again!
Yes, sir!
Man, where is the execution platform?
Straw Hat, Straw Hat...
I have no idea at all!
Where's the bastard hiding?!
Where is it?
You see him?!
Where's the execution platform?
--That way.
--Thanks!
That was...!
Find Luffy! He's gotta be hiding
somewhere in Loguetown still!
Yes, sir!
How many times do I have
to tell you not to shout?
He won't hide.
As long as I'm around,
he'll show up again.
Captain Smoker!
Did something happen?!
Tashigi! Where the hell'd you go?!
C-Captain! We have news!
It's you guys! Thank goodness!
You're conscious again!
I-It was Roronoa Zoro...
We were attacked by Zoro,
the pirate hunter!
Zoro?
Why would he attack you?
He will show up.
I will make it to the
execution platform!
I'm gonna get another look at
the view the King of the Pirates saw!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Apparently, Usopp's
gonna be in a showdown!
Is he crazy?! There's no way
he can beat him! He'll die!
Who's "him"?
The greatest gunslinger
bounty hunter there is.
Cool! Must be thanks
to the wanted poster!
Hold on, Usopp! Where are you
going with all that stuff?!
Is he running away?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Usopp vs. Daddy the Parent;
Showdown at High Noon"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!