ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the War of the Best against the Navy,
Luffy is consumed with sorrow.
Meanwhile, there is an untold story of the
brothers Luffy and Ace from 10 years ago.
"To The Sea Someday! The
Pledge of the Three Brats!"
Here I come!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Now tell me...
What are you doing?!
One point!
I won't lose a fight!
And I will...
I wanna get stronger!
I'm gonna get stronger and I will...
I win, Sabo!
Dammit!
Damn! It's always a close
match between Ace and Sabo!
Sabo! You gotta fight me next!
Shouldn't you run?! I have no mercy!
Gum-Gum...
"Gum" again?
...Shield!
That's just stretching your fingers...
How interesting is this?
N-N-No, stop it!
Like I keep saying,
is there any point in having that power?
Dammit! It's not working! It was so close!
One more time!
No! The rule is only 100
matches per person a day.
Wait until tomorrow.
Luffy lost 50 times to me and Ace.
Me vs. Ace is 24 - 26.
I lost by 2. Dammit!
You guys! When I become 10 years
old, I'll beat you two up!
We'll be 13 then. Let's go
get something for dinner.
Okay, let's go for crocodiles!
I love crocodile meat!
Luffy, don't get eaten this time.
You were okay the last time
because you were swallowed whole.
You wait here, Luffy. You can't
swim so you'd slow us dow...
Crocodile meat!
--What?!
--I said "wait"!!
The harsh environment of Mt. Corvo
made them stronger day by day.
On the north side of this mountain,
there is the place where all uncertain
things end up called Gray Terminal.
And on the north side of the Terminal,
there is a city with a solid stone
wall that doesn't let anyone enter.
The only entrance to the city
is called the Great Gate
through which twice daily passes mountains
of junk from all over the country.
--Oh, here they come!
--let's go treasure hunting!
Residents of Gray Terminal visit the city
sometimes to sell recycled products.
Hey wait! What's in that package?
It's a crocodile-skin. I'm here to sell it.
Crocodile?
G-Go ahead!
Beyond the Great Gate, there is a boulevard
where all passersby can be clearly seen
and then there is Edge Town.
Edge Town - where all the thugs and
gangsters from the city hang out.
Hey, pops! Leave your package here!
Hey, why don't you say something?!
Shut up, you punk.
What?!
Y-You little...
When you mug somebody,
be careful who you pick!
Th-They are the...
Let's do this!
--Okay!
In the middle of the walled city,
there is another high stone wall
which encloses High Town where
royalty and nobles live.
The name of this country is the Goa Kingdom.
There is no garbage on streets
and it is said
to be the most beautiful country in the East Blue.
Windmill Village where Luffy was born...
...is the part of the kingdom even
though it's a forgotten backwater.
DOWNTOWN
I'm glad they paid so much for the skin!
We got more for the "pirate savings"!
I'm hungry!
Just a little longer. We'll
have great ramen noodles!
What is ramen? Is it really good?
Whatever's fine! I wanna eat soon!
FINE DINING EIICHIRO
This is the restaurant!
Hi, may I help you?
W-W-Wait a minute!
What are you doing?! People
like you are not allowed here!
The VIP room will do.
Th-That mark is...!
We're so honored to have a noble
like you come to our restaurant!
We'll prepare a room right away!
That thing is pretty handy!
Yeah, I found it on the street a while ago.
Here are 3 ramen noodle bowls!
Thank you for waiting!
Enjoy your meal!
This is ramen?!
It looks good!
Well, try it.
Yum-yum!
Yeah, it is good!
I want more!
I need more. 3 more ramen noodles!
Yes, sir! Here they are!
More please!
Y-Yes, sir!
More!
Y-Yes, sir! Right away!
Next!
May I come in?
M-Manager!
Are you sure?!
Sir, we need to talk!
--Damn, they found out!
--Let's go!
They didn't pay!
Catch them, somebody!
--The ramen noodles were great!
--I told you!
--Catch them?!
--They're only kids!
I-It's them again! They're such
pests! Why were they let in?!
Don't let them run away!
Somebody catch those 3 kids!
I can't believe that they
jumped out of the window!
This is the 4th floor!
We lost 26 bowls of ramen
noodles and a window!
M-Manager! They left a note!
TREASURE TAB - LUFFY
"Treasure tab"?!
Sabo?
That must be Sabo! Wait!
You're alive!
Let's go home!
Hey, Sabo! He's calling you!
Who is that?
He confused me with someone else. Let's go!
W-Wait!
Sabo...
What?! I'm not hiding anything!
Oh, you aren't?
Yes, you are! Tell us, Sabo!
We can't have secrets among us!
--Tell us!
I said that I'm not hiding...
Tell us, you bastard! Or I'll beat you up!
Alright, I'll tell you!
The son of a noble?!
--Who is it?
I am!
--And?
You two asked me first!
The truth is, both of my parents are alive.
So I'm not an orphan and I didn't
grow up in the Gray Terminal.
The man who called to me today was...
...my father.
I was lying to you guys. I'm sorry.
He said "sorry" so we gotta forgive him.
Let's hold off on forgiveness -
it all depends on your motive.
Why were you living there if
you are from a noble family?
The reason I ran away was...
Listen, Sabo.
You must acquire intelligence and
knowledge that you'll need as a noble
and become a man that can marry
a woman from the royal family.
Then, we will live in security and
I'm sure that you will live happily!
Are you sure that if I could marry
a royal woman, I'll live happily?
I'm sure!
Yes, Sabo!
Okay!
I'll do it!
What?!
The cargo ship has sunk?!
I don't give a damn about the crew!
What are you gonna do about the
cargo that I paid for? Huh?
Hello?! Hello?!
--Clank.
--Damn!
Such a great loss! By thunder!
Dad!
DAD
Look at this! I drew it!
I'm exhausted from work, Sabo.
If you have time to draw this,
you ought to be studying instead.
Hey, you!
I'm from the royal family!
Which means I'm related to the king!
Carry me by piggyback to my house!
Stop, you rude jerk!
Hey, are you gonna ignore my royal order?!
Let me go!
You're just the son of some noble family!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Don't!
It's unforgivable to harm a
child of the royal family!
Sabo! Did you really have a fight
with this royal boy?!
Yes, I did!
Because he attacked me with
a knife all of a sudden...
I'm sorry! Did you get hurt?!
I'm so sorry!
Let's take him to a doctor
to get checked out!
Can we please settle this matter peacefully?!
They love those who can maintain their
status and defend their property.
Not me!
If I can't marry a woman from
the royal family, I'm worthless!
That's why they made me study
and take culture lessons.
And they were arguing everyday
because I wasn't doing well.
I had no place to be in that family!
I'm sorry for both of you but I was
all by myself even if I had parents!
I heard that you sneak out
and go somewhere sometimes.
I don't think you do but do you
ever go to the Gray Terminal!
We nobles are privileged to live
in the High Town with
the king and his family.
Those residents there and we nobles
are living in different worlds!
It's you again.
If you walk around a place like this,
you might get robbed and killed someday!
Let me hear the stories again!
About countries across the sea
that you guys have seen or visited!
--You're a strange kid!
--Come and sit down.
Uh-huh!
Nobles have a low opinion
of the Gray Terminal
but it's better than the stifling High Town
where your life has been
arranged for years to come!
I see.
Ace! Luffy!
We gotta set out to sea someday!
Let's get out of this
country and live freely!
I wanna see the world out there
and write a book about it!
I'm happy to study if it's about sailing!
Let's become stronger and
become pirates someday!
I'm gonna become one - you
don't have to tell me to!
I'm gonna become a pirate and
defeat others and become infamous!
It'll be the only proof of my life!
It doesn't matter if all the people
in the world reject me or despise me,
I'll become a great pirate
and show them what I can do!
I won't run from anybody or lose to anyone!
Because I'm feared or hated or whatever,
my name will be known all over!
I got it! Alright then...!
I'm gonna become...!
You fool... I was wondering
what you'd have to say...
You're funny, Luffy!
I can't wait to see how you
turn out in the future!
We can all become pirates
but isn't it a problem that
we all wanna become captain?
I wasn't expecting that.
Sabo, I thought that you'd wanna
be navigator on my ship.
You guys can come aboard my ship!
--No thanks!
Huh?! Come on!
Come aboard! I said "come
aboard", so you gotta do it!
--That will never happen!
--Yeah, never!
What did you say?!
But that's okay.
What's that?!
Man, you're funny, Luffy!
Well, let's just leave
it until the time comes.
Maybe we'll set out independently.
Oh, you stole that from Dadan!
Did you guys know?!
We can become brothers if we
exchange this cup of sake!
Brothers? Really?!
When we become pirates, we
might not be on the same ship
but our brotherhood will always be with us!
Wherever, whatever, we'll
always be bonded together!
So from now on,
we're brothers!
Yeah!!
Dreaming of the day when they'll
take to the seas as pirates,
Luffy and his friends polish
up their bad-boy skills.
Then, when an attack by a certain character
threatens their peaceful lives,
the three boys are forced to say
goodbye to the Dadan family.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Leaving the Dadan Family for Good?!
The Kids' Hideout Has Been Built!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!