The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Don't be stupid! You'll lose your arm!
Its sharpness is the real deal!
I'll take it.
Find Luffy! He's gotta be hiding
somewhere in Loguetown still!
Yes, sir!
There's no need.
He will show himself to me again.
The execution platform!
I wanna see the view the King
of the Pirates saw before he died!
I wanna see it now!
But... which way is
the execution platform?
"Usopp vs. Daddy the Parent;
Showdown at High Noon"
Captain Smoker!
Is this man named Luffy
really still on this island?!
We need to hurry and blockade the sea!
That won't be necessary.
How can you be so easygoing?!
--Stop!
--Hey! You can't come in here!
That's the navy captain's room!
--Heya, Smoker.
--So it's you, Daddy...
These are Two-Pistol Pete and
the Police-Killer Riley Brothers.
All three have bounties, huh?
I also dropped one off at the morgue.
I just need your signature
and I can get my money today.
One million Berries for four people?
These are all small fries...
Wanted men headed for the
Grand Line gather in this town.
I can earn money
more efficiently this way,
rather than looking high
and low for just one big name.
One of the Navy's most gifted snipers,
reduced to bullying weaklings.
How you've fallen...
I just don't feel like putting
my life in my guns' hands.
Because if you die, your
daughter'll wind up on the street?
Give Carol my regards.
Yeah. I'll tell her the
old smoky man said hello.
That was Daddy Masterson,
the bounty hunter?
Yeah. We joined at
the same time, long ago.
He was an elite, on the fast track
to being a key player at Navy HQ.
Then why is he doing this now?
A cursed sword, huh?
Interesting.
Oh! That's a cool sword you have!
Damn! Don't scare me like that!
What're you doing here, Zoro?
--No, what're you doing here?
--Me?
I'm lost.
Why're you acting cocky about that?!
--Hey, tell me.
--Hey! There he is!
--How do I get to the execution platform?
--It's him! That bastard!
--What's that?
--You bastard!
How dare you sell our
buddies to the Navy?!
You're gonna pay big-time!
Die!
Run on home and have your
mama bake you a cake, kiddo.
That old guy's cool!
I think that man might be...
...Daddy the Parent.
I bought a lot! A real lot!
Now my preparations to be a brave
warrior of the sea are complete!
All I'm forgetting now is...
Oh, yeah! I forgot
the most important thing!
Goggles!
A top-class sniper needs
to have top-class goggles!
That's just basic! The most basic of all!
Investing every last bit of money
to get the best goggles around
is the spirit of a top-class sniper!
Goggles! Goggles!
These ones! These goggles!
It's gotta be these! I like 'em!
Lady!
You got a good eye! Them's the
latest North Blue model there!
I got 'em from an import ship that
leaves the Navy only once a year!
What's wrong? You got no money?
I don't do business with
people who don't got money!
What's it gonna be?!
N-No, it's...
Oh! Right! Backpack, backpack...
I'll take these goggles, please!
My! What a cute little girl!
Yes, yes! You're in luck!
This is the only pair
of these goggles in town!
Hold it right there!
I was the first to--!
Butt out... old man!
O...
Old man?
Stop! Stop right there, you!
Listen! Let's set the record
straight! I am not an old man!
Call me "Mister"! Got it?
Huh?! What for?! You're an old man!
Dammit, you said it again!
Gimme those goggles back!
I found 'em first!
Huh?!
You got a problem?! Huh?!
Keep up yer damn complainin'
and I'll call the marines!
M-Marines?
Yep! I'm friends with
a navy captain in this town!
The old smoky man!
W-Who is this girl?
So you don't know who I am, huh?!
I'm Great Captain Usopp! I destroyed
Arlong's fishman pirate group!
It was truly a battle to the death!
Me, surrounded by 200--
no, 300 fishmen!
All alone, I punched, threw, stomped,
kicked, and tore them all up!
Thanks to that, I now have a
30 million Berry bounty on my head!
I see. 30 million...
Yep! That's right!
--Papa!
--Papa?! Why am I your papa?!
Here's a present for you, Papa!
Happy birthday!
Oh, Carol...
What a nice, angelic girl you are!
I love you, Carol-chan!
Papa! I love you, Papa!
W-What's with this family?
But guess what! That old man there
is trying to swipe your present!
Now, now! You mustn't say "swipe"!
It's not good manners, you know.
Are you the one who's
bullying my adorable Carol?
B-B-Bullying...?
--That's not all!
--Huh?
You have a bounty of
30 million Berries, I hear?
Let's see here...
Are those the new wanted posters?
Yeah, I got 'em from
the outpost just now...
600,000... 1,300,000... 700,000...
30 million... Straw Hat Luffy?
A starting bounty at this amount...
Hold it, boy.
Y-Y-Yes?!
No, you see, sir!
I'm obviously not the person
on that poster! I was just lying!
My funny plan to trick people was
a great success! Ha ha! Well, bye!
That's you, isn't it?
T-T-That's right!
It sure is! That's me, all right!
But I'll tell you this!
Just you try and lay a hand on me!
My captain Luffy won't sit by quietly!
He's an evil,
cold-blooded, devilish man!
No one's ever defied him
and lived to tell about it!
You got a kid, right?
You should really value your life...
I see. That sounds bad.
Yes, given that this Luffy
fellow is worth 30 million Berries,
he's clearly no ordinary man.
Papa! You're obviously
way stronger, Papa!
You're the strongest guy in the world!
Carol. It's all right.
All that matters is that I make
enough money to live happily with you.
You're far more important to me
than being the world's greatest!
Papa...
The guy's wimping out
after I said all that!
Alright! In that case...!
Well?! Now do you see
how terrifying I am?!
Take my advice! Just hand
those goggles over to me!
Huh?!
Don't worry! I'll pay for 'em!
So just give 'em here!
Why're you saying that right after
he's just about to let you go--?!
--Papa?
--Then let's do this.
I assume you have no problem
with us settling this in a fair fight?
--Fight?
--Here!
Fight? Y-You're not
talking about a duel, right?
If you win, the goggles are yours.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6... 30 pistols?!
D-Don't tell me you're...
...Daddy the Parent?!
The very same.
--A showdown!
--There's gonna be a showdown!
Daddy the Parent's
gonna duel somebody!
Did he say Daddy the Parent?
Daddy the Parent is the
greatest gunslinger bounty hunter!
Everyone in the East Blue knows that!
I wonder what the idiot who'd
challenge him to a duel looks like!
Oh. Like that.
Good luck, Long-nose!
Don't worry if he beats ya!
We already got a place dug for ya!
H-How did things turn out
this way? Am I an idiot?!
The rules are simple. We both
walk 10 paces and then shoot.
--Y-Yeah...
--What are you doing?!
Nami!
Fighting Daddy the Parent
in a duel... Are you an idiot?!
S-Shut up! Things just turned
out this way! Shut up and watch!
You get one shot. Are you ready?
--Yeah.
--Yeah...
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
This is bad... Really bad...
There's no way I can possibly
beat Daddy the Parent...
Six!
Am I going to die here?!
This can't be happening!
Seven!
I just started my adventure!
I haven't even gained any courage
or manliness or anything yet!
Eight!
Bye, now!
Papa! You're amazing, Papa!
You're so cool!
--Man, how pathetic.
--What a lame duel.
I thought he'd have more guts
than that. What a disappointment.
I only shot his gun away.
What's with you?!
Tryin' to cheat like that!
You coward! Weakling!
Can't you even fight honestly?!
I-I'm sorry! Forgive me!
I'm just a lowly, pathetic man!
Taking the life of someone like
me wouldn't gain you anything!
Right?! Right?!
Couldn't you just peacefully let me go?
--W-Wait!
--Nami!
Y-Yeah! If it's money you
want, she has tons of it!
Just please don't shoot me!
Please spare my life!
Hold on, now!
Oh? So you're trying
to hide behind a woman?
In any case--!
No! Forget what I just said!
She's just an innocent bystander
who has nothing to do with this!
Even if I wind up getting shot,
I can't let her get caught up in this!
--Usopp...
--Please! I beg you!
"Usopp..."
Is your name Usopp, boy?
Yeah.
It couldn't be...
Do you know a man named
Yasopp of the Red-Haired Pirates?
Yasopp? That's my old man's name.
Y-You've met my dad before?!
I see. So you are his son...
Papa?
I've never once told a soul
what happened on that day...
But you're an exception.
It happened at a hot, dry
port town, much like this one.
Let's do it, Ensign Masterson!
We each get one shot!
One! Two! Three!
--He won!
--Yasopp won!
Check it out! He beat one
of the Navy's best snipers!
That was truly a close fight!
You're the man, Yasopp!
Yeah.
Yasopp! Finish him!
Yeah! Killin' the loser of
a duel is a sign of kindness!
Kill me! Now that I've lost a duel,
I have no reason to live...
Yeah. You've got good resolve.
What are you doing?
Your daughter?
Give it back...
A navy ensign of all people,
carefully treasuring something like this...
She must be really spoiled.
Don't lecture me, you filthy pirate!
That's fine by me!
You were great, Yasopp!
It was nothin'.
The pain of this wound just goes
to show how inexperienced I am.
You took on Daddy Masterson!
You won because you're you!
We never would've stood a chance...
Thanks, Boss!
I appreciate your watching
the duel without saying anything!
That's the stuff!
You want some, Ensign?
Family, huh?
Family's not so bad.
But I'm no good at it.
Huh?
I got a son of my own.
His name's Usopp.
Haven't seen him in years now.
I hit the high seas around
the time he was a toddler.
Why? Do you not love your son?
It wasn't about that.
A pirate flag...
A Jolly Roger was calling for me.
You tell 'im, Yasopp!
Now, then...
There's nothing I can do for my son.
Just one hopeless
parent like me is too many!
Always stay by your daughter's side.
You can't let her feel lonely.
Though I'm in no position to talk!
I lost our duel!
Yasopp! Finish me off!
Don't give me your lousy sympathy!
Forget it!
You navy guys might hang us by
our necks right after you catch us,
but we pirates are free to let you
live or die however we please!
So long!
So that's why a navy elite
turned to bounty-hunting...
Papa! You lost to a pirate,
Papa?! He spared your life?!
Say it isn't true, Papa!
But that's amazing!
Your dad must be really skilled!
He even beat Daddy!
Plus he hadn't forgotten about you!
Even now,
when he's living an adventure,
he has an image of you
etched in his memory!
Usopp?
Yeah. I can understand
how you'd feel...
No! That's not why...
That's not why I'm crying!
Would you normally do that?!
Would you normally tell
some pathetic boy like me
a story about you shamelessly
having your life spared?!
You told me that to give me courage!
Most people would be vain
and keep a story like that secret!
You told me even though you
knew it'd make you less cool!
Regardless of how brave my
old man might be! Right?!
Weaklings or cowards
could never do that!
Carol! Your dad is
the bravest man alive!
You can find strong guys any old place!
But I've never seen a man as
strong and kind as your dad before!
I... I can't give in, either! I gotta
be brave, or I'll shame your dad!
Daddy! Give me a chance!
Fight me in another life-or-death match!
I won't cheat anymore!
All right. This will be our real match.
Choose the weapon
you're most skilled with.
Good. Now, then. Let's see...
Try and hit that weathervane.
Weathervane? That?!
Miss it, and...
Y-Yeah! You can shoot
me right through the heart!
Usopp!
My life is on the line for real this time!
There's...
There's no way he can
shoot that far with that thing...
J-Just like always...
Just shoot like you always do...
Yeah...
Concentrate...
You missed!
No, Papa! Don't shoot him! Papa!
I can't shoot him. Usopp shot
right through its crown!
H-He really did!
Right through the crown!
Usopp!
You're an excellent shot.
I'd expect no less of Yasopp's son.
Never forget that bravery.
Someday you will
become like your father!
Go to the Grand Line.
I'm certain Yasopp is there.
Daddy...
You're pretty good, old man!
Aren't these...
It's okay! So long!
--Papa!
--Carol, you know that's not right.
It's poor manners to say, "So long!"
Yeah! I'm sorry, Papa!
I'm going to grow up to be a nice
lady worthy of being your daughter!
So forgive me!
You're already plenty
nice as you are now!
--I'm going to be an even nicer lady!
--Even when people say he's a
disgrace behind his back now,
he's fought all this time
to protect the one he loves.
I'm going to be a
brave man like Daddy, too!
I'm gonna become a real warrior
and stand before my dad someday!
I'm certain of it!
Sanji! I've been looking for you, Sanji!
For ten years!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
They're saying there's
a cooking contest!
Huh? Cooking techniques aren't
meant for competing against people!
They're for delighting Nami-san!
Thanks, Sanji-kun!
What? You're not gonna enter?
You get that if you win, right?
Wait, that's... an elephant bluefin tuna!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Fiery Cooking Battle?
Sanji vs. the Beautiful Chef"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!