The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
I've been looking all over for you, Sanji!
Hm?
For ten years!
Her name is Carmen.
She's the No. 1 cook in the East Blue.
I'm a woman of passion!
People call me Fiery Carmen.
Ole!
And, I'm Carmen-sama's
first apprentice, Leo!
I'm her second apprentice, Jose!
"Fiery Cooking Battle?
Sanji vs. The Beautiful Chef"
Wow! How beautiful you are!
Say what?!
To think that you've looked all over
for me...! What a lucky man I am!
I'm honored to meet you, Carmen-san!
Don't you dare...!!
What a passionate woman you are...
B... But, Carmen-san,
have we met befo...?
Jose!! Leo!!
Explain it to him.
Yes, Ma'am.
Please have a look at this.
Hm? What're these?
They're all cooks...
Yes!!
They're all famous,
skilled cooks in the East Blue.
Every single one of them competed
against Carmen-sama and lost.
That's right! I'm the
No. 1 cook in the East Blue.
Those cooks who challenge me
are all disappointing cowards.
I thought that I no longer had
any rivals in the East Blue.
However...!
I came across a feature on
the Sea Restaurant Baratie
from when you still worked there.
That cook said that the Sous Chef
there is the No. 1 cook in the East Blue.
He said that you were an excellent cook
and that we were no match for you!
Since then, I've kept
looking all over for you...
searching every nook and cranny
of the East Blue... for ten long years...!
It's actually been ten days, though...
Carmen-sama likes to exaggerate.
Keep your big mouths shut!!
I challenge you, Sanji!
Come to the Cooking Championship
at the market at one this afternoon!
I'll defeat you for sure at
that championship! Got that?!
Well, then! We'll see you later!
Ah, Carmen-san...
What a passionate woman she is!
Young man, are you going to
participate in the competition?
Huh? No, I'm not interested
in things like that, so...
Damn...! That damn
detestable Straw Hat!
To think that we can't find him despite
looking all over for him like this...
But Captain, why in the heck do
we have to wear cloaks like this?
Don't you know anything
about being a pirate?!
There's an annoying Navy captain
named Smoker in this town.
If he finds us, my plan to get revenge
on that Straw Hat will be ruined!
Anyhow!
Hurry up and find that Straw Hat!
Got that?!
Man, I'm stuffed!
We have to eat good
before we leave Loguetown.
I was starving.
To be honest, so was I.
I was hungry, but I didn't have money.
I'm glad that I ran into you.
Hm? If you mean money,
I don't have any.
--What?!
--You don't have money?
Of course I don't!
That's true.
But, really... that Straw Hat
is an annoying bastard!
Next time I see him, I'll crush him!
Then how're we going to pay for this?
I can't let him off the hook!
I wonder if they'd let us off the hook...
There's no way I can!!
Oh, lucky!
Hey, you're going to treat us? Thanks!
Ahhh...
Thanks again!
Thanks for treating us.
You're... welcome...
Thanks for coming!
Thanks!
That voice...?!
Oh, yeah! It was that Straw Hat guy.
Uhh... Anyone home...?
You flashy idiot!!
Go after him already!!
Yes, sir!
Wh-Which way did he go?
A market, huh?
Whoa!
Just as you'd expect from Loguetown!
They have far better quality and more
kinds of seafood than other places!
Hm?
This is premium!
You have a good eye, young man!
Those're coastal fish
caught just this morning.
Coastal fish?
It's true that they're firm and fresh,
but I've never seen fish like this before.
Were they really caught in the East Blue?
Hmm... You're really knowledgeable.
As you noticed, these're fish that
you can catch only in the West Blue.
It's just expected that East Blue
people don't know this fish.
West Blue? Why do you
call them costal fish then?
Young man, I bet you've
never been here before.
Huh? Yeah...
It may be because Loguetown is
the closest town to the Grand Line,
but we can sometimes catch fish from the
other seas, in addition to the East Blue.
From the other seas...?
That's right. They probably get
mixed in crossing ocean currents.
That's something that often happens here.
Hm?
Oh... sounds like they caught something.
Wanna go see it?
What's going on?!
Wha...?! This is...!
Amazing! That's an
elephant bluefin tuna!
That's right! It probably got
mixed in from the southern ocean.
I caught it with a pole and line!
A pole and line?!
Elephant bluefin tuna...
Ah!
Look at this!
It's a weird looking fish!
What're you doing with the illustrated
food reference book? Studying?
That's the elephant bluefin tuna.
What? You know this fish?
Of course! That's a miracle
food called a gem of the ocean.
I've never seen it though.
Of course not, since it's
a fish from the South Blue.
You never see it in the East Blue,
but it's a different story
if there's the All Blue.
Now that's impossible.
Yeah, I know.
What's the All Blue?
It's a legendary sea. I hear that fish
from all over the world swim there.
Stop it. He's a kid.
He'll take it seriously.
Where is it?
See? He doesn't get jokes.
That was a joke, Sanji.
There's no way such a thing exists.
Don't worry about it.
Just keep studying.
All Blue...
Okay, then, haul it away.
--Okay!
--H-Hold on a second!
--Hm?
--How much is it?! Sell it to me!
What?!
I've got money! Let me buy it! Please!
No, you can't! This isn't for sale!
It's been decided just now that
this is going to be a prize. Sorry.
A prize...?
That's right.
The annual Cooking Championship
will be starting a little later today.
Cooks from all over the East Blue
gather for this competition.
This'll be given to the winner.
After all, this is an
elephant bluefin tuna.
It's exactly what a champion deserves.
So we decided to give it as a prize.
If you really want it,
you should participate.
You're a cook, aren't you?
Y-Yeah...
The registration is over there.
If you're interested, go register.
Hurry up or it'll close soon, young man.
See ya!
A cooking competition, huh?
All right, then!
Huh...? Wait a second...
I challenge you, Sanji!
Oh, well...
Now, the annual Cooking Championship
festivities are about to start!
We have famous cooks from
around the East Blue gathered here!
What a crowd!
I wonder what's going on...
This year's prize is
an elephant bluefin tuna!
It's a treasure of the
ocean and miracle food!
Who will earn the "East Blue's No. 1"
title and win the elephant bluefin tuna?!
That will be me!
I'm glad you came instead
of running away, Sanji!
But the East Blue's
No. 1 title will be mine!
This time I'll finally
prove my real abilities!
Oh, Carmen-san!
I'm excited to see you again!
Here's a kiss for our reunion!
Don't you dare!!
You haven't changed...
How passionate...
Hey! Hold on a sec!
Look! Look at that!
That's Sanji!
Yeah!
Hey! Hey!
--Sanji!
--Sanji-kun!
Nami-san! You came
to give me your support?!
Not really. I was just passing by.
But why in the heck are you
participating in a competition like this?
Oh, Usopp. I didn't
realize you were here.
I was the one who
called out to you first!
Now it's time to start
the championship!
These're the judges!
Also, to be fair, we asked Sam-san,
a member of the general audience
on his way home from a wedding party,
--to join the judges!
--Where am I?
Are you ready, Sam-san?!
--Sam-san?!
--Let's go!!
The rules are simple. First, each
cook will compete against another.
Whoever receives a higher
total score from the judges wins.
And whoever remains
undefeated through all the matches
will be the East Blue's
glorious No. 1 cook!
Well then, we'll now
start the first round!
The first match is Shoo the Lizard
from the easternmost extremity versus
Eoccoli, representing Loguetown!
Now, ready... Start!
What, Sanji? You're interested
in becoming the East Blue's No. 1?
Don't be stupid. It's nothing like that.
I just want to cook that fish.
Fish?
Oh yeah, that fish does
look different from others.
Though that fish's secrets
can't be obtained so easily...
Huh?
And at last, the final match!
Hey, people're really excited.
Yeah.
With his remarkable cooking sense
and skills, Sanji won through to the final!
With her gorgeous dance and cooking skills,
Carmen has kept crushing others!
--Which one will win the
glorious elephant bluefin tuna?!
--Hi!!
--Which one will win the
glorious elephant bluefin tuna?!
Hmph!
The anticipated
final match starts now!
Rinsing!
There she goes!
Carmen's cooking looks
showy at first glance,
but what she's actually
doing is quite simple.
Also her opponents get confused by
those two in front and lose their pace,
but how is Sanji doing?!
He's not affected!
Far from that, he's exhibiting
amazing knife skills!
Contender Sanji is silently proceeding
with the preparation at his own pace!
It definitely exists!
You're still saying things
like that? How silly!
That's why we say you're a child!
I'm not a child, you damn bastard!
That's enough, Sanji! We don't
have time for your stupid stories!
Forget it and go collect plates!!
I know... Theoretically it's
impossible. I know that much...
The North Blue, South Blue,
East Blue and West Blue...
They're separate seas
that you can't cross
due to the Red Line Continent
that runs from north to south
and the ocean current in the Grand Line
which extends from east to west.
A sea where you can find all
the fish from those four seas...
...should be impossible...
But it definitely exists!
That's right. Otherwise how do
you explain those West Blue fish
and the elephant bluefin tuna?
The possibility that the damn geezer
was talking about may refer to this.
If that's the case, I have no choice but
to look for it in the Grand Line after all!
It doesn't matter how long
it takes. I'll find it for sure!
The legendary sea...
All Blue!
Now it looks like Sanji
is starting to finish up!
Carmen is also close to the end!
Looks like all she has
to do now is dish it out!
The championship is reaching a climax.
Who will win the elephant bluefin tuna?!
The decision... will be made soon!
He did it!
Contender Sanji completed it!
And here is Contender Carmen!
Looks like she's completed it, too!
The dishes are all completed now!
Who will win the crown?!
Well then, here goes.
The winner of this year's
Cooking Championship is...
--San...
--Wait!!
--I can't forgive...
--Hm?
I can't forgive myself!
What?!
I always wanted to compete against
you some day. So I've trained like crazy!
I wanted to be on a level with you...
But ten years later...
...your dream hasn't changed!
I can't forgive myself for being stupid
enough to think that I could defeat you.
You win... Your dishes are delicious.
You're the No. 1 cook
in the East Blue, Sanji.
Oh... To think that Carmen-san
is giving me such a compliment...
I'm so happy!
Don't you dare!!
What'd you do that for?!
I'll withdraw for now, but be
prepared when we meet next time!
I definitely won't lose.
Yeah, if it's a challenge from you,
I'll happily accept it any time.
The winner is... contender Sanji!
Ah! That was fun!
I don't know why but today
was a day of face-offs.
Hey, why am I
carrying the heavier part?!
Well... an elephant bluefin tuna, huh?
I wonder what it tastes like...
Looks like I can use
the fins for making stock.
What can I use the ear areas for?
Ahhh! I can't wait to cook it!
Hm?
What's the matter, Nami?
The air has changed...
--Air?
--It'll rain.
Huh? When the
weather is nice like this?
There's no doubt about it. Let's hurry.
Huh? Hey...!
Ah! My hat!
Wait!
Wait, hat!
Luffy?
Phew! Good! My hat!
Hm?
Ahh... I'm here!
Lucky!
Found him! This way!
What?! Really?!
He showed up?!
Yes! We were watching
the square like you told us,
and the man on the wanted
poster appeared just now...
Okay.
Let's go flashily.
So he just walked right up...
Just wait, you brat.
Wow! So this is the scenery
that the King of the Pirates saw...
And he died here...
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
What?! Luffy's gonna be executed?!
No way!
By Buggy?! What a shame!
So all we have to do is beat them?
Yep! Help me!
Okay, then! We'll bring
down the execution platform!
I know.
Zoro, Sanji, Usopp, Nami!
Sorry! I'm dead.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Buggy's Revenge! The Man Who
Smiles on the Execution Platform!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!