ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy lost his brother Ace in the
War of the Best against the Navy.
After getting back on his
feet with Jimbei's help,
Luffy met Dark King Rayleigh.
What are you gonna do, Luffy-kun?
I'm gonna go back.
To Marineford!
And the rest of the Straw
Hats learned the news.
Why?! What's going on?! What
made Luffy do this...?!
Luffy! I'm glad he's okay!
It's in today's newspaper?
Luffy!
"Unexpected Relanding! Luffy, to Marineford!"
At Marineford - Navy Headquarters
in the Grand Line...
CONFERENCE ROOM
It's incomprehensible!
Events in the War of the Best
revealed he's the stepbrother
of the late Portgas D. Ace
and the son of the Revolutionary Dragon
and also, the grandson of
Navy Vice Admiral Garp!
The pirate - Monkey D. Luffy!
He went missing after the war,
but he was alive as expected
and resurfaced here,
at the Navy HQ, again!
A FEW DAYS AGO...
A few days ago...
How terrible!
It was an all-out war
between the Navy's elite and
the world's greatest pirate.
It's lucky that the island didn't sink.
Where did you come from?
I'm from Alabasta, to do a story
on Crocodile and Straw Hat.
Straw Hat could be dead already though.
I'm sure that the Navy wants to look
for the pirates involved in the war
but they don't have time for that now.
Yeah.
The One Piece is real!!
Pirates inspired by Whitebeard's dying words
are committing crimes all over the world.
All the Navy soldiers who can fight
are dealing with them everywhere.
I feel sorry for them.
Speak of the devil, here come the soldiers.
What's wrong with that ship?
It's not coming into the bay!
They're acting strange.
Firing a blank?!
What's going on?!
--Have they contacted us?!
--No, sir!
No way! Why did he come back...?!
What's the matter?!
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
What?!
--Did he steal a Navy ship?!
--Why now?
He never learns... Sink the ship!
Fish-Man Jiu-Jitsu!
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
Is that the traitor - "First
Son of the Sea" Jimbei?!
There is someone else!
Don't tell me that that's the legendary...
...first mate of the Roger
Pirates - Dark King Rayleigh!
Why don't they come ashore?
They went around the island once...
It's like a funeral at sea!
Funeral? Because our main
forces aren't here now?!
Damn pirates! Barrage
them from all directions!
Go ahead and let loose on them!
Yeah!
Catch Straw Hat!
I'll fight you guys!
I want you guys to play with me as well!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
What is he up to?! He's heading west!
Does he want to bring the HQ down?!
What is he gonna do with the Ox Bell?
Flowers?
This is gonna be a great picture!
Chase him! Don't let him get away!
Now he's leaving...
What was that all about?
Dark King Rayleigh and
the Warlord - Jimbei...
Are they taking his side?!
Rayleigh was a crew member
of the King of the Pirates.
Does that mean Straw Hat
is Roger's successor?!
N-No way! He's Dragon's
son! That can't be true...
In any case, this is...
...big news!
This article has spread all
over the world already!
It even covers the fact that
we let Straw Hat get away!
How humiliating!
If you look at it simply, what
Straw Hat did was pay a tribute...
...to his brother and Whitebeard and
all other people who died in the war.
No doubt about the moment of silence
and going around the island
but the bell should only have
been rung twice not 16 times!
So the 16 bells could be a challenge to us!
Honestly! How controversial he is.
Straw Hat Luffy...
But it's not so surprising
considering he's Garp's grandson.
I wonder how he knows Rayleigh.
I don't think Rayleigh wants
to come back to center stage.
Jimbei finally turned against us.
He being a Warlord was a
symbol of intertribal peace.
What a shame!
The Three Great Powers are off-balance now.
How should we fill the 3 vacancies
among The Seven Warlords?
We need to see what will
unfold in the New World.
There'll be some changes in power
relationships among pirates.
We have to pick the most powerful ones.
Blackbeard made his move
already in the New World
and took out one of the rookies
with a bounty of over 100 million.
He knows all there is to know
about Whitebeard's territory.
He has a lead over the pirates who want
to become one of The Four Emperors.
No one has ever eaten 2 Devil
Fruits in history except for him.
The people who might be able to
stop him are The Four Emperors...
...or Marco the Phoenix and the
remnants of the Whitebeards.
It's always the "D."s who make
trouble including "Portgas."
Those names are exposed to the public
a little bit too much these days.
I tried to talk him out of it
but Garp virtually resigned.
RED LINE THE HOLYLAND OF MARIE JOIS
But he has to keep his
title and stay in the Navy.
Educating young Navy soldiers.
If you want to resign from your
position as fleet admiral,
could you at least do that?
Sengoku.
Yes, sir.
I accept that offer. It's not a
bad way to spend my retired life.
The two of you who have led the
Navy at the front since Roger's era
are stepping down.
That's going to make quite a splash.
Including the escaped prisoners
from level 6 at Impel Down,
there are a lot of infamous
pirates still on the loose.
And Newgate was at the top of the list.
The Pirate Era is changing now
and old soldiers shouldn't
cling to power in the Navy.
Justice is based on values. And
those change every generation.
That's not what I want to hear.
By the way, Kong-san,
I want to recommend Aokiji
for next fleet admiral.
NAVY HEADQUARTERS--MEDICAL CARE FACILITY
They call the power Haki.
It's safe to say that's what you got.
I guess it was awakened
by the trauma of the war.
Normally, you can only obtain
it through long-term training.
Haki...? That's what it is?
The vice admirals are all using it.
Really?!
I feel other people's presence too
strongly...
It's uncomfortable...
You two are apprentices to Garp, aren't you?
Ask him about it.
Hey, doctor! Do you think
I will get the power, too?
How do I know?
Dammit! It's like you're ahead of me now!
I don't know what's going on...
But what is this feeling?
It's like I'm a different person from before!
Maybe... If I try hard, I can get stronger!
Much stronger than I am
now... As strong as him!
I'm sorry! I couldn't hold the fort!
Don't mind it!
He was alive, huh? Amazingly!
Did you hear about it? Straw
Hat caused trouble again.
Yes.
The War of the Best ended not so
long ago and the 16 bells now?
Is this some kind of message?
I don't know.
That aside, what about my transfer?
Well, I'll talk to Sengoku-san
about it but are you serious?
No one would say such a thing as a joke.
I know. G5 is not a place
that you go voluntarily.
That place has a bunch of problems.
Navy - Grand Line 5th branch.
That means you wanna go to the New World.
It's better to be closer to your target.
The news about Straw Hat Luffy
is spreading all over the world.
NEW WORLD
Even in the New World...
"Straw Hat Luffy was alive!"
EUSTASS "CAPTAIN" KID
"Rang the 16 bells for a
new era in Marineford."
What's the Ox Bell?
The Ox Bell is...
...the holy bell from the Ox Lloyd's,
KID PIRATES--KILLER
a Navy ship that was quite
influential a long time ago.
At the year's end, they ring it 8
times to appreciate the passing year
and 8 times at the beginning of the
year as a prayer for the new year.
So they ring it 16 times in total
- that's the Navy's custom.
That's the meaning of the 16 bells.
But it's not the season yet.
So maybe he did it to announce the
end and the beginning of the era.
He wants to say,
"Whitebeard's era is over.
I'll shape the new era"?
If it's not for those purposes, he
wouldn't go back to the place...
...where he has to relive the
pain of losing his brother.
What an annoying bastard!
In fact, after the war,
he took the lead among the rookies
with a bounty of over 100 million.
But I won't let him do whatever he wants.
The New World...
I thought I could have a lot of fun
here but what's with these cowards?
Come on! I didn't cause any harm to you!
We were about to get out of this sea!
Let us go back to paradise alive!
Paradise? You mean, a loving home?
You just got here so you have no
idea how horrible this sea is!
Straw Hat?
Yes, he caused trouble again.
CAPONE "GANG" BEGE
No need to be panic.
The one who has the final checkmate...
...will become the winner.
What happened?!
Father! The ship is not touching
the water - it's in the air!
What?!
What did you say? What do you
mean? Control the ship, dammit!
Father! Something's coming
down from the sky...
No, we are going up!
NEW WORLD FOODVALTEN ISLAND
I'm so sorry.
BASIL HAWKINS
Could you say it again? I couldn't catch it.
I'm Brownbeard!
A pirate with a bounty of over 80 million!
Brownbeard-sama!
Make sure you remember my
name! This is my territory!
What you did to my men is horrible!
I'll make you pay for it in blood!
I see. I thought I misheard it
because it's such a stupid name.
I'll tell you two things.
First, I don't like jokes.
Jokes?
And here is another thing,
I can see the shadow of death on your face.
Are you sure that the Log Pose
is pointing at that island?!
Lightning is striking the island like rain!
UROUGE
We can't go there!
How can we get to the shore?!
Bold men who set foot in
the New World even once...
High Priest, somebody is approaching!
Who is it?
...all call the first half of
the Grand Line the same thing -
Say, young man...
Who is this grandma?
"That sea was like a paradise."
Do you want an umbrella?
If we stay here, we'll be dead soon!
We just wanna go back to paradise! Please!
You're such a wet blanket.
If you're not prepared to die...
...then stay out of...
...this sea!
I'll take you down soon!
You better be ready for it!
Straw Hat!
Reports on the new incident
involving Luffy at Marineford
spread throughout the world
in the blink of an eye.
The people are bewildered
by his mysterious actions,
as are his friends.
But Luffy has a reason for his behavior.
What exactly is Luffy thinking?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"With Hopes It Will Reach My
Friends! Big News Spreading Fast!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!