ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy has returned to Marineford
with Rayleigh and Jimbei.
What is the real reason behind their actions?
"With Hopes It Will Reach My
Friends! Big News Spreading Fast!"
On the solitary island in the Grand Line...
Since they locked you up,
we couldn't even sleep at night
and in order to save you...
...We went east and west and
survived various hardships!
And then,
our captain who should be in prison
became a hero in the newspaper!
--Captain Buggy!
--We've been looking for you!
We've trusted and followed
you and we thought,
"Look at him, New World! That's our captain!"
I-I didn't know that you guys
had that much trust in me...
I missed you all!
Captain Buggy!
You guys...
Didn't you give up on Buggy?
So this is how it will be, guys!
I'm the first mate of the
Buggy Pirates - Mohji!
Brother Mohji!
I'm the chief of staff - Cabaji!
Brother Cabaji!
And he's my buddy - Richie!
Richie!
By the way, what they said
in the newspaper was true.
They're all infamous criminals
with high bounties!
Of course! They're heinous
prisoners from Impel Down!
Oh yeah!
Hey Alvida, do you wanna see something cool?
Ta-dah!
This is...!
Don't tell me it's Captain
John's treasure mark!
That's right!
This is amazing! How did you get it?
Straw Hat had it!
The wind doesn't blow east or west!
It looks like it's blowing right towards me!
Speaking of Straw Hat, he made trouble again.
You didn't know? He made
a raid on the Navy HQ!
Are you kidding me?
It's a miracle he's alive, let
alone doing this sort of thing!
Huh? Let's see...
"'First Son of the Sea' Jimbei and
Dark King Silvers Rayleigh..."
Rayleigh?
What?! Wh-What does Rayleigh-san
have to do with Straw Hat?!
Wh... wh... wh... wh... wh...
wh... wh... wh... wh... wh...
...what's going on? I can't
grasp this situation at all.
Wait a minute.
If I remember right, his father
is the Revolutionary - Dragon.
And his grandfather is
Garp. And if that's so...
Rayleigh-san could be his uncle!
Hey Buggy!
A Carrier Bat brought a
message from the Government.
Huh?! How do they know that I'm here?!
D-Don't tell me that the Navy
sent someone to get me here!
And the message is "Be ready for it"?
Hey, give it to me!
This is...!
--I can't believe this!
--Don't read it before me!
Meanwhile, at the place of Thousand Sunny -
Sabaody Archipelago, Grove
#44 in the Grand Line...
You fools, give us that ship!
That's Straw Hat Luffy's ship, isn't it?
He's the Revolutionary Dragon's son!
We can sell it to the Navy for a good price!
Since we're in the same business,
we can share the profit
if you just give it to us!
How's that, Flying Fish Riders?!
What? I'm handsome?
I didn't say that! Give us the ship, fool!
I won't give it to you!
Y-You bastard!
Listen, you all. I, good-looking Duval...
...won't let you fools become popular...
I mean, take our ally's ship!
I won't make that popular...
I mean, mistake!
You screwed up your whole speech!
As long as I live, I won't let you
touch the Young Master's ship.
I'd rather touch a girl...
Oh, I made mistake!
I mean, you can't touch it! Right, guys?
Yes, Rose-Some!
Let's go!
Duval-chin, you're so cool!
Because I'm so handsome,
girls won't leave me alone!
I-I love you, too!
Mermaid Cafe should be the
first! It's very sophisticated!
No, the most popular place
on the Fish-Man Island
is the Fish-Man Karate training hall, Camie!
I promised Bones that I'd introduce
him to the Mermaid Princess!
Duval-sama! She's not aware of you!
Oh yeah! Don't mind me!
Shakky-chin, we can get together
again using the Vivre Card, right?
Now we learned that Luffy-chin's
alive from today's newspaper!
I think so. It will take a little time but...
...Ray-san met Monkey-chan
using it without any problem.
We have to protect this ship until then.
We're here to do that, sis!
Whether it's the Navy or somebody else,
we won't let anyone take the ship!
I'm counting on you!
Duval-sama, we have a
crisis! Here comes Kuma!
Kuma?! There aren't any
bears on this island...
That's...!
It's the Warlord - Bartholomew Kuma!
Don't panic! He came to see Ray-san before.
You're on our side, aren't you?
Meanwhile, at Sandy Island - Alabasta
Kingdom in the Grand Line...
The capital - Alubarna...
What happened to the pirates?
We chased them away. The
city is virtually undamaged.
I see. Good job.
We're tightening our
security across the country
but pirates have become more active around
the world since Whitebeard's death.
We have to be careful for the time being.
I wish all pirates were like
Luffy-kun and his crew but...
...they're not.
Speaking of which, King, have
you read today's newspaper?
Yes, of course.
Vivi-sama was happy about
Luffy-kun and the others.
I bet she is.
But...
A FEW HOURS AGO
Karoo!
Look at this, Karoo!
Luffy-san is alive as I thought!
I'm glad! I'm so glad!
Huh? What is this?
In just a moment, she became very serious.
And as soon as she made that face,
she took the newspaper to her room.
What's on Luffy-san's arm?
Numbers? Marks?
Or is it some new fashion?
I don't think so. Luffy-san wouldn't do that.
Meanwhile, at some city in some
country in the Grand Line...
H-Hey, why is he here on this island?
Shh! He can hear you!
It's only been 3 weeks since the war.
They just barely escaped death...
...and what are they doing now?
They've got to be up to something.
If not, they're just crazy.
You think so, Daz?
Straw Hat is wounded and wounds
won't heal that easily,
don't you think so?
You smart ass! Are you being sarcastic to me?
I'm healed.
In fact, I'm gonna head back
to the sweet old New World.
You coming?
Of course.
The news about Luffy's recent exploits...
...has reached each crewmember's hometown...
Look at this, Ace!
You saved your brother's
life - Luffy is alive!
Rest in peace!
Meanwhile, in the Grand Line...
Sorry girls, for the long trip.
Don't worry, we're used to travel.
What are you doing?
We have to make sure that you're resting.
It's Snake Princess-sama's order.
Snake Princess-sama collapsed from too
much heart-fluttering a while ago.
That's why we have to keep an eye on you.
I hope that they'll get it.
They'll get it if they see the article.
The key is your actions and how
uncharacteristic they are of you.
Hey, stop!
There is one guy who looks a bit dull.
But I'm sure he'll manage
to understand it, too.
They will understand you
very well. I have a feeling.
Up in the air above the Grand Line...
Oh yeah! I got it, Luffy!
I got it now! Okay! Okay!
On the giant bridge in the East Blue...
I see. That's what it is.
Huh? What's the matter, Robin-san?
Roger that, Luffy.
Kamabakka Kingdom...
I see, Luffy!
What's going on?
Bowin Islands...
I...
...have to...
...get off of this island!
Bowin! Bowin!
Bowin Islands!
No matter what you have to say to me,
I gotta go see Luffy!
How's that? Have I finally
reached the edge of this island?
You only traveled 20 meters'n.
No!
Damn! What's wrong with my body?!
Oh, I'm hungry!
Don't, Usopp'n!
You're falling into
the island's trap by eating madly'n!
Shut up! Leave me alone!
I got it!
What is it this time, Usopp'n?
I got it, Luffy!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
The Sky Island - Weatheria...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, young girl.
Shh! That's too much!
But they closed the Balloon Terminal
so we have nowhere to run since
this Sky Island is so small.
But I have to run! Think of something!
It's not that easy... Can we
go back to my place for now?
What?
Hey, hey, can't we go in?
I see.
Honestly! He's not thinking
about how we feel - how selfish!
Young girl! They're coming!
Future Land Baldimore...
Grandpa, what do you think
happened to the old man?
Listen, Kitton, forget about everything.
About that man and about the incident.
That was a big explosion.
There's no way that he's alive.
I told him not to push the
self-destruct button repeated...
...ly...!
What?!
1, 2, 3!
Oh, boy!
Old man!
I see!
Tehna Gehna Kingdom...
There is no time to relax for
me in a place like this...
--Hey!
--Yes.
Finished eating? I'll take the plates.
Go ahead. And I thought I
asked for the newspaper...
Maybe there is a follow-up
story about my friend.
Honestly! You don't even have eyes.
How can you read a newspaper?
I-It irks me to hear someone mention that.
You're up soon! Give it everything you got.
Here you go.
Luffy-san!
Thank you for waiting!
Behold! The Supernatural Moving Skeleton!
Oh, is that what it's all about?
I understand, Luffy-san!
The ruins of Muggy Kingdom...
Hey, wake up! How long are
you gonna stay asleep?
Seriously! How many times
do you wanna get beaten?
I'm taking care of you - see it from my side!
Mind your own business!
Oh yeah? I brought you today's
newspaper that I got from News Coo!
There is an update on your captain!
What did you say?!
H-Hey, you! What did you just say?!
R-R-Relax! You better relax!
Hey, are you done yet? My hands hurt.
Give me a minute! There should be a catch...
Luffy doesn't do these kinds of things.
He's with Rayleigh - it
must be Rayleigh's idea.
I know there is a catch.
I don't care - just hurry up!
Just as Luffy's friends are
receiving his messages,
the pirates, who have made
their way to the New World,
begin to fight over who will take
Whitebeard's place as one of the Four Emperors.
As the battle intensifies, a Navy admiral
arrives to put down the pirates!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Pirates Get on the Move!
Astounding New World!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!