ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy, depressed after losing his brother
Ace in the war against the Navy,
realized the importance of friendship
and sent a message to his crew.
"Living through Hell!
Sanji's Fight for His Manhood!"
On the small Sky Island - Weatheria...
--There she is!
--We found her finally!
--How could you fool us?
--You didn't just steal our research notes...
--But you toyed with...
--Our pure hearts!
Surrender yourself now!
You thieving girl!
Okay.
--The research notes!
--The Weather ball!
And the hostage - Mr. Haredas!
It's unforgivable even if you return them!
I'm sorry. I regret what I've done.
--No, we can't trust her!
--Let's strip her and banish her!
That's so... naughty...
Huh? Naughty?!
Naughty...
No, no, no, no! I didn't mean it
that way! What I wanted to say is...
She changed the subject...
She changed the subject!
Tut!
Did you just tut?
No! How terrible! That's an unjust charge!
Yeah, that's too much!
Huh, is it my fault?! Didn't
you guys hear that?!
--I don't think so...
--Don't get fooled by her!
It must be a mistake! I
wouldn't do such a thing!
M-Maybe I misheard...
She's manipulating them completely.
--She's wicked!
--Let's kick her out now!
No! I'm sorry! I regret what I've done!
How could we trust you?!
Yeah, I understand. Alright,
to show you how sorry I am,
I'm gonna jump into the water.
Please forgive me in the afterworld!
Goodbye!
--We made her cry!
--Don't jump the gun!
You're too young to put an end to your life!
Bye!
We're sorry!
Okay, I forgive you!
Now, I'm gonna stay here a little
longer and study about weather!
Oh, my name is Nami. You
can call me Nami-san.
I need a house to live in.
Everybody needs a little privacy.
And a nice and comfortable bed, a
jet tub, and a big closet as well!
Thank you, grandpas in the sky!
Okay, let's do it! Yeah!
Mr. Haredas, come in! Over!
Good grief...
You were desperate to get
off of this island before.
What made you change your mind?
There's a lot going on.
Could you tell me now?
Hm, okay.
Weatheria travels on the wind and
wanders around the world in the sky.
Sometimes we descend to get
some supplies and information
and then continue on.
Information?
Well, to check records.
There are still a lot of unknown
weather conditions and phenomena
that are difficult to fathom!
--What's this?!
--Are you listening?
Huh? You gotta be kidding!
Lightning strikes like rain?!
Yes, literally "like rain."
That's how it strikes that island.
That island is in the New World.
If you're willing to go to that sea,
you have to open your mind to the unexpected.
It's a big world!
I beg you. Teach me, Haredas-san,
everything that you know about...
...the weather of the New World!
You're desperate.
Of course, I am! All of my
friends' lives are in my hands!
I'm a navigator!
I have to take
responsibility when we're on the ship!
I have to navigate the way
wherever my captain wants to go!
Luffy wants to become
the King of the Pirates.
I have to improve myself as a navigator!
Your captain must be happy to have
such a thoughtful crew member.
--I have no choice.
--You have no choice?
Yeah. He's so boastful, but he
doesn't know anything about the sea.
He always does ridiculous
things. If I left him alone...
Luffy...
Help me...
Of course I will!
If I left him alone, he'd
probably end up dead.
He's not-so-bright and high-maintenance!
Must be hard to have a captain like that.
Uh-huh. That's why I wanna help him.
Like he helped me.
Hey, tell me about the Weather ball.
It's not that simple. That's one of
the great inventions of Weatheria!
If you misuse it, it could
turn the world upside down!
It could be used as a weapon?
Hey, hey, that's too dangerous.
Don't smile like that!
Nami!
You’re my friend!
Meanwhile, on the Mechanical
Island Future Land Baldimore...
The unexpected bombing at
Dr. Vegapunk's laboratory!
We haven't found who did it!
Hey, hurry up!
It's not too much to say that it
was a greatest loss of our time!
Do you have any information?
I heard there was an intruder
that looks like a gorilla.
How mysterious!
In order to reach the harbor of this
island, you need a large ice-breaker.
But no one has seen one.
They say that the intruder was Cyborg
Franky of the Straw Hat Pirates
but he's just been seen on Sabaody
Archipelago within the past month and...
...we don't know how he
could've gotten to Baldimore.
Captain Gorilla! The search team
is leaving for the mountains!
Okay! I'm coming with them!
Th-This is...!
The hidden entrance has been
uncovered by the explosion.
What a surprise. We didn't
know about this place.
I can't believe it.
There was another laboratory!
The working cyborg animals
must have been created here.
Hey, don't break anything!
You can't talk to me like that!
In the laboratory that was blown away,
there
were some far-out inventions useful in daily life.
But what I wanted to know about
are the weapon inventions,
like the ones here.
This is great! Everything from
battleships to human cells...
How did he come up with
all these kinds of things?
Okay! I made up my mind!
I'm gonna live here!
Huh? Live here?!
Yeah!
I'll come down the mountain sometimes
to get more cola from your place.
Okay?
Don't worry!
As long as you don't tell anybody,
I won't cause you trouble
because I'll live here.
Don't panic every time you see my face!
--Don't look at us!
--That scary face is getting scarier!
How's this? A tiger rug!
--That's not bad...
--F-F-F-Franky!
--It's cold especially my legs.
--Why don't you wear your pants?
--Okay, now it's warm!
--Why don't you just wear your pants?
But you said you wanted to get off
of this island. What happened?
Well, not much but...
My dream...
I want you to sail on the ship...
...that I built!
Luffy...
You let me hold a dream.
Franky!
Thank you for the ship!
It's a great ship! I'll take good care of it!
If you want these shorts back,
you'll have to join us!
You brought me out into this big world!
We'll cross many seas and have
tons of battles and challenges.
And when we get to the end of the sea,
I will call it "the ship of dreams."
Hey, Luffy.
The Thousand Sunny still
has some life in her.
You're the only captain who can make it...
..."the ship of dreams."
I'll acquire skills that'll enable us to have
an even more harrowing adventure than before.
So Luffy...!
Hey, the tiger is burning.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
What is that?!
A monster?! Watch out!
So Luffy, we have to get over
the rough sea of the New World!
This incident will be known
around the Grand Line
as the Legend of Baldimore's
Sacred Burning Beast.
At the Kamabakka Kingdom, Grand Line...
Hey, what was it you saw in the newspaper?
I see!
You got so calm all of the sudden.
I received Luffy's message because it's
exclusively for his friends,
from the newspaper.
If you don't believe that I'm his
friend, I'm not gonna tell you, fool!
This guy's annoying!
Hey, who made this meal?
Oh, you have quite a discriminating palate!
It tastes good and oddly, I feel
like I'm overflowing with energy!
That's right! It's a dish of aggression!
There are a lot of chefs who
can make that on this island!
--Yes!
Yes!
Look at the beautiful tough
bodies of these candies!
And their gentle hearts.
The candies grew like this by
eating the dish of aggression!
What you eat is important for your condition,
physique, and personality!
It builds the whole human body!
If all the people in the
world drink milk everyday...
there'll be less crime - don't you agree?
So, it's good to be aggressive!
Food builds body? I never
thought about it that way.
I can help them building their
bodies with daily meals.
But besides that,
what'll I do if Nami-san and Robin-chan
get sexier than they are now?!
--What should we do with this guy?
--What should I do?!
I'm burning with passion!
Teach me how to cook the dish of aggression!
The answer is "No!!"
Ouch...
That was very wishful thinking!
This "99 - Vital Recipe" is...
...a part of the New Kama Kempo
techniques - Training for Married Life!
I can't just teach it to a nobody like you!
If you wanna learn it, you gotta
have a girlish heart and...
...learn the New Kama Kempo!
No way!
I wasn't born to become friends with ladies.
I was born to...
...love ladies!
Gah!
Heehaw!
You're quite a reasonable man. I like you!
Okay, I'll give you a chance!
A chance?
I'll hand out the recipes to 99 grand masters
of the New Kama Kempo on this island.
If you're a real pirate, get
all the recipes from them!
However, every new kamas on this island
will try to put this sweet
dress on you day and night!
I wonder if you can maintain your manhood.
--Sanji-kun!
--We won't let you sleep!
The sweet dress!
I'll bring back the exciting
feelings of wearing skirts!
Sanji! It's nice to be girly!
You...
...vs. the home of the New Kama Kempo!
If you can win this fight, I'll give
you a ship, too! You can have it all!
So what do you say?!
Hey you, cook!
Join my group!
Huh?
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
I won't die.
I'm not gonna die here.
You see idiots like that
every once in a while...
ones who will fight to the death once
they've set their eyes on a target...
I can't hear your answer -
does that mean you give up?
Yeah, if you lose...
When I win...
When I beat all of them, I bet I'll
be much stronger than I am now.
Even if hundreds of weapons are built in,
he can be defeated by someone with
a spear of blind determination.
Hey, Luffy, don't lose.
But I'm hoping to go some
day... to the Grand Line.
Then let's go now.
It's not the right time yet.
--Say... do you know the All Blue?
--No...
Oh, you don't?! It's a miracle sea!
We both have foolish dreams.
Hm?
In order to achieve my goal, the All Blue...
Sanji?
Yeah. I'll come along... on your journey
to become "King of the Pirates"!
What?
I'll be the cook for your ship.
Luffy, if I can see you again...
...I'll...
I'll give you the greatest
support in the world as a cook
so you can become the King of the Pirates!
After...
...I live through...
...this hell!
I accept...
...the challenge!
Great! We won't go easy on you!
I'm looking forward to it!
Alright, let's do it!
Sanji-kun!
Don't give me the cold shoulder!
--Shut up!
--Otherwise...
I can't lose here!
No!
Doesn't work!
I got you!
I'm not gonna lose either, Luffy!
I'll fight you now!
Get the recipe from me - Caroline!
This is great!
I'm gonna get revenge for the other day!
Here I come!
I will win!
Luffy's messages have
reached his friends safely.
Taking Luffy's feelings to their own hearts,
his friends make a decision
toward pursuing a new goal.
They meet at the captain's side once more,
their sights set on the day they'll
set out on a new adventure!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Will Get Much, Much Stronger!
Zoro's Pledge to His Captain!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!