The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Ah! My hat!
Wait!
Wait, hat!
Good! My hat!
Hm?
Wow! So this is the scenery
that the King of Pirates saw...
Wow...
Finally... Finally the time
for revenge has come.
Just wait, you damn Straw Hat!
He finally showed up...
Took him long enough.
Please wait... Captain Smoker!
Come with me, Tashigi.
Yes, sir!
"Buggy's Revenge! The Man Who
Smiles On The Execution Platform!"
Hey, someone's on
the execution platform!
Who the heck is that?
That old man said
that it was 22 years ago
that the King of the Pirates died here...
Hey you over there!
Come down right away!
Why?!
That's a special execution platform
under control of the World Government!
Come down right now!
Well, you don't have
to be so strict, officer.
If you don't come down,
I'll just arrest you. I'm coming up now!
Hmph! Now's not
the time for small fries.
Hm?
I've been looking for you, Luffy.
Long time no see...
Huh?
Don't tell me you forgot my face...
--How beautiful...
--She's so pretty!
She is a woman of unrivaled beauty!
Her skin looks very smooth.
I don't know anyone like you.
Who the heck are you?
I'll never forget you...
because you're the first man who hit me.
What? I hit you?
When your passionate
fist hit me that time...
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
Oh, it felt good...
You guys... what's the most
beautiful thing in the East Blue?
That'd be you!
That's right. It's me.
There's no man in this world that
doesn't bow before my beauty.
And I like strong men.
I'll make you mine, Luffy.
Shut up! No way!
Who the heck are you?
You still haven't figured it out?
This is the police!
Hey, woman, come quietly!
You're under arrest for
harming the police captain!
And you over there!
Get off the execution platform!!
Oh? Who'd you say you'd arrest?
Y-You!
Are you capable of that?
A-Asst. Captain, this is a problem!
She's beautiful!
So what?! We'll arrest her!
She's so beautiful
that she's dazzling!
Good for you!
Terrorist bombing!!
It's heading straight for her!
Wh-What the...
The fountain slipped!
What just happened?!
That was dangerous, you know.
Flashily sorry. But your smooth skin
is unharmed, of course. So don't worry...
...beautiful lady Alvida.
Huh? Alvida?
I don't see Alvida.
I'm Alvida! You blockhead!
Really? You don't
look like Alvida at all...
I changed after eating a devil fruit.
The name of the fruit is...
Smooth Smooth Fruit!
No attack can hurt my skin
because it slides off it.
Unfortunately, my beauty
couldn't be improved that much, though.
One big change was...
yes, my freckles are gone.
N-No, that's not really what I meant.
After becoming a new person,
I joined forces with him since we
had the same goal-- finding you.
Now, the ultimate star
appears super flashily!
Monkey D. Luffy!
Since the day you blew me off, I've
been obsessed with revenge on you.
That alone led me to finally find my crew.
It was indeed a great adventure.
I was missing parts of my body.
Laughs. Hell. Friendship. It was
tiny Buggy-kun's great adventure.
But Buggy-kun was...
Why am I telling you
a story, you bastard?!
What? Well, what was your name?
Boggy? No, Boogie?
No, Behie... isn't right...
Oh yeah! It's Buffoon!
Buffoon?! Stop messing around!
You sure haven't lost
your nerve, you moron!
I-It's Buggy the Clown!
P-Pirates!!
It's the Buggy Pirates!!
People! Remain flashily where you are!
I'll show you good how scary I am.
Oh! It's Buggy!
You just remembered it?!
Wh-What's going on?
Long time no see, rubber man.
Is Roronoa Zoro well, too?
Okay, Cabaji. Good job.
To my several hundred billion
servants around the world! Look!
We'll now super flashily
start the open execution!
Monkey D. Luffy! You can
no longer move even an inch.
You feel honored, Straw Hat?!
You can die in the same place
the King of the Pirates died.
The atmospheric pressure
is dropping abnormally.
I've never seen such
a bizarre drop before.
Now that you mention it,
I feel a strange wind...
A storm is coming... to this island!
A-A storm?
We'd better hurry back to
the ship or we'll be in trouble.
--Is it a pretty big one?
--Hey...!
--Hm?
--Zoro!
Have you seen him?
You mean Luffy?
Yeah... We got separated.
I also feel something strange...
...like... something terrible
is about to happen...
--Pirates're here!
--Run!
--It's Buggy the Clown!!
What?!
Buggy the Clown!
What? Then...
Y-Yes! In addition to Straw Hat Luffy,
Buggy the Clown and Iron Club Alvida,
all notorious pirates in the East Blue,
are taking over the square!
Right under my nose...
What impudent jerks...
What should we do,
Captain Smoker?
Send Unit #1 to the sea.
Unit #2 is to secretly surround
the square from the streets.
And have the rest stand by within
shooting range of the square.
--That's all.
--Yes, sir!
--Give this order to Unit #1.
--Yes, sir?
"Crush any pirate ships
as soon as they see them.
Don't let any pirates off of
this island. Not even one pirate."
--An execution!
--An execution will start!
Buggy the Clown will be
executing Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy's gonna be executed?!
That idiot!
Let's go!
--Take care of this!
--Ahh... Ahh... Ahhhhh...
--S-S-S-Sanji!
--Treat it like a lady! Got that?!
--Oops! Ahhh...
--We have to hurry, too!
Hey! Hey, Nami!
Where're we going?!
The harbor, of course!
H-Harbor? Oh yeah, of course!
Captain Smoker!
Please come here.
Things are getting weird.
Hm? Wha...! Th-That kid...
What's he doing?
Monkey D. Luffy. This can't be!
Looks like he's about to be killed!
How pathetic that kid looks!
I want to see the place where
the King of the Pirates died!
Hm?
He was somehow
different from the others.
He caught my attention...
So I thought, but...
Does this mean that he's just
another pirate after all?
Captain, are we
swooping in right away?
Idiot. Don't be hasty.
But if we don't hurry...
I'm the one in command here!
Y-Yes, sir!
A pirate is about
to kill another pirate.
This is great.
They're saving us the trouble.
Listen! Once that
Straw Hat's head falls,
surround Buggy,
Alvida and their gangs!
Don't give them time to think!
Pirate Monkey D. Luffy, the criminal,
is to be flashily executed for the crime
of getting me angry
by becoming stuck up!
Live it up flashily!
This is my first time
seeing an execution.
We're executing you.
Huh?
What?! Stop joking!
You stop joking!
--Take this board off!! You bastard!!
--Okay! We are now going
--Take it off!! You liar!
You jerkwad! You stupid head!
--to start the flashy execution openly!!
Ahhh!! Stop it!
Ahhh! I don't wanna die!!
I saw a big cumulus
cloud in the eastern sky.
A storm is coming.
An unimaginably big storm is...
If Buggy, Luffy and the others
go crazy, the Navy will come out.
We're done for if the ship is washed out
to sea when we have to get out of here.
I see. That really is a big deal!
The Navy may have
already started taking action.
The Going Merry is in danger!
Th-The Going Merry
will be in the Navy's hands?
H-Hey, Nami! Hurry up!!
Wait for me!
Hurry to the harbor!
Crush every single pirate ship!
Yes, sir!
Riding around on the Richie bike!
Who's that man?
Who? Who? Who's that man?!
Me!
So this is the rubber guy's ship...
He now has a bigger ship,
as if he's become a real pirate.
It's about time for him to get
flashily executed by Captain Buggy.
However...! Just in case the rubber guy,
who has no chance of escaping,
happens to escape,
burning this ship is... our job.
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
Please save me.
Why would I save you, idiot?!
Hmph! This is what happens
when someone goes against us.
I guess this is it for
the man I had my eye on...
Since you have a big audience,
do you wanna say
something before you die?
Well, that's okay. Whether you
wanna say something or not
doesn't matter since you're gonna die.
I'm the man who'll be
King of the Pirates!!
Wha...
K-King of the Pirates, he said?!
In this town, of all places...
That's a crazy thing to say...
Well then, I guess I'll do it now...
you damn piece of rubber.
--Stop...
--Hm?
--...the execution!
Zoro! Sanji!
--Zoro?!
--Hm?
Shame on you!
There's a limit to how much
you can fool around, Luffy.
If you're starting a sideshow,
let me join you.
What we have to do for now is
drive those damn pirates away?
P-Pirate hunter Zoro!!
Sanji! Zoro!
So you're here, Zoro!
But you are a little too late!
--We'll bring down...
--...that execution platform!
Roronoa Zoro...
Guys... get them!
We'll get them!
Big Sis Alvida!
Out of our way!
Not even Zoro can stop me now!
This is the end of your captain!!
Damn bastard!
If I cut down the execution platform...
Listen. The moment Monkey D. Luffy's
head falls, we'll attack all together.
All units. Get ready for battle.
Yes, sir!!
Zoro! Sanji!
--Hurry up!
--Usopp!
--Nami!
--This is heavy!
Sorry. I'm... dead.
Idi...
Don't say something so stupid!
He smiled!
I'm still alive after all.
I got lucky.
--H-Hey, do you believe in god?
--Phew, lucky me.
--Stop talking nonsense.
Let's get out of this town already!
--I was worried what was going happen for a while.
Another trouble seems to be brewing.
Now! Corner those pirates!
Yeah!!
--Here they come!
--Tsk!
Amazing! Amazing!
It's somehow gotten crazy!
Amazing! Ahh! Amazing!
Hey, Luffy!
Ahhh... Z-Zoro!
This is no time to be excited!
We need to get out of here!
We'd better hurry back to the ship
or we'll never be able
to leave the island.
We won't be able to
enter the Grand Line!
What?! That's not good!
The Straw Hat gang is running away!
--Capture them!
--Go after them!
Why did he smile?
Did he know he'd be saved?
No. At that moment, he seriously
thought his life was going to end there.
He accepted death and smiled
after preparing himself.
Captain, please go seize the pirates.
Hey... have you seen any pirates
who smiled on the execution platform?
N-No way! Even if it's
a brave-acting big shot,
at the moment of death,
he turns pale and dies in despair.
That straw hat man smiled...
...just like Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates,
smiled 22 years ago in this town...
on that execution platform...
Captain...
Where did that Straw Hat go?
Yes, sir. He's running towards the sea.
What's Unit #1 doing? They should've
blown up their ship by now.
Well... They're back for
refitting because they couldn't
light the powder
due to the sudden rain...
What?!
A reserve unit is currently getting
ready to attack the ship instead.
Captain Smoker! If we let them sail
out now, they'll enter the Grand Line!
The wind is blowing towards the west.
It's a tailwind for their ship.
Are these all coincidences?
It's as if heaven is trying
to let that man live.
--We'd better hurry
or we'll be in trouble!
--We're gonna make it to the Grand Line like this!
I am White Hunter Smoker.
On my honor as a
Navy Headquarters Captain,
I won't let that man
leave this island!!
Wind, blow!
The storm of fate has arrived!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there