Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago
to go on to the next stage - the New World.
Did you know about this?
What is Soul King?
Oh, about Brook.
He might not...
...come back to do pirating again.
Look!
Oh, you guys!
This is Grove #46.
Rookies who have joined the
Straw Hats keep showing up here.
I see some captains.
"Big Guns Assembled! The Danger
of the Fake Straw Hats!"
Thank you!
Thank you, baby!
Oh, here we go!
45 degrees!
Thank you!
That was great!
--Here you go, sir!
--Oh yeah!
This feels great!
It sinks into my bones...
Ring, ring, ring...
SABAODY ARCHIPELAGO GROVE #46
This is Grove #46.
A MEETING SPOT FOR THE STRAW HATS
There are more than 100 pirates here now.
If they all work for Straw
Hat Luffy, it's gonna be...
Hey, what's wrong?! Answer!
This is bad news!  Tell the backup to hurry!
Hey, hey, hey!
I was wondering who you were,
but you're a Navy soldier!
Oh gee!
What is going on here?
Oh! Oh! Don't tell me...
...that you just informed the Navy-san?
What?
He's a Navy soldier!
N-No, I haven't called them yet!
I was just about to...
Oh no, I don't want you to!
Otherwise, there's gonna be blood all over!
You and your friends' blood!
Isn't it right, Coribou?
Huh?! I'm sorry, brother, I'm so sorry!
I'm here, you fool!
I'm sorry!
No that way, you dumb fool!
Caribou, the Navy soldier killer!
Enough jokes.
--He did it!
--He's true to his reputation.
Oh, gods, have mercy!
This silly Navy soldier tried to reach
his weapon and attempted to kill me!
Please have mercy on him!
I'm sorry, gods, I'm so sorry!
Bury him, Coribou!
Bury this sinful Navy soldier alive!
Okay! I dig, I dig...
W-Wait a minute! Don't do it!
I didn't call for the Navy!
That's enough, Caribou!
Just dispose of that small-time
Navy soldier somewhere.
Here comes Captain Straw Hat Luffy!
You guys, look around you!
You probably don't know each other
but you are all gonna
work for me from now on!
As a crewmember of the Straw Hats!
That means when I become
the King of the Pirates,
you're gonna be a shipmate of the King!
To make that happen, from now on,
you guys should wait on me hand and foot
and fight for me at the
risk of your own life!
It's like a dream to work under
the unheard-of pirate
who caused trouble at...
...all of the 3 strongholds of the World
Government: Enies Lobby, Impel Down, Navy HQ!
He'll be one of the strongest candidates
for the King of the Pirates!
This is what they call
"getting on the bandwagon"!
Most of them are here already.
Is that it?
Can't wait to see everybody!
Shut up!
We asked you to assemble here because...
...I've had my honor insulted - your
big boss who is important to you all!
The perpetrators have to be somewhere
here on this archipelago!
I want you to find them and drag them to me!
Consider it done, boss!
I won't forgive those fools!
Well, people change a lot in 2 years.
You guys don't talk much now, do you?
This mustache guy knows the
real Straw Hats as I thought.
Who is he?
I don't know but he'll notice so don't talk.
All we gotta do is take him to Captain.
Okay.
And I don't think you two
were ever so friendly.
But maybe 2 years has changed all that.
Your looks have changed also.
Are you guys wearing disguises too?
Hey, wait!
Encore! Encore!
Encore! Encore! Encore!
I see. The Navy, huh?
I got it.
Don't push!
Soul King, come on now!
I need a little more time.
Yes... My fans are calling for an encore...
...and they won't stop so I'll go back.
Thank you for waiting, everybody!
There is something that
I have to tell you guys.
Today, I, Soul King, will...
This is it! The show is over!
The Navy? Why are they here?
The acting captain of the Rumbar
Pirates - "Humming Swordsman" Brook.
A 33 million berry bounty.
We suspect that you're this pirate!
In addition to that,
we have information that you're
working for Straw Hats Luffy now!
Soul King Brook!
No, Pirate Brook!
You're under arrest!
No, Brook-sama is not...!
Soul King is a criminal?
He's a pirate?
But I heard Straw Hat Luffy was dead!
It's all over, Brook.
I thought that you guys might be behind this,
Manager.
It was shocking to me when
you told me honestly
about your retirement backstage.
You've became very popular so we
were about to make a lot of money.
You betrayed us!
And our company will be out of business.
Let's die together, Soul King.
GROVE #17 THE ISLAND
WHERE THE SUNNY IS DOCKED
Cool!
Isn't it?! His body is amazing!
You're like a robot!
Can you shoot beams or missiles?!
What can you transform into?!
Yes! With the dreams and enthusiasm
of men riding on his back,
he goes into action now!
His name is...
...Armored Me!
Robot! Robot!
Calm down, Chopper!  Too much
excitement could kill you!
But, Franky,
you can't do detail work with
those huge hands, can you?
What did you say?
Whoa! A hand!
A hand came out from a hand!
Robin!
Nami!
You look great!
What's wrong with his body?
I don't know. I don't understand.
Oh, this is the coating?
Press my nose.
Nose?
Press it for a long time.
More than 3 seconds...
Please press the nose
for more than 3 seconds.
He tried to sound like a robot!
Exciting! Exciting!
1, 2, 3...
Whoa! Hair!
Hair...!
Can you set your hair?
Yes, I can!
--Wow!
Oh, Nami! Hey!
Okay, okay...
What was he doing for 2 years?
Can I see your weapon? Can I?!
No way! That's the main event -
you gotta wait for Luffy-mecha.
He moved like a robot!
He said "mecha" at the end!
Guys.
Rayleigh-san! Shakky!
I'm sorry to interrupt your reunion but...
...there are things going
on on this archipelago.
Pirate Brook!
Drop your instrument and
put your hands in the air!
Band.
Backup singers and dancers!
I want you to support me for one more song!
Don't worry!
My music's got power!
Are you insane?
It's all over for you, Brook.
Manager, thank you for everything
during the past 2 years.
And thank you for bringing
me here to this archipelago.
We have a sad memory of losing
a fight on this archipelago
but this is where we start again!
I'm a musician.
My role in the Straw Hats is
to make the journey more fun!
People think Straw Hat Luffy is dead?
That's nonsense!
Tell this to the whole world!
The pirate - Straw Hat Luffy is alive!
He will become the King
of the Pirates someday!
Head Office, can you hear
me? I have some big news!
His departure shouldn't
be a quiet one! Oh baby!
Soul King!
Love me to the bones!
Yeah!
I'll dedicate this to my dear friends.
Listen to my last soul!
Yeah!
Luffy-san, let's go to the New World!
You fool! I said the show is over!
Shut up, Navy!
Let us hear one more song!
Let him sing it!
She's right! We don't care who he really is!
See? Music is always on my side!
1, 2, 3, 4...
"New World"!
Oh yeah!
Kid!
This is the story of a hero
The story of a man who will become king
In war there are no "do-overs"
But he stands firm with
sandals on his bare feet
Oh yeah!
Come on baby!
Dreamers always struggle
Because sometimes their
dreams are out of reach
In order to live through the days in
which you have to battle your own demons
It's a big dream that seems quite a handful
But when he mentioned it,
I could see it coming true
Today is the day We got tired of waiting
We don't need nights because
we're short-tempered
Today is the day It's a great day
Kick the clock that was stopped
For the New world For the New world
For the New world The world is gonna change
One more time!
What?!
You fools!
I let him get away because of you guys!
He was a money spinner!
The Navy?
Yes, they think that the fake Straw Hats
are the real ones and
have started mobilizing.
I wiretapped them so there is no mistake.
I told Brook-chan what's going
on through the Transponder Snail
at the venue.
He's on his way here.
Oh, so he's gonna abandon stardom?
He has backbone as I thought.
Nami-chan, you're a navigator, aren't you?
I'll teach you how to operate
the coated ship so remember it.
Okay.
I'll try my best!
Oh, what is this?
It got tense all of the sudden.
But, Rayleigh, Luffy is not here!
Don't worry!
Captain!
Huh?
Call me big boss, fool!
We couldn't find the real pet but
isn't he the guy you're looking for?
Oh!
Luffy is here already!
I can't wait!
I gave Sanji a Baby Transponder
Snail when he came here.
He's with Zoro.
Oh, that's good because
you guys have to hurry
- the Navy will be here soon.
So it's only Monkey-chan that we can't reach.
But take this Vivre Card.
It will lead him to you.
Grove #42 will be perfect - it's on the sea.
Take the ship there and rendezvous!
It's a little busy but you
all got through these 2 years
and it's time for the new journey!
Only Luffy is still missing.
Everyone is waiting for the captain's return.
But Luffy got caught up in battle between
the Marines' Pacifistas and
the Fake Straw Hats.
The results of his two years of
training become apparent.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Battle is on! Show Them
What You Got From Training!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!