Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago to
go on to the next stage - the New World.
Why are they calling you Straw Hat?
Hey, you! Don't you know who I am?
Get out of my way or I'll kill
you and pull out your bowels!
Straw Hat is not scum like you!
What?!
I see. They all got fooled
and became his crew.
And I don't know why but the
real Straw Hat is here too.
That was close!
H-Here's his poster...
Looks exactly the same!
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
Straw Hat... He is using Haki!
Luffy! I knew it was you!
Why are you always in trouble?!
It's really been a long time!
I wonder how everybody is!
I'm so happy!
I came here to check but you seem alright.
Uh-huh!
Rayleigh!
I'll do it!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
"Everyone Together! Luffy,
Setting Out for the New World!"
It seems like things are
getting hectic over there...
What are you guys doing?!
Get Straw Hat already!
--Oops!
--Hurry up, Luffy!
Rayleigh, thank you for everything!
Well then, Rayleigh...
Thanks again for everything!
I'm going now!
Yes...
They went that way!
--Go after them!
--Don't let them get away!
Rise to the top!
The Straw Hats are heading for Grove #42!
Catch them at any cost!
What was that?
Dark King Rayleigh!
It's a new beginning for my pupil!
Don't be too hard on him.
Wh-What is this line?
I recommend you not to cross it.
Oh, Bon Bags! A lot of them!
What's in them?
They're all filled with food.
I know everybody's stomach got
bigger these past 2 years.
I'll let you fill up later!
Really?! Can't wait to eat your food!
There they are! They're this way!
Oh? They went round!
We have no choice!
Everybody, charge!
Yeah!
I wanna become a flea...
What's wrong? What're you...?
I wanna become a mite...
What?!
What happened?!
I... I...
I wanna become a louse...
It must be...
I knew it was you guys causing all of this!
I can't believe it!
You haven't gotten anywhere yet!
Oh! I know you from Thriller Bark!
Who was she?
What are you still doing here?
You can't talk to me like
that! I brought you back here!
If it weren't for me, you would be...
You must learn your place...
Sniff, sniff...
A real woman! A real woman!
Of course I am! What kind
of sickness do you have?
Anyway, set sail already!
I saw some Navy ships around here!
What?!
Soon, there'll be no way out!
That's no good. But it's strange.
I can't move from here.
What are you talking about?!
Real ladies are great!
I am scum...
What's that?
There you are!
THE SHORE AT GROVE #42 THE
RENDEZVOUS POINT OF THE STRAW HATS
--Oh!
--That must be...!
Usopp-san! Nami-san! Robin-san!
FFFranky-san!
Brook!
Hey! I can't believe you abandoned stardom!
Attaboy!
It's been a long time, everybody!
You two have become even more beautiful!
Alright, Nami-san!
It's been 2 years so...
Oh, are you gonna sing for us?
...Could I look at your panties...
What do you think?!
I never let you see them even 2 years ago!
I-I'm so excited to see you again... See?
It's shaking my soul...
--Although I don't have a soul to be shaken...
--Hey, the big star is having a spasm.
Honestly! None of you guys have grown up.
By the way, I don't see everybody here yet.
--Oh yeah, Chopper went to pick them up.
--Hey!
Here they come finally!
Wow, hey!
Everybody!
I brought them!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Hey!
Luffy-san! I missed you so much!
You guys sure do look stronger!
We all got together again!
Finally...
Guys!
What?!
Sanji!
Well then, thank you!
Say "hi" to everybody in
Birdie Kingdom for me!
Usopp! Is Sanji alright?!
O-O-One beautiful woman...
--Hey, stay with me!
--Two beautiful woman...
Hey, this is no good,
Chopper! Stop the bleeding!
F-F-Franky, you're...!
What's the matter?
Is there something that concerns you-mecha?
--Mecha?! I wanna play!
--Wait, Luffy!
I don't know what's so
great and besides that,
it looks like the Navy
ships are already here!
Oh no! When did they get here?!
There are 3 Navy ships!
Hey, should we fight back?!
They're gonna get us!
Shoot! Shoot and sink them!
Oh no! It's gonna hit us!
Slave...
...Arrow!
Wh-What just happened?
I-It's...
...The Kuja Pirates!
Who...
...put a Navy ship...
...in my way?
That's Kuja's logo!
Kuja?
They're strong amazonian pirates led
by a pirate empress - a Warlord.
A Warlord?!
Her name is Boa Hancock.
They say anyone who sees her
will be attracted by her beauty
and turned to stone in the end.
Oh, too bright! She is dazzling!
There is no end to her beauty!
Wow! She must be a goddess!
Goddess?!
Where is she?! Goddess? Goddess?
Goddess... Oh, goddess... Goddess... Godd...
--G...
--He turned to stone!
Oh, that's Hancock and the others!
Move your ship, Boa Hancock!
Are you trying to interfere
with us fulfilling our duty?
No, I'm not!
I just don't feel like making way for you.
Sh-She's acting like a child!
Is that a problem?
Go, Luffy... Now is the chance!
She just winked at us...
She helped us. Let's set sail now!
You know that Warlord?
Yeah, I was sent to the Maiden Island
and I became friends with them.
That's the legendary
female-only island, right?
I didn't know they were real...
Friend with the pirate empress?!
Hey, were you really training hard?!
Yeah, I'm so ready!
Damn... It's not fair...! It's not fair...!
What's the matter, Sanji?
Whoa, so they're Luffy's friends!
There are a bunch of creatures
that I've never seen before.
--1, 2, 3, 4...
--Looks like they're having fun!
Okay, let's get ready to set sail now!
--Yeah!
--Yes, Nami-san!
What's the matter, Usopp?
I was just thinking... did you
guys beat all those Navy soldiers?
No, we heard them shouting
while we were flying.
Then, why aren't they coming
after us from inland?
This is Backup Unit Platoon 3!
Can you hear me?
--What's wrong? What happened?
--We can't get to Grove #42!
--Why is that?
--B-Because...
...there are huge bugs standing in our way...
What? Bugs?!
What are they?!
Shoot!
I won't let them mess with
Usopp'n's new adventure'n!
When men part ways, we don't shed tears'n.
Good luck, Usopp'n!
As long as they're not coming, that's good.
If they're in trouble, we're lucky.
Let's just leave now!
Nami, lead the way!
You can count on me!
Alright!
This is Platoon 4.
I'm sorry. All of the sudden,
it started raining and the
gunpowder got wet!
Rain? Where?
Sabaody Archipelago should
be clear and sunny today!
No thunder. We don't want
normal people to get hurt.
The bubbles are a pain in the neck here.
But I can't believe we
caught such perfect wind.
It brought us here just as we wanted.
That's because Nami-chan is a good girl.
Good luck! We will miss you on Weatheria!
Oh, it's inflating!
What? This jelly inflates?
Oh, we got a bubble roof!
Listen, guys.
A coated ship has the ability
to reduce any kind of pressure.
So once the floating bag at the ship's
bottom which keeps it on the surface
has been removed,
it'll be less buoyant and start to sink.
That's how it works.
I see.
Too complicated, huh?
Anyway, spread the sail now!
Sail?
A coated sailing ship
is driven by the sea current
instead of the wind.
I thought it just submerged and travelled.
Alright, we better hurry
before the Navy comes again!
This is Central Unit Platoon 5 at Grove #42!
This is an emergency situation!
All the troops in Platoon 2 that
came before have become negative...
What are you saying? Negative?!
I wanna become like moss...
I'm no good. I wanna become a water flea...
According to them, Straw Hat Luffy got on a
giant bird and flew away!
Bird? What are you guys doing now?!
We're fighting against unknown enemies!
Damn, that bastard!
He gave me trouble to the last minute!
I've got to find a new boy-toy...
Navy reinforcements! We
were about to leave...
Everybody!
Straw Hat's ship is in range now!
Wait a minute! A giant
bird is coming towards us!
He...
They're coming from behind too!
I got it!
How do you like it, Nami-san?
Did you see me getting stronger?
Sanji!
Answer, Platoon 5! What's going on?!
W-We are...
We're facing an unexpected obstacle...
Don't do it!
How could you turn us down?!
Maybe they're all shy.
You don't have to be ashamed!
Let's have a cup of tea together!
I-I-I'm gonna go out of my mind!
Oh! You've got such a cute face!
No, don't do it!
What's wrong? Answer, Platoon 5!
Sanji-kun, now is the chance!
Hey, hey, what's wrong, Sanji?!
I-I-I don't know... Suddenly,
it felt like someone was
squeezing my heart...
The floating bag is removed!
Okay! What about sail?
We're ready!
Is it time to go, Nami?
Yes, at your command, Captain.
Alright...
You guys!
I've got a lot of things that I want
to share with you but in any case,
thank you for going along with
my selfish decision for 2 years!
That wasn't the first time.
He's right! You've always been selfish!
Rear Admiral-dono, the
pirate ship is submerging!
What?! Damn!
You fools!
Do you have any idea...
how heinous they are? Hey!
Rear Admiral!
Take care, Luffy...
Spread the sail!
--Yes!
--Yeah!
Set sail!!
Yeah!
Let's go to the Fish-Man Island!
Having departed for the New World,
the Straw Hats are amazed
by the unknown underwater scenery.
Franky tells them about the
man who protected them.
But there's something dark
lurking behind the Sunny.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Surprising Fact!
The Man Who Guarded the Sunny!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!