Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and set sail for the Fish-Man Island...
...located 10,000 meters below sea level
to go on to the next stage - the New World.
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Hey, Ankoro! You can't do that!
Don't eat ships!
D-Did he help us?
Let's go! We have to get away
anyway! He is a monster too!
What the hell is that?!
"Undersea Volcanic Eruption!
Drifting to the Fish-Man Island!"
--Dead men tell no tales, they have no desire.
--Is that...
--...me?
--In the dark land where even crows can't fly.
Dead men don't need jewels on their finger.
You can't even see
somebody's sorrow in the dark.
Look for it! Look for it!
Sunken treasures are mine!
I am the richest person in the
world - Captain Vander Decken!
Don't tell me it's...!
Even in the sea?!
A ghost ship?!
You shouldn't be so scared!
I turned! For no reason!
Oh no!
It's a ghost ship!
We thought that you were
a ghost at that moment!
Th-That is the real one! Look at that sail!
The infamous Flying Dutchman!
It shouldn't exist in the real world!
It happened several hundred years ago.
One stormy day, the captain of the
pirate ship suddenly lost his mind
and killed all his crew by throwing
them into troubled waters one by one!
And he even cursed the gods!
The name of the captain was Vander Decken
and the ship was the Flying Dutchman!
The gods got mad at him
and set him adrift forever
under constant tortured!
And the ship right in front of us is
Captain Vander Decken's haunted ship!
Calm down!
We thought that Brook's ship
was a ghost ship but it wasn't.
What we found on that ship was nothing
special - just this funny skeleton!
Franky-san is harsh!
And 30 degrees is hard!
You're right!
Ghost ships aren't something
that you see often.
We just saw the Kraken which was
believed to be an imaginary monster
so it's not that surprising
to see a ghost ship.
Then maybe that's...
A real ghost ship!
I'm scared!
Robin, you can't entertain
yourself by making them upset.
Captain Vander Decken!
Wadatsumi and Ankoro got a pirate ship!
Stupid humans! But they
have quite a good ship.
They have a whole bunch
of treasure! I suspect!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Please come back!
Shut up! We have to get
through this by ourselves!
So Luffy and the others can come back to us!
The water temperature has been
increasing for quite a while.
Could this be...
Ankoro! Wadatsumi!
We can't seize their treasure
if you eat the ship
so knock it down!
I got it!
--Oh no, the Sea Bonze is...
--He's our enemy after all!
--Franky, use Coup de Burst!
--I can't! The fuel has run out!
I have to fill up with
cola in the energy room!
We don't have time!
--No!
--He's gonna get us!
Kraken!
The Monster of the Arctic--Kraken?
You bastard!
Alright, that's enough. Stop!
Good job!
Hey!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
I'm glad that you're all alive!
What were you doing?!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
We've been looking for you guys!
They're so high-maintenance. They got lost!
Sanji, no! He's relapsing!
He needs rehab with less stimulating pics!
Hey! Wake up, Wadatsumi!
Avenge yourself! Get back at it!
Well, Sanji's bubble and mine
popped so we got into Zoro's.
I thought I was gonna die!
Don't make us worry!
Alright, here's a song to
celebrate your return.
Lots of space!  There's no place like home!
Luffy! I was scared!
You all have an amazing ability to survive.
I can't believe it!
You really tamed the monster octopus?
And are you gonna use the Kraken?
Yeah, I'm gonna use him like
experienced people do!
Right, Surume?
That's a squid snack!
Surume!
The Kraken is an octopus but
he named it Surume, oh yeah!
Alright, draw the Sunny, Surume!
Well, instead of making him draw the ship,
we have to make sure that
he's not gonna smash it up.
Captain, the pirate ship is...
Don't let it get away! Go after it!
Yeah!
What is it?
This is no good, Captain Vander Decken!
Oh no, the undersea volcano's gonna erupt!
What?!
We are too close to it!
Everyone! Let's go back for now!
Roger! Captain Vander Decken!
Ankoro! Wadatsumi! Draw the ship!
Oh, okay!
I am the richest person in the
world - Captain Vander Decken!
Oh no!
Luffy, tell Kraken to get away from here now!
Yeah!
--Hey, Surume!
--Wait, don't need to!
He's running like hell already!
That's a terrible look for
such a mythical monster!
Nice! Maybe we can hit it off!
He runs awful.
Don't say that. That's how
horrifying the eruption is!
That's right!
And what is he doing?
Wow! Yes!
--Come on!
--It's rehab!
But I wanna see the eruption!
--Evacuate to the front of the ship!
--Yeah!
It doesn't change anything!
It's only a few meters.
Lava's flowing along to the sea floor!
The temperature is soaring!
Feels like I'm in boiling water!
I'm gonna be cooked!
The ghost ship and the Sea Bonze!
Run, Surume!
You can do it!
Go faster, Surume, or you're
gonna become boiled octopus!
Boiled octopus? That's
great! I wanna eat some!
Because of the difference in temperature,
the sea current's starting to swirl!
Nami-san,
which way is the Fish-Man Island...
Even at a time like this?
Sanji, you have to focus on your rehab!
Keep going straight!
We're getting close!
Jump into that trench!
What?!
In there?!
No!
It's a sheer cliff! You've got to be kidding!
It's darker than dark!
Are you sure that the
Fish-Man Island is in there?!
It's hot in the back!
It's totally dark in the front! Scary!
I'm sure there'll be another monster!
I don't think we can make it home alive!
Luffy! The darkness is a bottomless
pot that connects to hell!
Iron pot! Tea caddy! Tea-tea caddy!
Jump in, Surume!
It's erupting again!
What is that?! Right above us!
--Rocks?!
--Mud?!
It's an avalanche of rocks and earth!
The eruption caused it!
I think even the Sunny would break apart
if one of those giant rocks hits it!
Get away, Surume!
I'm gonna go out and cut them!
Luffy! Hold on tightly to my leg!
Okay, I got it!
Zoro, no!
--Hey, let me go!
--Why are you stopping him, Robin?
We're 8,000 meters deep now!
If you go out, you'll be crushed
by the water pressure!
Then what should we do?!
If we can buy some time to
get away from the cliff!
Leave it to me!
Sure Kill; Green Star...
..."Sargasso"!
The sea plant popped out!
--It stopped...
--...The avalanche.
That's so cool, Usopp!
Cool!
It only holds for a while.
Now is the chance to get away, Surume!
Just in time!
Usopp, that was great!
Yes, it was great judgment!
We made it through!
It's not like I was fooling
around for the past 2 years.
Let me tell you about it!
It's a very touching story!
The days of the relentless
diet with Master Heracles'n...
Maybe next time.
Why next time?!
Nami-san is harsh!
Surume, you did great too!
--We're safe now!
--Thank you, Surume!
Surume! Surume! Hey!
Surume! Hey! Surume! Come on!
Su...
10,000 METERS BELOW SEA LEVEL "THE DEEP"
(THE BOTTOM OF THE OCEANIC TRENCH)
I... I'm alive!
Light? This deep in the sea?
It's too bright! My eyes are dazzled!
But I don't have eyes to be dazzled.
Hey guys, come here!
Look at that!
I can't see it--it's too bright.
Hey Nami, is that it?
Yeah, there's no doubt.
The needle is pointing at the island!
That is...
The Fish-Man Island!
It's huge!
It's in a big bubble! There are
clouds? Maybe there is air inside.
That's the Fish-Man Island
so we're 10,000 meters deep now!
How is there such a big
tree this deep in the water?
Yeah! We made it!
It's a popular site in the Grand Line!
They made it there!
The Mermaids dance around
here. The beautiful Mermaids!
I'm finally here!
The paradise that I've been
dreaming of since I was a kid!
Mermaido! Mermaido!
Mermai...
Sanji! You're not ready!
You shouldn't even think about it!
Sanji!
I'm sorry, Sanji! The rehab didn't work yet!
You shouldn't look at real Mermaids.
Doctor! It was his dream to see the
Mermaids on the Fish-Man Island!
But he's gonna die if he sees them!
No!
I don't care...
Sanji!
Rather than live longer without a dream,
I wanna die staring at the
Mermaids in a disgusting way!
You're scum!
I'm gonna look at the Mermaids!
--He's burning!
--The flame of his eroticism!
I can't wait! I wonder what
kind of meat is in their dishes!
Luffy, wipe your drool.
Can you give an order to Surume?
Let's look for the entrance.
Hey, what are they?!
Who are they?
The group of sea monsters!
We're dead! After we got all the way here!
They're so cool! The sea monsters!
Somebody's riding it!
Mysterious Fish-Men block their
entry to the Fish-Man Island.
They mention Arlong,
whom the Straw Hats had defeated,
and call themselves the New Fish-Men Pirates.
To evade the menacing sea beasts,
Luffy and Co. decide to force
their way onto Fish-Man Island.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Landing at the Fish-Man Island!
Beautiful Mermaids!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!