Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago.
And in order to go on to the
next stage--the New World,
they set sail for the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
Hey guys, come here!
The Fish-Man Island!
It's huge!
It's in a big bubble! There are
clouds? Maybe there is air inside.
That's the Fish-Man Island
so we're 10,000 meters deep now!
Yeah! We made it!
Hey, what are they?!
Who are they?
The group of sea monsters!
We're dead! After we got all the way here!
They're so cool! The sea monsters!
Somebody's riding it!
"Landing at the Fish-Man Island!
Beautiful Mermaids!"
Why are you obeying such fools as humans,
Kraken!
What are you doing, Surume?!
We were almost there!
Saying that won't help!
Hang on! Don't get thrown off!
My eyes are spinning!
So are mine! But I don't have eyes!
We're right in middle of the sea monsters!
You guys are the Straw Hats, aren't you?
Wh-Who are you? How do you know about us?
Yes, I know you all very well.
You are the ones who foiled the
plans of the Arlong Pirates.
That act was easy enough to understand.
But then you stood up for Hachi-san,
the former officer of the Arlong Pirates 2 years ago
and knocked one of the hateful
Celestial Dragons out!
Just like Fisher Tiger, the hero of
the Fish-Man Island who we respect.
Fisher... Tiger...
THE NEW FISH-MAN PIRATES - FIGHTER HAMMOND
It's hard to decide what I should do with you.
So, tell me. Are you guys our enemies or not?
THE NEW FISH-MAN PIRATES – ASSASSIN HYOUZOU
THE NEW FISH-MAN PIRATES - FIGHTER KASAGON
I give you an option.
Do you wanna enlist under our banner -
the New Fish-Man Pirates?
Or do you refuse?
If you refuse, we'll sink you.
What did you say?
Franky, fuel up!
What are you gonna do?
You know that Luffy and the
others won't give in to them.
But we're 10,000 meters deep now.
We can't even fight and
there's no chance to win.
So we run!
Do the Coup de Burst using all the air we
have and charge into the Fish-Man Island!
Are you serious?
Otherwise, we are all gonna
die after coming this far.
It seems like that's the
only way that we can survive.
Okay, I'll fill it up. Franky, steer the ship!
Alright, super count on me!
Looks like they're getting busy.
Aren't they up to something?
Humans are not so clever anyway.
It's no use doing anything.
So, do you wanna work under us, Straw Hat Luffy?
No way! Stupid!
You refused... the offer to join
the New Fish-Man Pirates!
Then you guys are the Fish-Men's
enemy! Just sinful human beings!
Bleah!
Why should we work under you?!
Luffy, don't rub them the wrong way!
It's a shame. Then we can't
let you pass through here.
This is where we sink you!
Sea Lion!
It's done! Franky, do it!
Roger!
Sink it!
Wanna fight?!
Go, Franky!
The Sunny is a lion too!
Let's fight someday, Sea Lion!
Here we go! Coup de Burst!
The ship is...!
We're losing air...
We're gonna get crushed...
I can't breathe! But I don't have lungs.
Endure it! Until we reach the Fish-Man Island!
What's wrong with that ship?!
We're heading in!
Wait for me, my dear Mermaids!
The coating came off!
It got stuck on the giant bubble!
Oh, look ahead!
What is that?!
The bubble here is a double structure!
Normal ships will fall in this
layer because there is only air!
We're gonna run into one
more bubble! Hold on tight!
Water?!
The current is strong!
Help... me...
Can't breathe...
We have 4 Devil Fruit eaters but...
Reach...
...out!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Damn! I can't swim against the current!
That's a crazy way to get in there.
Maybe they tried to self-destruct.
Do you wanna go after them, Hammond?
I don't know if they're still alive though.
Yeah, we'll go in.
I don't want Neptune's army to find them first.
But first, let's go back to
Noah and let Boss know that...
...Straw Hat who shattered
Arlong-san's ambition is here.
THE FISH-MAN ISLAND - THE SEA FLOOR
Hey.
Hey, look.
--I'll look.
--I won't!
--Maybe I'll look.
--I looked, so what?
Hey, he's moving!
--He moved!
--He didn't!
--Maybe he moved.
--He moved, so what?
Yeah, he woke up!
Luffy!
Where am I?
Oh, Luffy-chin!
I'm glad that you're okay!
How are you?
Camie! It's been a while!
You've gotten prettier, Camie-chan!
Yeah, long time no see!
I'm glad to see you again!
Camie is here - that means...
We landed on the Fishman Island?!
Yeah, we did!
I've been told that we were
drowning but some Mermaids rescued us!
That's right.
As a matter of fact, we just woke up a couple minutes ago too.
This is Camie-chan's house.
Here's your hat.
Oh, this is Camie's house.
I'm sorry!
I was gonna pick you guys up
but I thought it was a month later.
Don't worry!
Where are the others?
Well... it looks like we got separated.
I wonder if they're okay.
Is that so?
Yeah, I was following them up to some point
but they were taken somewhere else.
Well, I'm sure they'll be fine!
I think so. The bone can't do much in the sea
but they got the robot and the
green one so they'll be fine!
Yeah, they'll be fine
I wanna see the others too.
Oh, here! I know you're all freezing.
I made soup so have some and get warm.
Ta-dah! Cold seaweed soup!
You'll love it!
Cold soup?
Uh-huh!
You can't get warm with
cold soup! What should I do?!
What?!
I made a mistake!
Don't worry, Camie-chan!
It warms me up anyway!
How is that possible?
Hey, Sanji! I want some too!
Your clothes are dry!
--They are dry.
--They aren't dry!
--Maybe they are dry.
--They are dry, so what?
You dried our clothes! Thanks!
Thank you!
By the way, who are you guys?
Oh, they're my friends.
The Medaka Mermaid Quintuplets.
--I'm Ichika!
--I'm Nika!
--I'm Sanka!
--I'm Yonka!
I'm Yonka Two!
Why can't it be Goka?
They swim fast and they're pretty savvy.
Oh, really?
We're at the sea floor of the Mermaid Cove.
And this is the girls' dorm for the Mermaid Cafe
so I have a lot of friends here!
What?
G... G... G...
Girls' dorm?!
Oh no!
Camie-chan!
What... what... What is Mermaid Cafe?
It's a cafe where I'm working as a waitress.
There are a lot of beautiful Mermaids!
B-Beautiful Mermaids?!
Do you want a cup of coffee? Or...
--Sanji is...
--...In danger!
--Dammit!
--He endured!
I...
I swore that I'd never have
a nosebleed and pass out...
...on the Fish-Man Island!
So I should be rewarded by now, shouldn't I...?
How desperate...
Oh yeah, let's go up!
I want you to meet my friends.
Oh, it's a turtle!
It says "Sea Turtle Elevator."
Turtle-chin, take us up.
This is a coral apartment in the sea.
The dorm is at the very
bottom so the rent is cheap.
The top floor gets natural light
so it's the most expensive.
Are you poor? By the way,
where are Hachi and Pappagu?
Ha-chin got severely
injured about a year ago.
He tried to protect the Sunny at Sabaody.
I heard that he's pretty much recovered now
but Ha-chin is originally from the Fish-Man District so
he's resting there.
Fish-Man District?
Yeah, it's kind of a rough area
but I can take you there since
I feel safe with you guys.
Let's go later! I have to
thank him face to face.
Okay, I got it! And Pappagu is...
He's a very famous designer
so he has a big mansion in Fishverly
Hills, the high-class district.
I'm gonna deliver clams
there today so come with me!
He's your pet, right?
Why don't you live with him?
That area is way beyond my means.
We have better clams here, anyway.
We're almost there!
What's that straw-like thing?
Oh, that's...
...the Water Road that a bubble craftsman made.
We and the fish get in and...
Here, watch.
Oh, that's fast!
It's great!
Camie-chan, where are you going?!
We're here, on the surface!
Luffy-chin!
See? I can even swim in the sky!
Oh, looks fun!
Wait a minute!
Besides that, there's a sky
and clouds in the deep sea!
You're right! I wonder how it's possible!
Hey, Camie!
Huh? It's a girl's voice!
Where is she?
Everybody!
That's...
Are your friends fine now?
The pirates who were drowning.
You guys didn't come in by the entrance.
Hello! You guys don't look that scary.
You guys entered illegally?
So wild! I love pirates!
It's like a living fairy tale!
A land of coral! The Mermaid Cove!
Sanji is crying!
He's crying harder than
when he left the Baratie.
I found it!
This is my All Blue!
Is it really what you want, Sanji?
Let me introduce them to you!
He's the captain - Luffy-chin.
Yeah, good to see you!
The crying one is Sanji-chin.
The one with the nose - Usopp-chin.
Nice to meet you!
The racoon is Chopper-chin.
I'm a reindeer!
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
Come with me! Let's dance in the water!
Oh yeah, I get it now. This is too good to be true.
I'm probably gonna die today!
How negative!
Seriously, what happened to you in the past 2 years?
This is the paradise that
you've been dreaming of!
You're so funny, Sanji!
No, he's not trying to be funny!
THE FISH-MAN DISTRICT "NOAH"
I see.
Straw Hat Luffy finally got this far.
Yes.
What should we do, Boss?
Bring him...
...here!
At Mermaid Cove Sanji reverts to his
old self and fools around with the mermaids.
But then the three Princes
of Fish-Man Island arrive.
Not knowing what to expect, they hide,
though then an unimaginable accident occurs.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Excitement Blow-out!
Sanji's Life Under Threat!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!