Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and the rest of the Straw Hats
returned to Sabaody Archipelago.
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level...
...only to be attacked
by the New Fish-Man Pirates
out of  the blue and
become separated again.
Luffy and the others were rescued by
Mermaids and were brought to Camie's house.
Sanji-chan!
We don't have time! Anyone?!
Somebody please! I beg you!
Give blood to Sanji!
"The Fish-Man Island Will Be Annihilated?!
Sharley's Prophecy!"
Please! Spare him some blood!
My friend is dying!
Someone with blood type S RH negative?!
We don't have time! Donate your blood!
We beg you!
I'm sorry, Sanji-chin.
It's very hard for humans to get a
blood transfusion on this island.
But Luffy-chin and the others will...!
Damn! I've been looking so hard but I
can't find anybody who'll give blood!
I'm not gonna give up!
There must be somebody!
Sanji...
Human!
Luffy! I found a human here!
That barrel drifted here along
with Camie's friends. What's in it?
Liquor? Treasure?
I don't know. It's very tightly-sealed.
What do you think? Should
we open it secretly?
Is it okay to do that?
I think so.
Oh? You're well-prepared, Ishilly!
Sanji! Are you awake?
Sanji-chin!
Where am I?
What a relief!
We're in a town at the harbor.
Sanji-chin, you lost almost
all the blood from your body.
I'm so glad that we found the blood donor!
Oh, blood...
What's wrong with me?
Don't get up so fast! You need to rest more.
But why won't the Fish-Men donate blood?
We looked everywhere in the
town but we couldn't find a human.
I almost gave up!
Guys, thank you for doing that.
But I don't remember anything.
Where was I and what was I doing?
I can barely remember...
No, don't think back!
We don't want you to have a nosebleed again!
Oh yeah, Sanji! Let me introduce you
to the blood donor that
we finally found at a bar!
You have to say "thank you"!
Huh? Don't tell me that I got
blood from such a delicate lady!
It's okay! We're both humans.
We have to help each other
when we're in trouble.
It's okay, silly!
If you want...
...We can give you more, silly!
I'm glad that he's back to his old self!
Hey, say "thank you" to them!
Luffy, let me see your right arm.
Positive reaction for poison!
That's a poisonous wound as I thought!
Come to think of it, when I
fought against the Fish-Men...
I felt something sting me.
But you're okay?
Uh-huh.
Okay, let me see it.
This must be deadly poison.
Are you really okay?
Uh-huh.
I can't believe it!
An antibody must have developed
in your body to counter such poison.
Have you ever been poisoned before?
Poison, huh?
I almost died from
poisoning in the Impel Down.
Almost died? It's not funny!
I think it was that guy!
The swordsman with octopus tentacles.
He blocked my punch!
I bet he's very strong!
That's coming from the cove.
Those Mermaids are really noisy.
Now what should I do?
These guys are all messed-up.
And I accidentally poisoned Straw Hat.
I'll be in trouble if he dies.
Ishilly and the others were screaming!
Ishilly!
I heard them around here!
Where did they go?
I heard them talking about opening a barrel.
Everyone, come here.
There's somebody I'd like you to meet.
The owner of the Mermaid
Cafe who let Sanji stay...
What is this?
...Madam Sharley.
Oh yeah? Thanks!
Is the blond boy okay now?
THE OWNER OF THE MERMAID CAFE MADAM SHARLEY
Uh-huh. But since you're
such a beautiful lady,
it's best you stay away from the room.
And let's not tell Sanji-chin
that this place is in the
back of the Mermaid Cafe.
Why's that?
His doctor, Chopper-chin said that if
he finds out, there'll be trouble again.
What a strange prognosis.
Hey, Big Mermaid!
It's Madam Sharley, Luffy-chin!
--What's this?
--It's beautiful!
Don't touch it, Straw Hat boys.
That's the crystal ball she
uses to look into the future.
Madam's pre-vision is
famous in the Coral Hill.
I'm not practicing anymore.
It's better not knowing the future.
Well, how about this? Do you Mermaids poop?
What does that have to
do with her pre-vision?
Don't you have any class?
A-Apologize to her, Luffy-chin!
Sorry.
Camie, you can take a day off today.
Show them around the island.
Huh? Really?
You always work hard.
And...
...these days we don't
have human pirate guests
and my business is drying up.
The girls from the cove will come soon
so we have enough hands (hitode).
Enough starfish (hitode)...
Oh no! I should have delivered
those clams to Pappagu by now!
That was so out-of-context!
He must be hungry...
What? Monsieur Pappagu is having
fun at the cafe with his old friend.
At the cafe?
Old friend?
I couldn't mention this in front of her,
but when Madam was a little child,
she said that many pirates
would come to the island.
That was the year before
the Great Pirate Era began.
What?!
Among a host of other things,
she recently predicted the war at Marineford
and Whitebeard's death.
What?!
She can't stand knowing
what bad things will happen.
Must be scary!
Where's Chopper?
Oh, he's taking care of Sanji.
--Luffy-chin! Usopp-chin!
--Yeah!
This is the main street of Coral Hill.
Look! That's the entrance
of the Mermaid Cafe.
Oh, I'm getting hungry!
It's a cafe!
We have food too! Cakes and sea fruit.
What about meat?
We Merfolk don't eat meat and fish
so what we have is; Wakame Brûlée,
Mozuku Tart, Kelp Soufflé...
Are they edible?
--Oh, we have meat too!
--What?
Shellfish meat! Scallop
Sandwich, Freshwater Clam Pizza...
That's not meat!
Don't ruin meat's reputation!
Whoa... Anyway, let's
go in! The Mermaid Cafe!
Yeah, Pappagu will be there.
Hey, don't ruin meat's reputation!
Thank you very much!
Resting my bones! Resting my bones!
I'm happy for you, Bone!
--Brook!
--Brook-chin!
Oh, Luffy-san and Usopp-san!
And it's been a while, Camie-san!
Could I look at your panties...
She's a Mermaid!
Straw! Nose!
I missed you guys!
I didn't know that you were here!
Long time no see!
So you were with Pappagu!
Yes, I didn't expect to be
rescued by Pappagu-san!
I was so lucky!
Yeah, that was just as surprising to me!
While I was polishing off an
idea for a new design at the cove,
I saw some bones drifting
towards me rolling along.
Those are bones!
Soul King, come to see us again!
I had a wonderful time!
I'll be back, beautiful Mermaids!
What?!
I'm going boneless!
Oh, I can't exist without bones!
Oh, I don't care if I die now!
Oh no, I'm already dead!
How cool!
He got so hyper in the cafe...
Yeah, I wonder what's going on inside.
Wait, wait, wait!
You aren't leaving today, are you?
I know you are interested in the cafe
but you can come back with everybody later.
I was gonna take Bone to my house now.
Come with me! Do you like sea monster meat?
Do you have meat?!
I'm wild, I don't wanna eat
seaweed or shellfish!
What I mainly eat is violent sea monsters!
Oh, Pappagu, I almost forget!
Here are your clams for today.
Yeah! Camie's best clams!
So you eat shellfish!
Damn!
Lovely Mermaid...
Yes?
Fantastic Mermaid...
Are you alright?
--Beautiful! Elegant! Wonderful! Sniff, sniff!
--I wonder how they're doing...
Unlike Merfolk, Fish-Men eat meat and fish.
It's not like we don't have them here.
Oh, glad to hear that!
Oh, just what I was looking for! Hey, taxi!
Here I go!
What?!
Vander Decken! He's a ghost -
Why are they looking for him?!
Oh, this guy was on the
ghost ship that we saw?
--What?! Did you guys see him?
--Yes.
The whole nation has been
looking for him for years!
He's a pirate--an undersea bandit!
I'll tell you about it later. Get on first!
Vander Decken was sending love letters...
...to the Mermaid Princess of the
Ryugu Kingdom at least once a week.
Before long, the letters became
packages, then threats to marry him...
Oh, it's fluffy! Feels good!
Yeah, it's like heaven!
Listen to a starfish!
--Okay!
--Oh, sorry.
His eccentric behavior made
the Mermaid Princess afraid
and it became a national concern...
Yeah, the Mermaid Princess'
father - King Neptune got mad
and those 3 princes that we just met
have been looking for him with the army
but they can't find him.
Camie, Camie... I was just
telling them about it...
King Neptune, the God of the Sea,
who runs this country...
...has 4 children including
the Mermaid Princess.
The Mermaid Princess is the youngest
and the 3 princes are older than her.
Hey, Camie...
But what I can't understand is
Vander Deck must be a ghostly
pirate from hundreds of years ago...
Well, those legends are often exaggerated.
He truly existed and in fact,
I heard that the legendary
captain--Vander Decken...
...reached the Fish-Man Island and died here.
The ship that you saw was the
Flying Dutchman, wasn't it?
It's his descendent who is on the ship!
Vander Decken IX!
What?! His descendent?!
Oh, is that so?
That means he's not a ghost.
I thought that it was a real ghost and felt
more dead than alive since I'm a skeleton.
That's good. That's just good.
Camie... Camie... Camie...
When I look closer,
Merfolk and Fish-Men are all different.
There are old Mermaids! Like Grandma Kokoro!
Look, there's a baby!
The father is a Fish-Man and the
children are Merfolk and Fish-Men.
When a Mermaid and a Fish-Man get married,
their kids would be either Merfolk
or Fish-Man, either boy or girl.
So there are 4 possibilities.
Hmmm, that's why they're all different.
Interesting!
Alright, let's get on the highway!
It's fast!
What's that?
That's a candy factory.
No, why is there a pirate flag?!
That? You can see the same flag at the
entrance of the island and at the harbor.
That flag is protecting
the Fish-Man Island.
The mark belongs to a pirate called
Charlotte Linlin of the New World.
Also known as Big Mam,
one of The Four Emperors!
Th-The Four Emperors?
Before the war, Whitebeard was
protecting the island from pirates
but now it's Big Mam.
Hmmm.
But she demands a lot of sweet
candies every month in exchange.
That's what the factory is for.
Candies?
This country can't exist without the
protection of those powerful people.
That's how dangerous this place is,
where pirates come and go frequently.
But she's protecting the country
after old man Whitebeard.
Isn't Big Mam a good person?
It's hard to say.
Whitebeard never demanded anything.
So Big Mam views it as business, maybe.
Big Mam...
One of The Four Emperors like Shanks.
Wonder if I'll meet her someday.
Look forward!
We're in Fishverly Hills,
the town of the celebs!
That tall building right in
front of us is Pappagu's house.
That?! That's too much for a starfish!
We have to do something!
She's a madam from the Mermaid Cafe.
What's the matter, Madam Sharley?
Why are you so upset?
We have to do something before it's too late!
Hey, Madam! What's wrong?
Look for him!
The pirate boy with a straw hat!
And throw him out of this country!
Is it a pre-vision again?
I wasn't planning on using it.
But I felt something about him
so I couldn't help looking into the future!
What's wrong?! What did you see?!
Madam!
Sharley! Say it!
--Madam!
I hope it won't happen!
I hope it'll be proven wrong!
A human with a straw hat on...
At Straw Hat Luffy's
hands...  at his hands...
the Fish-Man Island will be...
...destroyed!!
Fish-Man Island shines with beauty.
But history has created a darkness
Hating humans, they desire retribution.
Their plans are mobilizing beneath the surface.
Meanwhile, Luffy and his crew run amok at Pappagu's shop,
and the king of Fish-Man Island, Neptune himself descends from his palace.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The King of the Fish-Man Island!
Neptune, the God of the Sea!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!