Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he
ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training.
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
they reached to the Fish-Man Island located
10,000 meters below sea level.
However...
The pirate boy with a straw hat!
Throw him out of this country!
A human with a straw hat on...
At Straw Hat Luffy's hands... at his
hands... the Fish-Man Island will be...
...destroyed!!
"The King of the Fish-Man Island!
Neptune, the God of the Sea!"
Guys! Hurry up-chin!
Quiet! Stay quiet!
We're in trouble if they notice.
Now is the chance! Get on the ship-chin!
Everybody, grab an oar and be ready!
THE FISH-MAN DISTRICT "NOAH"
Hurry up! They'll come
after us at any minute!
I'll never return to the Fish-Man Island!
Hurry up and cross the Red Line!
Damn! The Mermaid Cafe of my dreams!
I wanted to take one look
at the beautiful Mermaids!
Let it go, you idiots! Shut your
mouths and just keep rowing!
Damn! What a disaster!
As soon as we got away
from the sleeping Kraken,
we were surrounded by...
A PIRATE FROM THE SOUTH BLUE "CRAB-HAND" GYRO
...so many sea monsters at
10,000 meters below sea level
and couldn't even fight back!
Should I enlist under the
Fish-Men's banner or die?
I had no choice but to enlist
under their banner for a while!
How absurd!
Why do we humans have to enlist
under the Fish-Men's banner?!
Oh, we're moving away from the Mermaid Cafe!
Stop crying and let's go, guys!
We are lucky to even be alive!
Huh? They escaped?
Yes, Boss. As soon as my back was turned.
Did they escape again-dosun?
They never learn, don't they-dosun?
Humans always escape.
Should I bite off their flesh?
What a pain in the butt-ch!
No problem!
We can make them an example as always.
THE CAPTAIN OF THE NEW
FISH-MAN PIRATES HORDY JONES
Then I'll go get them-ch!
No, you won't, Ikaros.
Much, yes sir!
I'll go!
Huh?
Get the bubble ready!
You can't take that much at once!
That's the power drug!
Now here we are!
This is my house!
It's huge!
Welcome home, Master-sama!
Hey, that's Monsieur Pappagu!
--You mean that really famous guy?!
--Wow! Is it really him?
Oh, you're popular, huh?
Yeah! Are you guys surprised?!
When I'm in the water, I'm just a...
...fashionable starfish but...
...on the Fish-Man Island, I'm the president
and a very popular designer
of the Criminal Brand Co.
The brand is known all over the world now
and we have stores in many countries!
Even the famous Doskoi Panda is...
Oh, look at that! What is it?
Are you listening, Straw?!
--The 1st floor is a Criminal store.
--Oh!
Camie... Camie...
--Let's go there!
--Uh-huh!
Hey!
Listen to my story...
Whoa, Miss, that's impossible!
What is it?
A shop assistant sounds troubled.
A complaint?
As I said, the clothes
here are too expensive!
They're cute but...
That must be...
So let's make it 10,000 berries.
That's too cruel, Miss!
It's less than half price!
It's her as I thought.
Hey, Nami!
--Luffy!
--Nami-chin!
Camie!
It's been a while! How are you?!
Fine!
Hey, what's going on?
Oh, Monsieur Pappagu,
you came at the right time!
We have a troublesome customer.
Hey, so you own this store, huh?
Why is everything so expensive?
Are you ripping me off?
Monsieur!
Well, that's what they call brand
equity because I'm a popular designer...
--Give me a discount!
--No, you...
We're friends, aren't we?
I owe you guys big time from 2 years ago!
It's all free! Take as much as you want!
Free?! Really?!
--Guys! Let's not show mercy!
--Yeah!
Thank you!
Monsieur! They took everything!
You're so merciless!
I'm happy for you, guys!
Oh? What is it?
Something's going on outside the store.
Monsieur! Th-This is serious!
What is it?
I-I-It's him!
Him?
It's him!
Look! There in the air...
He came from the palace!
Jamon! Jamon!
Jamon! Jamon! Jamon!
What is it? A whale?
Why did he come down to the lower world?
This is the first time
I've seen him in person!
What's this about?
He doesn't even have guards.
This can't be happening!
He's never travelled like this!
Something wrong with the kingdom?
He doesn't bother coming down
here unless there is a problem!
Who is that old man?
Idiot, don't you know who
he is? That man is...
...the king of the Ryugu Kingdom
on the Fish-Man Island -
Neptune-sama!
THE KING OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
NEPTUNE THE GOD OF THE SEA
Neptune!
Whale!
HOE (A PET WHALE)
That's a big Merman there...
I prefer Mermaids...
Cut it out, guys!
He's a very hairy old man!
That's rude! Get down on your knees now!
The whale's cute!
--He came to see those humans?
--He personally came for that?
Hey, Megalo! Are you sure that
it was these people-jamon?
Oh? We saw that shark in the water!
Yeah, the one with clothes!
He had been captured by Surume!
You Straw Hat people.
Wh-What do you want?
I'm going to...
...invite you to the Ryugu Palace-jamon!
What?!
Ryu-Ryu-Ryu-Ryu-Ryu-Ryugu Palace!
Ryugu Palace?
THE RYUGU KINGDOM CORAL HILL
MADAM SHARLEY'S HOUSE
Good! Your pulse is getting back
to normal. You should be fine now.
You have to thank those
two for donating blood.
Those two...
It's okay, silly!
If you want, we can give you more, silly!
I thank them but I wanna forget about them.
I'm so glad!
It'd be crazy if you died
from loss of  blood before
you saw Nami and Robin again!
Nami-san...
Robin-chan...
Oh no! Sanji is in danger!
Hey, come here! Splash! Splatta!
What is it? Do you need our blood again?
If it's so, just tell us! You can have...
...As much as you want!
You have to stay calm, silly!
We'll stay here and...
...Take care of you!
No thank you!
--Don't be shy!
--Stay calm - it's bad for your health!
You two are the worst for my health!
--So shy!
--Stay away!
Be patient, Sanji!
Go away, fools!
Ryu-Ryu-Ryu...
Ryugu Palace?!
That's right-jamon!
What?!
I can't believe they're invited
to the palace...
Who are those humans?
King Neptune came to pick them up himself...
They know Monsieur Pappagu!
Maybe they're famous...
--Look, there's Soul King!
--Yeah!
What's the Ryugu Palace?
Idiot, don't you know what it is?!
I'll tell you.
It's pretty much a holy
place for us citizens.
A celestial world where
ordinary people are not allowed!
The Ryugu Palace is...
...the place where King Neptune,
the Neptune 3 prince brothers,
and the Mermaid Princess live - it's...
...The royal palace of the Ryugu Kingdom!
Oh...
Camie, again!
Hmmm... So, old man...
Don't call him that!
Is there a lot of good
food at the Ryugu Palace?
Straw!
Of course. We are prepared
to have a banquet-jamon.
Oh yeah? I can't wait!
I'd like to see the Ryugu Palace!
My heart is filled with expectations.
But I don't have a heart to be filled!
I wanna go too!
Ryugu Palace! I sense treasure!
I knew that'd be what you're interested in!
Okay, let's go!
Hmmm. Alright, Megalo,
give the Straw Hat
people a ride to the Ryugu Palace-jamon.
Can I get on?
Wow! Cool!
Are we gonna meet the Mermaid Princess?
I can't wait!
What are you doing? Come with us!
Huh? Well, we don't deserve to
go to the Ryugu Palace... Right?
Stop grumbling and come!
Let's have a banquet!
--You can't say goodbye here!
--Is it okay, grandpa?
You can't say "grandpa"...
Your friends can come-jamon.
Hear that? Grandpa,
you're an understanding person!
Like I said, that person is...
You guys... really... please!
Alright, let's go!
To the Ryugu Palace!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Go faster-chin! They'll come any minute!
It's hard to catch a current in the deep sea!
This is why we should've
put paddle wheels on!
You know, the New World is...
Captain! Look!
There's something in front of us!
That's...
Hordy Jones!
N-No way! He found us!
What? He has...
What the...? He has handcuffs on.
No way! He's gonna fight us, isn't he?
He vanished!
Where did that bastard go?!
What?! What happened?!
We've taken damage!
He's too fast!
He's here on the ship!
Take him out! He's the only enemy!
No way! It didn't work!
I fought a Fish-Man before!
I've been through hell to get here!
You're only a fish - Don't
mess with humans, you fool!
Captain!
Dammit!
Boy, what we got is a hell of a thing-ch!
The power drug - Energy Steroid!
Fish-Men were born to be 10
times stronger than humans.
But once we take one Energy Steroid,
our physical strength will double.
20 times stronger than humans.
If we take 2, it'll double that!
This dream power will shorten our lives!
But we're not afraid of dying
- we just adhere to the plan!
--Wh-What is he doing?!
--What is he gonna do with the mast?!
Is that why he has those handcuffs!
He wants to show us that he can sink
us without even using his hands!
Humans killed Fisher Tiger
and shattered Arlong's dream!
The dark and tragic history
of the Fish-Men will end now...
...with the help of us,
the New Fish-Man Pirates!
Take them to the New World
and set them adrift.
Oh no! You didn't kill all of them, did you?
No, I need them alive.
You humans, survive with cuts and
bruises to show the people on earth...
...what happened to you in the sea.
And who you met.
Tell them how horrendous it was.
We'll capture the center of
the world, the Fish-Man Island,
from the gutless God of the Sea - Neptune
and drag you humans down
to the dark sea bottom!
You'll all learn that the
Fish-Men are the supreme race!
At the king of Fish-Man Island, Neptune's invitation,
Luffy and his crew make their to a banquet at the Ryugu Palace.
However, Luffy's hunger gets the better of him and as soon as he smells food,
he separates from the group.
Luffy then and discovers a gigantic tower locked with a door stuck with swords and axes!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Ryugu Palace! Taken by
the Shark that They Saved!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!