Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training.
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
However, there they found the New Fish-Man
Pirates disturbing the peace and order.
What's wrong with you?
Who are you, sir?!
What?! It was a big
person... I mean, Mermaid!
Somebody! Father-sama! Brother-sama!
Whoa, whoa! I didn't do
anything to you, did I?!
Oh, damn! What's with you?!
"A Coward and a Crybaby!
The Princess in the Hard Shell Tower!"
Hey!
Keep lighting up!
How many times do I have to tell you?
A CREW MEMBER OF THE FLYING PIRATES
WADATSUMI, THE GREAT MONK
It's not time for playing!
A snack!
Wadatsumi!
Didn't you get a reply yet?
A reply from Princess Shirahoshi?
No, not yet, Captain Decken.
How long have I been waiting for it?
For 10 years or so. And it hasn't come yet.
It's all because of that hateful Neptune!
He wants to plunge Princess
Shirahoshi into a political marriage!
I suspect!
In fact, the Princess has been locked
up in the steel tower for 10 years!
Oh, how painful this is!
Because we love each other!
I suspect!
THE CAPTAIN OF THE FLYING PIRATES
VANDER DECKEN IX
Princess Shirahoshi! I love you!
I love you! I love you!
I love you!
No matter how much I roam this vast seafloor,
I can't find someone who is as
big and beautiful as you are!
It's fine if we end up together.
But I can't allow you to
live with somebody else!
I'd rather see you dead than
with someone else, Shirahoshi!
Your life is either dead or marriage!
Let me present you with an ax with a
rose painted on it just as always!
Accept it, Shirahoshi!
As proof of our marriage!
Captain? It's way off the target.
Don't be silly! I don't miss!
I suspect.
It's coming back!
It's heading towards the Ryugu Palace!
THE ROYAL PALACE OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE RYUGU PALACE
Hey, hey, whoa! What's going on?
I'm just a pirate who came
here looking for food!
Listen to me!
Hey!
She's loud! What should I do?
Princess Shirahoshi-sama's crying!
--It's from the Hard Shell Tower!
--What are the tower guards doing?!
What?! Why is nobody with her?!
I'm sorry! The guard shifts were changing!
In any case, get to the tower now!
A human is... here in the
room... trying to kill me!
Huh? No! Hey! That's not true!
I was hungry and I didn't
know that the food was yours!
What's that ax?! Where did it come from?!
THE MAIN ENTRANCE OF THE RYUGU PALACE
Oh, boy!
When can we have a banquet?
How long do we have to wait?
My stomach is growling...
But I don't have a stomach to growl!
--Hey!
--Yes?
It doesn't look like we're
having a banquet any time soon!
Does this mean that we've
landed ourselves in trouble?
What should we do?!
I'm sorry that you came all the way
here but we've just received a call!
You Straw Hat people, you are suspects
in 2 ongoing investigations.
S-Suspects?! What do you mean?!
First, for multiple counts
of Mermaid kidnapping!
We didn't do such...
Second, you people are suspected
of being a potential risk...
...to the Fish-Man Island due to
Madam Sharley's prevision!
Huh? Prevision? You don't know
if that'll happen for real!
--Shut up!
--What's wrong with them?!
Is this the right thing to do?
Therefore, we're here to
take you people into custody!
Catch them at any cost!
We have to protect the Fish-Man Island!
Yeah!
Go!
Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
Somebody's coming!
I'm sorry to do this!
--Are you alright?
--Did you get hurt?
N-No!
You were crying louder
than usual - we were worried!
What are you...?!
Who opened this door?!
Was it an intruder?
I-I'm sorry to make you worry!
I think I had a bad dream...
Hey...!
--No, I heard somebody for sure!
--No, that's... Um... Well...
My stomach made a noise!
A-Are you sure?
Who is it?!
Megalo! Welcome home!
Oh yes! There is something
that I have to tell you.
It's about Straw Hat Luffy,
the pirate who saved Megalo.
He is suspected in the kidnapping
of some missing Mermaid girls.
And due to Madam Sharley's prediction,
all of the Straw Hats are considered
as an uncertain but potential risk
so we've decided to lock
them in the palace prison.
We took the swordsman who
came to the palace first
into custody while he was
sleeping due to intoxication.
The 3 members who just arrived are
probably in custody by now, too.
But their captain--Straw Hat, who was with
them, might have noticed our intentions
and ran away.
He is probably hiding somewhere
in the palace so please be careful.
We'll catch the rest of them on the island
and defend the country at any cost.
--I just heard something.
--Did you? Isn't it just your imagination?
--No, I'm sure I...
--No, it's just your imagination!
Okay. Anyway,
I feel bad that we have to arrest the
people who saved Megalo's life!
Princess-sama,
you're acting strangely. Are you hiding...
Minister of the Right, we have to go.
Oh, it's been 5 minutes already.
We're gonna go now.
Lock the doors tightly!
Thank you very much!
I was being very rude to you
before. Please forgive me!
I didn't know that you were the
one who saved Megalo's life.
May I call you Luffy-sama?
Uh-huh.
Luffy-sama, you are a pirate does
that mean you are a bad person?
I don't know. You decide.
Okay.
Oh, they said that our soldiers
took your friends into custody...
Yeah but that's fine. You guys can't
keep them under control anyway.
Is that so?
Don't worry about it.
Now tell me, what was that ax?
Who threw it? From where?
I know who did it...
His name is Vander Decken-sama.
He holds a grudge against
me for refusing to marry him.
That gentleman has a Devil's
power called Mark-Mark.
He can strike me anytime or
anywhere with a thrown weapon
since he designated me as his mark.
That's why it's too dangerous for
me to leave this Hard Shell Tower...
I'm hungry!
Yum-yum! Can I eat this?
Go ahead.
Yummy!
He wants to marry you but
he's trying to kill you?
It doesn't make sense, does it?
It's been 10 years already.
For 10 years?! You must be bored!
On top of that, my father made a rule that
soldiers can't stay here more than 5 minutes.
Hmmm.
That's why Megalo is the
only one that I can talk to.
He's my dear friend.
That's why they wanted
to have a banquet for us.
It must be canceled now.
I wonder why they want to put
Megalo's liberators in prison.
I heard that Madam Sharley-sama's
previsions are unbelievably accurate.
That explains why everyone's afraid, but...
Anyway, you humans eat a lot
even though you're small!
That hairy old man said... that we
were gonna have a banquet, but...
he kept getting scolded...
so I couldn't wait any longer...
and I followed the smell.
By the way, did they call you Princess?
Yes.
Are you the Mermaid Princess?
Yes. I am King Neptune's daughter.
My name is Shirahoshi.
--Shirasu (Baby sardine)?
--Shirahoshi.
Hmmm. That's hard to pronounce.
Oh, I wanna eat that too!
I don't think you're such a bad person.
Do you seek adventures since you're a pirate?
Uh-huh.
Oh yeah! Have you ever seen the sun?
There are stars in the
night sky, aren't there?
And there are different kinds
of flowers and hairy animals!
Have you ever been to a green
place called a "forest"?
Wait, wait! That's too many
questions! Wait a moment!
Okay!
Oh, that's a big cheek pouch!
Push!
Stop it! What are you doing?!
P-P-Please...
Don't yell at me like that!
Luffy-sama is a scary
man just as I thought...
Whoa, whoa! I didn't do
anything to make you cry! Stop!
I have never been yelled
at by anyone before...
You may be big but you're
a coward and a crybaby!
I don't like you!
What?!
No one ever said such a
horrible thing to me...
How awful you are! Please leave now!
I can't take it anymore!
I'm full! Thank you for the food!
So you've been here for 10 years, huh?
It could make you sick!
Luffy-sama, please leave now!
Hey, isn't there anywhere you wanna go?
Huh?
Of course, there are a lot
of places that I want to go...
That's what I thought.
Then let's get out of here!
What?
Let's go for a walk!
No... No, I'm not supposed to do that!
Why? Let's go!
--You're gonna be okay!
--Huh?
If something's thrown at
you again, I'll deflect it!
Boy! How can he sleep under
these circumstances?
He was drinking like crazy so...
--Hurry up!
--Yes, sir!
A lot of activity in the palace.
What's going on?
Usopp-chin! Nami-chin! Brook-chin!
Catch them!
They're just 3 humans!
What're you gonna do?!
Guys! If you resist more,
you're really gonna become criminals!
But there is no reason for
us to obey them, Camie-san.
I was looking forward to a
banquet at the Ryugu Palace.
They'll just arrest us if we don't resist!
They made an unthinkable
accusation against us first!
We will fight them forever
if that's what they want!
--They're so strong even without the captain!
--Can't believe it!
I don't know what we're
gonna do in the future.
But you can't arrest us now
for things we haven't done!
The nose guy wasn't ever
that remarkable, was he?!
Brook-chin and Nami-chin became
stronger than 2 years ago as well!
See? That's the prologue to the
future that has been predicted.
Yeah, right! If you guys didn't start it,
we wouldn't have to fight back in the first place!
He's right.
But this is nothing compared to giant
insects' all-out attack on the Bowin Islands!
Witness the power of my
new weapon - Black Kabuto!
Bring it on!
Neptune-sama, we need your help!
I wonder if it's fair to arrest
somebody based on a prediction.
I need some time to think-jamon!
Thus,
you need to be in custody for now!
He's formidable!
Take this!
Zoro!
I thought you'd been captured!
I heard the sound of this
festival so I let myself out!
Captain Decken, we're here!
Wait there, Wadatsumi!
THE FISH-MAN DISTRICT "NOAH"
Uh-huh, okay!
This way, sir.
Thank you for waiting!
Vander Decken-sama is here!
Please!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
We ran into a volcanic eruption.
So you're the notorious Hordy?
I suspect?
You're notorious, too.
Nutty Vander Decken.
--Nice to meet you.
--Oh, a handshake?
It's no good. Just a minute.
I'm all set!
Never mind!
Nice to meet you too, Hordy Jones!
We're unbeatable on the seafloor now.
The worst of the worst coming together!
Decken! Decken! Hordy! Hordy!
Decken! Decken!
Neptune is a nuisance for both of us.
We have the same goal.
Beat Neptune's army who take no
pride in being Fish-Men or Mermaids...
...And kill Neptune, the God of the Sea!
And...
...We will destroy...
...The Ryugu Kingdom completely!
The Straw Hats are facing the
God of the Sea, Neptune's army.
Neptune's soldiers attempt to break
the bubbles protecting Zoro's group
to turn the tables of the battle.
Meanwhile, unidentified
pirates continue to attack
the Hard Shell Tower where
Luffy and Shirahoshi are.
The tension inside the Ryugu
Palace continues to rise!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"It's an Emergency!
The Ryugu Place Is Occupied!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!