Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training.
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
Go, Shark!
To the Sea Forest!
"The Ryugu Palace in Shock!
The Kidnapping of Shirahoshi!"
SOUTHEAST OF THE FISH-MAN ISLAND
IN THE DEEP SEA
Thank you for coming all the way to see me!
Well, Tom-san told me that one of his family
members at home is also a shipwright, so...
But it must've been difficult
to come to the Fish-Man Island.
Difficult?
I was trained by Tom-san since I was a kid
and I came here with a ship that I made.
Since you were my brother's pupil,
I bet it's quite a ship.
Yeah, it's called the Thousand
Sunny and it's my masterpiece!
I would love to see it.
Well, after we entered the Fish-Man Island,
it was taken away by the tide.
That's part of reason that I came to see you.
I was wondering if you could give
me a clue as to Sunny's whereabouts.
You'll find it.
I hope so...
When a ship sinks in these parts,
it usually gets carried by the tide
and ends up at a certain place.
I think the Sunny will be there too.
Count on me, completely!
Completely, huh?
We'll get there soon.
The place known as the Sea Forest!
The Sea Forest?
Hey hey, Luffy-san!
Hey wait, Megalo! Where are you going?!
Father-sama, Brother-sama,
everybody at the palace, please forgive me!
I am going out without permission!
I'll be home by dinner!
Let's go for a "walk"!
What is going on, Megalo?!
I can't believe he left the doors open!
What if something happens to...
Skeleton, hurry up!
See if the Princess is okay!
Hey! You're riding my bones too hard!
She's not here!
Princess Shirahoshi is not here!
What?! The Mermaid Princess is not here?!
This is bad! This is a matter of
great consequence to the kingdom!
When did this happen?! Who did this?!
She must have been kidnapped!
Kidnapped?!
Princess-sama!
Princess-sama...
She must've been kidnapped?
Hey, what are you doing?!
The gate that connects the Fish-Man
Island and the Ryugu Palace...
Where is the switch to open it?!
Huh? The switch?
Skeleton, hurry and go back to Neptune-sama!
We have to tell him what is going on here!
We have no choice but to do as we're told.
They told us the only way
we'll live is if we obey them.
Just tell us!
Who are "they"?
They're gonna kill us if you don't tell us!
Kill you?
Tell us!
I don't know what you're talking about!
A FEW HOURS AGO THE FISH-MAN DISTRICT "NOAH"
What a pain in the ass!
Humans are such lowly creatures -
they can't even breathe in the water!
Listen, you pirates under
the control of Hordy Jones!
You should all be happy! Because you
can be part of this historic mission!
That's Vander Decken
of the Flying Dutchman?!
The captain of the cursed ghost ship?!
Don't worry, I'm his descendant.
I'm not a ghost.
Though I am cursed as well. I can't
swim even though I'm a Fish-Man.
I got this devil power alongside
of the Mark-Mark curse.
Let me show it to you!
Alright, you human right there! Step forward.
Huh?
Hordy!
Are you guys serious? Don't be crazy!
--It's Hachi-san!
--Hatchan-san!
--It's Hatchan-san!
Hachi-san...
The Energy Steroids will
do nothing but ruin you!
What's the point of destroying the island?
Don't underestimate the
Great Knight Neptune!
Hachi-san, give me a break.
I don't want to hear your voice anymore.
I can't believe you were an officer
of the pirate group that I admired.
You became a coward.
It's time for a generation change.
To teach humans a lesson,
we need the Fish-Man Island
so Neptune is in our way!
You all taught us that
we're the supreme race!
But Arlong-san lost!
Decken! Hyouzou! Why are you doing this?!
You even refused
Arlong-san's offer back then
so why are you helping these youths now?!
Helping? I'm just in this for the money.
Arlong was stingy so he couldn't pay me much.
I felt sorry for him that he could only
take crappy swordsmen like you with him.
Hachi from the Arlong Pirates?
Oh, sweet memories!
Your captain even tried to make
me work under him at that time.
That was ridiculous!
I won't work under anybody!
Hordy understands that.
Arlong-san had a dream and an ability
to take action that I could respect.
But at the same time, he was too
rough and lacked cleverness.
When you guys were running wild on the sea,
we were all too young to become pirates.
We all witnessed what they did
so we plan things more carefully.
Because we've learned from
our predecessors' failure.
I will continue where Arlong left off.
As a member of the group I admired so much,
your opposition is so
discouraging, Hachi-san!
Straw Hat Luffy who shattered
Arlong's dream is here, by the way.
But you don't mind at all?
He called me his friend even though I'm
a former member of the Arlong Pirates.
All three of you are my friends now!
Plus, Straw Hat Luffy saved my life.
I wish I could go see him now but...
I'm too ashamed to face him when somebody
is trying to keep Arlong's dream alive!
How pathetic of you to
become friends with a human!
I'm disgusted by you!
Lock on to you, Hachi!
You forgot how pirates do things?
If there is something to say,
you have to use violence!
I suspect!
Here!
Where is he throwing it?
When I touched you just now,
you became my mark.
No matter what I throw or where I
throw it, it's like a living bird,
it will strike you at full speed!
--The knife he just threw somewhere else...
--...Flew at the octopus Fish-Man!
Mark-Mark curse...
Of course, there are a number
of ways to defend yourself.
Give it a try.
No... You have so many arrows.
I knew about your power - I heard the rumors!
Hey, Hordy, he's trying to kill me!
Stop Decken!
As he told you, Hachi-san.
Vander Decken is not working under me.
We are allies on equal footing.
And you're annoying me anyway!
Coward!
Damn!
Alright, get him!
That's it! Run, run!
But they will chase you, chase you,
chase you and chase you
to the end of the world!
If I can get out of here...!
Yes, now I can get away!
In the water, arrows will...
Damn! They aren't even slowing down!
Stop following me!
I can have two marks - one for each palm!
I haven't washed my right hand for 10 years
ever since I touched Princess
Shirahoshi and designated her as my mark!
Do you understand? It doesn't matter
if it's love or a weapon that I throw,
they'll both follow
until the furthest hell!
This is my power!
Awesome!
That's why he could continue
stalking her insidiously...
...without showing himself or
getting caught by Neptune's army!
That's right!
What a sinister guy!
Sinister! Sinister! Sinister!
Now you human pirates.
Now that you've seen Decken's power.
Here is the first stage of the mission.
They say the Ryugu Palace
is impregnable but...
...someone has been able to pierce
the defenses for 10 years
and that's him - Vander Decken.
So for this mission,
you'll be thrown by Decken
and fly to the Mermaid
Princess in the palace.
What?!
Where you'll be landing is the
solid wall of the tower though.
Then, open the gate from inside the palace
and let us in - that is your duty.
--No way! If we get thrown...
--...We could die from hitting the wall!
You're right!
That's why I want you humans to do it
because your lives aren't so important!
You humans are less
valuable than slaves here!
Those of you who survive hitting
the wall carry out your duty.
If you succeed it, I'll set you free.
If you refuse to do it, I'll kick
you out of the bubble right now!
You lowly creatures!
N-No way... If we leave the bubble,
we'll drown for sure!
In that case, you have no choice but wager
on the possibility you'll survive, right?!
Go!
Today, a new history for
the Fish-Men will begin!
First, we conquer the Ryugu Kingdom!
Yeah!
I'm coming to you soon, Shirahoshi!
THE NORTHWEST SIDE OF THE RYUGU PALACE
A PASSAGEWAY TO THE HARD SHELL TOWER
And now...
Wait!
No way!
Hurry up, Skeleton, get to the King!
Wait... We have to open the gate or...
...Hordy will kill us!
Hey, I have a question for you guys. Um...
Sanji, you have to stay in bed!
I mean, at that place called
the Ryugu Palace... Is she there?
You know, the Mermaid Princess!
S-She is there! So what?!
Then I'll go. Even if it kills me.
You're going?! You never learn!
If she's beautiful, you'll die!
Of course she's beautiful, isn't she?!
I've never met her but I
heard she's very beautiful.
So she's beautiful, just as I thought!
I'll go, I'll go, at any cost!
Now lead me to the Ryugu Palace!
--What's wrong with him?
--I don't know but we have to take him.
You need to be handcuffed if
you're going to the palace!
Do whatever you want as long as
I can see the Mermaid Princess!
Sanji!
No! Wake up!
Fools!
I can't cook for the Mermaid
Princess if you handcuff me!
That's the reason?!
I knew you were gonna resist! Cart them off!
You bastards wanna ruin my chance
to get close to the Mermaid Princess?!
Do you?! Do you?!
Hey, Sanji!
Oh no, you beat all the soldiers...
We didn't do anything wrong but now...
It's their fault - they tried to handcuff me.
--They're part of the Straw Hats...
--Dangerous people...
Look, everybody's looking at us coldly
like they're a bunch of deep-sea fish!
Stop complaining! What's done is done!
Think before you act!
You beat the half of them with kung fu!
You were pretty strong...
Don't try to compliment me, you bastard!
It's the voice of a lady!
There is a man covered
with blood at the shore!
You're the guy from the Fish-Man District!
What happened?
Call a doctor!
Huh? I am a doctor!
What? Hachi?
What happened to you?!
Hey, Hachi! It's us!
Why are you hurt?! What happened to you?!
Oh... It's you guys...
Good to see you... Is Straw Hat with you?
He's not here! Wait for a moment!
I'll treat you in a sec!
Summon all your friends... Hurry...
You guys don't wanna get involved...
...with this island! Get out of the island!
The New Fish-Man Pirates will
come and attack the island soon!
And the Ryugu Kingdom will... fall!
Neptune-sama!
There was a kidnapping!
Somebody kidnapped the Princess!
And pirates are falling like
rain at the tower! In any event,
they're your enemies! They're attacking!
Kidnapped?! Shirahoshi?! Who did it?!
Somebody's making a
raid now? What should we do?
Why now?!
We're occupying the palace ourselves!
Wh-What should we do?!
No, don't answer!
I'll cut them.
I said "Don't answer"!
In order for us to survive...
...We have to open the gate at any cost!
Th-They're here!
Why don't you come out of Shark now?
N-No, I'd rather stay in here still...
How do you like it out here after 10 years?
My heart is racing! This is very bad...
How can it be bad? You
just got out of the tower.
You're weird!
This is...
...what they call an adventure?!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
If your heart is racing, that's an adventure!
Did you say "the Sea Forest"?
What is that? Something fun?
It's a graveyard.
There is a grave that I haven't
been to since they built it.
That is the place that I've wanted
to go to the most for 10 years!
THE SEA FOREST IN THE DEEP SEA
It's been 10 years already.
Since her assassination in broad daylight
which threw the Fish-Man
Island in an uproar.
Time flies.
Princes have grown into tough soldiers.
Princess Shirahoshi is still in the tower.
But nobody forgets your ideals.
Queen Otohime!
Hordy's plans for revenge are underway!
The pirates he has sent lay
siege to the Ryugu Palace,
and throw it into a state of panic.
The crew has been caught up in the attack,
and the once impregnable Ryugu
Palace gate is breached,
The New Fish-Man Pirates have arrived,
intent on destroying the kingdom!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hordy's Onslaught! The Retaliatory
Plan Set Into Motion!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!