Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew returned
to Sabaody Archipelago.
And on their way to the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates, who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom
along with Vander Decken, who is after the
Mermaid Princess,
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught
up little by little in the turmoil.
Vander Decken blocks Luffy and
Shirahoshi's way to the Sea Forest.
I found you! I suspect!
Shirahoshi!
Vander Decken-sama!
Why do you wanna interfere with
my business with Shirahoshi?!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Hammer!
Go Shark!
Meanwhile, at the Ryugu Palace,
Zoro and the others...
...are fighting an intense battle with
the New Fish-Man Pirates led by Hordy!
Drop dead, you lowly creature!
One-Sword Style...
...Lion Strike!
"The Straw Hats Defeated?!
Hordy Gains Control of the Ryugu Palace!"
Zoro!
--Boss!
How could a human move faster
than a Fish-Man in the water?!
What's wrong with that man?!
I need to breathe now!
Damn! How dare he cut Boss!
Don't be afraid! He's just a human!
He can't stay long in the water!
Catch the swordsman!
Let's take the Energy Steroid!
Screw this! Kill them all
--Neptune's army, too!
Damn!
What's this? I sense a great deal of madness!
Zoro!
Zoro! Is he okay?! He's not surfacing!
I can't take it! I'm losing my
strength and I can't take it!
What's going on?
Take this!
Beat him up!
All you can do is defend yourself!
Just give up.
You're choking already, aren't you?!
Ah-ha!
You're desperate, huh?
But this is the end of the line!
Drop dead!
Don't push your luck, bastard!
One-Sword Style Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
Damn! Now let's just kill them all!
Zoro!
This place is going to be filled with water!
You have to hang onto me, too!
They defeated my strong army very easily.
They've got some kind of uncanny strength.
I have to get all my men out of the palace!
Here! Secure some air with this-jamon!
Oh, thanks!
Hang onto my body very tightly!
Got it!
We don't have time-jamon!
Zoro, this way! Hang onto the old man!
I hope my strained back can take it!
Now, my soldiers! Here is your way out!
Abandon the battle and get out of here!
Merman...
...Combat!
Zoro! Use this!
Here we go!
Neptune's up to something!
Zoro!
Ultramarine!
Ow, ow, ow...
All soldiers, go!
Yes, sir!
Ride the current at any cost-jamon!
Damn! They're escaping without fighting us!
Boss Hordy! You gotta take this now!
We're out now! Keep going!
Get through the gateway and go inland!
Hey, old man! Don't pass out, please!
I hate getting old!
I can't move even a millimeter-jamon!
What?!
--King-sama!
--King Neptune!
Hey hey, what should we do?!
This is the end-jamon!
No!
Whale!
Oh, Hoe!
Great!
Thank you. Ow, ow, ow...
I can't even turn my head-jamon.
Are you okay?!
Good! Well done, Hoe!
Go!
Can't take it anymore!
What was that?!
What's going on?!
King-sama!
Oh no! King-sama's been caught by Hordy!
Hordy has been severely wounded, hasn't he?!
Minister of the Right-sama, let's go back!
If nothing is done, King-sama will...
No, don't turn back-jamon!
You have to keep going and...
...bring Fukaboshi and the others!
There's no time to lose! Do as he said!
Yes, sir!
Boss Hordy, should we go after them?
No, just let them go.
Soldiers who abandon their
king can't amount to much.
Anyway, tie the stupid king up!
Yes, sir!
I'm sorry, you guys!
But I'm not going to let you down!
What is it?
No idea. Whose skeletonized body is it?
Prince Fukaboshi.
Did you find the Straw Hats' crew?
Yes. I mean, no. Someone from
the store had seen them here
but he said Neptune-sama took
Straw Hat Luffy and 4 others away.
I think those are the ones
occupying the palace now.
I think so.
So they're not here. What about the two
from their crew who were in the Coral Hill?
I've been trying to reach
them but I can't-mi-re-do.
I see. I have a bad feeling about this.
Moonfish! Shake, shake!
I think something happened there.
We better go check.
Oh, you got a call?
Prince Fukaboshi! Prince Fukaboshi, come in!
Brother.
This is Fukaboshi.
Prince, we have a problem!
I'm in Waterwheel Town.
Waterwheel Town?
Men from the Fish-Man
District invaded the town
WATERWHEEL TOWN
and Queen Otohime...
You shouldn't have done that.
What about my mother?! Hey! Answer me!
--Let's go to Waterwheel Town!
--Yes, sir!
Are they gone?
Yes, to Waterwheel Town I assume.
Dosun acted too early-ch.
There's no point in doing it
unless it's simultaneous.
But that's okay. Alright, let's do this-ch.
Listen, guys! Our dreams
will finally come true!
Be as wild as you like -ch!
Yeah!
SEA FOREST
It's a beautiful place!
So this is the Sea Forest!
I... always wanted to come here!
Thank you very much, Luffy-sama!
Maybe I can treat him carefully here.
Mermai-do!
Sanji...
Oh, that's the Sunny!
Yeah, Franky is there too!
Hey, Franky! I didn't
know that you were here!
Luffy?!
What the hell?!
You're with quite a pin-up girl!
Let me introduce you. She's Coward.
Oh, you're Coward! You have
to get tougher, don't you Sis?
Yes, I'm sorry. My name is Shirahoshi.
Franky, no one else is here?
Yeah. Actually Robin came here too but
she said she had to look for something
and went into the forest of huge coral.
Hmmm...
Luffy-kun!
Jimbei! Oh, Jimbei!
It's been a while!
You look stronger. I hardly recognized you.
They said you weren't here so
I thought I couldn't meet you!
Oh, I thought you came here
because you got my message.
What's that? I didn't hear about any message.
Hm, that's odd.
Boss Jimbei-sama. It has been a long time.
Oh, Princess Shirahoshi-sama,
you're here too! Long time no...
What?! Princess Shirahoshi!
Why are you here?!
Hey, Franky! Can you help
me with Hachi and Sanji?
Yeah!
You're the octopus guy!
What happened to you?
Hachi?! What?!
How were you injured?!
Before that, why are you
here at the Fish-Man Island?
I thought you'd been caught with Arlong!
Jimbei-san, why are you here?
Franky, Sanji is next!
No, you don't need to do that.
Oh, Mermaid Princess!
I feel like such a bad painter
when I'm standing in front of you!
Because I can't depict your splendor
in any of the paint that I have!
Um...
That's the way he always
acts in front of women!
He's okay now!
Your beauty won't fit on my canvas!
--Yeah, he's back to his old self!
--So I can't draw!
It's so noisy. What's going on?
Huh?!
Why is Princess Shirahoshi here?!
Hey, who the hell are you?!
Why are you on board the Sunny?!
That's Den-chan, brother of
Tom - my shipwright master...
...doing the recoating for us.
Oh, okay!
So he's a shipwright who's
coating Franky's brother!
Yeah, something like that!
What?
Princess Shirahoshi-sama,
I know why you wanted to come here but...
Again?
I beat him up so badly but he kept throwing
dozens of things! How persistent he is!
Look at what you've done.
Why did you bring her here, Luffy-kun?
Don't worry. You know I got your back, right?
Yes!
How careless!
So that's the grave she talked about.
She's been at that for a long time.
That is her mother--Queen Otohime's grave.
Vander Decken's relentless courtship
began right after the Queen's death.
That's why the Princess couldn't
even attend her mother's funeral
and has spent last 10 years
in the Hard Shell Tower.
The things that she
wanted to tell her mother...
...kept building up inside
her heart, probably.
Luffy!
Luffy-chin!
Nami! Camie!
Nami-chin, look!
That's Boss Jimbei who's standing
right by Luffy-chin's side!
Oh?
Princess Shirahoshi is with them...
Shocking!!
Nami! Did the banquet start?
--Nami-san!
--H-He's cured completely...
Hatchin! What happened to you?!
Camie...
Is that true?! Hordy did it?!
Uh-huh.
I never thought that such things
could happen at the Ryugu Palace!
What happened to Zoro and the others?!
I don't know. I was gonna
go back as soon as I met you.
N-No!
I can't believe Father-sama
has been caught!
Luffy-kun, I'm sorry!
I left you the message because I
didn't want to get you into trouble
but I let you get involved already.
We have to hurry but let me just say,
2 years ago when I met Luffy-kun, it was
harder for me to talk about it than it is now.
I've been feeling very thankful...
...to those people who stopped the Arlong
Pirates running wild in the East Blue.
That was you guys, wasn't it?
Thank you! Let me express my gratitude.
And I want to apologize at the same time.
Jimbei-san...
The person who is responsible for setting
Arlong loose into the East Blue was...
...me!
Jimbei reveals shocking past events as
Nami recalls her difficult time with Arlong
Things become tense between
the crew and Jimbei.
Jimbei then tells the great
story of two individuals
who tried to change the bitter history
between Fish-Men and humans.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Haunting Ties!
Nami and the Fish-Man Pirates!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!