Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
--Mother-sama!
Otohime-sama!
Where are you going, Otohime-sama?
Otohime...
Trust the woman who you chose to be your wife
and the humans.
Mother-sama!
Otohime-sama!
Your Majesty! Please be careful!
Mother-sama!
"A Sudden Tragedy!
A Gunshot Shuts Down the Future!"
Queen Otohime's voyage was to determine
the fate of the Fish-Man Island.
Of course, we were all worrying
but it was nothing compared to
the burden of the Neptune family.
The whole Ryugu Kingdom was restless.
But all we could do was pray
for the Queen's safety.
What? A Tamate Box?
Yes, Captain. I heard that they
have one at the Ryugu Palace.
And it makes anyone grow older?
That's what they say.
For instance, a small brat like her...
...would become a sexy mature woman?
I think so.
Great! Problem solved!
In that case, I can get married to
Shirahoshi right away, I suspect!
Go steal that Tamate Box thing now!
Wait a minute. There is no way
to break in to the Ryugu Palace.
--But if you get married to Shirahoshi first...
--You can go in and out as you please.
You guys are smart!
Shirahoshi is not bad-looking.
If she grows older by 10 to 20 years,
she will be really hot!
But she'll get even bigger.
She'll look just fine! I like big women!
She's the legendary Mermaid
Princess who can control the Sea Kings.
When I become her husband
and seize that power,
our dream will come true!
It's the dream of all the ancestors
of Vander Decken family!
Alright, I'll start writing
an invitation to our wedding.
You have to propose to her first!
Oh, I don't have any friends!
There had been no word
from the Queen for days.
WE NEED YOUR SIGNATURE FOR
THE FUTURE OF THE ISLAND!
And worries kept growing.
I wanna hear her speeches again.
Please come back safe!
Hey, Boss. Where is Otohime-sama?
When will she come back?
Keep faith in her and wait.
She embarked on a voyage to make
the future better for you kids.
Your Majesty, please be safe.
Mother-sama...
She will be fine-jamon.
Let's trust in her and wait-jamon.
That one week felt like 100 days.
And then...
That's...
Yeah! Otohime-sama!
Your Majesty!
We are so happy just to see you alive!
Welcome back!
Your Majesty!
After a few days of convincing,
Queen Otohime finally succeeded...
...in calming down the Celestial Dragons and
she brought back with her a sheet of paper...
...which held the fate
of the Fish-Man Island.
CONCHCORDE PLAZA
Everyone, the World Nobles
are very influential...
...in the World Summit - the Summit of Kings.
Listen to what they wrote
on this sheet of paper.
"To foster friendship between
the Fish-Men and humans,
we will pledge our endorsement
of their duly signed petition."
That means if we can submit a petition
with many signatures at the Summit,
this one sheet of paper will
give us all the support we need.
We can relocate!
--The Celestial Dragons will support the petition?
--I have mixed feelings about it.
So what I need now is more signatures.
All I can do is wait for
you to make a decision.
Express your intention...
...to relocate to the world above and
live together with the humans!
Please! Sign!
I need your signature!
You children, you aren't going to go back
on your pledge after raising my hopes?
We won't! My mom said she will sign too.
Otohime-sama,
this small box won't be enough.
Don't you know the
population of this country?
Here, here, here! Put
them in here from now on!
Those of you who support the Queen's passion,
put your signature in here!
The Fish-Men and humans.
We were trying to ignore
the history of racism.
But the Queen took the first
step herself and now we have hope.
If she can get enough signatures,
the future of the island could change for real.
It would have helped Arlong if
he could have understood better...
...about Queen Otohime's firm belief.
I wish Brother Tai were here to see this.
Mother! Signatures keep coming
in from all over the country!
--It's going well, isn't it?
--Yes, it's like a dream.
It's because of your courage!
Courage?
I got encouraged at that very moment,
that this island would change for sure.
That moment?
Yes, the moment that the Sea Kings
came and stared at the island.
That was surprising!
Shirahoshi called them.
What?
We Merfolk can communicate
with fish and talk to them, right?
But no one can talk to those great Sea Kings.
Even your father Neptune who can talk to whales,
doesn't know how to talk to them.
But according to our royal family's legend,
once in several hundred years,
one with an ability to communicate
with the Sea Kings, will be born.
--With those giant Sea Kings?!
--And Shirahoshi is the one?
Yes, and she will meet someone who will guide
her and her power in the right direction
and it will cause a major change the world.
And that is the whole story.
The world?
If it's true, there will be a
major change on this island too.
Could it help what you're doing?
Yes, it could.
It's a power of love that can save thousands
of lives if only the bearer wishes to.
But with the wrong intentions, that power
could sink the whole world into the ocean.
It is one of the most
fearsome powers in the world.
Shirahoshi doesn't know that she
has that power and she doesn't know
how to control it yet.
If something were ever to shock her,
she could unintentionally
drive the Sea Kings berserk.
What?
The Fish-Man Island would be flattened
like a pancake! What should we do?!
Don't worry! I can take care of it for now.
But the three of you will have to
become strong warriors someday
and as her brothers and as warriors,
protect your baby sister with your lives!
--Yes!
--Of course!
Thank you.
But then the unexpected happened...
Signatures were mounting up at a rapid pace.
The islanders still didn't trust humans
but they were hoping to see
the beginning of a new era.
Queen Otohime!
We brought our signatures again!
That's against the rules!
Each person can only vote once!
W-We're sorry...
But it means a lot to me that you did so.
Thank you so much.
Your efforts finally paid off.
Get away! Fire!
--How could the box catch fire?
--Water! Water!
Put out the fire now!
I can't believe it!
The signatures we collected!
Run now!
O-Otohime-sama!
Put out the fire! We have
to save the signatures!
No! It's too dangerous!
They are very important! I have to save them!
Your Majesty!
We can't let them burn!
They are everyone's dream!
They are the future of the Fish-Man Island!
Yes, ma'am!
Save the signatures now!
Yes, sir!
Please save yourself!
Leave the rest up to us!
Otohime-sama has been shot!
Who did it?!
The shooter must be here somewhere!
Protect the royal family!
--Mother!
--Mother-sama!
It's dangerous here! Get on the gondola now!
Princes!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
--Your Majesty!
--Otohime-sama!
Oh no, Princess, this is pretty serious...
--Who're you?!
--Oops!
--Stay away from the Princess!
--Stop!
--Mother-sama! Mother!
--Mother!
M-Mother!
Dammit! Who the hell did it?!
--Didn't an emergency team arrive yet?!
--Mother! Mother!
Open your eyes!
This can't be forgiven! I'll make him pay!
Mother!
Stay near me, my angels.
Don't lose your temper.
My guard was down. Because I was
thrilled that everybody was signing.
I was so happy!
Prince Fukaboshi, I should
be the one who is frustrated.
Your Majesty, you need treatment now!
So it doesn't matter who did this...
Don't get angry on my behalf.
Don't let resentment or hatred
get the better of you for my sake.
M-Mother-sama...
Shirahoshi, keep your senses.
If something were ever to shock her...
This is just like...!
Shirahoshi, no!
Hey, Shirahoshi!
Moonfish mambo! Moonfish mambo!
Look, Shirahoshi!
--It's fun! It's fun!
--Shake, shake! Shake, shake!
--It's nothing! Let's sing Shirahoshi!
--Moonfish mambo! Shake, shake, shake!
We three will always be
there for you-la-ti-do!
Mambo dance is fun!
It's fun!
It's fun-do-re-mi-fa!
P-Princes, what are you doing?!
--Stop them!
--That's not appropriate!
Mother, look, we're fine!
We will protect our baby sister
like this forever-la-ti-do!
Stop it! Can't you see
the Queen's situation?!
Mother-sama!
We will collect the signatures
that burned away again.
We three will become great
warriors like our father...
...and protect Shirahoshi
with our lives as we promised!
So please...
Please don't worry!
We are almost there!
At that place under the real sun!
After Otohime's death, Fish-Man
Island is consumed by rage.
Is this the end for her ideal?
After relating the subsequent
events on Fish-Man Island,
and finishing his story, Jimbei
again apologizes to Nami.
But Nami's reply was utterly unexpected!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Back to the Present! Hordy Makes a Move!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!