Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
while Zoro, Usopp and Brook get
captured by Hordy at the Ryugu Palace.
She broke... She broke my heart!
Oh yeah.
What's wrong?
I got an idea!
What don't I just destroy
everything altogether?!
Boy, he gave me a lot of trouble...
Take care of Hachi, Camie!
Y-Yes.
Go, Megalo!
So that was the true power of the drug!
"A Surprising Confession! The Truth
Behind the Assassination of Otohime!"
We are almost at the plaza! Hurry up, Megalo!
Father-sama...
Hey! I'm here-jamon!
Boss Jimbei-sama! Megalo!
I'm so happy to see you!
Father-sama!
I'm coming!
No, wait!
Father-sama!
Please stop!
Princess Shirahoshi!
If you don't wanna see the
Princess get hurt, freeze!
L-Let me go!
Alright, let's take her!
CONCHCORDE PLAZA
No way!
We have quite an audience.
Damn!
What a view!
Prince Mamboshi!
Prince Ryuboshi!
Prince Fukaboshi-sama!
How did the pirates manage that?!
The Princes were winning by far!
Suddenly, the tables
have turned against them!
Oh, I wanna fight some more-zugon!
Much! Don't get so heated up! Or I'm gonna
become a piece of dried squid-ch!
Soldiers of the army. The ministers.
And the royal family. There is no one
left in this country, who can fight us now!
What unbelievable power!
I'm sorry, Father!
You don't have to be!
Those powers are fake-jamon!
That doesn't really matter if it
enables them to take over the country!
Captain Hordy, let's put them to death!
--Burn them alive!
--No, impale them!
I wish a terrible death on those who lack
pride and look to coexist with the humans!
Let's show the audience!
Let's just kill them!
Kill them! Kill them!
Kill them!
Silence.
I haven't heard from Decken's crew yet,
with regards to Shirahoshi's death.
There is no point in doing
this if we can't lure her here!
Don't do anything to our sister!
She won't fight!
She wouldn't harm you in any way!
You think that I don't know anything?
She's the Mermaid with that troublesome
power so I want to be rid of her the most.
Hordy!
Captain Hordy!
We got them!
Princess Shirahoshi and
Jimbei got caught in a trap!
Shirahoshi!
Father-sama! Brothers-sama!
How lucky I am!
We caught the two that I
concerned about most, all at once.
This is too good to be true!
I-I am very sorry!
You wouldn't have to go through
this if I hadn't been fooled...
What's done is done so never mind.
So you're here as I thought, Jimbei.
I liked you back when you were a wild man.
What happened to you, Hordy?
You look so different from before.
It's Boss Jimbei!
I thought he left the island
after he quit the Warlords!
I heard that Princess Shirahoshi had
been kidnapped by Straw Hat Luffy.
Did Boss Jimbei rescue her?
Now, everyone that I wanted to see is here.
It was easier than I thought.
My only concern now is
what the Straw Hats will do.
But I assume they're desperately looking
for a way in to the Ryugu Palace now.
Even if they make it here after
they find their friends dead,
we're totally ready to ambush them!
There are 30,000 human slaves we've
caught in the sea over the past month.
And 70,000 Fish-Men who know how to use arms.
Wh-What the...
They moved here from the
closed Fish-Man District.
Behold...
...100,000 outlaws altogether!
There are a few female and child slaves
who can't fight, outside the plaza.
We will take care of them later.
But we'll soon have more human slaves!
So, 100,000 of you islanders!
You fools are a dishonor to our
race so vacate your houses!
You can either drop dead or run.
Think about what you want!
Horsing around in public...
You kids have no class at all!
Don't push your luck!
Hordy Jones.
I haven't seen you for a
long time. What do you want?
I just wanted to say one thing to you
since you're at the height of your glory!
Madam Sharley?!
According to my prevision, a man
will destroy the Fish-Man Island.
I may be the one.
Was it me that you saw?
No.
The man who will destroy the island is...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
What?!
I can't tell what the Straw Hat
boy will do specifically.
What is your point?
My point is that it's not you!
That's all I can say.
The one who determines the
fate of the Fish-Man Island is...
...not you, Hordy.
Oh, I see! Madam's previsions are accurate!
That means Hordy will never
reign over the island!
Madam Sharley!
--Madam!
--How could he do this?!
That's nonsense!
What do you mean by that, Sharley?
What do you have against me?!
I'm not like your brother.
Well, when I was a kid,
everybody in the Fish-Man District
may have looked
up to your brother Arlong.
But then we seized power.
In fact, the name "Arlong Pirates" is
nothing but a symbol to unite us now.
We don't even need the
name "Arlong" anymore!
The only man who can break the whole country
to its foundation and rebuild it, is...
...me! Because I have enough power to do so!
Look how powerful I am!
This is the power that I'm talking about!
I started this whole thing 10 years ago.
Let me tell you something.
Concerning the late Queen of the Ryugu
Kingdom, who you fools still love!
Otohime was killed by...
...me!
What?!
No...
What about the human then?
How could you not notice it, idiots?!
The day before that fateful
day 10 years ago...
I don't know who you are but...
...I would do anything if I
can make some big money.
Is this real money?!
That's just a half of it. You can have
the rest after you finish the job.
Alright, I'll do it!
Just this is enough to drink
all day for quite some time.
And what do you want me to do?
It's so easy. Even a child can do it.
However, don't let anyone notice.
And on that day...
Get away! Fire!
--Put out the fire!
--Run!
--Protect the royal family!
--Put out the fire now!
Otohime-sama has been shot!
Hey, give me the rest of that money now!
I set fire to those
signatures like you told me to!
I wanna make a run for it
already so give me the money!
What's going on here?
You stupid human.
Shit! Dammit!
It was a human...
...who killed our queen!
Queen Otohime was killed by a human!!
Everybody got fooled completely!
Damn! It was him!
He killed Queen Otohime!
Hordy, you bastard!
Father!
Hordy, stop!
She was annoying.
Don't you think so, Shirahoshi?
She begged everyone not to
seek revenge against humans
but to become friends with them instead.
She was bugging me because she
almost accomplished her goal.
I knew I wouldn't be satisfied
with just killing her.
To me, your mother was...
...someone who deserved death!
Don't say such a thing to the Princess!
How dare you?!
And then I came up with an idea
to make the best of her death.
Which would allow me to stoke
the hatred towards humans,
that citizens of the
Fish-Man Island once had
and destroy the islanders' stupid
dream along with Otohime - all at once!
I'd point the finger at a
human for killing Otohime.
If I blamed it on a human, I knew that the
islanders will get pissed off at humans again.
And it turned out that you all got
fooled by my trick exactly as I wanted!
She was worth killing! Right, Shirahoshi?
Your mother was not murdered by a human!
I, her kinsman, did it!
I, standing in front of you now, killed her!
I already knew it.
Shirahoshi!
What?
A long time ago, everyone on the
Fish-Man Island came together
and built a mysterious
giant ship called Noah.
The reason remains a mystery.
It's just a leftover from the past now.
Let me touch it with my right hand.
Captain Decken, what are you up to?
Wh-What is it? What's going on?!
The pain of heartbreak will never go away.
It's moving!
--Wh-What's going on?!
--Run!
I'm throwing the Noah...
...at Shirahoshi!
What?!
The ship is half the size
of the Fish-Man Island!
That means if it hits the island,
not just Shirahoshi
but the whole island will be shattered!
She can't run or hide from me anymore!
Shirahoshi has no choice but to
stay with me in my heart forever!
Burn in hell with the island!
Goodbye my sweet Shirahoshi!
Goodbye Fish-Man Island!
Shirahoshi continues to fulfill her
promise to her mother, Otohime.
Hordy ridicules her and
commences Neptune's execution.
The despairing citizens call out
the name of their last hope.
And their voice resounds
throughout Fish-Man Island!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Shirahoshi's Tears!
Luffy Finally Shows Up!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!