Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in
the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hordy's merciless plot puts the
Fish-Man Island in unprecedented danger!
Weren't you listening to what I said?
I will save the Fish-Man
Island and Shirahoshi...
Luffy-sama...
...and keep my promise to a friend.
Straw Hat...
I'll protect...
...everything!
Song of Scratches, Blizzard Slice!
Impact Wolf!
Cloven Rose, Palm!
Franky...
Squid! Squid! Squid!
...Radical Beam!
Vagabond Drill!
Hell Memories!
Purgatory...
...Onigiri!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
I will stop the Noah!
Keep falling, Noah!
Kill all the pride-less Fish-Men!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gatling!
"Stop, Noah! Desperate Elephant Gatling!"
Even those demon-like officers are a joke
to them. That's how strong they are!
Stay alert!
Look up! You're in danger!
What?!
--Wadatsumi is...
--...Falling toward us!
You should've dropped him
elsewhere, you worthless chef!
Shut up! I'll make someone
fall onto you next time!
That was amazing, Sanji.
Hey Chopper! Could you shrink
yourself a little bit?
You're upstaging the giant robot!
Franky, I loved the beam!
That robot was totally useless.
Oh! Nami-san!
What?
Please wear a miniskirt.
Shut up!
That's just what I'd expect
from Luffy-kun's friends.
He did it!
This time for sure! Luffy-san beat Hordy!
--Did you hear that?
--Yeah...
The Straw Hats defeated
the New Fish-Man Pirates!
Hey.
The Noah!
The Noah is right there!
Run!
It's gonna destroy us along with the island!
If we stay here any longer, Neptune's
army will bar us in the plaza!
Hurry up! Those crazy officers are gone now!
Oh my goodness! How is the evacuation going?!
Only a few citizens have escaped to the sea.
Most people are still here on the island!
Are you okay?
Is it too late?!
Can't you do anything, Straw Hat?!
Straw Hat!
The threat of rebellion is now gone but...
This is it!
No, not yet!
What?
He is not...
...giving up yet!
Straw Hat Luffy-san is...
...trying his best...
...to destroy...
...the Noah!
Destroy the Noah?!
Trying to destroy it?
Destroy that giant ship?!
Really?! That's impossible!
Prepare for the worst, guys!
Yeah. Let's just stand by him.
Luffy-san!
Luffy-sama!
If he can destroy the Noah before it
hits the island, we'll be okay but...
...if he can't,
the Fish-Man Island will fall!
Give it everything you got, Luffy!
--Luffy-san!
--We're counting on you, Luffy!
Luffy!
Luffy-kun!
What's wrong?!
I'm not gonna run!
Don't be ridiculous! Can't you see the Noah?!
I know! I know, but...
...Straw Hat's heroic actions
bring back memories of...
...what happened 20 years
ago when I was a kid!
There was one human that the people of
this kingdom thanked with all our hearts!
What a haul!
Hey wait!
No!
Who are you?! Do you wanna die?!
You got to be kidding me! Why is he...
...taking the Fish-Men's side?!
Neptune helped me when we
were young and we exchanged
cups of sake as a pledge of friendship!
Don't kill me! I promise I'll never
kidnap Mermaids and Fish-Men!
Don't mess with my friend's country!
You wet-nosed brats!
I declare that this island
is my territory now!
Are you talking about Whitebeard?!
Are you saying you trust them like
you trusted the great pirate?!
Because,
to be honest, I don't even like humans
and this is the Fish-Men's kingdom,
but they...
Our minds were made up when
we arrived at the plaza that,
along with Jimbei, we wouldn't
let anyone harm the island!
Leave it all up to us, Brother-hoshi!
We're friends, right?
He said such things and they're
all risking their lives...
Straw Hat...
Don't lose, Straw Hat!
Yeah, Straw Hat, we're supporting you!
Hang in there, Straw Hat!
--You're a human and you're fighting for us!
--We're not gonna run!
Go, Big Bro Straw Hat!
Please save the Fish-Man Island, Straw Hat!
Go, Straw Hat!
We believe in you!
Straw Hat!
Luffy-chan!
--Straw Hat!
Stop, Noah!
Stop!
I only broke half of it so far!
Luffy-sama!
The wound is opening up...
Stay away!
Stay there and watch!
I need to keep destroying this thing now!
Stop, ship!
--Straw Hat!
Luffy, go for it!
Break it into pieces!
Super!
I'm sorry, Father.
Destroying the Noah is the only way.
Straw Hat!
The Ship of Promise...
But it cannot be helped.
People's lives are the most important.
I am sorry. I cannot keep the promise-jamon,
Joy Boy!
Just a little more to go!
Please...
Stop.
Who is it?!
Luffy-sama! Please stop!
Luffy-sama, you have to stop!
Move, Yowahoshi! I need to
destroy it to save the island!
It's okay now!
It's not okay! Everybody's on the island!
The Noah is already...
...stopped!
Sea Kings? Why?
Luffy-sama is angry!
Hey, this is no time for crying!
I don't quite understand, either.
But the Noah is stopped now!
What happened?!
What's going on here? The
Sea Kings stopped the ship!
Luffy-sama! The wound is opening up again!
You are bleeding a lot!
Well... Well... That's good...
...as long as the ship is stopped.
I'm glad everybody's...
...safe.
Luffy-sama!
He's fine.
Boy, what a human!
He is a very strong one, isn't he?
If we were late, we could
still have saved the island
but the Noah would have
been completely destroyed.
I'm glad that we made it!
I'm glad that Princess Shirahoshi called us!
What? I didn't do anything
and I was just sad...
No, you were moved by Straw
Hat boy's strong determination
and prayed.
You wished strongly to
help him save the island.
Our power is your power.
We helped him because you called us.
A-All people of the kingdom.
Wh-What just happened here was beyond words
but it happened for sure!
The Noah is stopped!
The ship didn't get destroyed completely
and the Fish-Man Island has been saved!
Straw Hat did it!
--Straw Hat!
--So we're safe, aren't we?
Yeah!
Straw Hat!
I'm so relieved!
--Yeah!
--Oh, he did it!
Luffy did it!!
Fish-Man Island is saved.
However, in his fight to achieve this...
...Luffy is in critical condition
with a multitude of wounds.
Yet the Fish-Men, still bound
by the island's past...
...hesitate to come to his aid.
Just when Luffy is almost out of time...
...a single man's actions
alter the course of history.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Secret Revealed! The Truth
about the Ancient Weapon!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!