Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates
who are looking to destroy
the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken,
who is after Shirahoshi, are
engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil and...
The Noah is already...
...stopped!
Sea Kings? Why?
Luffy-sama! The wound is opening up again!
You are bleeding a lot!
Well... Well... That's good...
...as long as the ship is stopped.
I'm glad
everybody's...
...safe.
"To the Future! The Path to the Sun!"
Princess Shirahoshi.
We have been waiting for you
to be born for a long time.
For me?
This ship is designed to be pulled by us.
Since very early times, the
duty has been passed on.
Is that why the Noah is so big?
Yes.
Once in many centuries,
our queen comes into the
world in the form of Mermaid.
I wonder why.
I wonder why as well.
Ever since you were born,
you have been our queen.
Brother!
Yeah, I think Shirahoshi is...
She is talking with the Sea Kings.
I can't believe it!
What is going on, guards?
How did the Noah stop?
Well, actually a group of
Sea Kings showed up here
around the island, out of the blue.
It seemed like they came
to protect the Noah...
...from getting destroyed by Luffy-san.
I wonder if the Noah is something
very important to them.
Neptune-sama?!
Sea Kings...
It awakes finally-jamon.
The power that could destroy the world!
Look,
the bubble is getting absorbed by the island.
The human can't survive in the deep sea.
You better go and save him.
Luffy-sama! Oh no!
We should go capture Hordy and the others.
Yeah.
We have to hurry!
Noah... I wonder what
secrets that ship holds.
Am I imagining things?
What?
That human with the hat noticed our voice.
I doubt it.
Something like this happened not so long ago.
Yes, I remember.
Rayleigh, did you just hear that voice?
What are you talking about?
It's really quiet down here.
Who are you, talking in such deep sea?
Hey, show yourself!
--I wonder why.
--I wonder why as well.
I wonder if Straw Hat
and the others are okay.
They're strong, aren't
they? Then they're fine.
Uh-huh, we have to trust them, Hatchin.
You're right.
S-Sea Kings?!
They're pulling the Noah!
They're gonna eat us!
The ship is falling apart.
Can it be fixed?
Does it still work?
I don't know.
In order to fix it, we need
help from "them" but...
...times are changing.
Can it be fixed?
I hope it can be fixed...
...by the appointed time.
This is the Ryugu Palace!
Minister of the Left, you
might want to hear this!
What is it?
We found the Mermaids who
had been kidnapped...
...inside the palace!
What?!
Are they all right?
Yes, they are. They say
they still feel groggy
but they remember the
kidnapper's face clearly!
Also, the treasure chamber's been emptied.
There isn't even a single
piece of treasure left.
Not to mention the national
treasure--the Tamate Box!
King-sama! S-Somebody robbed
the palace while we were gone!
Forget about the treasure thief.
We almost lost the whole
country just now-jamon.
Instead, let the whole nation know
that those Mermaids were okay.
I know it's too late
but we need to clear Straw Hat
and the others' name-jamon.
We did them wrong.
We shouldn't be here!
Hurry up!
They'll catch and kill us!
Let's go! We humans have nothing
to do with this battle!
Where are you going?
Let us go!
Let's fly over him with bubbles.
Water Shot!
I will shoot you down if you
try to fly over me with those!
Dammit!
I beg you, Boss! Let us go!
We were just afraid of Hordy and the others!
We have nothing to do with this
civil war because we're humans!
I thought this island was a tourist spot
largely depending on us
human pirates for money!
Let us get out through the exit!
No one says that you all are
going to get your heads cut off.
Wait for Neptune royal family's decision.
There is something that we would
like all islanders to know.
The Straw Hats were not involved in
the kidnap of the Mermaids at all.
We admit that we made a mistake
in our fact-checking process
and we take full responsibility
- we want to apologize.
I didn't think the Straw Hats did it.
I knew it wasn't them the whole time.
Don't lie!
We all thought that they were the kidnappers!
--N-No, we trusted them, didn't we?
--Y-Yeah.
--Liars!
--Hey!
That's not fair!
He's right!
Admit it.
We didn't trust them.
We didn't trust them because they're humans.
That's how we've always treated humans...
Super...
...Afro!
--Franky-san, that's so cool!
--Isn't it super?
Hey Chopper, are you alright?
Yeah... I'm fine...
Whoa!
--Thanks.
--Oh boy...
When I use the Monster Boost,
I can't even walk for a
couple hours from fatigue.
But I can still treat you.
Is anyone hurt?
Look who's talking!
Everybody looks okay.
Robin-chan! I used a daring
technique and I'm exhausted too!
Let me put my head in your lap, too! Please!
--Put your stupid head somewhere else!
--You do it!
Luffy...
There they are! Hey!
Prince!
Everybody!
It's the Princes!
I'm glad that they're okay!
--Hordy!
--Vander Decken!
Father! We are sorry to make you worry!
I am glad that you are all okay-jamon.
Well done!
Thank you!
Everybody! No worries!
We won't allow them to make trouble again!
We can live without fear now!
I can't believe there was such an awful
guy so nearby in the Fish-Man District.
--C-Captain Hordy!
--He looks like a monster!
This is great!
Hey, that's...
They are back!
Luffy-san!
Hey, Luffy!
It's Straw Hat Luffy and Princess Shirahoshi!
Please help me!
I cannot stop Luffy-sama's bleeding!
Hey Luffy, stay with us!
Luffy!
Luffy-sama pushed himself
so far in order to save us!
Straw Hat!
This is bad!
There are hemostatics in my backpack!
--Get it for me, Robin.
--Okay.
This makes me worried about how
you'll fight from now on, Doc!
Okay, go ahead!
-I'll help you move.
--We have an odd doctor here!
A little bit to the left.
Will Luffy-sama be all right?!
I can stop the bleeding but he
already lost a lot of blood!
He's lacking blood!
Luffy is the only one  with
blood type F among us.
Oh no!
There must be somebody in the plaza!
Somebody!
Hey!
Is there someone with blood type F here?!
He needs blood!
Can somebody donate blood?!
Really? Nobody?
My blood type is F.
Mine is F but...
Dad, your blood type is F, isn't it?
Well, I mean...
Oh yeah! Donating blood to humans
is prohibited in this country!
What?!
What kind of law is that?!  That's horrible!
I beg you! Luffy is dying!
M-My blood type is not F but mine's red too!
It's no good?!
Yes but thank you for offering!
Princess Shirahoshi...
Oh yeah! There are human pirates!
Hey please! If nothing is
done, Luffy is gonna...
Luffy is gonna die!
Take my blood.
It's F.
You can have as much as you need.
Jimbei!
Jimbei-chan!
But it's against the law...
I am a pirate!
Boss! I'm so glad!
Jimbei-san!
Thank you!
Jimbei, you...
It is okay-jamon.
K-King-sama!
What is so wrong with it?
That old law is also...
...a curse-jamon.
Okay, let me prepare for the procedure.
I'm fine now. I can move for a while.
Let me help with something.
OK, thanks.
Jimbei, it may hurt a little bit.
I don't mind.
If you hurt somebody...
...or if somebody hurts you,
the same red blood will be shed.
It hardly seems like a path...
...because it's a very thin and narrow
tube - but it makes its way through...
...the prejudice that makes
people fear each other...
...and blood feuds...
...so very easily.
This is a path towards a very real sun,
not some empty wish.
Jimbei...
Luffy-sama, you came to life again!
Luffy!
--Luffy!
--Luffy-san!
What is it?
I didn't know that you were awake.
Straw Hat!
Luffy!
We are back to zero now!
Mother!
Hey, Jimbei.
Join...
...my crew!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Secret Revealed! The Truth
about the Ancient Weapon!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!