Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they instigated an all-out war
against the New Fish-Man Pirates.
Luffy finally defeated
Hordy in a fierce fight
and thwarted his plot.
All right! Spread the sail!
Let's set sail!
Take me out for a fun stroll again!
I want to go to a real forest above ground!
Okay, fine!
I'll take you there next time!
We promise!
Once we pass through this deep sea,
we'll get to the ultimate sea!
Let's go!
Guys!
To the New World!
"To the New World! Heading
for the Ultimate Sea!"
After leaving the Fish-Man Island,
the ship ascends toward the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
--It's going very well!
--Yeah, almost too well.
I'm starting to get hungry. Let's do it now!
Wait until I finish making this, Luffy.
How nice!
It's called Shower Tempo.
Do you wanna use it?
Oh? Me?
I'm okay. I just brushed myself 2 days ago.
By the way, doesn't that
cloud look like cotton candy?
You can't eat it!
Oh yeah? It's not sweet, sweet cotton candy?
What? There is something sweet
and yummy in the bathroom?
Oh yeah! Looks pretty sweet and yummy!
Nami-san, please! Turn around!
Chopper, step away from the cloud.
How scary!  I don't wanna
eat that cloud anymore!
It's so relaxing!
My first bath on the Sunny in 2 years!
It's so luxurious with a view of the deep
sea - it's as beautiful as the night sky.
Don't they need you on the deck?
It's okay. I'll go up before
we ride an upward current.
If a sea monster strikes,
they can take care of it.
Hurry up, Usopp!
Just one minute.
We want a giant fish so
the ropes gotta be strong!
Okay, I think this is good.
Finished!
Ta-dah!
Oh? You guys are having fun.
I hadn't even thought about it
on our way to the Fish-Man Island
because I was excited to see the island
but if we catch a deep-sea fish
now, Sanji can cook it for us!
I hope it'll go with cola!
Cook, huh? That's a good idea!
Can't wait to have a drink in
celebration of entering the New World!
Now, which one should we catch?
I want something that looks yummy!
That one would taste good
fried up with some salt!
A fried fish with salt sounds good!
How about slicing it in half and grilling it?
Like an eel, huh?
Oh! That one looks good too! It
would be yummy with some mayonnaise!
Which one?
No, it doesn't look good at all.
No matter how you cook
it, it won't taste good.
You think so? Well, whatever's fine with me!
Second Gear!
I'm sure Sanji can cook up any fish!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
I knew you wanted that one!
Hey, isn't it a little too big?!
Hurry, hurry! Catch it!
Special Attack - Capture Star!
Yeah!
We got a deep-sea fish!
I wanna eat it already!
Are you sure it's a fish?
Looks like an old man!
An old man?
It got eaten!
Hey, hey, not again! They keep coming!
Reel it in already, Usopp!
I can't, I can't! The
ship is gonna flip over!
I can't believe this! Is it a Russian doll?
Do you think something happened?
The ship is shaking and  I
hear them yelling on the deck.
I shouldn't have trusted them!
One-Sword Style - 360 Pound Phoenix!
Nice, Zoro!
What's going on here?
Hey Sanji, look at that!
I see! That's great!
A deep-sea fish, huh? Can't wait to cook it!
Well, first of all, how did you get burned?
Listen to this! You won't believe it!
There are 2 more fish inside that one!
But, is the ship really moving forward?
It feels like we're sinking...
No way!
What is that?!
What?
It's a giant sea snake! No!!
Alright, get closer! Let's eat that too!
We have too much to carry already!
Wait! Don't tell me it's...
Whitestrom!
It's a giant whirlpool that appears
out of the blue in the deep sea,
like a living dragon!
What?
A whirlpool in the deep sea?!
What the hell is that?! This
is dangerous, isn't it?
Damn, those fools!
What?! Oh no! It must be the Whitestrom!
When a ship gets caught up in the whirlpool,
it'll end up somewhere far
off usually missing its crew.
What?! That means the crew
all died, doesn't it?
This is dangerous! Let's get away!
A ship will end up somewhere far off?
So it's like the wormhole of my dreams?!
No, it's not, you fool!
Guys! We have to get away
from that whirlpool now!
There! Our navigator's back! Let's go, fools!
Augh! What is that fish doing there?!
Oh, we caught it!
What do you think you're doing?! We
can't advance if we're pulling that!
See? The fish got caught in the whirlpool!
--No! Get it back!
--Yeah!
No! We're gonna cut it loose!
What?! We wanted to eat the deep-sea fish!
Which is more important to
you - the fish or your life?!
How could you get in this much trouble
while I was away for only 10 minutes?!
Franky, Coup de Burst?!
No, it's super too late for that!
--Huh?
--Stop "Huh?"-ing me!
We're gonna get caught in the whirlpool!
We're in big trouble!
Oh no!
--It's too late!
--I don't wanna die!
Hold onto the ship!
How fun!
This is super not good!
Even the Sunny can't endure
a whirlpool this wild!
I blame Luffy and the rest of you!
My head is spinning!
Can't we get out of the whirlpool somehow?!
There are no records of someone
escaping the Whitestrom! Because...
No one has ever survived!
Instead of the New World,
we're all going to hell!
It stopped.
The Sunny was not destroyed.
We hit something and got
bumped out of the whirlpool.
In any case, we're alive!
Where are we?
What's this black wall?
It doesn't seem like the Red Line.
A ghost!
What is it?
It's gonna eat us!
A monster!
What is that?!
It's going away!
A fin? Don't tell me it's...
I can hear it singing. It must be...
Wow, it's a pod of whales!
Oh, those scars!
We'll come back to see you again.
When I come back, let's fight again!
Laboon?!
Laboon! Wait for us! We'll come
back here for sure...! For sure!!
Laboon! You got so much bigger!
Don't be ridiculous! Laboon should be
in the first half of the Grand Line.
He's gigantic! He can't fit
through the hole in the Red Line!
Amazing!
It's like a miracle to come
across a pod of Island Whales.
Some of them have scars like Laboon.
Yeah, the scars look the same! I can't
believe it! But it's not Laboon?!
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
Laboon! Stop! Listen to me!
It's me from the Rumbar Pirates! Brook!
Come to your senses!
That's a different whale!
Laboon!
We're not on a whale watching crew!
It's still dangerous out here!
Now, let me call the roll to make sure
no one got lost in the whirlpool!
--Nami-san!
--Yes!
Robin-chan!
Here.
Okay, we gotta get out of here now.
The ship will be destroyed if
those giant whales crash into us!
Why didn't you call our names?
Sanji-kun! Six more of us
are alive and well here too!
Nami-san, what should we do?!
Let's not do anything.
Yeah, we shouldn't do anything,
fools! Let's watch the whales now!
What's wrong with you?!
Since they're such giant whales,
they're creating a current.
It'll be dangerous to go against it!
Tighten the sails!
Turn the ship in the direction
that the whales are heading!
Okay!
Oh yeah! This is where Laboon came from.
Are any of you related to him?
Be careful, Brook!
Is anyone looking for a calf
who got lost 50 years ago?
Don't worry! He's doing okay
on the other side of the world!
According to Luffy-san, he's very big now.
So please don't worry!
I think Laboon would...
Catch the stream!
Okay!
We're okay now.
We'll stick with the whales for a while.
That's kind of nice.
Oh? Brook?
Yo ho ho ho… Yo ho ho ho…
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
Sea wind blows to where, who knows?
The waves will be our guide!
O'er across the ocean's tide,
the sunset is goin' wild
See the sky! Birds singing
in circles passing by!
Bid farewell to weaver's town!
Say so long to port renowned!
Sing a song, it won't be long
before we're casting off!
Cross the gold and silver waves,
changin' into water sprays!
Sailing out on our journey
to the ends of the sea!
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
Pirates we, we'll divide
and conquer all the seas!
With the waves to rest our heads,
ship beneath us as our bed!
Hoisted high up on the mast
our Jolly Roger flies!
Somewhere in the endless sky,
a storm has started comin' by!
Waves are dancing having fun,
it's time to sound the drums!
Hey, you're giving us a ride?
If we let blow winds of fear,
then the end of us is near!
Let him take us!
Looks like they're gonna go upward too!
Even so, tomor-row the sun will rise again!
Yo ho ho ho… Yo ho ho ho…
It's the New World, the final sea
of the Grand Line, up above us!
I can't wait!
Luffy?
That's it!
Finally!
Let's do it, guys!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6...
...5, 4, 3, 2...
...1!
--We're out!
--In the New World!
--We did it!
--We finally made it!
But it's not time to celebrate yet!
Oh, the whales!
We'll tell Laboon about
you all if we see him!
Laboon's relatives! Take care of yourselves!
Thank you for everything!
I had heard about it but
it's more than I expected!
The New World has...
…really bad weather!
The sky is filled with thunder!
The wind is so strong!
The sea is very rough!
The needle is going crazy!
I see some ships!
Pirates are having a party!
No, those are warships!
Couldn't ask for anything better!
The Navy?
The Straw Hats finally
make it to the surface.
They encounter many grueling trials...
...including a mysterious girl small
enough to fit in the palm of you hand.
However...
...it also brings to light a conspiracy...
...between pirates and the
Navy of the New World!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Z's Ambition!
Lily the Little Giant!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!