Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
The Straw Hats have left the Fish-Man Island
and finally reached the New World.
But not before entering the
treacherous Maubeugemour Sea.
What's this weather?!
We're in the Maubeugemour Sea!
Momemomejuban?!
No, "Maubeugemour"!
Also known as the "Ill-Tempered Sea"!
Home to weather conditions you've
never seen or heard of before!
Arriving there, they met a Giant
girl who ate the Mini-Mini Fruit
and decided to help her save her father
- Panz Fry from the Navy's ship.
But I have to save Dad at any cost!
Before they take him to Impel Down,
this is my last chance to save him!
Lily.
Let me help you!
I wanna try that heavenly food
that only your dad can make!
However, a mysterious
group called the Neo Navy
is trying to kill her father.
Dad!
Consider that our greeting.
Surface and finish them off at once!
Yes, sir!
And a three-way battle erupted
between the Straw Hats,
the Navy and the Neo Navy.
Another bomb?!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Move!
A man?!
Outta my way!
Damn!
I won't let you do whatever
you like on this ship
while it's under the control of the Navy!
Pops' heavenly food is...
...all mine!
"Z's Ambition! A Great and
Desperate Escape Plan!"
Invade the ship!
We won't let you!
Kill the pirates!
A 400 million berry bounty,
huh? Are you a pirate too?
Yeah.
Then to hell with you too!
Leave it up to me.
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Iron Body!
What a strange technique.
Did you eat a Devil Fruit?
I'm a rubber man.
But that wasn't strong enough
to break my Iron Body!
Oh yeah?
I said I won't let you do
whatever you like on this ship!
Roronoa Zoro!
Thank you for waiting. Let's
pick up where we left off!
Advance! Kill the pirates!
Party Table Kick Course!
Get ready to open fire!
He's an easy target.
Dad!
Treinta Fleurs Strangle!
Robin-chan!
Who on earth are they?!
Oh no! It's a big mess!
Hey, Nami!
I know!
I'm trying to think of the best
way to bring back Lily's father!
No! Is that the Thrust Up Stream?!
Bastard! Gum-Gum...
Both Luffy-san and Zoro-san
are on the defensive.
Those two must be very strong!
Take this, you monster!
Hey you!
Even though I'm a soul without a body now,
I'm not happy to be shot at!
There's no mistaking it! Damn! Not now!
Thank you for waiting! Nami!
Franky! We have a problem!
The weather's gonna change drastically again!
It's not safe here!
What?!
Everybody, listen carefully!
The Thrust Up Stream is coming soon!
--The Thrust Up...
--...Stream?
What's that?
Is it something like the Knock Up Stream
that we rode to get to the Sky Island?!
Yes, it is! But it's not that big!
Oh good!
But it could easily blow away a warship!
What?!
And once it starts erupting, it
could appear anywhere around us!
So return to the Sunny immediately!
R-Roger!
Armament Hardening!
Gum-Gum...
Don't you get it yet? Iron Body!
...Jet Bazooka!
What? Haki?!
One-Sword Style!
360 Pound Phoenix!
Franky! The anchors!
Roger!
You brat!
You have some nerve.
You too!
Sanji-kun! Lily!
Nami-san! I guess she's worrying about me.
It's not safe here!
Something like the Knock Up Stream is coming!
What?!
Did the anchors dig into the raft?!
Yeah!
Then, get away on the Sunny now!
--Okay!
--Uh-huh!
What happened?!
Luffy! Silly swordsman!
Let's get away from here with
Coup de Burst and her dad in tow!
Alright!
--I won't let you...
--...Do that!
Usopp!
Oh no, Luffy and the others!
Don't get in my way!
Th-Th-That was scary!
Yo, super welcome back!
Usopp!
Franky, use Coup de Burst now!
I'm afraid I can't!
Huh? Why?
I didn't notice until I got
closer but the raft is too big.
What the hell... Oh, what should I do?
Yeah! That just might work!
What?! Use the eruption of the
Thrust Up Stream to catapult us?!
There's no other way!
But you don't know if it'll
erupt at the right moment...
Shut up!
Sanji-kun, are the anchors still holding?
Yeah!
Hang on tight now! You
have to fly on the raft!
Damn! That was a little off!
Another one's coming.
Nami, not yet?
No!
Not yet.
Now, Franky!
Chicken Voyage!
Coup de Burst!
Luffy!
A flying ship?!
You can't get away from me!
Rescue mission accomplished!
Yeah!
Now, I get to eat that heavenly food!
Um... Don't forget about me!
He got away again.
Once we set our sights on
someone, he can't get away.
I can say the same for you guys
since you know our secret now!
Go to hell!
We've wasted too much time here.
Let's go after them!
What a fight! It's been
going on for 5 hours now!
--They're equal in strength?
--No, Shuzo-san has an advantage.
She doesn't have enough strength left.
I know you're suffering.
Let me finish this for you!
Did I miss?! No worries. I'll
get you with the next one!
What?!
Damn you Devil Fruit eater!
The battle is over.
The winner is Ain!
After that practice match,
Ain became Master Z's aide
and I became leader of this flying squad.
But soon, he will find out
which one of us is more suited
to be his right-hand person.
Looks like we got away
from the Maubeugemour Sea.
The weather is really different
from before. It's quiet here.
Yeah, we've come so far! I don't
see any ship coming after us!
Of course, you don't! That was
an extra-large Coup de Burst!
No one can follow us - even
with a high-speed craft.
We can hide behind these reefs
and catch our breath for now.
Uh-huh! How's it going there?
He's got a deep wound but...
but he's gonna be alright if
he rests for a couple days.
Thank you, Chopper-sa! I appreciate it!
B-Being thanked doesn't make
me happy at all, you bastard!
Anyway, I'm glad that he's okay.
So can you make the heavenly food, like now?
Are you a monster?!
Huh?
Why?! Chopper said he's gonna be okay...
You weren't listening to me, Luffy!
I said he needs to rest!
What? What about the heavenly food?
Boy, even if Lily-chan's father were okay,
we don't have anything to
make heavenly food out of!
Oh, I got some food!
What?
Where? Lily, where is it?!
There, look!
Oh, there it is! When did you get it?!
When the warship blew away
earlier, food was raining down.
I thought "What a waste!" and
picked up as much as I could!
Excellent work!
But under those circumstances? How greedy!
Oh yeah!
Dad, Luffy-sa and the others were
in danger! What was I thinking?!
I got some sake too.
Excellent work.
Hey!
But even if we have food, frying
pan pops can't cook, can he?
Of course not!
I'll cook for...
What are you doing?! I told you to rest!
Ow, ow, ow... It's just for
a little while. I'll be fine.
Dad! Do as Chopper-sa says!
Your name is Luffy, isn't it?
Yeah!  I'm gonna become
the King of the Pirates!
Ow, ow, ow...
Dad!
Listen, Lily.
Dad?
Luffy wants so badly  to
eat the food that I make.
What an honor for a cook!
W-Well, I understand that. But...
On top of that, they saved our lives.
If I don't return the favor, I should
be ashamed of myself as a cook... No.
As a Giant!
Dad!
Now, bring that food here!
I'll make them my heavenly food!
Really?! Thanks, frying pan pops!
No, I have to thank you
instead. Thank you, Luffy!
Lily-chan! I'll make something too!
Okay, I'll help him too! I'll
carry those bags of food!
Me too!
Sake! Sake!
You go and help them too.
Uh-huh! I will!
Shuzo-san, I found them!
They're hiding behind a reef!
How annoying! All ships, prepare for battle!
Let's blow them up along with the reef!
I-I'm afraid we used up all our
torpedoes in the battle earlier
and we're almost out of bombshells too.
All right. Then...
No, we still have a torpedo.
No, we don't.
We can use this submersible as a torpedo!
We are the proud soldiers of
the Neo Navy's flying squad!
We trusted in Master Z and
Shuzo-san and got this far!
Shuzo-san! Let us fight with you! Please!!
Me too!
I'm proud of you guys! I'll
care for you to your deathbed!
Fight to your heart's content
as a Neo Navy soldier!
All torpedoes, go!
I'm not gonna let you get away this time!
Damn pirates!
The Neo Marines have launched a surprise attack
and the Straw Hats begin their final battle against Shuzo.
Both sides deal blows
until Shuzo reveals his ultimate weapon
and unleashes it on Luffy.
As the shockwave hits the Straw Hats,
Lily takes fate into her own hands
and makes her decision!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Z's Ambition! Luffy vs. Shuzo!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!