Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
It's erupting again!
It's right there! Who
cares about the needles?!
Hey, what's this? The
Transponder Snail is crying!
Hey, what's wrong?! You have a stomachache?
Fool! That's an emergency signal.
Somebody's calling for help.
If I pick it up, can we hear them?
Wait, Luffy!
More than 50 percent of
emergency signals are fake!
Help me!
My colleagues are getting
cut one after another!
The samurai are gonna kill us!
Samurai?
Hey you, what's your name?! Where are you?!
Somebody please help me! I'm on...
...Punk Hazard!
It's hot!
This is the place. The name matches.
So this is Punk Hazard...
Those were probably not people's houses.
I think there were some kind
of Government facilities here.
What's wrong, Luffy?
Is that...
What?!
Huh? Does it actually exist?!
No, it's a mythical creature!
There's no way that it's real!
But look at those features...
I don't think it could be anything else!
"A Battle in the Heat! Luffy
vs. The Giant Dragon!"
Aw...
Awesome!!
How cool is that!
D-Don't be so impressed!
Cool!!
I'm outta here!
Wow! I like how he snarls, too!
Cool! So cool!
Who are you?
Don't come after me!
What're you doing, you fool?!
Hey!
The dragon just talked!
No way! You're hearing things!
You think so?
I-I'm not even sure it's a dragon!
Is it really a dragon?
Yes, it's hard to believe but...
...it has a lizard-like
body with giant wings.
It looks exactly how it's described in myths.
No way!
Oh no!
H-He breathed fire!!
This creature is unreal! Am I dreaming?!
How exciting!
It's my turn!
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
Bullet!
It didn't work!
He's well-armored!
Behind you!
Luffy!
He's looking at us!
Come on!
Don't provoke him!
I sense your presence-bu!
What?
Luffy was right!
That dragon just said something!
Three-Sword Style!
Ultra Tiger Hunt!
Damn! He's so strong and durable!
Take this!
Luffy!
I heard him talking!
See?!
I heard it too! But how?
Oh no!
He's flying!
Cool!!
Bu! Are you people allies
of the Seven Warlords too?
The Seven Warlords?!
What're you talking about?
He's gonna breathe fire!
He's right above us! We can't get away!
It's hot!
Wait for me, Nami-san!
I'll keep making good desserts for you!
Oh yeah!
Let's change our perspective.
Pretend that you're in a sauna.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I am breaking out in a super sweat of cola!
It's strange.
The sky above the island is divided.
One half is burning hot and
the other is freezing cold.
I wonder why.
I hope Luffy and the others are not melting.
Huh? What was that?
What's wrong?
I don't know. I feel faint...
I feel lightheaded...
Maybe it's heat stroke...
Is this...
...what they call de-cola-ration?
Y-You guys!
Oh? I'm losing it too...
It's hot!
It's hot and that dragon
said something again!
He said "the Seven Warlords."
Does he have something against them?
Oh no!
Luffy! Leave him up to me!
I'll cut him up this time!
All right!
In that case...
Ow, ow, ow!
Let me knock him down first!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
His body is hot!
Bu! It's strange but it's cool here!
Bu! The flames are cool-bu!
Oh no, not there! It tickles-bu!
Stop it!
That's enough-bu!
That's what I thought!
Hey!
You're not gonna believe this!
Somebody's stuck in the dragon's back!
Huh?! What's going on up there?!
Then the talking voice was...
You bastard!
Eat your own wing!
Fool!
Zoro! Here he comes!
Usopp!
All right!
Special Attack - Green Star!
Trampolia!
One-Sword...
...Style!
Lion Strike!
He did it!
This dragon looks yummy!
We can grill it with the fire on the island!
That sounds great!
Cien Fleurs!
Nami-san!
This time I made a cold crepe
with the Giant Shellfish!
It'll pair nicely with champagne...
Huh?
Oh? Are they sleeping?
Fog?
No, it's not!
Damn! I inhaled too much!
The gas made them sleep!
Is it a natural phenomenon,
indigenous to the New World?
Or did somebody sneak into the ship?
I hope those four
that went to the island took a
Baby Transponder Snail with them.
I have to let them know... somehow...
Two humans...
...one cyborg.
And their pet.
Tie them all up!
Alright!
It's good that they're pirates.
No one will care if they go missing.
Let's take them to the Master!
Luffy and crew have saved
someone from the dragon...
But they are extremely shocked
when they see his bizarre appearance.
Meanwhile, Sanji and the others
have been captured by someone
and are locked in a mysterious room.
It is there that they see an unbelievable sight!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Straw Hats Stunned! Enter: A
Samurai's Horrifying Severed Head!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!