Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,--
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
Responding to an emergency
signal, Luffy and the
others were heading to the
other side of the island.
Meanwhile, Nami and the
others were held captive
in a mysterious facility
on Punk Hazard Island...
I came to this island to rescue my son!
I don't mind cutting thousands
if they get in my way!
--There!
--Shoot! Don't let them get away!
Oh no, that'll be far enough!
Weapons Left!
What's wrong with them?!
Who are they?
Giant children?!
Ch-Children?!
What's going on here?
"Save the Children! The
Straw Hats Start to Fight!"
THE ICE LANDS - A MYSTERIOUS FACILITY
BISCUIT ROOM SANJI'S GROUP
Who are these kids?
Is this the island's day-care or something?
They're so big but are they Giants?
Did we come to an island of Giants?
But there are not-so-big ones too.
Then it's a multi-racial nursery?
There are no adults.
Hey, who are you?
I don't know any of them.
Oh, you must be the ones who got frozen!
Did you escape?
--Frozen?
--What is she talking about?
The mystery of the island deepens.
Isn't that...
...A robot?!
Wh-What's going on?
It's a robot!
How awesome!
--I love robots!
--They're the best!
Huh? The best?
Oh? Sanji-kun?!
Robot! Robot! Robot!
You kids. So you really love...
...my armored self?!
Hey, tell me about "the ones who got frozen."
Look! There's a stuffed animal!
It's a stuffed racoon!
I'm a reindeer!
Lovely!
Cute!
--Help me!
--I want it!
Franky is so popular among boys.
Spiral eyebrows!
Shut up, you brat!
--You're right!
--So weird!
Stop!
A stag-beetle robot!
I can change my hairstyle as I want!
See?
Here is another hand!
With this I can...
...pick my nose!
Super!
Hey, somebody, listen to me!
Boy...
Hey, children!
Do you know a child named Momonosuke?!
He's a boy!
I'm scared!
The severed-head talked!
Run!
Hey kids, tell me about this facility...
Wait!
You fool, shut up!
We can't get any information out of them!
You're scaring them!
The door to the Biscuit Room is open!
They're coming! Let's run to the back!
It must be those pirates!
Don't let them get away!
What kind of facility is this? Tell me!
I'm looking for a boy named Momonosuke!
Keep your mouth shut!
I got hit by a woman!
This is a dishonor to a samurai!
I should commit ritual suicide!
Go ahead! Just stop whining!
You male chauvinist pig!
--Those damn escapees!
--You can't go anywhere!
Wait!
Easy! We're not allowed to
use guns and explosives.
Use as few gas canisters as possible!
If we hit a child, the
Master will be furious!
Hey.
Do you really wanna cross this lake, Luffy?
THE BURNING LANDS LUFFY'S GROUP
Yeah!
But how do we cross it?
Some parts are burning but
there are ice flows as well.
The temperature could be just right.
We're all sweaty so let's swim!
No way!
Robin and I can't swim so...
Are you implying I should carry you?!
Why should I do it?
Stop looking at me like that!
I'm sure Zoro wouldn't wanna...
He's already stretching for it!
Having said that, if we don't cross
it, we have to go all the way around.
I have no choice. All right!
Okay, let's do it!
Special Attack - Green Star!
Fan Grass!
What's this plant?
Boaty Banana!
Oh, it's a boat! That's awesome, Usopp!
And we can use this Fan Grass as an oar!
You have many kinds of seeds!
That's wonderful!
There were a whole bunch of weird
plants on the Bowin Islands.
The deeper I went into the dangerous areas,
the more handy plants I found.
I survived on that islands for two years!
There is no difficulty
that I can't overcome...
--Get on board already, Usopp!
--Or we'll leave you.
Hey, I'm the one who supplied the boat!
All right! Let's go!
To the land of snowcones!
Why aren't you rowing, too?!
It's so windy!
--There's a headwind!
--No wonder.
There is a big difference in
temperature on this island.
It makes for strong winds.
The water is boiling around here.
If we were swimming, it
would've been horrible!
--It's so slow!
--Why don't you row then?!
I won't let you get away! Wait, you bastards!
Oh no!
That centaur again!
Hey!
Did you change your mind
and decide to join us?
Were you recruiting again?!
Stop asking strange creatures to join us!
Is that a horn?
Boss!
Boss?
The guy on the Snail said "Boss," too.
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
The intruders are going that
way! Please finish them off!
Something appeared on the other side.
Is that the Boss?
So the emergency signal
was meant for that Boss?
Then he shouldn't mean us any harm!
I see a man with swords.
So is that the samurai who cut our people?
Now kids, move out of the way.
--Stay out of the way.
--It's dangerous.
Hey, Robot-san! Did you come
from outside the island?
Yes, of course! But I'm
a cyborg, little guy...
Do you have a ship?
Oh yeah, our ship - the Sunny is the best...
Then help us!
What does he mean?
Help us! Please!
Why is he saying that?
Then this is not a day-care?
Sis!
You have to help us! Please!
Please!
Nami-san, don't stop!
Take us out of here!
Please!
Nami-san, let's go!
We are not sick anymore! We are all fine now!
Sick? What kind of sickness?
Damn brats!
Hey, kids!
They are all scary people! You
need to stay away from them!
Is it true? They didn't seem like bad people!
They fooled you.
Then the stag-beetle robot is a villain?
That's right.
--Same for Racoon-chan?
--Yes.
And the man with the spiral eyebrows?
Yes, so let us protect you all.
We will protect you sick kids.
We will put them to sleep
with our cloud guns.
Please... Wait...
I want to...
I want to go home!
Wait!
Dammit! Brats!
Please wait!
Get us out of here!
Sis, please! Help us!
Now, kids, you need to stop!
Sorry! I have to run now!
What's going on?
Hey, let's take them with us!
Crazy! We don't even know
how to save ourselves!
There's no way we can take that many kids!
But what is this?! I have a feeling
- something tragic is gonna happen.
Then,
come back later and help us!
I knew! Even if I've never
been out of this building!
There is nothing on this island, right?!
There is no city! There is no one else!
That's why nobody comes to help us!
I want to see my father and my mother!
Sis, please come back!
Come to help us later!
Nami-san, come on!
Let's help these children!
What are you saying, Nami-san?!
We don't know for sure they need saving!
They said those kids are sick
so this could be a hospital!
We just met them and we don't
know what's going on here!
It's not our job to help every single person!
I understand what you're saying but...
...you can't turn your back
on a child crying for help!
Sis!
--They'll get away if nothing is done!
--Those brats are in the way!
Who cares! Shoot the brats too!
--But the Master will...
--Better than letting them go!
It's too late!
Sanji-kun!
Spiral Bro!
Diable Jambe Collier...
...Strike!
That's amazing!
That guy is very strong!
Damn!
Kung Fu Boost!
Racoon-chan!
Strong Right!
A rocket punch!
Th-They...
...stopped running!
She's kind to kids.
I mean, she's only kind
to kids but I like it.
I'm falling for her even more!
Chopper, you go ahead with Nami-san.
Yeah, I'll protect her!
Hey, brats!
Follow the beautiful lady
and the Kung Fu Racoon!
I will fight our pursuers!
But don't get me wrong!
I'm just doing this to answer Nami-san's
beautiful wish to help you kids.
In fact, I don't like you all
precisely because Nami-san
cares about you so much!
Spiral Bro, thank you!
Shut up, brat! Just run already!
Let's go now!
Everybody, follow us!
Damn! They're taking the kids!
You don't have to do this, Franky.
Letting down Armored Franky
fans is not an option for me!
We will fight you!
Bring it on!
Snow! Snow! I love playing with snow!
IN FRONT OF THE MYSTERIOUS FACILITY BROOK
It's a great way to kill time!
Robin-san told me to wait here
but what's taking them so long?!
Ta-dah! Snowmen!
Let's rearrange its eyes and nose!
It looks like me!
Oh?
Hey! Hey!
Hey, who is it? Why are you doing this?!
Who the hell...
What?
Whaaat?!
J...
Just a torso?!
Nami and Chopper frantically push through
the mysterious facility to save the children.
While Sanji and Franky fight for their lives,
Brook is at the mercy of the powerful torso samurai,
until finally, the two begin their duel.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Swordplay Showdown! Brook vs.
the Mysterious Torso Samurai!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!