All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen,
and regrouped at Dr. Vegapunk's
former laboratory.
What?! The samurai left?!
--Yes.
--Damn!
When I said I saw a torso earlier,
he asked me where in detail.
Boy, that fool!
Sanji, Brook, and Zoro
headed to the lake looking
for the missing samurai.
What's wrong, Synd?
Are you in pain?
Mocha!
What happened, everybody?!
NHC10.
I detected it in their body.
Although it was just a trace amount, it's...
...a drug!
The candy...
Straw Hat bro!
Are you gonna go get me the candy?
No, I can't! If Chopper says "No," I can't!
He is our doctor. Trust him!
You said you're gonna go get it for me!!
Special Attack - Sleep Star!
All right! They are all sleeping now.
Luffy decided to take the
children back to their parents
and set out looking to find the "Master"
who is responsible for the experiment.
What about Straw Hat-ya's group?
Since Monet told me to be
careful with the Straw Hats,
I sent those two just to make sure.
"To Annihilate the Straw Hats!
Legendary Assassins Descend!"
PUNK HAZARD THE REMAINS OF THE
FIRST AND SECOND LABORATORY
They could come after us at any moment.
So please come back as soon as possible.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Control your strength! You're a robot now!
I hope this Master guy will just
come clean about those children.
If he doesn't, I will force him to.
I'll shove my finger into his nose
and make his back teeth rattle!
Franky, please don't talk!
All right! Let's go now!
Good luck!
Take care!
By the way,
why is he sleeping, too?
It's me.
We just took care of three
of them for starters.
What?
Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Cat Burglar.
Soul King.
We left their bodies at the bottom
of the cliff in district F-16.
Can you recover them?
--D-Did you kill them?
--Do you have a problem with that?
W-Well, I mean...
If you don't want them
dead, then don't call us!
No, I'm sorry! The Master
said dead or alive so...
Whoa whoa, don't get so heated up.
Oh, I can't believe I lost it.
Let's stay cool.
We will be counting on you.
CAESAR CLOWN'S LABORATORY
Did you hear that?
Three of them are dead already, Monet!
Yeah?
That's disappointing.
The Straw Hats are a part of the
Worst Generation; as is Law.
The Government is keeping its eye
on them as well as Blackbeard.
And there was a scintillating
newspaper article
with the title "They're Back in Force"
so I thought they were stronger.
What do you think, Law?
You know them well, don't you?
Two years ago, at Sabaody and Marineford,
THE STRAW HATS ARE BACK
you got involved with the Straw Hat twice.
What?
You didn't summon them here, did you?
I told you that I didn't know they were
held captive in the lab until I
ran into them at the entrance.
If I knew, I would have warned you...
...that locking them up
in a room wasn't enough.
I wasn't able to drive the Navy
out thanks to your carelessness.
You know it's bad news for me, too,
if anybody finds out about this place.
Master!
Not now. I'm doing an experiment.
But it's a Warlord!
What did you say?
You wanna stay on Punk Hazard?
It was a pain getting here since Log
Poses don't work for this island
because there was the
Government's secret facility.
Why do you want to stay?
Since this used to be Dr.
Vegapunk's laboratory,
I assume there are traces leading
up to today of Government activity.
All I'm asking for is free roam within
the laboratory and the island.
I can help you with something if you want.
And we'll stay out of each other's business.
But it means you can't tell
anybody that I'm here.
Not even "Joker."
You know a lot. How did
you know all those things?
Do you prefer to have an
amateur who doesn't know
anything over me?
I see what you mean.
We're birds of a feather.
Although I can't trust you, perhaps
there's no harm in what you ask.
What do you think, Monet?
He is from the North Blue.
The Surgeon of Death.
An Op-Op Fruit eater.
So you're a doctor, huh?
There are a whole bunch
of former prisoners who were
paralyzed by poison gas.
Can you treat them?
Well,
you would've been wiser about it if you
wanted to summon your friends here.
You became a Warlord intentionally
by kissing the Government's
ass and came to this island.
I don't think you would do
something to mess that all up.
I'm sorry.
You said...
...those kids will have an urge to come
back here even if you don't do anything.
What do you mean by that?
Oh.
That's because I'm giving them
this drug candy everyday.
When you eat it, it's sweet and fizzy!
And gas fills up your mouth.
It causes instant addiction!
If they go back to their homes,
they won't be able to have it.
You're a sick man. You remind me of somebody.
Aren't you gonna fight the Navy?
Call me if you need me.
I'll cut whoever's head for you.
It's hard dealing with a smart guy.
I wonder how far Zoro went.
He's with Sanji and Brook so I don't think
he's lost in the snow-capped mountains.
Wh-What happened?!
Again! What's going on?!
This is not an earthquake or anything!
We're under attack!
What are they?
They are footprints, aren't they?
Is it an animal?
If it's a human, he must be a Giant.
--Are those bomb blasts?
--That's from the direction we came from.
Does it have something to
do with these footprints?
I sense something. Two
beast-looking creatures.
Let's go back! Nami and
the others are in danger!
Y-Yeah!
Oh no!
If it collapses, the kids are...
Luffy! Everybody! Come back!
There's no time!
We have to handle this on our own!
Do you see anybody?
How many are there? What do they look like?
Well...
Nobody's out there!
No way!
Let's get the party started.
So cool!
What're we gonna do?!
Where are they?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Oh, I fell asleep.
Something's going on outside.
Somebody's come to rescue me, maybe?
Law? The Master?
No, we're on a snow-capped
mountain so it must be them!
Hey, brown guy! You know
something, don't you?!
Who is it?! You better say
it or you'll get this!
Beam!
Beam! Beam!
You're not taking the beam seriously!
It's no use looking for them because
they'll never show themselves!
We don't even know their faces.
What?
However,
they'll carry out an assassination at
any cost in exchange for their reward.
All we know about them is their
footprints are huge and they have low voices.
Oh yeah! There is one
more thing that we know.
They're furry, giant, beast-like men.
The Snow Mountain Killers - stalking
out from deep in the snowstorm!
And we happened to know their
names - Rock and Scotch!
People call them the Yeti Cool Brothers!
We really don't know much about them
but they were from a snowy
region and their age is...
You know a lot!
But nobody knows what they really look like.
They're giant and tough!
And they came here to rescue me!
Your names are on their kill list now!
You're Brownbeard, aren't you?
Your name is also on our kill list.
What's with that guy?!
He's huge but I didn't notice he was here!
Huh? Are you Rock?
--I'm Scotch.
--You just made a joke, I think.
Oh, I probably misheard it.
Gee, was I scared!
The Master asked you to save me, right?
Then just unchain me and let's
take care of the Straw Hats...
You didn't mishear it.
I'm here to kill you by the Master's request.
No way!
Listen.
Oh yeah, and what was that guy's name?
It's his voice!
He has been captured by them.
That shit with a beard.
He was known for his stupidity.
Oh yes, Brownbeard!
What? Master!
That's him?
He was easy to manipulate because
he was so dumb, but he's a pain now.
I don't need him.
Kill him.
Hey, I was right! There's smoke!
Nami! Chopper! Are you all right?!
Answer my question. You're
Brownbeard, aren't you?
I'm glad that you got here.
You'll be alright. Don't worry.
You are...
Be quiet.
These are...
Your new legs.
No...
How is it going?
Master! It's all clear around
here today like any other day!
Good.
Brownbeard, you're such
a great security officer.
You're flattering me!
No...
No!
Master!!
How annoying! You should
drop dead in a cooler way!
Hey, Scotch!
There's another one!
Don't shoot too wildly. You
don't wanna hit those brats.
Oops. That's not cool.
Brownbeard!
How terrible! They're on the same side!
Look at that. Their captain is back.
Let's start with them.
Huh? They're pretty big.
--Are they Giants?
--No, they're slightly different.
You guys, you didn't harm
my friends, did you?!
Oh? Where did he go?!
Luffy!
You alright?
I'm sorry! They took Nami with them!
What?!
He said he wants this one alive.
A robot with Vegapunk's laser weapon, huh?
And kill all the rest.
Okay, let's enjoy every minute of this hunt.
In a cool way!
I assume the detachment team must
have stolen the ship by now.
What is that sound?
THE LABORATORY - THE FRONT AREA
We've been ambushed!
It's not gonna be that easy, huh?
Let's go!
THE LABORATORY - THE BACKDOOR
--Oh?
--Law-san, where are you going?
We just ran into the Navy.
Room.
I don't give a damn.
I'm free to go...
...wherever I want.
In order to get Nami back,
Luffy and crew go after the assassins.
However, the ingenious trap
set within the snowy mountain,
and the relentless attacks from the Cool Brothers
send Luffy into a dilemma. But then
Law appears and makes an unbelievable move.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Save Nami! Luffy's Fight on
the Snow-Capped Mountains!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!