All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After landing on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen,
the Straw Hats learned about the hideous
experiments performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
and headed off to investigate
but as things got going,
Luffy came to form an alliance with
the Heart Pirates led by Trafalgar Law
and is now headed to see
the Master Caesar Clown.
I'll never let him take these children again.
I can't believe he was using them as
his test subjects and drugged them.
I can't forgive the Master guy!
Hey, look at that!
Wh-What's that?!
--Something's flying toward us!
--It's a big bomb!
No, it's not!
Cien Fleurs!
Wing!
Wham!
Master, show yourself!
We will kick your ass and kidnap you!
Luffy, that was supposed to be a secret.
Straw Hat!
Go, Luffy!
That fool! Who said anything
about confronting everyone?!
"On the Verge of Annihilation!
A Deadly Monster Comes Flying In!"
CAESAR'S LABORATORY - THE FRONT DOOR
That bastard! Did he just say he will
kick our Master's ass and kidnap him?!
Screw it! Take the Straw Hats down!
Strong...
...Right!
Smoker-san, what should we do?
Obviously, we have to capture the Straw Hats.
Catch the Straw Hats!
Cien Fleurs!
Clutch!
CAESAR'S LABORATORY - THE BACKDOOR
What should we do?
Just let it be.
Let's go inside.
Do you have a key?
Oh, you can use teleportation, huh?
Room.
Do as we discussed.
Yeah. While you're taking Caesar
and that woman somewhere else,
I'm gonna find out about the drug.
Weapons Left!
We made it here but where's the Master?
I don't think he's out here.
Then where is he?
Probably in the lab.
Okay, that big door must be the entrance.
Let's go.
Straw Hat Luffy!
Oh, Smokey!
THE REMAINS OF THE FIRST
AND SECOND LABORATORY
Unchain me!
Big brothers, unchain me!
Withdrawal symptoms again!
What should we do?!
We should just let them sleep
it off! I'll use it again!
Special Attack - Sleep Star!
Let me go!!
No way! Sleep Star didn't work?!
What?! What should we do now?!
Oh no!
They fell asleep at last.
But it didn't work as well as before.
Yeah, we're gonna have a problem
next time they wake up.
Straw Hat Luffy! What are
you up to on this island?!
Smokey! I'm glad that you're okay!
I was worried because they
were beating you up before!
Don't monkey around with me!
What? You have a stomachache?
Is it constipation?
I did it!
What happened, Smokey? You got weaker.
N-No, I'm...
On top of that, you sound strange today.
Hey hey, please.
Don't get your ass kicked by him...
...when you're in my body!
Oh, that weapon!
You're back out at sea, huh? Straw Hat!
But I won't let you do whatever you want!
I got hit.
It's tipped with Sea Prism Stone.
The girl with the glasses
became this strong, huh?
Her name was...
I'm Smoker!
What?!
Luffy, I think Law did it to them, too.
What? Ah, the "shuffle" thing. I see.
That's why that one was weak.
So this one is...
You're...
...Smokey?!
What's so funny?!
Fight me, Straw Hat.
Second Gear!
That makes it more exciting!
Strong...
...Right!
It'll take forever to beat all of them up.
Let's break the door and
get into the lab at once!
Here we go! Franky...
Too fast!
Let's finish this some other time!
What?!
It's not worth fighting when you
can't use all of your strength!
Don't get...
...saucy with me!
Bye, Smokey!
...Radical Beam!
He made a hole on the door!
How strong are they?!
Was it a laser beam?
Luffy, Robin, I broke the door!
Charge!
You did it already, Franky?!
Smo-yan!
Something strange is flying toward us!
There!
What is it?
That's...
What?
The ship!
What is that?
Luffy! Franky! Wait!
What is it?! It's moving!
Let me handle it!
You're giving me the creeps!
Wh-What is this?!
It's poison gas! Back off!
When it got cut and shot,
it spewed out poison gas!
Put on your gas mask!
Run!
Huh?! What the hell is that?!
Is it some kind of living thing?
I have no idea. What is that?
Say it! What is that?
I-I don't know! I've never seen such a thing!
It fell from the sky, didn't it?
Yeah, but it's moving!
It's disgusting!
Is it alive?
Oh, look!
They merge into one another...
...And get bigger!
What?!
I can just kill it by
pushing it into the river!
Hey, don't do it!
--Poison gas again!
--Pull him out!
1, 2, 3!
--Hey...
--I-It's...
Ow! Ow! It touched my skin!
Wipe it off! Somebody!
Hey, get me a piece of cloth!
We shouldn't touch it as I thought!
--What should we do?
--I don't know!
Back off, you guys!
It doesn't look like it's resistant to fire!
Let's just burn it!
Take this!
There is no living thing
that isn't afraid of fire!
You're smart!
Burn it up!
See, it's weak against fire!
That serves you right!
--Clearly, it's suffering!
--It's starting to burn!
Take it! Take it! Take it! Take it! Take it!
Yeah!
Take it! Take it!
What?!
You guys!
Hey, what just happened?
I don't know! I've never
seen something like that!
When we touch it, it spews poison
and when we burn it, it explodes!
We don't even know if it's alive
or not in the first place.
Who cares. It's gone now.
Oh yeah, you're right.
That's not all.
It killed those Navy soldiers who
stole the ship and sailed out as well!
For us, that was...
What?
It's here!
It fell from the sky again!
--That's like the one from before.
--How many are there?
Is it some kind of living thing?
I don't know. I've never seen such a thing.
Me, too.
I'm so stunned - my eyes
popped out of my head.
But I don't have eyes in the first place.
Quite a strange thing...
...Doing quite strange things.
Wow! It's really flying up high!
Isn't it coming toward us?
What is this?!
Disgusting!
It's raining down!
Run! Don't ever touch it!
Smoker-san, it's too dangerous here!
Let's take cover!
Yeah.
Good boy! I'm sorry that I
locked you up for three years!
Master!
Why are you here?! It's dangerous out here!
I knew it. So you're Caesar
Clown, aren't you?!
You are...
...the Master?!
Yes, indeed!
Everyone from the Straw Hat
Pirates and the Navy G-5!
Behold! The greatest scientist in the world!
Master Caesar Clown!
Just wait a few moments.
Since he's weak to water,
he's flinging pieces of himself
over little by little...
...in order to cross the lake!
From the Burning Lands...
...to the Ice Lands!
When all of his pieces reach this side,
you will all experience it!
The chemical weapon explosion that
happened four years ago on Punk Hazard!
A world of death in which no one can survive!
And you will learn!
Just how powerful my weapon is,
that it can destroy an island!
And the greatness of the world's best
scientist who created the weapon!
It's me - Master Caesar Clown!
I got you!
What?!
Luffy and Caesar Clown have an intense battle
where neither side is willing to yield.
At the end of the fierce battle,
Luffy believes that he has Caesar, but then
the fearsome power of the
Gas Gas Fruit is revealed.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Intense Battle!
Caesar Exercises His True Power!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!