The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
It's coming!
Shoot it, quickly! Shoot it!
Grandpa Ryu!
Grandpa Ryu! Hang in there!
"Through the Sky They Soar!
The 1,000-Year Legend Lives Again!"
Hang in there!
What happened to going to the
dragons' nest?! Try hard to live!
Grandpa Ryu...
--Grandpa Ryu!
--Damn those guys!
--This is bad!
--Yeah. He can't swim, huh?
Whew, what a scare...
It suddenly came right for me...
Commodore! The Millennial
Dragon is starting to sink!
Don't fret! We'll still make it in time!
Fire a harpoon and drag it in!
Target the Millennial Dragon!
Okay! Fire!
Yes, sir!
What?!
What are you doing?!
You've no idea of the value of the
thing you're standing on right now!
All I want are the
Millennial Dragon's bones!
Once I have its Dragonite,
I can attain everlasting life!
Why, you...!
Grandpa Ryu isn't a thing!
He's our friend!
He's a dear friend
who's on a journey with us!
What utter nonsense!
In that case, you can sink
into the sea with your friend!
How dare you try to harpoon me?!
Fire at that brat!
B-But, if we do that, we'll blow
the Millennial Dragon up, too!
No matter!
Bone fragments will do just fine!
Y-Yes, sir! Aim the
sub-cannons out to sea!
Yes, sir!
You're fine staying here?!
What kind of wimpiness is that?!
You still haven't
accomplished your goal!
What happened to going to your nest?!
Don't give up by saying
you're staying here!
Of course I will!
Don't worry about Apis!
Just think about yourself now!
Untie these ropes!
--I gotta go to Grandpa Ryu!
--What's that?!
I gotta save Grandpa Ryu!
L-Leave Grandpa Ryu to Luffy!
No, no, no!
I gotta go! I gotta go!
If anyone, he'll manage somehow!
The entire sea is shaking!
What is this?! What's happening?!
What the...?!
What the...?! What the...?!
Grandpa Ryu!
Really? So that's it!
What is happening?!
There shouldn't be any underwater
volcanoes in these waters!
No matter! Fire! Fire! Fire!
I see!
You have dear friends of your own, too!
--Grandpa Ryu!
--What's he bellowing for?
He's calling...
Calling?
He's telling Millennial Dragons
all around the world that it's "time"...
It's "time"?
What's that mean?
Hey! W-What's that?!
S-So many Millennial Dragons!
--These're Grandpa Ryu's friends!
--Yeah!
--What the...?!
--Where the hell'd they come from?
T-Those are...!
Dragonite!
It's a mother lode of Dragonite!
Shoot them! Shoot them down!
W-We can't! Our cannons
can't reach that high!
Grandpa Ryu!
Yeah! I know!
I promise I'll tell Apis!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Gonna borrow your neck!
...And...
...Battle-Axe!
What?!
What was that?!
The commodore's been beaten!
Troops sure are weak once
their bosses are taken out.
Are they just gonna reel in
their chains and run away?
We better get goin' too.
They're circling around...
What's going on?
Hey! Let's go!
Yeah!
The chains!
--You idiots! What're you doing?!
--We're gonna crash!
That's really somethin'!
Nami-san! I'm back!
--Just get on already!
--Where's Luffy?
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Sorry to bother you again!
--Yo!
--Don't give me, "Yo!"
Can't you come back more quietly?!
You're gonna wreck the ship!
Grandpa Ryu...
--An earthquake?
--Again?!
Grandpa Ryu...
I wasn't able to keep my
promise to you, Grandpa Ryu...
I wasn't able to take
you to the dragons' nest...
No, Grandpa Ryu's wish came true.
Can't you hear the
Millennial Dragons' voices?
W-What the...?!
What's with these earthquakes?!
T-This one's big!
Hey! Look!
T-The sea's pulling way back!
So that's what it meant!
What is it, Nami-san?!
The dragons' nest really is here!
They're not called "Millennial Dragons"
because of their life spans!
It's because they come to this
island only once every 1,000 years!
Millennial Dragons are migratory!
And it's by no coincidence that
they've all flocked here now!
It's no wonder they call it Lost Island!
Because it only surfaces
once every 1,000 years!
So of course no one today
remembers the last time it surfaced!
And now... this very moment...
...is when the dragons' nest has appeared!
Whoa...
Say, is that what I think it is?
Yeah! It must be the dragon nest
Grandpa Ryu wanted to go back to!
This is?
--H-Hey! Apis!
--Apis!
--Why'd she suddenly run off?
--Grandpa Ryu.
Grandpa Ryu is here...
Grandpa Ryu!
Grandpa Ryu! Grandpa Ryu!
Just by coincidence,
the place Grandpa Ryu sunk
was where the dragons' nest was...
Do you suppose that might
help him rest in peace better?
It's okay! He said his wish
came true when he was sinking!
So this is the dragons' nest?
Look at all these weird rocks...
I think they're probably
made of Dragonite...
Huh?!
Look at this rock here.
Doesn't it look just like a dragon?
Oh, now that you mention it...
But why are the rocks dragons?
Because they were on the ocean floor
for a thousand long years.
The materials in their bodies fossilized.
Oh, I see!
--Do you really get it?
--Nope! Not at all!
They say when elephants are about to die,
they hide themselves
in their elephant graveyard.
Maybe the same is true here.
This might be a dragon graveyard...
A dragon graveyard?
No! It's not!
Grandpa Ryu said going back
to his nest would make him better!
This can't be a graveyard!
Apis...
Grandpa Ryu was
a lost Millennial Dragon...
Luffy?
He was all alone,
for a thousand years...
But he made friends with you, Apis.
He said out of the
1,000 years he was alive,
this last year with
you was his happiest.
Luffy... You understand
the dragons' language?
I just somehow know.
Geez, talk about half-baked...
But there's no doubt about it!
You liar...
You're such a liar, Grandpa Ryu!
If this is the dragons' nest...
If you've made it back to the dragons' nest,
then open your eyes again!
Talk to me!
Get better!
Grandpa Ryu wasn't lying at all!
He said that Millennial Dragons
return to the nest every 1,000 years
and are reborn again.
Grandpa Ryu said that?
There!
A baby Millennial Dragon?!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
You know, Apis.
This isn't just a
Millennial Dragon graveyard.
I think it's a place
that connects to new life.
--Thank you, everyone!
--Eh?
For bringing Grandpa Ryu
back to the dragons' nest.
I realize it now, too.
I realize what kind of place this is,
and why Grandpa Ryu
wanted to return here so badly.
Apis...
It's an amazing place, isn't it?
Now I understand why my ancestors
went so far as to build a temple...
Thank you, Luffy!
Okay! Let's go back to the village!
Everyone there must be worried,
and probably surprised, too!
Yeah!
Alright! Let's hurry back to
the ship and leave the island!
Yeah!
Whew, I'm starving!
Sanji! Make me some food!
--Yeah!
--Meat! Make meat!
I'll have sautéed veggies
with lots of bean sprouts!
Where've I heard that before?
Man, these rocks are cool!
These all used to be
Millennial Dragons?
Yeah, it looks that way.
Even if they are Dragonite,
there's no way to extract it like this.
Then the whole elixir
of immortality thing...
...was nothing but a
dream within a dream.
Even if we took these
coral-covered fossils back with us,
we'd never get an elixir from them.
Yeah, huh?
Meaning those Navy bastards
did all that work for nothing.
Fools! As if I would ever
kick the bucket so easily!
I must pay you back
for what you've done!
But first...!
Millennial Dragons!
With this many, I can have
all the Dragonite I want!
Move.
Eric! Look!
A flock of Millennial Dragons!
I'll pay you money!
What do you say to another deal?!
We can make elixirs of immortality
from living Millennial Drag--!
Get out of my way!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
--That's Eric!
--Man, he's stubborn!
--I'll handle him.
--No, I will!
Get lost!
Lost Island, huh?
It's sad to leave it now.
Alright! Set sail! The Grand Line,
at last! Isn't this great?!
Yeah, I can't wait!
--There it is!
--So that's the Red Line!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Angry Showdown!
Cross the Red Line!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!