All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,--
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
After forming an alliance with Trafalgar Law,
Luffy finally encountered Caesar Clown
but was beaten by his mysterious power.
Meanwhile, Law, too, got taken down by
the Navy G-5 base commander - Vergo.
So what I'm going to do is give Smiley,
the weapon from four
years ago, a big "boost."
It will add a new effect to the poison gas
and the weapon of mass destruction
will reach completion.
The new weapon that will make
its debut today is called...
...Shinokuni!
Hey, guys! I see a ball!
Let's go!
Smiley! I missed you!
It's been three years!
Oh yes, Smiley?
This brings back memories!
I have something good for you!
That's a big candy!
What is that?
Good boy, Smiley.
Nobody can stop him now!
"The Deadliest Weapon of Mass
Destruction in History! Shinokuni!"
--What is that creature?!
--Doesn't it look like those creepy jellies?!
What is going on?!
He ate it!
He ate the candy!
You ate it!
Smiley!
Be reborn!
What can he be reborn as?
The perfect weapon of mass destruction.
That's such a big frog!
Now...
...be reborn!
Smiley!
Look out! Something's going on!
What is "something"?!
How do I know?! But I'm
sure it's something bad!
Just do as the Master
says and run to the lab!
Damn! I can't believe the
sled broke! Why now?!
Master!
He's acting strange since he ate the candy!
I wonder if the candy was that good!
Let's just run!
Even soldiers from this island
are running desperately!
I have a bad feeling about this!
Couldn't agree more!
Good work, Smiley!
See you again!
Now, come to life!
The weapon of mass destruction - Shinokuni!
What is that?!
Change the face of the island completely!
Hey, don't tell me...
Run!
Wait for me!
Oh! Hey, wait!
Oh, my legs!
What happened?!
Help me...
--What's happening?!
--I don't know! Just run!
My body...
I can't move it!
Run! Just run!
Master!!
Yes! It worked!
Nobody can get away this time!
This is it!
The problem with the last experiment
was there were survivors.
They could still move even after being
poisoned so they were able to escape.
Which means...
...I should've petrified them!
The gas clings to people's bodies like ash.
It enters through their skin and
paralyzes their whole body at once!
Now, the perfect weapon of
mass destruction, Shinokuni!
Give us a good glimpse of hell!
What the hell is going on?!
People are...
Help me...
...solidifying!
Master!
Hey, what is that?
This is something out of a horror movie!
Those who just died looked
like Caesar's men...
What was that purple smoke?
By the way, where are they filming this?
If you don't know yet, you
better not turn around!
Don't tell me that was...
No! That was happening on this island?!
Master!
Oh no! We have to run! Or
we'll end up like them...
It's impossible!
There's nowhere to run on
the island from such gas!
Oh, I see! That's why
they sealed off the lab!
They didn't want the gas to enter!
Open up, Caesar!
Damn! I don't wanna die here!
Damn! Damn! This is not joke! Open up!
Hey! I found him!
Brownbeard, you okay?!
He's still breathing but...
He's badly wounded...
We're okay thanks to you...
Caesar!
Gastanet!
Brownbeard...
Anyway, let's pull him out from
under this iron pipe, Sanji!
I am Nami!
Hey! Don't be so disappointed again!
Well, it's just...
It's gonna be pretty heavy physical work!
We have no choice!
Uh-huh!
Damn! It won't budge an inch!
Come on!
We'll pull you out soon!
Hang in there, Brownbeard!
He's right! You can do it!
You two...
Don't die, Brownbeard!
I'm not gonna...
…kick the bucket yet!
That asshole - Caesar is...
...unforgivable!
Brownbeard...
But I have to save my crew first!
Otherwise, I can't die in peace!
Hey, you...
I gotta get to the lab where my
crew are as soon as possible!
But you're hurt all over...
So we all wanna go to the same place!
We have to save those
kids from that jerk, too!
So why don't you join forces with
us and beat that gas bastard...
What's that smoke?
Huh? What's that? It's
a huge amount of smoke!
That doesn't look like just smoke to me.
It could be poison gas.
What? Poison gas?!
It's coming this way!
Hey hey hey! What should do?!
Don't ask me!
Do something about it!
Oh no no! What do you want
me to do about that smoke?!
--Let's just go to the...
--You two, get on my back!
What?
R...
Run!!
It's gonna reach us soon!
Guys, run at full speed!
If anybody gets caught,
we'll have to leave you!
Zoro-san, it's gonna catch
us if we don't do something!
We're dead! It's catching up to us!
Run faster than the wind!
Did we outrun it even a little bit?!
Don't turn around! Just focus
on running at full speed!
We can't run like this for very long!
I see a mysterious animal up ahead!
What is that?!
That's...
--A dragon!
--A dragon?!
A dragon?!
No way! A dragon is a mythical creature!
They exist on this island!
But that one is way smaller
than the one I saw!
Oh yeah! If we can catch
it, we can fly on it!
That's a great idea!
Alright! I can't run like this any longer!
Let's catch it!
Wait, dragon!
Oh, that's Zoro and the others!
They're being chased by the smoke!
Dragon!--
What are they doing there?
I mean, why are they running like that?
Samurai-san got his whole body back.
Oh yeah! He's not gonna let
me have those legs, then.
Hey, Robin! That's not important now!
Hey, guys! That smoke is
deadly! You have to run...
Oh no... I can't even raise my voice.
Damn Sea Prism Stone!
Are they your friends, "Straw Hat Luffy"?
That's just what I'd expect from
your friends - they're tough!
But soon they're going to be running
out of breath and poisoned by the gas.
And eventually, there'll be only an
uninhabitable "Land of Death (Shinokuni)"!
No one outside of this
laboratory will survive.
Neither will any of you!
What's happening?!
Now prove it to the world!
Before this weapon of mass
destruction - Shinokuni,
a pirate with a 400 million berry bounty,
a Navy vice admiral,
and even a Warlord...
...are totally helpless...
...against the tide of death!
Oh no! Oh no!
He's gonna do something
to Luffy and the others!
What should I do?!
I want to help but I'd be easily
caught with these wounds!
And then the formula for
the drug that I found
and the sedatives I got will be wasted!
Oh no! What should I do?!
Ouch! Oh!
Boy! That was close!
Huh? A paper?
"Don't do anything"?
Who wrote this?!
What's that?! A cage?!
Could it be...
--Smo-yan!
--Tashigi-chan!
What a relief! They're fine!
Oh no!
--But they're still held captive!
--Damn! So we're all gonna die!
Smo-yan! Tashigi-chan!
Everybody!
By the way,
that laboratory is really well-built!
Yes, it is.
You can easily carry big
equipment with this thing.
H-How can you two be so relaxed?!
Hmmm... Okay, what should we do?
It was unexpected to see Vergo
here but Straw Hat-ya...
We can't miss a beat here.
The plan is still on.
Don't mess it up this time.
Let's fight back.
Okay!
As it garners attention all across the New World...
...the Straw Hats finally come face to face with Shinokuni.
Just when the crew's annihilation is all but guaranteed...
Law's life-or-death plan is set in motion!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Launching the Counter Attack!
Luffy and Law's Great Escape!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!