All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen.
After learning about Caesar's motive,
they are on the move to save the children,
kidnap Caesar, and escape from the island--
all while trying to escape Shinokuni.
I have treated him
as my young brother
and watched closely
over him as he grew up.
What a shame.
I understand.
I know it's hard for you, Vergo,
but I need you to take care of Law there.
I wanna make him wish
that he was never born.
So kill him in a horrific way.
"Luffy Dies from Exposure?!
The Spine-chilling Snow Woman Monet!"
D BUILDING - THE "SAD" MANUFACTURING ROOM
I feel like my hand has been bitten
by my own dog.
Law.
This is too much -
even for a mischievous child.
You were too smart
for your own good.
People like you...
...tend to die young.
It'd be easiest for me to kill
you by crushing your heart
but I'm not gonna do that.
I'll torment you slowly as I please
and warp your smart-ass face...
...with fear.
Like that time!
Stand up, Law.
It's too soon to die.
C BUILDING 4TH FLOOR - CAESAR'S RESEARCH ROOM
Damn! What does she want?!
Hey, bird woman!
Come on out!
I won't let you go after the Master.
This thing again! But it's nothing!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
Another wall?!
What's going on?
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
What?!
What are these walls?!
Hey, bird woman!
What are you doing?!
Ten-layer Kamakura!
There are ten layers to this Kamakura.
It's not easy to break the snow walls
if they're layered one after another.
What? Are you trying to buy time?!
I can break them all quickly...
I bet so.
I think you can break this Kamakura.
If you think so, stop wasting my time!
Don't get so hot!
I don't think I'm gonna lose you at all!
I'm not surprised.
I don't think I will win
if I fight you.
However,
the strongest isn't always
the winner in a fight.
It's cold.
She's like a block of ice.
Let go of me!
You can't push me away.
You're now in my embrace
and your power is diminished.
You will lose all of
your physical strength
to my cold body in no time.
And eventually,
your heart will freeze
and you will
die in your sleep.
Look.
It's snowing heavily around you.
You feel very tired, don't you?
That's it.
It's okay.
Just let it be.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Close your eyes slowly.
Now, relax.
Good night.
Get a grip!
This is just the beginning
of the New World!
Jet Spear!
The floor!
What tremendous hidden strength he has.
But falling through here
will land him in the slide to the
garbage dump deep underground.
He'll never be able to come
back up unless he can fly.
I didn't expect him to
sabotage himself like that.
Goodbye!
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - NEAR THE BISCUIT ROOM
The candy!
Give us the candy!
You must never
eat that candy again.
Shut up! Get out of our way!
Don't you wanna go home?
I know it's hard
but you have to endure it.
I won't let you pass through here.
You can't go to the Biscuit Room!
Move!
You're in our way!
You bastard!
The candy!
Wait.
Let go of me!
Give me the candy!
The candy!
No!
Ouch! You're hurting me!
Oh, sorry!
I didn't mean to hurt you...
Don't get in our way,
you monster!
It's our candy!
Damn!
I can't stop them without hurting them!
Now is our chance!
Let's go to the Biscuit Room!
No!
Don't go that way!
Oh no!
The effect of the Rumble Ball
is about to wear off!
We can eat the candy soon!
The candy!
Run! To the Biscuit Room!
We can eat the candy!
Hey, kids, wait!
Oh no!
I can't move!
Damn!
Kids, no!
If you take more of the drug,
it will ruin your body!
Please, everybody!
Stop!
Please stop!
Don't eat the candy!
Damn! Dammit!
Damn! Damn!
I can't save them
because I have no power!
Chopper!
What's going on here?!
Nami!
Everybody!
Are you all right, Chopper-san?!
What's wrong with those kids?!
They've gotten more violent!
Momonosuke! Where are you?!
I'm glad that you're all here!
Tell us what's going on, Chopper!
Caesar is trying to turn them into giants
in order to make them demonic
soldiers, just as we thought.
I can't handle them alone anymore!
You guys have to stop them
as soon as possible!
The Biscuit Room is to the left!
The candies are there!
Mocha is the only child in her
right mind and she's helping me.
We were trying to stop the other children
but we couldn't!
She is protecting the candies
in the room all alone!
We're here at the Biscuit Room!
The candy!
Mocha is in danger!
Mil Fleurs
Gigantesco Mano!
Go forward while I hold them here.
Yeah, thanks!
Get out of our way!
They're not gonna be
stopped so easily!
They'll stop at nothing
when they're in that state!
Mocha is...
Mocha!
Give us the candy!
No, everybody!
I can't give it to you!
The candy!
It's evil candy!
Pull yourself together!
We asked Chopper-chan and
the others to help us!
Give it to me!
No!
If we don't listen to them,
we can't go home!
It's no use! Just run!
Run, Mocha!
Hey, wait! That's no fair!
Chase her!
Wait!
Are you gonna eat it all yourself?!
I'm not gonna let them have it!
I wanna go home with everybody!
What's this?!
It's cold! I'm freezing!
The exit is sealed!
What should I do?!
You don't have to
worry about anything.
It's Monet-san!
Who is that woman?
Oh, it's her!
She is the bird woman
that I told you about!
Monet-san, please help me!
Mocha, it's not nice
to keep it all to yourself.
You have to share
the candies with everyone.
What?!
Oh, she uses sorcery!
She's a Logia-type?!
So she's our enemy, huh?!
Monet-san, why?
B BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - AN EXAMINATION ROOM
Oh yeah, where did the boy go?
The boy?
Uh-huh.
He entered into the "secret room"
where no one is allowed
and transformed into a small dragon.
The boy named Momonosuke.
The brat who transformed into a dragon?
I mean, "the boy"!
How did you know
about that, young lady?
I was watching it secretly.
It happened in the "secret room"
so I didn't tell anyone.
But I got here on the same ship
with him so I've been worrying.
Oh I see.
But he's doing okay.
This laboratory is big and...
...there are various treatment rooms
and he's just in a different room.
Hmm.
Is he eating something?
Why doesn't he eat anything?
No no, he's eating.
Don't worry.
He's fine.
Listen.
Don't tell anyone about him
and the "secret room." Okay?
Uh-huh.
I can't believe one of the
children knows about it.
We have to let the Master know.
I never thought
I'd come to this secret room myself.
But this is the only place I can pull it off.
It's all their fault!
It could've been a great show -
everything perfect and lovely,
and more befitting of the
world's greatest scientist!
But they screwed it up!
Straw Hat Luffy!
And his crew!
The Navy G-5!
Trafalgar Law!
I'll make them regret ruining my plan
even after they go to hell!
Bow down to my scientific prowess!
Are you guys frustrated because your
scheme is coming crashing down?
It is that important to you guys, isn't it?
This thing?!
Watch your mouth, you squirt!
Room!
Come back to me, my heart!
Counter Shock!
I have a message from Joker.
He said "What a shame."
It didn't work!
I was pretty sure that I could
take my heart back from Caesar.
But I didn't expect you here.
Vergo!
It's Vergo-san to you!
I'm in the middle of something.
Does it have to be now?
Vice Admiral Smoker.
I was going to silence
you anyway, though.
You better make your move.
It's not so pleasant to watch...
...a scumbag like you!
The pirate -
Vergo!
Smoker's rage explodes at the fact
that Vergo's betrayed his men,
and Vergo closes in on him
with overwhelming Haki!
The fierce battle between Smoker and Vergo intensifies,
as Smoker puts his spirit and
pride as a Marine on the line.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Fists Collide!
A Battle of the Two Vice Admirals!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!