All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen
and learned about the ruler of the
island - Caesar Clown's motive.
All while trying to escape Shinokuni,
along with their pirate ally
- the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
Luffy and the others are on
the move to kidnap Caesar,
-- save the children, and
escape from the island.
Give us the candy!
--No!
--Give it to us!
No, you can't have it!
Shut up!
Just give us the candy already!
What is she thinking?!
No, spit them all out!
Mocha, can you hear me?!
Mocha!!
I told you what kind of drug they are!
What?!
Straw Hat Luffy! Why are you here?!
Shoot! Shoot!
Where's Caesar?
I don't know! I-I don't know anything...
Where's Caesar?!
"Brownbeard in Grief! Luffy
Lands a Furious Blow!"
Shinokuni, the deadly gas, is
flowing into the Third Laboratory
and starting to fill up B
Building where the Straw Hats,
the Navy G-5, and the children are.
It's not this way! Go back, go back!
It's only gas - how is it outpacing me?!
Because you went the wrong way!
Keep still, you brats!
Sedate them already, G-5!
A few more to go, brother!
--Don't resist, children!
--Calm down!
Hey, hurry up, racoon! We don't have time...
Don’t give up, Mocha!
You can make it!
Mo... Momonosuke!
W-W-Wait, Kin'emon-san!
If you go that way, you'll run into the gas!
I don't even see any soldiers,
let alone my people!
What was that creepy room?!
What's this door?
I hear something...
...or not.
Master! Look!
That's Brownbeard!
I thought he was captured by Straw Hat.
--He looks okay.
--Good, good.
The Video Transponder Snail is running.
That means...
Soldiers of Punk Hazard! Listen!
I know you're watching me somewhere!
You're all being fooled!
Caesar is telling you nothing but lies!
You're all gonna die if you stay here!
What is he talking about?
Has he gone crazy after being
captured by the Straw Hats?
Brownbeard is on the floor
below - R Building 1st floor.
But the Straw Hats and Navy
soldiers will arrive there
soon according to your plan.
Should we tell Brownbeard to come up here?
I'll tell you the truth about Caesar!
No, I'll go down.
We're coming with you then.
Caesar!
Oh, my dear underling - Brownbeard!
I'm glad that you got away from Straw Hat!
Are you alright?
You look awful!
Don't touch me!
Oh? Why are you in such a bad mood?
What's wrong?
I want my people back!
We got robbed at the center of
the island but they didn't die!
I'm sure they're back already!
Whoa-whoa, he's messing with the Master.
Huh? Your people?
Oh yeah...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank!
M-M-Master!
Master!
What's going on?
Oh, you must be one of Brownbeard's.
Master! There are Navy soldiers at
the main entrance and it's closed!
We can't get inside! Please guide us!
Oh no! That's serious!
Let me see what I can do! Wait there!
Th-Thank you very much, Master!
Master...
Master, how are you going to let them in?
Forget about it.
Shinokuni will be inescapable
out there soon enough.
I wonder what happened to them.
They don't even call me anymore.
If they're not here, they must be...
Are you worried? I think you are.
If they were out there, they're
definitely dead because of Shinokuni!
What'd you say?!
Screw you!
Hey, what're you doing, Brownbeard?!
Brownbeard?!
I can't trust your words anymore!
--What happened to him?!
--What is he doing to the Master?!
I'll tell you guys this
because we spent the last two
years together on this island.
Leave the island now!
Do you wanna know what he
called you behind your back?!
This was his special name for you!
Guinoa pags.
Guinoo pah!
Guinoa poh...
Guinoh... Guinah...
What're you trying to say, Brownbeard?!
--Speak clearly!
--Is it some kind of spell?!
He's a funny guy!
Guinoh...
I don't know what you're saying!
They will keep following me
thinking I'm their savior!
They don't know that I kept them
alive because they're my guinea pigs!
I said "Guinea pigs"!
Why?! I got tongue-tied!
You did something, didn't you, Caesar?!
Oh, what is it this time?!
Are you putting on an act?!
Oh, are you okay? Huh?
It's a muscle relaxant.
You're losing strength around your mouth
and your whole body, aren't you?
Oh yeah, I remember now, Brownbeard.
About your former subordinates...
I let them die!
You asshole!
How dare you!
How dare you kill my people!
Oh, there is another thing
that I'd like to tell you.
The chemical weapon explosion
that nearly killed all
these soldiers four years ago?
I was the one who caused it!
It wasn't Vegapunk?!
This bastard did harm to everybody
and pretended that he saved them?!
Hey, stop! Stop it!
Help me! Brownbeard is going crazy!
Run, everybody!
Everything that's been going on this
island is all staged by Caesar!
Run, guys! He's a devil disguised as a human!
Hey, Brownbeard!
How could you do that to
a person who saved you?!
Oh no! He's really dangerous!
It's too late!
I guess Straw Hat did something to him!
Brownbeard!
Shoot! Shoot him! He's gonna attack you guys!
Shoot!
Now, let me finish him off.
Gastane...
Oh?
Did we make it out of that hole?
Yeah.
You climbed that wall to the top, huh?
Shoot!
Now, let me finish him off.
Momo, stay back!
Gastane...
Master!
Oh, that was close!
It grazed my body!
Dammit! Who is it?!
It's Straw Hat...
...Luffy!
His kindness saved my life
as it did to the others.
The Master was our warm-hearted savior!
Return to 2nd floor, everyone!
The Straw Hats and the
Navy will be here soon!
--Get ready for the experiment!
--Yes, sir!
Broadcast it for the brokers!
--Let's go!
--Hustle!
I assume they'll all be dead in five years.
So we need to find more kids.
Luffy! It was him!
He was the one who were talking about...
...harming those kindhearted children!
I know.
People on this island were tricked
into being here, weren't they?
What is this island?!
All right.
You don't know anything so let me
tell you the secret of this island.
--There's no sound!
--Hurry up!
--Checking the video!
--Pull the elevator up!
This island is like gas or air.
An island that doesn't seem to exist.
Do you get it?
Listen, this island shouldn't even exist.
That's why it's suitable to the
work of an underground community.
It's an epicenter of evil science.
We can do unlawful experiments or get
test subjects illegally as we like!
We have some powerful people backing us
and they'll cover up everything.
So no one out there would know a thing.
No matter how much you cry or scream,
no one will come to the rescue.
You don't know a damn thing
about this island, Straw Hat!
If you're getting involved without taking
it seriously, you'll end up dead!
Allying with Law is also not a good idea.
He wants to mess with SAD.
He is using you to kidnap me because I'm
the only person who can create SAD.
Let me tell you about SAD, Straw Hat.
The most dangerous Warlord - Don
Quixote Doflamingo owns this factory
and here, SAD is processed
into a fruit called "SMILE."
Do you know what SMILE is?
We successfully recreated a Devil Fruit!
SMILE is a Zoan type, man-made Devil Fruit.
Anyone who wants to become
powerful yearns for it.
Doflamingo is selling SMILEs
to big-timers in the New World.
I heard one of the Four Emperors
is already on the move...
...to form an army of hundreds
of Devil Fruit eaters with SMILE.
Doesn't it send a chill down your spine?
Do you understand what you're dealing with?
By interfering with Doflamingo's business,
you'll piss so many big names off.
When they start going into action,
it's gonna shake up the whole world.
And that's what Law wants.
What fools!
They're out of your league!
Catch me if you can! But I'm protected!
Doflamingo! The Four Emperors!
Do you even have balls to
pick a fight with them?
I don't think so!
If you wanna run, do it now!
Get out of my face!
A fight?
Wow!
I've been...
...picking fights all along!
Undaunted by the powerful Gas Gas Fruit attacks...
...Luffy corners Caesar with his fists of rage.
But elsewhere, Smoker,
facing another powerful Haki user,
is fighting an overwhelmingly losing battle...
...and lies on the verge of death and defeat.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Surprising Outcome!
White Chase vs. Vergo!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!