All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen
and learned about the ruler of the
island - Caesar Clown's motive.
All while trying to escape Shinokuni,
they are heading to R Building with
the children that they rescued.
Finally, a climactic battle rages
on-- between Luffy and Caesar!
LAND OF DEATH
This is my scientific power!
Caesar is...
...the type of person that
Luffy hates the most!
H-Help me, Master!
Luffy won't forgive Caesar!
Caesar!
I don't ever wanna see your face again!
Go to hell!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Magnum!
Oh yeah, Straw Hat!
You can work under me if you want...
"Raid! An Assassin from Dressrosa!"
VARIOUS PLACES IN THE NEW WORLD
What is going on?
Is this some kind of joke?!
This is what they call a "public experiment"?
He kicked Caesar's ass!
Mama should know about this-bon!
Joker is going to take action.
Let "Jack" know about this.
You sure?! It's not gonna be pretty!
I think they formed an alliance.
Let the world know.
This is not just a problem
in the underground anymore.
Watch out! This place is gonna collapse!
B BUILDING 2ND FLOOR
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Mocha! You can make it!
Mocha! You're gonna be alright!
Show some medical team guts, guys!
Hey, Chopper-yan! Are you
sure this is the right way?!
I think so!
We gotta join the rest of our
crew as soon as possible!
Chopper, can you hear me?
Is that Usopp?!
Keep going straight and
go down the stairs.--
That's the fastest way to R Building!
R BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - THE SECRET ROOM
I'm gonna shut the door to R building
before the gas flows in!
So hurry up!
A-Alright, thanks!
Everybody, hurry up!
Okay!
Hurry up, Chopper!
Everybody, you're almost there! Keep running!
Nami, you're almost at R Building!
Why is this happening to us?
You guys are just a bunch of guinea pigs!
No one would care if
hundreds of you die or not!
You are the dregs of society!
I can't believe the Master
was such an awful person.
Who should we trust from now?!
This room is not gonna
last very long, either!
Hurry up, everybody!
I found the stairs!
We're almost there!
A little more to go, Mocha! Stay with me!
Chopper-san!
What? Brook?!
This is serious! Kin'emon-san got...
Kin'emon-san got harmed by the gas and...
...died!
What?!
What happened, Brook?!
While we were helping the children
in the examination room evacuate
and looking for Kin'emon-san's
son, we met a girl.
And she said...
What?! Momonosuke turned to a small dragon?!
Uh-huh! I shouldn't tell
anybody but it's true.
Could it be...
Corpse-dono! Maybe, the dragon
I sliced up earlier was...
Momonosuke!
I've done a terrible thing!
Kin'emon-san, you can't go back!
That area is filled up with the gas by now...
The deadly gas is right in front of us!
My spirit will carry me through anything!
Whether it's fire or gas!
Momonosuke!
No, that's impossible! Kin'emon-san!
And he ended up like this.
That's crazy!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
Chopper! Brook!
What are you doing?! Don't stop!
Just go down the stairs right
there and get into R Building!
The gas is really closing in!
We're almost at R Building! You can make it!
We're almost there! Keep running!
R BUILDING 1ST FLOOR
Luffy!
Oh, Nami!
Great! You're here already!
Oh, Brownbeard-cchi's on the ground!
Is he okay?!
Yeah, he's okay.
Oh, I mean, he's not okay.
The children!
See, Momo? I told you!
Don't worry about the children.
My friends are on their way to help them.
Really?!
They always keep their word!
So don't worry!
Hurry up! Get to where
Nami-san and the others are!
--This way!
--Hurry up!
This way!
I see R Building!
Chopper and the others are not there yet?
He was giving the girl first aid.
Can he make it?
This is no good.
I made it!
Are you guys okay?! Good to see you!
He's not here.
Smoker-san...
THE PATH BETWEEN BUILDING R AND D
Do we really need this?
Yes, this is the truck that they
use to transport containers of SAD.
I'm gonna let everybody ride it.
This laboratory will collapse soon.
We have to escape as soon as possible.
Straw Hat-ya!
Tra-guy! Smokey! I didn't expect
you to come from that way!
Trafalgar Law!
Oh, Smo-yan!
What?! Smo-yan?!
--It's Smo-yan!
--Smo-yan!
It's really him!
Smoker-san!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Smo-yan! I'm so glad! We
have so much to report!
Stop screaming!
I know.
Hey! Where did Caesar go?!
Oh, I kicked his ass and he got blown
away along with the door that way!
How far did he go?
Hey! You... Our plan was to kidnap him!
But I don't even wanna
catch that bastard anymore!
That was the plan if you like it or not!
What are you gonna do if he runs away?!
Who cares about that jerk?!
You think you can just
change a plan as you like.
I shouldn't have trusted you!
Let's get him!
What?!
The Straw Hats have foiled the plans
of Master Caesar Clown, scientist
and ruler of Punk Hazard Island.
However, A Building has filled up
with Shinokuni, the deadly gas.
And now, B Building is almost filled as well.
On top of that, Caesar's laboratory
has started collapsing.
Hurry up! Brook! Chopper!
Run! Run!
The only exit to escape from
the laboratory as well
as the island is the "R-66"
door in R Building.
Hang on, Brownbeard-cchi,
for a little bit more.
Chopper will take care of you soon!
Hey, Luffy.
Do you think they are alright?
Of course.
I'm sure they will get here!
Meanwhile, before the showdown
between Luffy and Caesar...
In the sky near Punk Hazard...
The end of mission is the end of love.
DON QUIXOTE PIRATES - A
SERVANT / AN ASSASSIN BABY 5
I'll finish him off when I get back!
Joker! What an asshole!
He killed my sweet fiancé
by destroying the whole town!
I won't forgive him!
And this is the eighth time!
He killed eight men that I loved
and made a commitment to,
and destroyed eight towns!
Why does he want to screw up my happiness?!
Because the Young Master loves you-dasuyan!
DON QUIXOTE PIRATES - A COMBATANT BUFFALO
He loves you like his own sister
so he doesn't begrudge destroying a town
or two-dasuyan!
You have to learn to say "No"!
What was wrong with him?! He needed me!
I fell in love with you at first sight!
Will you marry me?
What?!
Just ten days later, he
became the eighth victim.
I feel terrible!
He shouldn't have loved
me in the first place!
When someone asks you something,
you can't say "No."
You have to do something about it!
It's weird to subscribe to
50 different newspapers!
You lend others too much money!
You are forced to buy so much stuff!
How much debt do you have now?
It's none of your business!
About 98 million berries!
It's my life!
Stay out of it!
Oh yeah! Can I borrow 2 million berries?
What?!
He needs me!
Um... When do you need it?
When I go back, I wanna hit a casino!
Th-Then, I'll get it ready for you
as soon as we complete our mission!
I'll carry out this mission because he
asked me but I'll kill Joker at any cost!
There it is!
Punk Hazard-dasuyan!
The island is covered in Caesar's
gas and I can't see a thing.
Will it go away if I fire this?
No, it won't!
Let me take care of it!
Could you hop off and wait for me, Baby 5?
Okay!
Behold! My typhoon-like power!
Gust - Matasaburo!
Now let's wait there until Caesar,
Monet, and Vergo come out.
I wanna get back quick to play
roulette at a casino-dasuyan!
What's this noise?
It's from there!
What?!
The tanker exploded?!
No! Something hit it-dasuyan!
It's a human! There!
What?! Caesar Clown?!
No way!
DRESSROSA
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring... Clank!
Joker! This is Buffalo from Punk Hazard!
What's up?
Joker! We just arrived
at Punk Hazard-dasuyan!
We don't know what's going on
but we just saw Master Caesar...
...getting blown out of the
building, injured-dasuyan!--
What?!
Recover Caesar immediately
and come back to Dressrosa!
Okay! We'll recover Caesar-dasuyan!
What about Monet and Vergo?!
There must be a reason. Let's do as he says.
Roger! Joker!
Clank!
Fools.
Hey, squirts! Luck is on my side!
As long as I have Caesar in my
custody, he can create SAD for me!
Hey, you all! We got to go! Get on the truck!
I wonder what happened to him-dasuyan.
Huh?! Do you see someone
on the deck of the tanker?!
No, I think no one could survive that gas.
What's that?!
A robot?!
What is that strange bird?
In Building R, which is on
the verge of collapse...
...Luffy waits intently for his
crewmates to wrap things up.
Meanwhile,
with the help of some powerful Devil Fruit powers...
...Baby 5 and Buffalo attack.
General Franky alone confronts them.
On the next episode of One Piece!
Running Wild!
Invincible General Franky!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!