Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in
search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that's what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner :D
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It's important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won't left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has
ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen.
They learned about the ruler
of the island and the puppeteer
of Shinokuni - Caesar Clown's motive
and along with their pirate ally -
the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are caught in a climactic
battle in order to
kidnap Caesar, save the children,
and escape from the island.
What's that?!
"Running Wild!
Invincible General Franky!"
General Left!
You okay, Buffalo?!
What is that-dasuyan?!
How do I know?!
Can't believe it's just
shooting at us like that!
Again?!
What is that?! A Pacifista?!
No, it can't be!
Caesar has no interest in human weapons!
Buffalo!
Alright! I don't know what it is but...
...if it wants a fight,
that's what it'll get!
I don't know what it
was but I destroyed it!
THE THIRD LABORATORY- R BUILDING
Everybody, hurry up! Get on the truck!
--Get on the front car, too!
--Watch your step!
--Kids, come on!
--Hurry up!
The building will collapse soon!
--I can't climb!
--Come on, you can do it!
They're not here yet.
Yeah, that's not good.
It's dangerous here. We have no time!
Hey, where does this passage lead to?
If we go through, we'll reach a harbor
that has a tanker docked in it.
That deadly gas is covering the island!
Are we gonna be okay?!
Yes, we have to risk
exposure to the air outside
in order to get on the tanker
but isn't it better than
being buried under some wreckage?
But the children...
We'll be fine, Sis!
We want to get out!
Get out and go home!
She's right! We can make
it if we hold our breath!
We want to see our fathers and mothers!
Please! Take us with you!
Please!
You're right. When it comes to this,
we have no choice but
to leave it to fate!
Kids! We'll make it
through this at any cost!
You have to survive this and go home!
Yeah!
Now, let's go and
recover Caesar-dasuyan!
Okay, I can't believe we
got sidetracked like this!
General I'm-Okay!
No damage at all?!
No way!
Take this! Now's my chance!
General...
...Shield!
Too slow and too small!
Too slow? Too small?!
Are you saying...
...that I'm too dull and
I have no tactical skills?!
No, I didn't.
Don't underestimate General
Franky, the pervert robot!
General Shield...
You're trying to make up your mind now?!
Oh, um, what should I do...
Boomerang!
--He threw his shield!
--Is he desperate?!
My "toy" wasn't enough for you, was it?
All right!
If you're not letting us recover Caesar,
you're our enemy!
Hm? What is she doing?
She gave up fighting?
The real fight starts now.
Weapon-morphosis!
What the hell is that?
Espada Girl!
Buffalo, ready?!
Dasuyan!
Dasuyan! Dasuyan! Dasuyan!
Dasuyan! Dasuyan!
Dasuyan! Dasuyan! Dasuyan...
Interesting!
General Shield Boomerang!
That's nothing!
I'm at full blast-dasuyan!
Not bad! Weapon Girl and Fan Man!
Are you trying to fight
against my weapon?!
I'm just trying to protect the Sunny!
General Left!
The Young Master said
"immediately"-dasuyan!
I know! I'll finish him
off with a single blow!
Missile Girl!
--You ready-dasuyan?!
--Go ahead!
Dasuyan!
Spin-Spin Projectile Cannon!
We'll take Caesar with us!
What are you talking about?! Caesar?!
General Left!
Now that was a dramatic finish.
Where am I?
I can't move! Damn! Am I going to die?!
Dammit! It's all because of them!
The Navy G-5 Vice
Admiral Smoker's heart!
What a nice gift, Law.
The fight is over.
Smoker! The least I can do is...
...take you along to hell with me!
It's a shame that I
can't watch him dying!
He'll open his eyes wide,
spew up blood and suffocate in no time!
It'll cause fear and panic
in all those he's with!
I get excited just by imagining it...
The door's starting to close!
Who did that?!
Hey, what is that?
The deadly gas!
Hurry up! Get on now!
Hey, what're you guys
doing, Straw Hats?!
All of you, get on now!
If we let Caesar get away,
our plan will be ruined!
What're you talking about?!
This is not "all of us"!
Some of my crew are not here yet!
Mocha is not here, either!
Some of our soldiers
are not here, either!
THE PATH BETWEEN BUILDING B AND R
Hurry up, Chopper! Brook!
Okay, I'll hurry, Usopp!
We are the ones who are running!
Outrun the gas somehow!
Hurry up! 50 meters to go!
R BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - THE SECRET ROOM
The gate is closing! Slide in!
This building is gonna collapse soon!
I better go, too!
Oh no! I completely forgot about
the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs!
Hey guys, I don't think you know where
they are but I'm looking
for the Sea Prism Stone...
These, young man?!
How easy!
Yeah, there are a lot of them!
I don't need that many!
But I'm glad that I asked!
Are you gonna go downstairs?!
It's too mortifying to die here
because of that jerk!
We'll come with you!
Do as you like!
Chopper, Brook! Get clear safely!
The gate is gonna close!
--Damn! We're dead!
--We can't make it!
It's only over when you give up!
We'll survive at any cost!
--But the deadly gas is...
--It's the end!
Luffy!
It's them!
Hey, everybody!
Mocha!
What a relief!
Hey!
We made it!
--Okay, we're all here!
--You had us worried!
I'm glad that you made it!
Yeah, thanks to you, Usopp!
We were the ones who ran like hell!
We have no time! Hurry up!
Get on, everybody!
This place is gonna collapse!
Hear that?! Get on the truck, you...
Huh?! Where did they go?!
Let's go!
That's fast!
Hurry up!
Let's get out of here, guys!
Yeah!
Hey, what should we do?!
What should we do about Kin'emon-san?!
What?! Kin'emon?!
What can we do? I mean, he's like...
Ki... Kin'emon?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank!
Joker... Can you hear me?
It's...
...Monet.
Monet. I can't believe you're alive.
Vergo's been beaten.
Caesar, too.
But Baby 5 and Buffalo
will probably recover him.
Oh. That's good to hear.
It's all because of my misjudgment.
I feel bad for you all.
But I want to make sure
to wipe out all those squirts now.
Yee-haw!
At the Third Laboratory,
there is another weapon
that was responsible for
destroying the First
and Second Laboratory
and the rest of the
island four years ago.
With just the push of a button,
there will be only one survivor on the whole island.
No one else can take
that highly toxic gas.
And that's Caesar!
The button is at...
You don't have to say it, Joker.
I was gonna do that, anyway.
I'm right in front of
the triggering device.
The explosion will ruin the tanker
that they're planning on escaping with.
You're gonna lose one of your tankers -
is it okay?
Thank you.
I need you to perish along
with everything else.
Understood.
Young Master.
I'll make you realize my anger!
Go to hell, Smoker!
I'm sorry, partner.
I've known you the longest.
Thank you for all your work.
Goodbye, Young Master.
I know you will become...
...the King of the Pirates.