The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Hey! I see the mystery mountain!
What?!
I can't see the top because of the clouds!
So this is the Red Line!
This can't be for real!
The damn ocean really is
flowing up the mountain!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
We made it!
Yahoo!
We're above the clouds now!
We've made it to the top!
Yahoo!
All we gotta do now is go down!
So this is the
greatest sea in the world!
The Grand Line!
"The First Line of Defense?
The Giant Whale Laboon Appears"
Whoa!! This is great!!
Did you just hear something?
Huh? What'd you say?
Don't you hear a strange sound?
Isn't it the wind?
There must be lots of unusual landforms!
What's that?
Nami-san! I see a mountain up ahead!
A mountain?! That can't be!
But it's really there!
Who cares?! Go!!
After passing the Twin Capes up ahead,
there should be nothing but ocean!
Hm?
Oh, crap!!
It's not a mountain!!
It's a black wall!!
No, it's not!!
Then, what is it?!
I-I-I-It's a whale!!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What're we gonna do?!
Shall we fight?
Idiot! There's no way we can fight that!
B-B-B-B-But, our path is blocked!
What're we gonna do?!
Hold on a sec!
If it looks like a wall from this close,
then where are its eyes?!
That's right! It's possible
that he may not have noticed us!
But unless we do something,
we'll run into it!
Hey! We can get through on the left!
Port! Hard to port!
But the rudder is broken!
Do something!
I'll help, too!
Oh, yeah! I've got an idea!
Luffy...? Hey, what're you doing?!
It doesn't work! The ship doesn't turn!
Dammit!
Don't give up!
Is this it...?!
Cannon?!
All right! Did it stop?
Ah... We're screwed...
This might be it...
My special seat...!
Let's get out of here before it's too late!!
What the heck is going on?!
Did he not notice the cannon
attack because his body's too big?!
Or is he just slow?!
Who knows?! Anyway,
let's get out of here now!
Ahhhhh! My ears hurt!
Paddle! Just paddle!!
We have to get away from him!
Luffy...?
You...! What the hell did
you do to my special seat?!
Dumbass!!
How was that?! Bring it on, you bastard!
Shut up already, you idiot!
Wh-What?
--Luffy!
I'm not gonna die!!
What am I gonna do?
They've all been eaten...
Hey you! Spit them out!
Give everyone back to me!
Spit them out!
I'm saying give them back!
You...! You...! You jerk!
You're diving into the water,
aren't you?! Stop it!
Hey! I'm telling you to stop! Hey!
Please wait! Give my friends back!
Hey! I said stop it!
We're gonna go on adventures together!
They're precious to me!
Give them back!!
Huh?
What do you think...?
What do I think...?
How should I think...?
H-H-H-H-How...
I was sure that we were
swallowed by the whale...
Is this a dream?
Yeah, it's probably a dream.
Then, what're the island
and house doing there?
They must be illusions.
Then this is...
...a Great King Squid!!
Looks like there's at least someone there.
I hope it's really a person...
I've had enough. I wanna go home.
Luffy went somewhere, too.
What's gonna happen to us?
Come to think of it, where's Luffy?!
What the heck is this?
Why is there a door and
a passageway in a whale?
A ship...
Sh-Sh-Sh-Shall we fire
the cannon at that island?!
No, hold on a sec...
Someone's coming out...
--Ah?! It's a flower!
--A flower?
Oh, never mind. It's a person.
What is he?
That old man killed a
Great King Squid with a single hit...
Was he just fishing...
or did he do it to save us...?
Say something, you jerk!
I-If you wanna fight,
we'll fight, you bastard!
We've got cannons!
You'd better not, or someone will die.
Oh? Just who're you saying will die?
--Me.
--You?!
--Why, you...
--Well, calm down.
He's mocking us. That bastard...
Hey, old man. Tell us where
we are and who you are.
When asking someone a question,
isn't it proper manner
to give your name first?
Hm? Yeah, good point. Sorry.
--My name is Roronoa...
--My name is Crocus.
I'm the lighthouse keeper
of the Twin Capes.
I'm 71 years old and a Gemini.
--Can I cut him?!
--My blood type is AB.
--Now, calm down.
You're asking where we are?
How dare you run your mouth when
you barged into my private resort?
Does it look like we're in a rat's belly?
S-So we were eaten by a whale after all...
But is this really inside
a whale's stomach?
Wait a sec! What's gonna happen to us?!
I don't wanna be digested!
Would you cut that out?!
Haven't you guys heard of
the "repeating gag"?
That was a gag?!
The exit is over there.
We can get out?!
Hold on a sec! Why's there
an exit in a whale's belly?!
Why's the door in the sky?!
Wait... Look at it carefully...
This sky... Those seagulls...
They're all painted! It's all a painting
inside of the whale's stomach!
Huh?!
Call it a doctor's playful mind.
You bastard! What the hell
are you doing here?!
That's enough. Leave him alone.
Agreed.
Nami! There's an exit, so
let's get out of here already.
Yeah.
What's going on?!
It's started...
Look!
That's not an island! It's a ship.
On top of that, it's made of iron!
Of course! It's because
this sea is gastric acid!
I guess that means that wooden ships
would melt if they stayed here long.
Hey! What's started?! Tell us!
This whale has...
Laboon has started hitting
his head against the Red Line.
What?!
Come to think of it, this whale
had terrible scars on his forehead.
He was also howling at the sky...
What does that mean?
He's suffering!
I see! So that's what that
geezer's trying to do!
Likely... He's probably trying to
kill the whale from inside his body!
Now...
What a vicious way to kill it...!
Now that the mystery is solved,
it's time to hurry up and get out.
If we take our time here,
we'll be digested.
We have nothing to say
about his whale hunting
nor are we under obligation
to save the whale.
Let's get out of here.
Ahhh! Dammit! With the
waves surging like this,
I don't know if we can
even reach the doors...
We have no other choice but
to paddle! Take the oars!
Let's leave quickly!
I'm worried about Luffy.
He's outside!
I saw him fly out of the mouth!
That old man jumped in!
Huh? What's he gonna do?
He's gonna be digested.
What?! What's going on?! Huh? Why?!
Dizzy... Dizzy... I'm dizzy...!
What is it this time?
The sea? A river? A channel?
Okay. We've succeeded
in infiltrating this far.
Listen, Miss Wednesday.
Behind those doors is the stomach
and that geezer is likely to be there.
We must eliminate him.
Everything is for the whale.
Yes, Mr. 9. This whale is a
precious sweet honey to our town.
Hey! The geezer came out!
Forget about him.
More importantly,
how do we open these doors?
Okay, Miss Wednesday?
We'll open the doors with
"Three, two, one, baby!"
Don't let down your guard.
Roger, Mr. 9. I'm ready any time.
I can't stop!!
What is this voice, Mr. 9?
I don't know, Miss Wednesday.
Those guys're...
Ahh!
Huh?
This isn't good, Miss Wednesday!
It's a sea of gastric acid below us!
--Luffy?
--Hey! So everyone's okay?
In any case, help me!
Aside from Luffy...
there're two weirdoes...
Hey! That old man disappeared!
Don't bother! For now, let's save Luffy!
Stop it, Laboon.
Don't hurt yourself any more.
There's only a little sedative left.
I have to make some more...
That wall divides the world's oceans.
Even if you hit it until you die,
it won't break, Laboon.
It's calmed down.
The whale is quiet now.
Seems like it. Now...
We did save you guys for the
time being, but who are you?
Mr. 9, they're pirates.
I-I know, Miss Wednesday.
B-But if we talk to them,
they should understand... perhaps...
You thugs're still around?!
--Huh?
--Don't make me say this yet again!
I won't let you lay a finger
on Laboon as long as I'm alive!
He's back.
Who's that pops?
Huh?
Even if you say so, we can't leave.
Taking down this whale is our mission.
We won't let you interfere with
our whale hunting this time!
We'll open an air vent in
his stomach! Let's go, baby!
Roger!
Ah! Bastards!
That pops jumped
straight into the bullets...!
Could it be...
that he protected the whale?!
Stop this pointless resistance!
If you want to protect the
whale that badly, go right ahead.
We'll turn it into food for our town!
What's going on?
Huh?
Luffy...?
I just... felt like hitting them.
I thank you for saving me... but why?
I wasn't trying to save you.
I just didn't like them for some reason.
Huh?
--Say, who are these guys?
--Hey, Luffy! What're you doing?
--What're you doing inside this whale?
--Stop it! Hey, Luffy! Stop it!
--They're thugs from a nearby town.
--They're after whale meat.
--What're you trying to do?
It belongs to someone else.
If they capture Laboon,
it can feed the townspeople
for at least 2-3 years, so...
Laboon?
It's the name of this whale.
It's the world's largest whale,
called the Island Whale,
which live only in the West Blue.
I won't let them have him as food.
There's a reason he keeps
hitting himself on the Red Line
and howling towards Reverse Mountain.
A reason?
Yeah. He's a whale with a human heart.
And he's been devotedly
waiting for a certain pirate group...
...for 50 long years...
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
There's a reason he keeps
hitting the Red Line?
What a strange whale...
--So he's a whale with a human heart...
--Okay!
When he says "Okay!" nothing
good usually comes of it.
H-Hey, look!
What's he thinking?
Now how is this?
What're you doing?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Promise Between Men!
Luffy and the Whale Vow to Meet Again"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!