Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in
search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that's what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner :D
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It's important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won't left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
I can't stand still, I can't stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
we go!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has
ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen.
They learned about the ruler
of the island and the puppeteer
of Shinokuni - Caesar Clown's motive
and along with their pirate ally -
the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are caught in a climactic battle.
And they finally defeated Caesar.
Smoker! The least I can do is...
...take you along to hell with me!
Monet. I can't believe you're alive.
Vergo's been beaten.
It's all because of my misjudgment.
I feel bad for you all.
But I want to make sure
to wipe out all those squirts now.
At the Third Laboratory, there
is another weapon that was
responsible for destroying the
First and Second Laboratory
and the rest of the
island four years ago.
With just the push of a button,
there will be only one survivor on the whole island.
No one else can take
that highly toxic gas.
And that's Caesar!
The button is at...
You don't have to say it, Joker.
I was gonna do that, anyway.
Thank you.
I need you to perish along
with everything else.
Understood.
"A Critical Situation!
Punk Hazard Explodes!"
It's fast!
Hey, get off of him!
I won't!
Hey, you're heavy! Get off!
Why is there a dragon here?!
Oh, I met him at a garbage dump.
You brought him with you?
It's no mistake!
Father!
What's wrong with him?
The eel is gonna attack me!
Hey, Momo!
Who is this dragon? He said "Father."
Find out later.
I don't see any light.
The exit must be farther away.
How far did Caesar fly?!
This is it for you!
Smoker!
The Straw Hats.
Trafalgar Law.
G-5.
Poor children.
You all...
...have to...
...die with me.
Goodbye, Young Master.
I know you will become...
...the King of the Pirates.
Why is the Transponder Snail
still receiving the signal?
Are you okay?
Uh-huh!
Seems like there was an explosion!
I think it was in D Building.
The SAD Manufacturing
Room where I was before.
Monet.
Goodbye, Smoker!
What happened, Monet?
Young Master...
Hey, Law.
If we can get out of here,
we'll go separate ways.
But there is something
I want to ask you.
What?
This is yours.
I thought Caesar had my heart.
How did it end up in your hands?
He just got the wrong idea.
Let me keep your heart!
And that's a deal!
To earn the trust of Caesar,
I let him keep my heart
and took his secretary
Monet's heart in return.
Now it's a deal!
And then I cut your heart
out when you got to the lab.
So I had two hearts in my possession.
The Navy G-5 Vice
Admiral Smoker's heart!
What a nice gift, Law.
I gave his secretary Monet's heart
back to him out of kindness.
Respond.
Monet.
As they say, if you are kind to people,
good things will happen to you.
How did you like it?
This Missile Girl's...
...flame of love?
Hey, Baby 5!
Do you need this weapon?
Even though you're a weapon woman yourself.
Thank you for picking it up, Buffalo!
That's my good luck charm!
An owner of this weapon is
destined to become happy
and if you buy this,
you'd make me happy, too!
What?! He...
...needs me!
I'm absolutely sure that he fooled you!
Behind you-dasuyan!
I don't know who you are but...
I'm an invincible Iron Pirate!
I don't fight for the peace of the sea!
--Iron Pirate!
--How persistent!
Weapon-morphosis!
Revolver Girl!
Oh! It doesn't work!
It just made me itchy!
This guy's pretty tough!
Baby 5!
Catch it!
Thanks, Buffalo!
It's not over yet!
This is no good!
It's collapsing faster!
Look out!
The passage is gonna collapse!
We're in a tunnel through a mountain.
If it collapses, we'll be buried alive.
Don't say it in a relaxed matter!
Oh no! The wreckage blocked our way!
Where are the brakes?!
Keep going.
What?!
Cool!
Can't believe it! He saved us!
I don't want him to be my enemy!
Although he already is!
Don't get too comfortable yet.
The deadly gas!
You've got to be kidding!
It's that thing again.
Is it flowing in through
cracks of walls?
It's gonna be more than
just being buried alive.
Stop saying such horrible things
in a cool manner!
There is going to be
gas around the exit.
Can anybody here generate wind?
What?
It's not so easy to find a person
with such a special skill!
I can do that.
How easy?!
I see the exit!
Alright, we're almost there!
Go faster!
Young Master!
Young Master?
I can't find him.
Young Master!
The Young Master is nowhere to be found.
He must be in the room
on the fourth floor.
Uh-uh! He wasn't there.
The window was open.
Oh, okay.
Then I don't know where he is.
He went out by himself again.
It's me. Tell me what's
going on over there.
W-We've actually been blocked by
some kind of iron guard!
Is it still safe there?
Yes, it is!
Which means the island and those squirts
haven't been wiped out.
You two.
Take care of that guard.
I'm on my way!