Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in
search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can't stand still, I can't stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that's what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner:D
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It's important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can't stand still, I can't stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won't left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can't stand still, I can't stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
we go!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has
ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors
and landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with
two parts, one burning,
the other frozen.
They learned about the puppet
master of Shinokuni -
Caesar Clown's motive
and along with their pirate
ally - Trafalgar Law,
were drawn into a climactic battle
which ended with Caesar's defeat.
You haven't eaten anything until today,f
have you?
That's my son!
But it must've been hard!
You don't have to worry
about anything anymore!
Let's hope that everybody
else is okay, too!
Now,
let's keep living, Momonosuke!
Uh-huh.
Guys!
Somebody's coming after us.
So...
...you gotta hurry!
It's a banquet!
Thus, they started the victory banquet.
"It's Time to Say Goodbye!
Leaving Punk Hazard!"
Super!
Law.
I know you don't really think that
I'll keep my promise with a pirate like you.
But if you really wanted to silence me,
there were several occasions
that you could've killed me.
What are you up to,
taking advantage of Straw Hat?
I'm taking advantage of him?
Maybe he's taking advantage of me.
Which of the Four Emperors
are you talking about?
The Emperor's name is...
...Kaido, the King of the Beasts!
As long as Shanks is not
the first one to fight,
I have no problem.
Because...
...I plan to beat all
of the Four Emperors!
"Beat all of the Four Emperors"?
We share a mutual interest
but you're underestimating them.
They are the emperors of the sea
who have skirmished over territories
even against Whitebeard himself.
And above all, they say Kaido,
the King of the Beasts
is the strongest creature in the world.
Huh? What? He's not even a human?!
We'll ally with each other
until we kill Kaido.
And our chances of success are...
Well, I'll just say they're really low.
What?! We shouldn't go
along with this, Luffy!
I see.
Okay, let's do it!
What?!
Wait a minute!
There is no particular reason
that I didn't kill you, White Chase-ya.
By the way,
I'm thinking about going to Green Bit.
I wonder if I can handle the Straw Hats.
You're doing great!
He can barely lift the kid up!
Gum-Gum...
...Big-eater!
Brother Luffy, you're big!
--Stretchy!
--Cool!
Mocha, are you alright?
Aren't you cold?
Uh-huh, I'm fine!
You guys are kind of nice!
Shut up! We are the fearsome Navy G-5!
Law!
It's all ready now!
I thought you guys were
gonna take the tanker.
Well, no, because Nami
and Chopper claimed
we're not going anywhere until
we see the children sailing out.
It's a pain to wait
for other Navy people
so take the tanker with the children.
Get on board, kids!
We're gonna take you home!
There is no need to hurry. One by one.
Take care!
Hey hey, Straw Hats!
If the tanker is ours,
this is the line!
Don't think of crossing it!
This is the line between good and evil!
Don't step on it! Stay away!
Again?! You were enjoying the banquet
a few minutes ago.
No, no! No, idiot!
About that, we really...
...Thank you for the meal!
But you guys are pirates!
A dishonor to the human race!
Looks like they're leaving.
1, 2, 3!
Hm? What's that?
Big Sis Nami!
Chopper-chan!
--Where is the robot?
--Oh? Where are the pirates?
Take that down! How annoying!
It's a barrier!
Even just looking at pirates hurts your eyes!
You guys are not so
different from us, G-5!
But they got on board safely.
Hey!
--Brother!
--Sis!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
We are the champions of justice!
And we're gonna exterminate all pirates
who cause civilians grief!
Pirates are the scum of the world!
And we're men of justice!
Don't let the kids see them!
--Sis!
--Robot!
No! You shouldn't see them!
--Brother!
--Where are you?!
You don't wanna see them!
--They lifted it up!
--Move it!
I can't see them!
You shouldn't see them, brats!
It's nice to see them well
and yelling like that.
She said she'll ask Vegapunk for
assistance about their treatment.
Oh yeah?! That's great!
Franky, I've been thinking.
What happened to the Mini-Merry
after we took it to get to the island?
Oh, Robin! You're the fifth person
to ask that question.
Don't make eye-contact
with those trashy pirates!
It'll ruin your eyes!
But we Navy won't let it happen!
We're men of justice!
Run, guys!
The deadly gas from earlier!
What?!
Run if you don't wanna die!
We're... men of justice!
The spiral-eyebrowed brother!
The Navy's in our way!
Move!
If you wanna say goodbye to
pirates, you're a bad kid!
If you say "Thank you" to them,
we'll drag you out of the
tanker and leave you here!
Listen! Pirates are bad
and the Navy is good!
Pirates have been causing
so much chaos in the world!
You should know that even
if you're just a kid!
We'll never forgive pirates!
Because we should not!
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Pirates are unforgivable!
We don't want pirates!
Say "No" to pirates!
Pirates are unforgivable!
We don't want pirates!
Say "No" to pirates!
But when we asked them to help us,
they helped us!
They didn't even know
what was going on with us
but they took us with them
without being bothered by our size!
I wanna go home!
We can go home soon! Hang tight!
There was nothing on the island
and no one had come to help us!
But they came!
I'm sorry!
That we didn't find you sooner!
Pirates stink and they're disgusting!
But the Navy is...
...always clean and beautiful!
Pirates are a bunch of cowards
and they're sloppy!
We don't want pirates!
The Navy is great!
If they don't let us say
"Thank you" to them,
the Navy is...
Wait! I'm sorry!
We don't want pirates!
The Navy is great!
But, in contrast, the Navy is...
...very brave and righteous...
Stop it, you guys!
Shame on you!
B...
But Tashigi-chan,
unless we keep saying bad things about them,
we will start...
liking these outlaws!
E-Even though they're pirates!
They're odd Navy soldiers!
Pirate brothers and sisters!
Thank you for helping us!
When we grow up, we will become...
...Pirates!
Don't!
Take care!
Get good rest!
When you get home,
you deserve to be spoiled by
your father and mother!
Kids! You gotta eat something healthy!
Super!
Alright, shall we go?
The weather is good considering
it's the New World.
But I know the sea will be rough.
Hey, is he coming with us?
Oh yeah! We haven't told
you about the alliance.
Luffy got us involved in trouble again.
Straw Hat! Next time we see you,
we'll take you down!
--You're our enemy next time!
--Be ready for it!
See you!
We will catch you!
Whenever you're ready, Luffy!
Yeah!
Hey you, what's your name?!
Where are you?!
Somebody please help me! I'm on...
...Punk Hazard!
Who are they?
What?!
NHC10.
I detected it in their body.
Although it was just a trace amount,
it's...
...a drug!
There are children who were
kidnapped two years ago
in this laboratory!
Steal a ship and let's
escape from Punk Hazard!
Wait for me, Caesar!
I'll beat you up and kidnap you!
Mocha!!
Catch me if you can! But I'm protected!
Doflamingo! The Four Emperors!
Do you even have balls to
pick a fight with them?
A fight?
I've been...
...picking fights all along!
Caesar!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Magnum!
Let's sail out!
Looks like those squirts
have the devil's luck.
I can't believe the
Sky Path ended there.
Young Master!
Damn! That bastard Law
really betrayed us!
I'm sorry-dasuyan!
I want to pay for it with death!
You needed me but I couldn't please you!
This is a life yacht
that was on our tanker.
I'm so ashamed-dasuyan!
After I hung up...
It's okay. You don't have to explain.
You two were just following my orders.
What a surprise.
I didn't expect the boss
himself to show up!
Is that Law?
I haven't seen you for a while.
It's a shame that you're not here.
If you're looking for
Caesar, he's with me.
J-Joker! Help me!
Where are Baby 5 and Buffalo's bodies?
I don't know.
Don't ask me about
such frivolous things.
Let's negotiate.
Hey Law, come to your senses.
A squirt like you shouldn't
imitate what grown-ups do.
Where are you now?
Don't make me mad.
Make you mad?
Your most important business partner is
one of the Four Emperors.
The big-time pirate - Kaido,
the King of the Beasts.
And I know you can't make
him mad at any cost.
What would happen if he finds out
you can't produce SMILE anymore?
Since he's not the negotiating type,
there'll probably be a fierce battle.
Young Master, you're turning blue.
And he'll destroy you.
Hey, you carried the joke too far, Law.
What do you want in exchange for Caesar?
Name your price.
Resign from the Seven Warlords.
I can't believe this squirt-dasuyan!
Then he can no longer stay in Dressrosa!
All I want is for you
to abandon everything
that you spent a decade to attain
and go back to being
a common pirate again.
In that case, however,
the Admirals from the Navy HQ
will hunt you down!
I'm expecting to see it in the newspaper
tomorrow morning.
If your resignation from the Warlords is
in the paper,
I will call you.
If I don't see it, the
negotiation is off.
Goodbye.
Clank.
Wait a minute! Law!
Young Master!
Damn squirt!