iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
Their plan was to destroy the
SMILE manufacturing factory
and rescue a samurai
but after Zoro's sword was stolen,
they got separated.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
at the Corrida Colosseum
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter.
The other competitors, however,
were the heavy hitters
from all over the world!
Hey you, right there.
That's no good.
There is a weight limit for gear.
Huh? Is that so?
Whatever you do,
there is no chance for you.
I will win the Flare-Flare Fruit.
Yes! That beautiful power belongs only to me.
"A Pirate Noble!
Cavendish!"
My name is Cavendish.
CAVENDISH OF THE WHITE HORSE
I didn't have to tell you my name because...
THE CAPTAIN OF THE BEAUTIFUL PIRATES
BOUNTY: 280 MILLION BERRIES
...everybody knows who I am.
How beautiful!
The "Pirate Noble" of the
white horse - Cavendish-sama!
Oh, I didn't expect to see you here!
How sinful it is to be this beautiful!
Perfect as this rose. That is what I am.
I've been blessed with
everything all my life.
Because I've made it this far without
eating a Devil Fruit or even really trying.
Just with my natural gifts!
You're overweight.
What?!
I told you earlier! Come here!
Tsk! I look awesome this way!
That's why everybody's half-naked.
Everybody's excited!
Do you know what makes them so excited?
It's blood.
Gladiators are just part of a show for them.
People get excited seeing a loser's blood.
At the Colosseum, people
really show their true color.
They're bottling up frustration,
fear, and anger everyday
and hiding their bestiality
deep inside of them.
But they want to let it all out.
Who wants to see a prolonged match
between heavily armored competitors?
For them, this competition is just a show.
Should I take off this cape, too?
But it looks so good!
Hey you.
I was watching you take
down that big guy earlier.
Who are you?
I'm Luffy!
--What?!
--Lu...
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Lu...
Your name is Lucy!
Oh yeah, it's Lucy.
Ouch.
Don't confuse us!
Oh, you're Lucy!
I thought Straw Hat Luffy was here!
No way!
I heard the real one is
an eight-meter-tall giant!
This is nice!
If you were really...
...Straw Hat Luffy, I would have...
...killed you here and now.
What?
Why?
I entered the New World three years ago.
The whole world was talking
about this beautiful rookie
who was worth over 200 million.
Newspapers covered me everyday.
Girls went nuts over my wanted posters.
They stole all of the
posters throughout a town.
Everybody was going crazy about me.
"Hey, big star!"
"Who? Me?"
"Of course!"
"Cavendish-sama, look at me!"
"Don't worry! I'm always looking at you all!"
But...
...a year later,
Whitebeard's War of the Best
drew their attention away!
Straw Hat Luffy came into the public spotlight
along with Whitebeard!
On top of that,
new rookies kept coming up one after another
and became popular as the Worst Generation
and wreaked havoc like crazy!
Reporters don't pay attention to me anymore!
That's why I'm gonna kill them!
Those annoying newcomers!
All of them!
What you're saying is absurd.
Say whatever you like!
To recapture everybody's heart,
I would kill as many newcomers as it takes!
To do so, I'm gonna win the
Flare-Flare Fruit today!
Your weight is okay now.
Great!
Hey, you can't ignore me like that!
Dammit! I'm gonna win the
Flare-Flare Fruit at any cost!
Are you a competitor?
You don't look strong but you're cute!
Damn, she's not very friendly.
Don't mess with her too much.
Why?
Don't you know?
Hmmm... How interesting.
I ended up looking like this old man.
Are you interested in that guy?
Who are you?
I'm Rebecca. A gladiator.
REBECCA
A GLADIATOR OF THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
Thank you for what you did earlier.
I didn't like Spartan.
Ah, don't mention it.
This man was a legend.
A legend? This old man?
He was the strongest
gladiator in the history
of the Corrida Colosseum, named Kyros.
He won 3000 out of 3000 matches.
The only wound he ever
got was a single slash.
Wow! He was that strong?!
He used to fight here until 20 years ago.
But no one in this country knows about him.
Huh? What do you mean?
None of elders or gladiators in this country
has ever seen him.
It's the strangest statue in Dressrosa.
We don't know if Kyros the
Gladiator actually existed
or somebody made up the story.
And when and why they built this statue here.
All we know is
what's written on this plate right here.
Although nobody knows about him,
nobody wants to remove it.
That's strange, too.
Hmmm... It's so mysterious but...
...I like this statue! It's so manly!
I like it, too.
Hey, great warrior - Rebecca-chan!
An undefeated girl!
We know you'll do it today, too!
I'm sure you were happy earlier!
To see Spartan who bullied you for
a long time got his ass kicked.
Stop it, idiot! Let's go!
Everybody's looking forward
to see you get beat!
What's wrong with them?
Don't pay attention to them.
I...
I'm gonna fight for the last time today.
I'm gonna win the Flare-Flare Fruit and...
...kill Doflamingo!
What?! Mingo?!
What block are you in?
C.
Great. I'm in D.
I hope we both survive the first round.
Lucy.
That guy is so strong!
Happy Store!
He's overwhelmingly strong!
The man with a paper bag mask!
Mr. Store!
I wonder if anyone can defeat him!
Hey, there is an extraordinary
guy in Block A!
Huh? What? Who?
I'm not gonna lose here!
I don't think he can't get away now!
Happy Store!
The winner of Block A is the masked man!
Mr. Store!
It was so fast!
We got the new hero in the Colosseum!
Oh? Is he going to take his mask off?!
For real?!
He took it off!
What?!
He's...
I can't believe this! We all know him!
What an interesting beginning!
And an unexpected competitor!
The battle royal of Block
A - the winner is...
Oh, he's...
The winner of Block A is...
...the captain of the first ship of
the fearful Emperor Blackbeard's group -
Jesus Burgess!
He's...
The champion I met that time!
I'm the Fighting Champion.
The Blackbeard Pirates?!
Why is such a guy fighting here?!
I can't believe it was Burgess!
No wonder he was so formidable!
This is exciting! Go, Burgess!
Burgess! Burgess! Burgess! Burgess!
The Blackbeard Pirates, huh?
I was expecting
Luffy will win this thing pretty easily
but maybe it's gonna be tough.
I hope no one finds out who he is.
Now, I've got work to do.
Hey! Wait a minute!
I'll come with you!
What?! Go away!
Can we talk a little bit?
I don't have time to waste!
Wait!
You fool! That's enough!
I don't need a guy who doesn't
know where the factory is!
I'm gonna beat the hell out of
some high-ranked guy in the Doflamingo Family...
--...and make him cough up where it is...
--Whoa-whoa! Wait! Be quiet!
What?!
Peeking, peeking... Peeking, peeking...
Let's go some place else!
You shouldn't say such a radical thing here!
Who the hell are you?
Medical team! Give aid to
the injured of Block A.
"Pirate Mercenary" Hajrudin! Cavendish!
And "The Missionary" Gambia?!
Let's go!
Hey hey, you don't have to rush like that.
Yeah, there are a bunch of bad eggs.
It's gonna be big trouble if one of
these guys wins the Flare-Flare Fruit!
I was surprised about Burgess, too.
I'll talk to Issho-san right away.
Okay.
Hey hey!
Young man, are you talking to yourself?!
You were talking to somebody
A STAFF OFFICER OF A PIRATE GROUP
- THE BARTO CLUB - BOUNTY: 67 MILLION BERRIES
out there, weren't you?
You're fishy!
"THE MISSIONARY" GAMBIA
Am I right? Am I right?
What's that note?!
You were whispering those cool guys' names!
"The Missionary" Gambia. That's... me!
What are you up to?
You can't say?!
Don't tell me you're a Navy soldier...
Are you all right, sir? Please respond.
Everything's fine.
I'll call you back in ten minutes.
Roger that.
Clank.
You don't wanna put your nose in any further.
(I won't!)
"The Missionary" Gambia.
Go away.
That bastard!
I'm scared! Th-That beast is gonna kill me!
Come to yourself! It's over!
You're okay now!
The Colosseum is still excited
from the battle of Block A!
I wonder how it's going to be for Block B!
Shall we go?
There are so many familiar
names, aren't there?
What should we do now?
Oh, your coat.
Here. Are you okay?
Uh-huh!
Thank you, mister!
You're welcome!
Issho-san, here is your coat.
Oh, thank you.
Shall we?
We need, maybe, three Navy ships.
And in the meantime, let's head for... um...
AN ADMIRAL OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
What was the name?
It's Green Bit.
FUJITORA (ISSHO)
Yes, let's go there.
And um...
We need as many medics as possible.
Just in case, we have casualties.
Yes, sir.
I also want to know how many spectators
there are in the Colosseum
and the population of this town.
Okay... Instead of the enemy numbers?
Is it necessary?
What we have to consider first is
not the number of enemies...
...but the number of people we have to protect -
don't you think so?
Yes, sir!
All Navy soldiers in Dressrosa!
We're gonna head for Green Bit now!
Meet us in front of the Colosseum!
Under command of the Admiral,
we put our plan...
...into action!
This is Maynard.
Excuse me for hanging up earlier.
Everything is okay here.
Oh, and earlier, I mentioned a name -
"The Missionary" Gambia...
...who works under Bartolomeo.
No. 0429 - CAPMAN
But you can cross it out.
It wasn't him that I saw after all.
D-Damn! That Navy soldier...
A VICE ADMIRAL OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
"MAYNARD THE PURSUER"
I'll keep going on with the plan here, too.
The medical room is that way!
We don't have enough stretchers.
Walk by yourself if you can!
They got beaten badly by the champion.
Hey.
I'm not blind.
No matter how you disguise yourself,
I can't help recognizing the face of the guy...
...who put a blot on my record!
You!