Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that
the prize for a fighting
event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
The first round is a battle royal
where only one can win.
Burgess from the Blackbeard Pirates won
the match of Block A.
Now, the battle of Block B is about to start.
Straw Hat.
I visited the Sky Island.
I lost my crew but it turned my
view of the world upside down.
You didn't do anything to the people there,
did you?!
Maybe. Maybe not.
Anyway, I'm not holding a grudge
against you anymore.
I'm gonna get on board Doflamingo's ship
to ride through the "wild wave"
that will come soon or later.
I'm done picking on you.
Can I watch it with you, Lucy?
Of course, you can!
Now, the next competitor to enter is...
...a latecomer!
He's in Block B, too!
It only took him a year to become infamous
and enter the New World!
An incomparably brutal and crazy rookie!
He roasted some pirates on a skewer
and shared the video!
And he also bombed some innocent civilians!
He ranked No.1 in the "most
annoying pirate who should
just go away" competition!
A pirate -
Bartolomeo!
"A Super Rookie!
Bartolomeo the Cannibal!"
All of you!
Go to hell!
What did you say, you asshole?!
Go home!
You go to hell!
Don't throw stuff!
Please don't throw stuff!
Hm? What?
Oh? Why is everyone so angry?
Because of him.
THE CAPTAIN OF A PIRATE
GROUP - THE BARTO CLUB
He's the captain of a pirate
group called Barto Club -
BARTOLOMEO THE CANNIBAL
BOUNTY: 150 MILLION BERRIES
Bartolomeo the Cannibal!
Go away!
What are you doing, you bastard?!
What is that?
What?
Don't tell me it's...
It's a bomb!
It's packed and I can't get out!
Move aside, old man! You're too slow!
You're in my way, too!
You have to let ladies go first!
Let me out!
Forget the others, just help me!
I'll give you my money!
It's landing!
A ball...
Gross.
Gross!
They hate you so much, brat.
I don't even want those shitheads to like me.
He's smiling. That guy's so weird.
He's not just a menace
but he also has an insolent manner.
Unlike me, he has a bad reputation.
Damn Bartolomeo,
how dare he make fools of us!
But there is another competitor for Block B!
He's the last one!
He's nothing like that Crazy-lomeo!
He admires our king - Doflamingo
and declared his loyalty to him
by bringing him a giant gold
pillar from a distant country!
Oh, don't tell me it's...
Since then, he's been
destroying various towns
in many countries where they insulted us...
...by calling us a barbaric kingdom of pirates,
and bringing them to terms!
He is the "Bullet of Dressrosa"!
He has been given a chance
by the royal finally!
Here comes a leading competitor of Block B.
If he wins this competition,
his tenacity will bear fruit
and it has been decided that
he will get promoted to
an executive position in
the Don Quixote Family!
He is a real contender for
winning this competition!
A pirate!
Bellamy the Hyena!
--Bellamy!
Bellamy!
Now, all 138 competitors are in the ring!
He can't be that popular
even if this is his home.
There are so many!
They're gonna fight at once, aren't they?
Where should I look?
It sure is a battle royal
but this is just a preliminary round.
There is no chance for the weak to win.
You can just focus on the big names.
Do you want me to tell you
who I think has a chance?
Ah, please!
The king of the Prodence Kingdom.
"The Fighting King" - Elizabello II!
And his tactician.
Dagama!
A Jiaokungdo martial artist
from the Longfeet Tribe.
Blue Gilly!
The Military Captain of
Dressrosa's Self-Defense Army.
Tank Lepant!
A criminal - Abdullah!
Another criminal - Jeet!
A master of the Fish-Man Karate
and a martial artist of the Fish-Man Jiu-Jitsu.
Hack!
Lastly, the pirates - Bellamy and...
...Bartolomeo.
One of them will win this match, I suppose.
Hmmm...
Can you repeat that?
What the hell?
Alright, the battle royal of Block B
is about to begin!
A competitor will be eliminated
if he gets killed in the ring!
Or if he gets thrown out of the ring!
There will be only one winner!
Let the battle...
...begin!
Now, who should I start with?
Bellamy!
Five men at once, already?
Spring Hopper!
H-How strong?
He's so great!
Bellamy!
What the hell? It's like an army!
That's not fair! They're teaming up!
That's not a battle royal!
You can call us cowards
as you like after you die!
There will be only one winner!
All we need is to win!
Looks like we have some competitors
who are fighting together!
Is that allowed?
It's not sportsmanlike
but it's not against the rules, I think.
The man behind such a trick must be...
...Dagama, a tactician
of the Prodence Kingdom.
We the Prodence Kingdom will take home
the Flare-Flare Fruit.
Our king - Elizabello II was born to be
a weapon of destruction!
A punch that is thrown
from his naturally gifted
physique is terribly powerful...
He blew a hole
in an enemy country's fort
with a single blow, shocking the world!
However, his power has one drawback.
It takes an hour to increase
concentration and warm up to throw one punch.
He can only use it once per battle!
They say it could take
down even the Four Emperors
if it hits them. The "King Punch"!
His victory depends on his timing!
King-sama, how is the preparation going?
It's gonna take a while. Guard me.
As you wish!
I need you guys to earn your salt!
Protect the king and
cut down the number of the
competitors in the ring!
Yeah!
The king's punch that broke down a fort...
I heard about it.
They're trying to buy themselves some time
to throw the punch, aren't they?
The punch! No way!
I'm gonna kick his ass before he throws it!
Oh shit! I'm gonna fall!
Three competitors got eliminated
by being thrown out of the ring!
And of course,
in the water outside of the ring...
The Colosseum's unique attraction!
Get them!
A school of Little Fighting Fish!
Doesn't matter if you're in
or out of the ring! It's Hell!
No one can survive uninjured!
That's the Corrida Colosseum!
Is it okay, Lepant?
For the captain of Dressrosa's army to help
a tactician from another country?
Bellamy, money controls this world!
They bought you off, huh?
Should I fight him, Dagama?
Yes, let's get rid of those
pains in the ass first
before we lose too many people on our side.
Be ready for it, Bellamy!
I'd rather make easy money
than chase a big dream!
That makes my ears burn.
You can't hit me like that!
Spring...
...Death Knock!
Bellamy! Go for it!
Bellamy!
It's not easy to beat him as I thought.
He got so much stronger!
It's so exciting to see
so many different people!
He's pretty strong, too!
Indeed.
The gladiator - Ricky...
His background is a total mystery.
Who do you think is gonna win?!
How do I know?! It just got started!
--Look at him!
--What?!
What are you doing?!
Do you wanna get killed?!
Why isn't anybody attacking him?!
Bartolomeo!
If you're not gonna fight, go home!
I wish somebody would kick your ass already!
He's fooling around again.
That guy is one of those annoying newcomers,
just like Straw Hat Luffy.
I need to take care of him,
too, in this competition.
What are you doing, Cabbage?!
I'm checking the wanted posters of
the Worst Generation.
But I have to get new ones.
I can barely see their pictures
with these knife cuts.
Why don't you just let it go already?
No way!
I'll kill them!
There is a big prize for this competition.
I was hoping Apoo or Kid or at
least one of them
would enter but...
...I don't know yet
if any of them are here or not.
They can hide their face
like Burgess did earlier.
If any of them are here,
should I wait for them to move
on to the next round or...
Oh, is this the place to watch the battle?
You're...
We have a good view of the match from here.
T-T-Too tight!
Oh, excuse me.
Who are you, old pops?
By the way,
how is Garp-san doing?
Straw Hat Luffy-kun!
What?
You know my grandpa?
What?!
I almost got killed by Garp-san once.
And I've made up my mind to carry the
grudge even against his
children and grandchildren.