iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the prize for a
fighting event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
Finally, the match for Block C
which Luffy registered for, started!
Let's do this together!
Meanwhile, Nami and the others who stayed
on the Thousand Sunny, encounter...
Wh-What's going on in here?!
"A Blow of Anger!
A Giant vs. Lucy!"
OFF THE COAST OF DRESSROSA
THE THOUSAND SUNNY
Wh-What is this?
What's going on in here?
It's so creepy.
Franky-san will be pissed if he sees this!
What?!
Th-The door got deformed, too!
Is she a Devil Fruit eater?!
But what kind?!
"BAD TASTE" Fruit?
Oh boy, oh boy!
I don't like people who
have no artistic sense!
W-Who are you?!
Be quiet!
Did you just call me a mermaid?
We didn't say that!
Whoa-whoa, who do you
think you're talking to?!
This is Giolla-sama of
the Don Quixote Family!
GIOLLA
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
(THE TRÉBOL ARMY)
The Don Quixote Family?!
Oh boy!
My soul is swinging!
I see an image! My mind is gonna erupt!
It's gonna explode!
An image of liberty and beauty!
Wh-What the...
Oh my face!
It got all flattened and smooth!
How dare you!
No!
Hey you! What do you think you're doing?!
It's art. A work of art.
I know you ordinary people
can't understand art.
Cut the art crap! Turn us back!
Yeah, turn us back!
No no, I can't do that.
All right, I can turn you back if you want.
But in exchange, you need to hand Momonosuke
over to us without any trouble!
Don't worry, Momo-chan!
We won't let them take you!
I heard you!
Oh, my soul is swinging!
I'm gonna make you more beautiful!
Here it comes again!
If we get distorted anymore,
what will we look like?!
They're gone!
--There is a hatch!
--Should we go after them?
Oh boy, oh boy! What a pain!
--There they are!
--When did they get out there?!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
Get back here!
Or I'll make you look more like art pieces!
Screw you!
You can't reach us with your
bizarre power ever again!
That's right!
Just try it!
Oh boy, oh boy!
She's getting mad, just as we planned.
Uh-huh.
Boy, if she keeps using that weird power,
the Sunny will get all messed up!
I know Franky-san will be furious
but aside from that, can
we even turn it back?
The room that used to be
the men's dormitory...
I don't know.
But all we can do now is
try to keep it from getting
any more screwed up!
I hope she focuses out this way!
Away from the ship!
Huh?
She's going to the other side!
What's going on?
How annoying! Oh boy, oh boy!
Hey, guys!
Yes, ma'am!
I-Is that...
Doflamingo's submarine?!
Ah, so that's how they got here!
They came hiding in the fog, didn't they?!
This is no good.
I didn't realize there were so many of them!
What are you guys doing?!
They're going to get away!
Just go and take Momonosuke away
from them already!
Yes, Giolla-sama!
My soul is swinging! I see an image!
My mind is gonna erupt!
Oh, she's gonna do it again!
Hello?! We're here!
You have to aim at us!
Don't bother with the ship! We're here!
Oh, it's gonna explode!
An image of liberty and beauty!
No!
The world should be free!
Shouldn't it?!
Damn!
She did it! We're in big trouble!
This is what beauty is!
What do you think?
Isn't it beautiful?
Oh no! You can't call it a ship anymore!
Oh boy, oh boy!
I'm not gonna fall for your trick!
Young Master-sama ordered
me to kidnap Momonosuke
and hijack your ship!
Now, there is no way for you Straw Hats
to escape from Dressrosa!
Our plan failed!
Just give up and surrender yourselves!
I don't need any medical attention!
I'm leaving!
Mr. Ricky! We can't just let you go!
Our job is to take care of all competitors
including treatment of injuries,
especially you guests.
Treatment?
You let people kill each other
in front of an audience!
Cut the treatment crap!
You're bleeding from the head!
Take off your mask and let us take a look!
Don't touch my mask!
A-Are you alright, Mr. Ricky?
I don't need treatment.
Open the exit!
No, we're not allowed to do that.
Everybody, hold him down.
He's badly wounded!
This is serious.
You have to get treated.
Here.
Move! I can walk by myself!
Go straight and take the
stairs to the basement.
Rebecca... I'm sorry.
A WAITING ROOM FOR THE DON
QUIXOTE FAMILY IN THE COLOSSEUM
Straw Hat is fighting in
the match now, Diamante.
After the match is fine.
Joker wants me to kill Straw Hat?
Doffy's too indulgent.
He's giving the man who couldn't
win the match one more chance.
Aren't you happy, Bellamy?
Assassination is an easy task.
Finish it up before the competition's over.
Hey, Bellamy! Don't give up!
Then, you'll get promoted
to be an executive of the Family.
I heard you're trying
to kill Lucy, Cavendish.
You're Bartolomeo, aren't you?
Congrats on making it to final.
About Lucy, it's none of your business.
No, that man is...
...not yours to kill!
I see. You want to kill him, too.
Because he's in the limelight!
But I'm the one who will kill him.
I won't let anybody else to do it.
Of course, you're no exception!
If you get in my way, you'll get hurt.
You scare me!
My connection with him is much deeper.
Many people are eliminated already!
The battle for Block C is heating up!
It's so fierce both
offensively and defensively!
But even though they're all tough fighters,
there is one giant warrior who is
literally sticking out!
He is a warrior of the new generation
from the famous Giants' country - Elbaf!
The most formidable "Pirate Mercenary"!
His name is...
...Hajrudin!!
He's gigantic!
You're too big, you bastard!
That's not fair!
Have you ever seen a Giant
who ate a Logia fruit?
That's what I'll become once
I win the Flare-Flare Fruit!
I'm gonna become the king of...
...all Giants!
With just a single blow!
It was like lightning!
Who can stop him?!
Whoa, on the other hand,
there is a fighting bull
running out of control
showing no fear for all those tough contenders!
He's a killer bull who slayed
21 death row prisoners
during a fight in this very Colosseum!
The Colosseum's Grim Reaper!
Because of his behavior, people call him Brutal Bull!
And somehow, someone knows how to tame
and ride this Grim Reaper!
Bursting into prominence,
with his cool strength,
he instantly became a crowd favorite!
Lucy!
Go Usy (bull)!
I like that guy, too!
Gyats-san, you should be impartial!
Good boy! Go, go!
Take them all down!
He became popular even under
a fake name! Straw Hat!
What a funny guy.
Go Ucy!
Oh?
Oh no, they're challenging Hajrudin!
Do you wanna fight me?
Oh, crap! Run, Ucy!
Ucy!
Bull!
Lucy!
What a disappointment!
It was obviously a mismatch!
The rookie from Elbaf...
...crushed the Colosseum's Grim Reaper
and the unknown gladiator - Lucy.
Gyats-san!
They couldn't do anything...
The Giant's been knocked down!