The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Welcome to the Grand Line!
Welcome to our town!
To the welcoming town, Whisky Peak!
Pirates! Welcome to our town!
This is delicious!
You're hopeless!
What fun!
Looks like there're about
100 bounty hunters here.
I'll fight you all...
...Baroque Works!
Humph...! Was it a secret?
If you know our secrets,
then we have no other
choice but to kill you.
Another gravestone...
...will be added to the Cactus Rocks...
Kill him!
H... He disappeared...!
"Explosion! The Three-Sword Style!
Zoro vs. Baroque Works!"
H-He's gone!
Wh-Where the heck did he disappear to?!
--Ahh!
--What?!
All right then.
Shall we?
How dare you mock us?!
Fire!
Idiots! They shot each other!
H-He disappeared again!
Darn! Kill him already!
It's just a single swordsman!
Let me ask you a question.
Are you sure that you need
to add only one gravestone?
There he is!
I-Idiots! Don't!
Are you gonna shoot me, too?!
Stop! Igarappa!
Where did that man disappear to?
Phew.
So that's a shotgun?
That thing sure is dangerous.
It seems he's good enough
that even we must be cautious.
Does he seriously think that
he can fight all of us by himself?
It's hard to believe
that he challenged us
even after knowing
we're with Baroque Works.
Ladies, please come closer...
I'm gonna sing Usopp Cheer #721!
So the welcoming town, Whisky Peak,
is the bounty hunters' nest, huh?
I thought it might be something like that.
Where did he go?! Find him!
The new recruits that I got in Loguetown,
Yubashiri and Kitetsu III...
This is a good chance to
try you guys out in earnest.
I'm going to go all-out!
There you are!
Die!
Tsk! Dammit!
First, I'll try Yubashiri.
It's light! This is a good sword!
There he is! This way!
Hold it!
Looks like they found me!
He went up!
Welcome!
Whoa! That thing's dangerous!
This is it for you.
Miss Monday!
Ahh... That was an expensive drink.
What a waste!
What was that feeling
in my hand just now?!
How sharp this Kitetsu III is!
A legendary sword cuts only
when its master wishes it,
but this one is a problem child.
So this is what a cursed sword is like.
Huh?
Lord have mercy!
I beg you for mercy.
Lord have mercy! Please save us!
Merciful Lord Blinding Powder!
You should use such a cheap trick
on someone with a pure heart.
I used the back of the blade,
so forgive me.
He went further up!
Corner him!
He's over there!
Cut him off!
Go around to the back!
Okay!
Did someone step on me?
Mademoiselle, would you
care to dance with me?
Darn... Is this all the treasure they have?
Some bounty hunters' nest this is!
Whisky Peak sure is a crappy town.
There's nowhere to escape up there!
S-Stop it!
Help me! Help me!
The ladder's falling!
Ahh! He's jumping over here!
Shoot him!
Two-Sword Style!
Hawk Wave!
Watch out. That place is unstable.
What?
That was close! It grazed me!
Don't try our patience.
There's no man who can best my strength.
This is the end of you.
Superhuman...
Brass Knuckles!
We've wast...
Ma-ma...
We've wasted time,
but we finally settled it. The End!
What?!
M... Miss Monday!
What's the matter, muscle woman?
Didn't you want to have
a contest of strength?
Well?!
Shall we continue, Baroque Works?
Fighting isn't a joke.
M-Miss Monday was overpowered...!
I-Impossible! This can't be true...!
I-I got it! The Navy made a
mistake on that wanted poster.
I see. It makes sense if this guy has
a 30 million-Berry bounty on his head.
He is the real captain.
Right. I thought it was strange
that such a namby-pamby guy
was worth 30 million Berries.
But, even so, how disgraceful...
If we lose against one pirate swordsman,
we'll be held responsible since
the boss put us in charge of this town.
It seems that it's finally our turn to fight.
You may know this,
but with members of Baroque Works,
the smaller his number, the higher
his level and destructive power are.
The three of us, Mr. 9,
Mr. 8 and Miss Wednesday
are agents with a single digit number,
which means we're powerful people
who are beyond comparison
to those you just beat.
Humph. Aren't titles useless
when it comes to fighting?
The stronger one wins. That's all.
Igarappa!
Let's go, Miss Wednesday!
Okay, Mr. 9!
Come, Karoo!
I didn't say "give me your hand"!
Come over here!
Now, show him your quick speed
that leaves leopards in the dust!
Who said "sit"?!
What the hell is that?
Can you afford to let your guard down?
Follow my acrobatics, if you can!!
Hot-blooded...
...Bat of Guts!
These're metallic bats. Be careful
not to chip your blades on them.
What's the matter? Are you
so frightened you can't move?
What happened to your proud acrobatics?
If you wanna see it that bad,
watch carefully!
Ahh...
Don't they have anyone better?
Anyone better? That would be me!
Be prepared... Mr. Bushido!
Now, take in my allure
to your heart's content!!
Charming Perfume Dance!
Good boy...
I'll finish you off with...
Peacock Slasher!
Go, Karoo!
You went too far!
Fighting these guys is
starting to get embarrassing...
He escaped below using that hole.
That's useless...
Get a good taste of how
frightening I really am!
That shotgun of his is a pain...
How should I close the distance?
Ka-boom!
How dare you beat me like that earlier?!
You won't get away with it!
You fell on your own!
Home Run Sneaky Bat!
I tied up one of your arms!
It's an iron chain...
You caught him.
Mr. 8, do it now!
I won't let you escape!
That's right. Don't move.
If you make a stupid move,
I'll have to take your
precious friend's life as well.
Good job, Miss Wednesday.
You can't escape or attack now.
That idiot! At least wake up
when you're being held hostage!
Prepare to open fire!
Preparations completed!
What?!
Igarappappa!
Is he a toy?!
Igarappappa! Igarappappa!
Luffy! Let me use your belly!
What?!
Okay! Done!
It's finally become a quiet, nice night.
Huh? Why am I outside?
Oh, well. I'm sleepy. I'm gonna sleep.
I never thought that four agents
with numbers under 12 would lose!
But where are you
planning to escape to?!
In any case, we'll hide somewhere
until they leave this island and...
Ahh! The Unluckies!!
H-Hold on a sec!
We're not running away!
It's not that...
Please! Don't report to the boss!
Hold it!
This town is quite lively
despite how late it is.
Ha! What a boring job he gave us...
...sending us all the way
to the front lines...
Hm?
I can't fall in a place like this.
I've got an important mission...
How pitiful...
...losing against just one swordsman...
Hm?!
Mr. 5! Miss Valentine!
Are you guys kidding around? Huh?
After all, this is the difference
between our rank and yours, isn't it?
Did you come to laugh at us?
That, too, but...
Of course, we're here under our mission.
Thank goodness. If you help us,
that man is no match for us!
That's right. Please beat
that swordsman right away.
Huh? Enough with the bad jokes.
Us help you?
Did you really think that
we'd come all the way
to the end of the Grand Line for that?
What? Then what mission
did you come here for?
You really have no idea?
There're criminals here that
are big enough for the boss
to send us here to deal with.
These're the boss' words:
"They've found out my secrets."
Of course, I don't even know what
kind of secrets they are, but...
...our company's motto is "mystery."
No matter whose identity it is,
the rule is that you never nose around.
If someone finds out the boss' secrets,
that's, of course, a sin worthy of death.
So, when we very carefully
investigated who learned his secrets...
Oh boy, we found out that a VIP
from a certain kingdom
sneaked into Baroque Works.
A certain kingdom? W-Wait a sec!
Although I'm wearing a crown,
I'm not a king or anything!
It's just my hobby!
We're not talking about you!
The sinners are those who're missing
from Alabasta Kingdom right now...
They know! It's all over!
Die! Igarappappa!
I won't let you lay
a finger on our princess!
On my name as Squad Captain
of Alabasta Kingdom Security!
Igaram!!
Igaram, the Squad Captain
of Alabasta Kingdom Security.
And its princess, Nefertari Vivi.
In the name of the Baroque Works'
boss, we'll eliminate you two.
This isn't good...
I left Luffy down there...
You've got me!
Ah, gentle song
Make it there for us
After a wave washed away
that little sand castle
You looked up at the passing
clouds with a sad smile
If you find the world is full of enemies,
I've got your back
Don't lose faith
You've got me!
Ah, my love
I'll hold you in my arms forever
You've got me!
Why do I have to help
Nami make money?!
--Zoro!!
--What's the matter, Luffy? Oh, you too?!
I'll beat up an ungrateful jerk like you!
What're you talking about?!
Shut up! I won't forgive you! Fight me!
Are you really serious?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"All-Out Battle! Luffy vs. Zoro,
Mysterious Grand Duel!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!