Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter and fight
fierce battles against other
tough contenders from the New World.
Stop whining over one punch!
I can't count how many times
I got punched by him!
I'm going to smash you
to the marrow of your bones!
Eight-Impact Fist Technique!
Gum-Gum...
...Thor...
Non-Drill Dragon...
...Elephant Gun!
...Non-Nail!
Whaaat?!
What a man!
He beat the legend and
won the fierce battle for Block C!
Lucy the Gladiator!
Yeah!
"Luffy and the Gladiator of Fate - Rebecca!"
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
The battle royal at the Corrida Colosseum!
Now, three contenders have
gotten the chance to challenge
the Don Quixote Family!
The winner of Block A is
the "champion" of the Blackbeard Pirates,
Jesus Burgess!
From Block B,
the captain of a pirate group, Barto Club,
Bartolomeo the Cannibal!
And from Block C,
everybody's favorite gladiator - Lucy!
Only one more contender can advance
to the championship.
However, due to the extensive
damage to the ring,
the start of the battle for Block D
will be delayed by 15 minutes.
Just fix it up already!
Don't you have a backup ring?!
Please wait for a while,
for the Block D match.
Straw Hat!
You can't run this time!
Cabbage!
Durandal!
Don't try to get away!
Cavendish is going at it again!
That bastard!
What's going on?
He's yelling "Straw Hat" again!
Straw Hat is the pirate who couldn't even
save his brother's life in the
War of the Best, isn't he?
Anyone could do what
he did if he doesn't have
to save anybody's life!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Cut it out, you fool!
I'm a noble of the Kingdom of Biggschots!
Stop it!
My body's gonna be crushed!
What was that joke you just made,
so lightheartedly?
Listen!
The Straw Hat Luffy-senpai
will eventually be
the standard-bearer of this era!
He's gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I saw it with my own eyes.
It was more than two years ago...
At Loguetown in the East Blue,
on the legendary scaffold where the
King of the pirates, Roger, died,
he shouted it out in that
desperate situation!
I'm the man who'll be King of the Pirates!!
At that moment, straight from heaven...
...came a bolt of thunder
which saved his life!
I'm still alive after all. I got lucky.
What I saw was a miracle.
I've been following
news stories on the Straw Hats
from that day on.
Alabasta, Enies Lobby,
Impel Down!
And the fateful event...
...at Marineford! It was all fascinating!
Boss! What should we do with
the soldiers that we defeated.
Dump them into water or something.
I was just some leader of a
gangland who took control
of 150 towns back home
but I've been inspired by Luffy-senpai and...
...sailed out to the sea!
Now, why don't you say it again?
You shut your eyes to your crappiness
and said something about Luffy-senpai
like you're better than him!
Is this the tongue you used to say it?
You think you're capable of doing anything?!
You worthless shit!
Bartolomeo is at it, too!
Let it go!
I won't!
Get your hands off of my sword already!
Why should I fight you in the first place?!
I'm tired!
Hey, stop them!
We can't approach them!
It's too dangerous!
H-He's right! I can't approach him.
When it comes to it, I can't do it.
I'm too nervous to go anywhere near him.
The scar under his left eye... It's real!
He's really cool!
Oh? My eyes are blind with tears.
That stupid cabbage shit!
I wanna beat him to death
and save Luffy-senpai!
Hey you, Cav... Cavendi...
I can't! I can't even speak!
Hey, Straw Hat!
Listen!
Our old man wants to say something to you!
Grandpa, are you okay?!
What?! Leave me alone! I won!
No!
I don't even hold a grudge
against Garp anymore.
I want to express my deepest
appreciation to you.
Let me say thank you...
Wait, Garp's grandson!
Wait, Straw Hat!
He just passed by me!
Excuse me... Wait!
Hey, you can't run from a fight!
Wh-Wh-What should I do?!
What should I do?!
I wanna talk to him but how can I?!
Please wait!
In appreciation for restoring my head,
I want you to put my grandson's Happo Navy
under you command.
Wait!
What's wrong with them?!
So persistent!
--Wait!
Please wait!
Boy... There's no place that
I can feel comfortable.
This way, Lucy!
Oh, you're...
It's Rebecca.
You have so many enemies!
Follow me!
Oh, thanks!
By that logic, Shiryu is no different!
But I can't trust Aokiji!
Oh, hold on a sec, Captain.
Straw Hat is here.
Are you there?
Straw Hat.
You're...
...Blackbeard?!
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
I was surprised, too,
when I heard that you were
the brother of my commander!
Are you sure you want to be here?
You're gonna miss it!
Your brother's public execution!
...Blackbeard, aren't you?
Yes, it's me! It's been a while.
I heard you're fighting
in the competition, Lucy!
But my man, Burgess,
is gonna win the Flare-Flare Fruit!
I can't wait because it'll be like having Ace
in my group!
He turned me down in the past!
You guys are the last people I want,
to have Ace's power!
I can't wait to fight you!
Let's go!
Lucy!
Yeah.
Do you know that pirate?
A little bit. I can't let him win!
Hey lady, there're no more samples?
You're gonna just keep eating
and not gonna buy anything, are you?!
Hey!
I'm sorry, ma'am!
Which one do you want, Lucy?
What?! Are you gonna buy it for me?!
Oh, Rebecca, is he your friend?
Thank you!
Yum-yum! I'm gonna eat!
Sorry that I don't have that much money.
No, thank you for the lunch, Rebecca!
Where are we?
This is a quarter
for us gladiators of the Colosseum.
Some people call it a prison.
Guest competitors wouldn't come in here
so you can stay here until your next match.
Yeah? Thanks!
REBECCA: A GLADIATOR ATTACHED
TO THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
That battle was amazing!
I was surprised at your strength!
Is it good?
Yeah, this Colosseum lunch box is so good!
Aren't you hungry?
Mother-sama, I'm hungry.
I know.
We haven't eaten anything for two days.
Rebecca, do you think you can
stay here alone for a while?
I don't get hungry.
Huh? Sounds like you're
a samurai or something.
I got you!
Rebecca, just do it!
What?!
You brought him to do it, didn't you?!
Hey, what's going on here, Rebecca?!
Hurry up!
Hey, my lunch is gonna spill out!
--Do it!
--What's wrong?!
If you don't do it,
you can't carry out your purpose!
Her purpose?
Rebecca got caught!
I can't believe he can move faster than her!
Do whatever you like to me.
I'll pay the price.
I'm not gonna do anything
to somebody who bought me food.
I tried to kill you!
That's okay. I'm not dead.
And I think you weren't gonna kill me.
Ow, ow, ow.
Being forgiven that easily
makes it more obvious
that it was really unevenly matched, Rebecca.
If we could beat one Devil Fruit eater here,
there was still a slight hope.
Huh?! Mummies?!
No, we're not!
We are convict gladiators!
So is Rebecca.
We will keep fighting
and get killed someday
in the ring, as part of a show!
Just because we protested against the
Doflamingo Family, even moderately.
The king says we will be released
if we can win a thousand times.
But no matter how tough you are,
you'll die when you fight to
the death a hundred times!
Everybody who tried to escape from here
got shot and killed.
There is nowhere to run for us.
Before Doflamingo became king a decade ago,
gladiatorial matches were not to the death.
In this kingdom that he governs,
there are very bright side and very dark side.
I'm...
...going to win today's competition
no matter what it takes...
and kill Doflamingo
with the Flare-Flare Fruit power!
Today, an army led by Soldier-san
will come to let us out...
...by provoking a battle against Doflamingo!
He is willing to sacrifice his life
to destroy this kingdom!
It's gonna be alright!
I'm a brave soldier and
I will always be by your side!
I'm gonna do it before he does!
I don't want to be just protected anymore!
I want to protect Soldier-san this time!