iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the prize for
a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter and fight fierce battles!
I don't want to be just protected anymore!
I want to protect Soldier-san this time!
"Protect You to the End!
Rebecca and the Toy Soldier!"
Soldier-san's gonna die.
Soldier?
He's a one-legged toy soldier.
A toy?
Oh, elderly people!
Do you want me to carry
your bag or something?
Oh?
Am I funny?
I met a guy like that
in front of the Colosseum.
Yeah, I guess that's him.
We're not allowed out of the Colosseum.
We can't do anything if there's
something going on out there.
You're worrying that a toy is gonna die?
A living toy seems really odd to me.
You're not from here
so maybe it's hard to understand.
They're the same as humans.
They are friends for the friendless.
They are siblings for those who have none.
They are lovers for the loveless.
I don't understand why they
aren't allowed to live with us.
Since the day I lost my mother
who was my only family,
Soldier-san raised me.
He's like a father to me.
I see. So that toy is...
Thank you for waiting!
The ring has been fully prepared!
Rebecca, the match is gonna start.
Uh-huh.
Hey, what are you doing, Lucy?
When we struggled earlier,
the two lunch boxes fell on the floor.
Sorry! You emptied your
wallet to buy me these.
But they still taste good!
You don't look like a prisoner to me.
Buy me lunch again sometime!
See you at the finals.
Yeah!
Good luck!
We're gonna start the match!
Competitors of Block D, enter the ring!
Alright! I'm gonna win the Flare-Flare Fruit!
Say whatever you want now!
Mother-sama!
Mother-sama, I picked so many flowers!
Wow, Rebecca!
Would you like to have one?
Thank you. I would like to.
And this is from your mother to you!
Okay, let's go.
Uh-huh!
1, 2! 1, 2!
We sold all the flowers today!
Yes, we did.
Maybe people bought them
because you're so cute!
Let's eat!
Go ahead. Dig in.
You must be tired
from walking all over the town.
Yeah, I'm so hungry!
My stomach was growling!
Oh no!
--It's yummy!
--Yeah!
The King Riku Army is setting
the village on fire!
Please stop!
Why is the king doing this?!
The palace is on fire!
What's going on in this country?
Go! Don't let them get away!
Run, Lady Scarlet!
--Who are you, shorty!
--Outta our way!
Run!
As far as you can!
Mother-sama, I'm hungry.
I know.
We haven't eaten anything
for two days.
Rebecca,
do you think you can stay
here alone for a while?
Promise me to stay here, no matter what.
I'm gonna go buy something to eat.
Uh-huh!
Mother-sama!
I... I couldn't protect her!
I'm sorry!
I couldn't protect your mother!
She told me to give you these.
She said that you're waiting here hungry.
Mother-sama, I'm hungry.
I'm gonna go buy something to eat.
Mother-sama?
Mother-sama...
Mother-sama!
Mother-sama!!
I saw a trail of blood on the staircase!
They must be hiding somewhere!
Let's search!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!!
You have to eat.
I-If you don't want it, I'm gonna eat it.
Okay?
I'm really gonna eat it!
Your mother was high-born.
Do you know we have a new king now?
The new king wants to capture
all the former nobility.
He even wants to capture
you because you have
your mother's blood in your veins.
Although I couldn't protect your mother,
I'm gonna protect you to the end,
with my life!
Until the day you are filled with happiness,
I will always be by your side!
I want my mother!
I don't like you, Soldier-san,
because you couldn't protect my mother!
H-How do you like this?
Or this?
Where are you going, Rebecca?!
I'm going home!
You can't!
The new king's friends
are all over the town
and at your house looking for you!
Doflamingo-sama!
Doflamingo! Doflamingo!
The Riku family has been running
this poor country for centuries!
In the end, they became shameless and robbed
money and goods from citizens for themselves!
I'm gonna make this country wealthy, instead!
I didn't know toys are capable to work.
I need money!
Rebecca!
Idiot!
Look! I'm unbreakable!
I'm unbreakable and strong - a super toy!
Soldier-san is a brave man
He will always be by your side
She must be feeling cold.
With this tin body, I don't feel anything.
Isn't this warmer?
Yes, it's much warmer!
Soldier-san is a brave man
He will always be by your side
How much is the rent here?
It's abandoned so you can just use it.
Since the King Riku Army ransacked this area,
so many residents have moved away.
It's warm in the house!
Close the window.
No.
There are other toys.
Other children as well.
Go out and play with them.
I guess you're gonna be safe here.
Since there are other people in the village,
we have to follow the law.
After you fall asleep at night,
I'll go back to my toy house.
But I'll be back before you wake up.
To let you know I'm here all the time,
I'll drop a new flower
petal through the crack
in the window every morning.
Good morning, Soldier-san!
Yeah, good morning!
You little monkey!
There are so many clothes that would fit you!
Cute!
Cool!
W-We're not here shopping for me.
Go ahead and pick out what you want.
Yes!
Ta-dah!
You're small but you really go at it!
I need money.
H-Hey!
I need money!
Happy Birthday, Rebecca!
It's yummy!
Here!
Rebecca! Try to catch this!
Ouch!
How did you like it?!
Hey!
What do you want?
Um...
Read this!
Hey!
W-Why?
Here!
Bye-bye!
She must be an orphan.
She has no family who cares about her.
Rebecca!
Where are you?!
Rebecca!!
She's cute. We probably can
sell her for a high price.
Rebecca!
Hey, that strange toy is chasing us.
Soldier-san!
Who cares.
He's not gonna catch up with us.
You bastard!
You're just a toy!
Don't stand against humans!
I'm gonna destroy you!
Soldier-san!
Rebecca!
I'm sorry.
They put me on the wanted list.
I'm on it, too! Let's find a new place!
I want to live with you one day,
in the same house.
Let me teach you how to fight.
There's no need since I have you.
If something happens to
me, what are you gonna do?
Come on!
My mother said I shouldn't hurt anyone!
I'm gonna teach you how to not get hurt!
Come on!
I don't wanna do it anymore!
Take up your sword!
Alright, here we go!
Listen. We're not playing here!
Faster!
Use the lower half of your body!
We're gonna do this everyday!
What?!
He has always been by my side
and he saved me so many times.
Here she comes!
Are you all ready?!
She's the most beautiful
gladiator in the Colosseum!
The "Phantom Princess"!
No one else can make
the place heat up like she does!
Please don't die, Soldier-san!
I won't...
--Screw you, Rebecca!
--Cut her to pieces!
King Riku's line - burn in hell!
A corrupted family!
...give up, either!
What?!
Why does everyone hate her so much?!
She's a very nice person! Screw them!
She bought me lunch...
I know!
But Rebecca's grandfather is...
...despised by the whole country!
He's the former king!