Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the prize for a
fighting event was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter and face
the fierce competition!
Please don't die, Soldier-san!
I won't...
...give up, either!
"The Last - and Bloodiest - Block!
Block D Battle Begins!"
Drop dead, Rebecca!
You foul-blooded wench!
Go to hell, Rebecca!
Today's your execution day!
The shame of Dressrosa!
Set her on fire!
That'll make her pyromaniac
grandfather happy!
The battle royal in the
Corrida Colosseum - Block D!
As the "Phantom Princess" Rebecca enters,
the crowd is really heating up!
Even if she's the former king's granddaughter,
it had nothing to do with her!
Whatever her grandfather did!
Yeah, you're right.
I wouldn't expect that to come from you.
Even if her grandfather is the former king
who the whole country despises,
Rebecca is our hope!
Your hope?
Yes, Rebecca and all of
us have been fighting
desperately to claw our way
up from this dark abyss…
...with no way out.
We were not strong enough
so we ended up like this
but Rebecca isn't hurt.
I mean, hurt or not,
only Rebecca can keep our hope alive.
If she can win this thing
and get the Flare-Flare Fruit,
things may get a little better here.
Go to hell!
You're hated by the whole
country, Rebecca-chan!
Despite that pretty face,
people think you're a bigger villain
than Bartolomeo from Block B!
That's right!
--Screw you, Rebecca!
--The corrupted King Riku's family!
That's enough!
Oh! The man that's coming into the ring is...
What an ill-behaved crowd! I can't stand it!
Shame on you!
Here comes the captain of the Beautiful Pirates -
Cavendish of the White Horse!
CAVENDISH OF THE WHITE HORSE
Cavendish-sama!
Oh, how beautiful!
Get ahold of yourself!
Some women in the audience are collapsing!
He still has the look that everybody
was talking about three years ago!
Cavendish-sama!
Kick that little tramp's ass!
Teach Rebecca a lesson!
Shut up, you bastards!
I don't know why you hate her so much,
but she's a young girl who stands in the ring,
putting her life on the line!
You guys are not risking your lives
so you have no right to jeer at her!
If you really want to kill her,
take a weapon and come
down to the ring yourself!
The voices of people who have no guts
are nothing but irritating noise!
I have my reasons for entering this event,
but even so I can't stomach it!
The lives and deaths of
warriors are not a show!
Thank you, Farul.
What are the horse and the bullhorn for?
Oh, Cabbage spoke up and
said the right thing.
I'm impressed.
I still don't like him though.
--Cavendish-sama!
--What a great man!
I don't care about Rebecca anymore!
I'm gonna support you!
Cavendish!
I can't believe it! He's so charismatic!
He turned the tumultuous booing
to a shower of applause!
Hey, I understand how you feel.
This is not what you wanted, right?
I think it bothers you
how easily they change their mind
but people are often like that.
They don't listen to you...
They love me so much! I'm so happy!
--You like it?!
--It's been three years...
Excuse me.
Thank you for standing up for me earlier.
Don't mention it.
It's true that it aggravated me.
It must be hard for you.
But forget it.
We have to fight each other.
Right.
By the way, there must be one
or two news reporters here.
What should I do
if this gets in the newspaper?
After the match, they'd interview me and go,
"Hey there, big star!"
And I'd go, "What did you call me?"
Maybe!
While all of that was going on,
we have all the competitors in the ring!
With one abstention,
there are 137 contenders for Block D!
A tough warriors' battle royal!
Now, let's start...
...the match!
Alright!
Cavendish-sama!
Decapitate somebody, Suleiman!
Kick their asses, Orlumbus!
Go to hell, Rebecca!
Watch me, Soldier-san!
GREEN BIT
I have no interest in your past but...
...only people who can use the World
Government just to deceive us are...
...the Celestial Dragons!
So what?
You can't buy any more time, Law.
You said "It's more complicated" earlier.
What did you mean by that?
If you wanna chat with me,
hand Caesar over first.
And his heart.
Caesar is...
I mean, those SMILEs are
that important to you?!
I guess they are.
Without the SMILEs, Kaido's gonna
kill you and it's all over for you.
Room!
Shambles!
You damn pip-squeak!
Fujitora?
Excuse me.
Why did you help him?
I have to stop you right there,
Heavenly Demon.
I'm here to...
...arrest him, not to kill him.
Alright.
But I need Caesar's heart back, Law.
By the way, you seem quite curious about
that "complication" that I mentioned.
Do you wanna hear about it?
DRESSROSA - THE FLOWER FIELD
AN ANTI-DOFLAMINGO COALITION -
"THE KING RIKU ARMY" HEADQUARTERS
Hey!
We brought the legendary heroes -
Usoland and Robiland!
Usopp! Robin!
Yellow Cub and Pink Bee Squad!
Arrived from Green Bit!
Thank you, Leo!
The time has come, Commander!
This battle is to restore
the honor of King Riku
who was dethroned in
disappointment ten years ago
and to take back our freedom!
That day, Doflamingo came to this country
and took away everything with violence!
I'll never forget that!
We spent one whole year...
...preparing our plan!
Even though they're the Warlord's pirate group,
we have a chance to win!
I should listen to their plan carefully
and look for the best timing to get away!
DRESSROSA - ACACIA
Zoroland, we're gonna turn left soon.
Left is the side that you
don't have your swords.
--You don't even trust me with "right" and "left"?
--Not at all!
The one who's attacking your ship is...
...one of the executives of the Don Quixote Family -
Giolla!
She can disarm her opponent
in an artistic way!
She's quite strong!
You know that much?!
I memorized the names and
faces and abilities of those
at the executive rank and
up as much as I could!
Especially those three top executives...
...who destroyed the entire Dressrosa army
ten years ago.
Trébol!
Diamante!
Pica! I'll never forget those three faces!
Ten years ago? How old are you?
I'm 27!
Y-You're 27?!
He's...
This way!
Zoro-dono! Zoro-dono!
We're here! Hey!
Don't shout, you fool!
Who are they?!
They're fooling around with each other.
Spiral-eyebrows-land and Topknot-land.
What?! Are you gonna go save Nami-san?!
So she was in trouble!
That's why she didn't pick up the Snail!
Okay, I'm coming with you!
Wait, Sanji-dono!
.We're here to tell
Luffy-dono what's going on!
Black Foot!
My sweet Violet-chan!
I wish that dumb passion
would kill you already.
My colleague, Giolla, hijacked your ship!
What?
And they're on their way to Green Bit!
Alright!
Who's going to win the battle royal for Block D?!
I can't get eliminated here!
No matter what it takes, I'll win this
and get the Flare-Flare Fruit
so I can take down Doflamingo!
Let's start with Rebecca!
Good idea!
And I will protect Soldier-san this time!
Everybody hates you, Rebecca-chan!
If I defeat you, I'm gonna
become the hero of the country!
It's not fair!
Those five men are going for Rebecca at once!
You're right. But it's always like that
when Rebecca enters a competition.
Most of the time, Rebecca is the only woman
competing among tough guys!
In addition, everybody in the Colosseum
wants to see Rebecca beaten!
So it's only natural that
they're going for Rebecca first!
Go get them, Rebecca! Don't lose!
Go go, Rebecca!
Let's have fun, Rebecca-chan!
You do realize you can attack, too, right?
You think you're better than me?!
What?!
--Screw you!
--Dammit!
--You bitch!
--Go to hell!
Damn!
You're such a coward, Rebecca!
Show us blood!
Kill each other!
Let me teach you how to fight.
My mother said I shouldn't hurt anyone!
You...
All you can do is deflect attacks?!
Take this!
I'm gonna teach you how to not get hurt!
Drop dead!
What?!
Stand up, Rebecca!
You have to become stronger!
You bitch! Stop moving around!
Screw you!
Way to go, Rebecca!
Stay at it!
I won't give up!