Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition - in which a winner will get
the Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize - and won the first round.
And Rebecca, the gladiator girl Luffy supports,
is now fighting the last match of the first round.
I didn't know she used the Observation Haki!
Haki?
She has also never been
wounded by anybody
and she won it all by letting opponents fall out of the ring!
She has never been defeated!
Let's see what happens
if I break your bones!
Ill Weed-chan!
If I bring Luffy-senpai here,
can I have your autograph?
You can do that for me?
I'll be counting on you!
I'm gonna bring him at the risk of my life!
I've got to do this right!
"The Most Violent Fighter!
Logan vs. Rebecca!"
I have to be careful
not to bump into Luffy-senpai.
Because his awesomeness might blind my eyes and make my heart explode.
I need to look for him with caution.
Come to think of it, since the captain
and the vice captain are here,
other members must be here
on the island, too.
Sniperking-senpai and...
..."Black Foot" Sanji-senpai!
Sis Nami!
The great doctor - Chopper-senpai and...
...Big Sis Nico Robin!
The great shipwright - Franky-senpai!
The great musician - Soul King - Brook-senpai!
I can see them, too!
I'm getting really nervous!
I can't help getting excited!
By the way,
I know I didn't miss a thing
but why isn't there anyone here,
besides Luffy-senpai?
There were a whole bunch
of people here earlier.
Is that...
...a staircase?
I haven't been downstairs.
It's really creepy down here.
I don't think Luffy-senpai is here
in such a gloomy place.
What is it? I hear voices.
Hurry up! Out of our way!
Get out of our way!
What is this place?
A WAITING ROOM FOR MEDICAL TREATMENT
IN THE BASEMENT OF THE COLOSSEUM
Next! Come in!
There are so many people here.
Well, let's go look.
They're all injured.
Is Luffy-senpai here?
Hey, look!
Why is he here?! This is bad!
He's gonna agitate everybody here!
Mr. Bartolomeo!
Wh-Why are you here?
I'm looking for someone. Excuse me.
Y-You shouldn't be here!
This is where we treat the losers!
If they see you...
Treat the losers?
I see! They're losers!
Damn you! Did you come here to make fun of us, Bartolomeo?!
You won the match with your pathetic power!
I'll kick your ass right here!
S-See, I told you!
Please don't cause any trouble in here!
All right. I think he has no business here.
Sorry to bother you all!
Get yourselves looked at!
What did he come here for?
Next! Mr. Sai from the Kano Kingdom!
Next?!
Our old man that you carried in
hasn't come out yet!
Oh, Mr. Chin Jao.
Is he dead?! Huh?!
Ah? What's going on?
Shut up, you martial arts fool!
He's quite tough but he is really old now!
If he's dead, don't hide it!
He's so loud.
You're overreacting.
Mr. Chin Jao hasn't come out here
because...
...there is an exit at the back of the room
and those who are treated are not coming back here.
Oh, is that so? I'm sorry.
Do you understand?
Then, please come in.
I'm sorry for getting it wrong!
Really, I'm sorry!
How can I even make it up to you?
I'm on my knees! Please forgive me!
Don't worry!
He gets emotional easily.
Oh, I see...
This way, sir. Please come in.
Mr. Sai from the Kano Kingdom, am I correct?
Yeah.
Lie down on the bed here.
Like this?
Yes. And close your eyes.
All right. We're going to start.
What the...
Next! Come in!
Ow, ow, ow...
What is this? A toy?
Is this a stack of toys?
Toys and fighters.
Who is it?
Hajrudin!
You guys?
Why are you all here?
Old man! You're alive!
That's great!
What's so great, you fool?!
I guess they dropped all the losers of
the competition in here.
What?!
What do you mean by that?!
How can I get out of here?!
There's no way out!
We must've got set up by Doflamingo!
This means war, Elizabello-sama!
I can't believe it but, even with my King Punch,
I can't break this wall.
Whoa-whoa, we're underground.
That means the wall is the ground itself.
No matter how strong your punch is,
it's impossible to break it.
What are they gonna do
collecting us here?
I don't think they're gonna treat us here.
If this turns out badly, Doflamingo,
I'll carry this anger
even towards your grandchildren!
Listen to this rousing cheer!
Now, the potential winner of Block D...
...Rolling Logan sets his sights on Rebecca!
Let's see!
Which bone should I break?
Should I break her neck?
Neck!
Or spine?
Spine!
Or...
...arms and legs sound better?
Much better!
You guys are too sweet.
This Ill Weed-chan deserves...
...her whole body smashed up!
Don't you think so?!
It's so irritating!
What's wrong with them?!
Like I told you, that's how much they hate the former king.
But it has nothing to do with her!
She's a great person!
We all know that.
When I got seriously injured
and my life was hanging in the balance,
Rebecca sat up with me
and kept encouraging me.
Not just me!
Everybody here likes her!
But the people outside will never forget...
...what happened that night.
That night?
Yeah, it's a long story but...
Never mind then.
What?!
Go for it, Rebecca!
All right. Should we start?
Rolling Logan has started attacking
with the momentum from the crowds!
Using his long reach,
he's going for Rebecca from both sides!
They say his max grip strength is over 500 kg! Rolling Logan!
Once she gets caught, it's all over for her!
This is not good!
It's no use!
He calmly tracks her down
and narrows the space for her to run!
She's literally like a frog
in the sights of a snake!
What is she gonna do now?! Rebecca!
Your back is wide-open!
Both of you, go to hell!
How cowardly are you to
try to attack me from the back?!
Do you want me to break your bones?!
Watch this carefully, Ill Weed-chan!
Now's the chance!
Oh? Taking advantage of him being off-guard,
Rebecca started to run!
Rebecca is scurrying like a rat!
Rolling Logan is chasing her...
...mowing down the other contenders!
Stop running, Rebecca! Fight!
Fight and bleed!
Oh no!
I'll never let anyone get away
once I've got them in my sights!
Rebecca lost her precious sword!
She's totally cornered!
Rebecca finally got caught!
Now, Rolling Logan!
What is he going to do from that position?!
Ill Weed-chan!
What do you want me to do?!
Do you want me to throw you to the ground?
Or...
...like the guy earlier...
I like the way you scream!
I'll do this then!
I'm gonna pulverize you slowly
so let me hear it more!
That bastard!
--This is it for her!
--Rebecca!
Would the undefeated girl
lose here finally?!
Pulverize! Pulverize! Pulverize!
Pulverize! Pulverize! Pulverize! Pulverize!
Soldier-san... I...
Faster!
Use the lower half of your body!
I can't take it anymore!
Today's competition is a chance and I'll take it!
You're out of your mind!
It's not a chance!
It's impossible for you
to win that competition!
You're gonna die!
I won't allow you to enter it!
Let go of Rebecca!
Oh, the smiling gladiator Agilia joins
in this fight!
She saved Rebecca with a merciful smile!
She got away thanks to Agilia!
Way to go, happy-faced old woman!
"Happy-faced old woman," you said?
Are you okay, Rebecca?
I'm okay! Thank you, Agilia-san!
It's too soon to say that!
You want to win the Flare-Flare Fruit, don't you?
Then, have courage to fight!
How dare you!
I'm gonna finish both of you off
and send you straight to hell!
This competition is nothing
like the other events!
You can't win this thing
just by running around!
Agilia-san!
Angry Rolling Logan is overpowering Agilia!
Agilia-san, bend over!
Let me step on your back!
Oh! No way! Rebecca is going to make an attack?!
It's not gonna work against me!
What?!
No! This can't be true!
I can't believe it!
Rebecca won an upset victory!
She moved unbelievably fast
and fended off Rolling Logan's attack
forcing him to fall out of the ring!
You made him believe that you were gonna attack,
drew his attack, and took advantage of it.
You're unbelievable.
Prepare to die!
Now you're facing the moment of truth!
You gotta move to the finals at any cost!
Uh-huh!
She did it!
All right! Rebecca! Agilia!
Another one's coming!
Kick his ass, Rebecca!
Hey, not Cabbage!
Show me Rebecca!
Yeah, we want Rebecca!
I just realized it's hard to watch it from here.
I'm gonna go closer to cheer for her!
Oh yeah. It seemed to me like everybody was happy in this country but...
...by seeing you guys,
I noticed it's not true.
What you saw was the bright side
where "winners" are living happily.
Doflamingo labels...
...the people who obey him "winners"
and the people who disobey him "losers."
Just like the World Government!
Rogue "Losers" are like trash
and once you hide that trash somewhere dark,
the country looks good, but only on the surface.
Let's go treasure hunting!
It's similar to the country I grew up in.
Once you start feeling something's wrong,
you'll see there are so many strange things going on here.
We think there is an even darker part.
You better be careful, too.
Okay! Bye!
Where did Luffy-senpai go?
I can't find him anywhere!
I can't face Zoro-senpai like this.
L-L-L-L....
Luffy-senpai!