Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law
who's been captured by Doflamingo.
Meanwhile, at the Colosseum,
the final round of the competition is about to start.
Who is that? He's not the Lucy that I knew.
This is the Rampart Tower B-2 -
in front of the main dining hall!
It's no mistake!
One of the intruders is Straw Hat Luffy!
And Pirate Hunter Zoro!
And... V-Violet-sama!
Th-There is one more person!
Lucy is showing it off!
Straw Hat Luffy has snuck in?
Then, who is the guy
fighting at the Colosseum?!
What the hell is going on?!
"A Moving Castle!
The Top Executive Pica Rises Up!"
Where's Mingo?!
Shoot! Shoot!
Are you okay, small person?!
Thank you!
Kin'emon, you take care of her!
What?
But I have to find the
place called the Toy House
where my friend Kanjuro is held!
I want to go there, too,
to take part in Operation SOP!
You do?! I didn't know that!
Zoro-dono, we're gonna go to
the Toy House together, then!
Do as you like.
Now, where is the Toy house?
--It's beneath this building. But...
--Oh, it's down below?
--Maybe, go down those stairs first and...
--Stairs?!
Oh, now I know which way to go!
Get deep inside so you don't fall out again!
What? Oh, wait a sec...
Luffy-dono! Zoro-dono! Ninja Woman!
I'll take my leave!
Excuse me!
THE ROYAL PALACE B-1 -
THE RAMPART TOWER
Straw Hat Luffy
has gone up to B-1 of the Rampart Tower!
Which way?!
To the left!
No one's here!
I'll get to you soon, Mingo!
Their security isn't keeping up with us!
Wh-What's this?
Something is in the wall.
A face?!
What the...
A stone monster?!
Oh no! It's Pica!
He's huge!
What's up with him?!
Be careful!
He's a top executive of the Family!
This stone monster?!
He's Pica, eater of the Stone-Stone Fruit -
a stone assimilation human!
A stone assimilation human?
He doesn't look like a human to me.
Are you really a human?
I'm asking you a question!
Say something!
Can't you talk?!
If we get it in the teeth,
we'll be crushed with one blow!
Damn! We can't advance if nothing is done!
I don't care
if you're a top executive or something!
I gotta go kick Mingo's ass!
Get out of my way!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Alright, I did it! Let's go!
That was too easy.
He's back for more!
Now you know it's not that easy to take down
the top executives of the Family!
He's not just a stone man.
He can merge with stones.
Which means he's practically...
...taking control of this whole stone palace!
The walls!
THE TOY HOUSE
Bring it on, Navy!
It's dangerous-in!
Hey, hold your fire, Navy!
How could you intrude in the
territory of the Family like this?
Our target is Cyborg
Franky of the Straw Hats!
Move aside if you don't wanna get shot!
You can't tell me what to do,
you stupid Navy!
What?!
--He's brushing his teeth!
--With two shoebrushes!
Señor is an executive of
the Don Quixote Family!
He's so strong!
It doesn't matter if I'm strong or weak.
It's a matter of a man's pride.
You tramps should stay out of it!
Oh! Scold us more, Señor!
We want more!
Whether you're an executive or not,
if you stand against the Navy, we...
Don't shoot him!
Regarding the Navy's involvement,
Issho-san and Doflamingo have talked
and come to an agreement-dara.
I don't like it but
if the Young Master is okay with it...
Oh, Señor!
Why are you relaxing?!
I was super bored.
Now, listen to my song. "The Pirate Blues"!
No thanks!
Everybody!
We're going to make a full-scale charge now!
Capture or scrap Cyborg Franky
of the Straw Hats-dara!
Yeah!
I'm super ready anytime!
Huh?
--He's swimming...
--...In the ground?!
--Señor, you must be tired!
--Take a good rest!
I'm sweating a little bit.
Let's see how much the Navy can do.
So hard-boiled!
I didn't expect the Navy to cut in but...
...it's becoming like a party and I like it!
Weapons Left!
And...
...Franky...
...Rocket Launcher!
Don't hold back! Keep shooting!
Ha! That fool.
He's facing that many soldiers alone
but he doesn't budge an inch.
I like his gutsiness.
--Use the new cannon-dara!
--Yes, sir!
What kind of cannon is that?
It sounds exciting!
Fire!
Cyborg Franky is on fire!
We did it!
Even his steel body can't
take that much heat!
He's gonna get all melted up!
I'm... dying...
Or not!
What?!
You think I'm that weak?!
Did you think you could kill me
with those crappy toys?!
Super!
Dammit!
Oops!
What should I use this time?
Give me just about three seconds.
This?
No.
Not this one either.
This is it after all!
He's playing with us!
I'm not gonna run or hide!
So...
Let's have a big party, Navy!
Shoot-dara!
THE CURRENT LOCATION
THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT
USOPP AND THE OTHERS
Toys are coming out of there
one after another!
It means Sugar is there in the
Executive Tower at this moment.
What are those tentacle-like things?
There's an exclusive lift for
the executives in the middle.
And those pipes stretching on all side
s are for Big Humans and broken toys to fall.
There are chutes to the junkyard
coming from everywhere in Dressrosa.
When someone gets dropped from there,
he'll fall to the junkyard beneath the Executive Tower.
Help!
Damn! It's horrible!
First, it was the piles of trash - now what?
Where am I?!
You're a pirate - Cavendish, aren't you?
--Yes, I am...
--We're gonna have to examine you.
Examine me?! I'm totally healthy...
What the hell?! What's going on?!
What the hell is going on?!
And what is this slimy stuff?
I thought it was strange when
they took me to the medic room
even though I wasn't injured!
It's not "slimy," it's "sticky"!
What? Wow, you're too close!
Who the hell are you?!
You're in the Executive Tower.
INSIDE THE EXECUTIVE TOWER
But for some reason, new toys
keep coming out of here.
This factory-like room has...
...a special name besides
the "Executive Tower."
Sugar, what's the other name?
The Executive Tower.
No!
Snot comes out! It's hanging!
Yuck. Drop dead.
No, I'm not gonna die!
TREBOL - A TOP EXECUTIVE OF THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
(THE STICKY-STICKY FRUIT EATER)
I'm not gonna listen to a brat like you!
Hey, I'm stuck, kid!
Do something about this sticky fluid...
What?
Here is the contract.
Do not harm any human.
Follow any orders from the Family.
What are you talking about?
Hey! What happened to my body?!
Change me back...
Stop talking and just go work!
What?! I can't talk!
Why am I doing as he says?!
Follow any orders from the Family.
The contract?!
Nobody remembers you now!
I even forget who you were!
You're gonna work and fight for Doffy
for the rest of your life!
Hey, what's going on?!
I've become a toy!
If you walk out the door at
the very end, there is a port!
Oh, you're a newcomer?
Let me take you to your position.
Where am I?!
Keep moving!
This is it! Now, work!
I'm a pirate!
This must be a bad dream! I wanna wake up!
Just carry it!
No! I don't wanna work!
Along with these creepy moving toys!
I'm not gonna work here
for the rest of my life!
So this is where they export the weapons!
But I can't disobey them!
I can't do anything!
I can't believe there is
such a port underground!
I wish I could make a call!
Koala is waiting for my call!
Is there any way I can move on my own will?!
I'm the king of Prodence!
Damn Doflamingo!
Live as a toy for the rest of my life?
No way! Somebody, help!
Swift!
That must be Trebol and Sugar.
She really looks like a kid.
Yes, she does.
She loves grapes - she's always eating them.
--So what?
--We're gonna use that against her.
Take a look at this!
This is a clump of Tatababasco Sauce,
the hottest spice in the world!
We made it look like a grape.
Don't tell me you're gonna let her eat it?!
I'm gonna go and put this in to the basket!
We tested it on 50 people of our tribe and...
...all of them got knocked out
and 18 of them almost died!
You tested it?!
We left nothing to chance!
I'm gonna make her eat it!
Alright! Leo, go!
I'm gonna be watching you!
That's so encouraging!
I gotta be able to get away
if something goes wrong.
Good luck, Leo!
You guys are too loud!
--Watch out for Trebol!
--Watch out!
I said you are too loud!
I can do this!
You all have to get ready!
When you hear Sugar scream,
that's when all the toys in the country will
change back into their human forms!
And at the same time,
everybody will get their lost memories back!
All his evildoing will be revealed
and the pirate - Doflamingo - will...
...show his true color!
I'm gonna go now!
Let's save all our friends!
Guys! You're too loud!
We will take back King Riku's kingdom!
I said...
...you're being too loud!