iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law
who's been captured by Doflamingo.
Meanwhile, at the Colosseum,
the final round of the competition is about to start.
All right! The final round starts soon!
It's going to be a battle royal of the five
including Diamante the hero!
A scramble for the Devil Fruit!
A death match involving the Fighting Fish!
Which one of them will win
the Flare-Flare Fruit?!
Everybody! We're going to
make a full-scale charge now!
Capture or scrap
Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hats-dara!
Let's see how much the Navy can do.
I'm not gonna run or hide! So...
Let's have a big party, Navy!
She loves grapes - she's always eating them.
--So what?
--We're gonna use that against her.
Take a look at this!
This is a clump of Tatababasco Sauce,
the hottest spice in the world!
We made it look like a grape.
Don't tell me you're gonna let her eat it?!
I'm gonna go and put this in to the basket!
I'm gonna go now!
Let's save all our friends!
Guys! You're too loud!
We will take back King Riku's kingdom!
"Dragon Claw Strikes!
Lucy's Intimidating Attack!"
THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT -
IN FRONT OF THE EXECUTIVE TOWER
With this world's hottest grape
made of Tatababasco Sauce,
I'm gonna knock Sugar out!
Here I come, Sugar!
I wonder what kind of guy he is,
the Executive of Doflamingo's clan!
I'm pretty sure he's strong.
What was that?!
Blasted a hole in the wall!
What was it?
This is...
There was a fly.
He shot down a fly?!
Unbelievable!
He shot down a fly behind him!
Who else would blast a hole in the wall
just to kill a fly?!
It means it was just a
casual attack for him?!
Let's not do this, Leo!
It's not too late!
He's totally ready and willing!
Leo, we'll be counting on you!
Uh-huh! Leave it up to me!
We'll carry through
Operation SOP at any cost!
Even if he can shoot a fly,
he can't shoot me because...
...I'm quicker!
So fast! I can't even see him!
Maybe, he can pull it off!
We'll take back our friends
who're being held captive!
--Go for it!
--Leo!
You can do it!
Please! Make it through!
Go!
Wait, Leo!
Robiland?!
There's another blood-thirsty
Fighting Fish jumping out!
It's going for Burgess!
Maybe he was off guard!
He isn't moving!
No, maybe he can't move!
Is he gonna fall victim
to the Fighting Fish?!
Shockwave...
...Elbow!
H-How powerful!
The whole Colosseum is shaking!
It blasted a massive hole
in the spectator area!
Burgess's terrific Shockwave Elbow!
The upstart pirate - Blackbeard!
The Ten Titanic Captains are supporting him!
And one of them is...
...Jesus Burgess!
--That bastard!
--Don't involve the audience!
How destructive!
There's another Fighting Fish
charging towards the ring!
That's...! Here it comes!
It's the "01" Fighting Fish
carrying the Devil Fruit!
There it is!
Is it going for Bartolomeo?!
Oh no, it's made a turn!
Who is it going for?!
Oh my, oh my! The other Fighting Fish are
surfacing one after another!
Is it going to be all-out battle between
the contenders in the ring and the Fighting Fish?!
These fish will never learn!
It's no use!
Charging at me?
You must be out of your mind!
They've come all at once!
I've no business with you!
I told you! It's no use!
Who is the "01" Fighting Fish targeting?!
Oh! It's going for Rebecca!
It is the survival of the fittest!
It's the mechanism of the natural world
that the weak fall prey first!
It must've set its sights on her
from the beginning!
I've gotta cut the chain at least!
Yes! I've got you!
You can't have it!
He wants a fight.
Here we go! The battle
between Lucy and Diamante!
Straw Hat!
I'm gonna fight you next!
I'm gonna have the Flare-Flare Fruit!
I'm gonna bring you down
along with that fish!
Burgess is gonna do it again!
--Run!
--He's gonna do it again!
How smart of you to stand behind me!
He's not gonna try to get away? Lucy!
Shockwave...
Dragon Claw!
Lucy!
Oh my, oh my! Burgess's armor
has shattered into pieces!
O-Only he could done that!
My great senpai!
They're not gonna just give up
the Flare-Flare Fruit, huh?
His fighting style has changed.
Is that really Straw Hat?
They're all in another league!
It's impossible for you
to win that competition!
You're gonna die!
Have courage to fight!
I've got to attack like I'm willing to kill!
Or I have no chance of winning!
Soldier-san, I am...
...going to do it!
--That's our commander!
--Alright! We're taking control of the lift now!
I guess you do have some fight in you.
What?! I know that voice!
You've hijacked the lift
and what are you gonna do now?
I will take down Doflamingo
and restore the King Riku dynasty!
That's ridiculous!
LAO G
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
(THE DIAMANTE ARMY)
Commander!
You bastard!
Cub-san!
What has just happened?!
You fools!
You couldn't see what happened?
I'll tell you if you wanna know.
Commander!
You bastard!
That's what happened.
I didn't expect one of the Executives
to be in the lift!
When I was ordered to stand guard
at the entrance of the Toy House,
I happened to take the lift downwards and
waited ready at the entrance
of the underground trade port
but got on the lift again.
In other words, I...
...took the wron"g" lift!
There's "G"!
I won't let you reach the palace! Intruders!
No!
We must get there!
THE RAMPART TOWER B-1
LUFFY'S GROUP
A-Are you guys okay?
Yes, barely!
Hold on a sec! I'm gonna...
Gum-Gum...
...Storm!
--He's such a pain!
--Let me do it!
What?
What?!
What the hell is that?!
How annoying!
Three-Sword Style - 108 Pound Phoenix!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
It's no use hitting those walls!
THE RAMPART TOWER B-2
KIN'EMON'S GROUP
The stairs that we were going down...
...suddenly bent upwards like
they're leading to the heavens!
Oh, that's good!
What are you talking about?!
We were heading to the Toy House underground!
We can't go any farther like this...
It's actually good we were stopped here!
What do you mean?
To get to the Toy House below,
we have to go up to the palace first
and then take the lift downwards.
That's the only way!
We have to go up in order to go down?!
It means we didn't have to split up
from Luffy and the others!
--No, we didn't!
--Why didn't you tell me?!
I tried to tell you many times!
--To go down...
--Stay inside!
You're my guide!
I wouldn't know what to do
if you fell out of there
while I was unaware!
You didn't listen to me!
You guys are all such blockheads,
jumping to conclusions!
What?! No, no!
We shouldn't be fighting here!
We have to go back now!
Wait! We have a problem!
Even if we can get to the lift in the palace,
the security is tight!
I'm sure I can get on but
since you're a Big Human...
So what if they couldn't figure out
who I truly was?
Poof!
What?!
Whaaat?!
THE TOY HOUSE - FRANKY
That was easy!
Why are you guys taking such a long time
to kill one guy-dara?
Finally, the big fish is coming in?!
Prepare yourself-dara!
That's our Bastille-san!
Huh?! Why is the Navy here?
What's going on?
Don't tell me it's over.
Super!
What?!
You can't take me down that easily!
You're so persistent!
It's my turn!
I'm gonna pay you back double!
Prepare for it!
Take this!
Coup de Vent!
We can't leave it to the Navy as I thought.
That's what I wanted to hear!
Can I do it?
Don't get so cocky!
What's your problem?!
Although he's just a robot,
he is a pervert, just as you are.
Be very careful.
What?
Oh, Señor! You're so hard-boiled!
Let's run away from the stone man!
He's not gonna go down easily!
We're trapped!
Luffy, take her and go on!
Leave him up to me!
You go ahead and kick Doflamingo's ass!
This stone guy…
…is gonna get cut!