iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever
fully explored it except for
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get
the Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize - and won the first round
but now, he's heading for the
palace to take back Law who's
been captured by Doflamingo.
We're gonna head for the palace!
And...
...beat the hell out of Doflamingo!
At the Colosseum,
the final round of the competition started.
Shockwave...
Dragon Claw!
Meanwhile, at the underground trade port,
the Tontattas started to
put Operation SOP into action.
With this world's hottest grape
made of Tatababasco Sauce,
I'm gonna knock Sugar out!
Even if he can shoot a fly, he can't shoot me
because...
...I'm quicker!
Wait, Leo!
Robiland?!
That's our commander!
Alright! We're taking control of the lift now!
I guess you do have some fight in you.
Let's run away from the stone man!
He's not gonna go down easily!
We're trapped!
Luffy, take her and go on!
Leave him up to me!
You go ahead and kick Doflamingo's ass!
"Defeat Sugar!
The Army of the Little People Charges!"
This stone guy is gonna get cut!
Okay! I'll be counting on you!
I'm gonna fight you!
It's gonna block our way!
It's coming from behind, too!
I said I'm gonna fight you!
Three-Sword Style!
Onigiri!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
Let's go!
Okay!
Black Rope Dragon Twister!
Now you're quiet all of a sudden?
One-Sword Style...
...Iai...
...Death Lion Song!
Commander!
How arro"g"ant of you
to think you can invade the palace!
There's the "G"!
I'm gonna get there at any cost and...
...take down Doflamingo!
THE ROYAL PALACE 1F
Commander!
This is no good! If nothing is done,
not only can we not defeat Doflamingo,
but we won't be able to save our people
who're working at the factory as slaves!
IN THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT
We haven't had any new workers for a year.
Yeah. I heard they don't even come to the palace.
LUMINOUS FLOWERS "ELEGANT SUNFLOWERS"
Who is taking a break?!
THE MAN-MADE DEVIL FRUITS -
SMILE MANUFACTURING FACTORY
N-Not us!
When 500 of your people didn't come back,
you'd think there's something wrong.
But the Tontattas don't think
somebody's doing something bad.
That's why they're so dumb...
I mean, pure.
Then, why don't they come
around here anymore?
I don't know.
Well, if they don't come,
we'll just keep making these 500 work like hell!
Too slow! Here's a lesson in tough-love!
Hey, hey! This SMILE is unripe!
Are you okay?!
I thought you Tontattas could grow any plant!
W-We can!
But SMILEs are very unnatural fruits.
No excuses!
Could you give my brother
a few minutes to rest?
Today's meal was a little spoiled.
Now you're complaining about your meal?
Don't you wanna cure
your princess Mancherie's illness?
W-We do!
Then, make more SMILEs!
It's the only medication for her illness!
The average number of
acceptable fruits you produce
in one season is still less
than one out of every ten!
Use your head and
increase the production rate!
Could we see Princess Mancherie?
No!
W-Why?!
Because...
If you pick up her disease,
we would be devastated!
You Tontattas are important partners to us!
S-Sanshita-san!
We're gonna work very hard!
Please take good care of our princess!
Alright!
How could they believe in such a lie?
Wh-What are you doing, Robiland?!
I'm sorry.
But if I didn't stop you,
you would've been taken down.
What?
The fly that got shot...
This is...
It was so tiny
but it was shot right between the eyes.
Trebol's dynamic vision
and ability are exceptional.
I think it's too dangerous to approach Sugar
while he's protecting her!
What should we do then, Robiland?
We should separate Trebol from Sugar!
It's easier said than done.
Usoland! Tell us what to do!
What?!
Our legendary hero - Usoland!
Y-You can count on me.
Put it there.
Hey, what's wrong with that load?!
There is a swarm of pink hornets!
I'm here to report, Trebol-sama!
We have a problem with
Captain Yves' pirate group in
trade port district 4!
They're going wild saying they
want to talk to an Executive
about the price!
Aren't they afraid of Joker's name?
They must have a lot of nerve!
Hey, did they change the person
in charge of reporting?
He's out to lunch now!
And it's an emergency!
We have a few casualties on our side!
Please help us!
Casualties?
Alright, I'm coming!
Hey, hey!
Yes!
Trebol-sama, are you gonna go somewhere?
Tighten security at the four doors
to the Executive Tower.
Yes, sir!
But if something happens,
let me know immediately!
Y-Yes, sir!
Trebol-sama!
Thank you for your leadership!
Hey, hey!
Where is it? Where are they fighting?
District 4.
What? Aren't you gonna fight for us?
I could easily handle this.
But I'd better do nothing!
I'll just stay and watch
so you can build your self-confidence!
Self-confidence?
I see!
Now we understand!
Don't worry! If something goes wrong,
I'll make everything right for you!
That's good to know!
We'll follow you to the end!
The legendary hero - Usoland!
Th-That's me.
Who is it?
I'm gonna go now!
Oh! He did it!
Now we wait for her to eat the
clump of Tatababasco Sauce,
the hottest spice in the world!
That's not it!
Eat the right one this time!
Idiot! Don't scream!
If Operation Sugar Oversurprised and Panic fails,
it's gonna ruin all of our plans!
We have no choice!
Uh-huh!
Don't fight back, Sugar!
Those fools!
We're here to take back our friends
who're working like slaves in the factory!
And we're gonna knock you out!
Knock me down?
But I don't know anything about your friends.
What?!
Really?!
Uh-huh.
All right, then!
It's not all right! Don't be fooled!
Oh, that was close!
Give us back our friends!
Who's putting this idea in your heads?!
There's no way that you dummies notice
that you've been fooled, yourself.
You Tontattas...
You haven't come to the palace
for a year or so, but...
...I guess that's because
somebody talked you into something.
Charge!
Restrain her and open her mouth!
I don't like it. They think I'm weak.
Little Black Bears!
Here is the contract.
Oh no! She has turned us into toys!
You must follow my orders until you die!
Did they forget about us?!
Oh? Oh?
Some toys have appeared from nowhere!
What were we doing now?
Kill everyone in the Executive Tower!
I can't help myself from following her orders!
Kill everyone? Including me?!
No! I don't wanna fight!
They must be Sugar's subordinates!
I didn't know there were bodyguards
other than Trebol!
Leo! It's me! Flapper!
Take down the enemies!
No! No!
No! Nooo!!
Trebol, come back here!
It was a trap!
Trebol!
A trap?
Hey!
Look at that! Trebol-sama!
The pirates are running wild
and there's nothing we can do!
Hey, hey! You guys!
What's the problem here?
Trebol-sama!
Hey! What is it?!
Well, it's just there was a swarm of bees
on a load!
We have no problem with the deal itself.
That tramp!
Hey, hey! Wait up, wait up!
You bitch!
Hey! Who are you and
where did you come from? Hey?
She vanished!
Hey! Hey!
Don't tell me she's... I know her face!
Is she a member of the Straw Hats?!
How did she get here?!
Trebol!
Why do they wanna attack Sugar?
Come back here now! You've been fooled!
Good-for-nothing idiot! Drop dead!
I'm losing it!
Sticky-Sticky Chain!
Stick-Stickem...
What's going on?!
...Meteora!
The furious Trebol's powerful attack
devastates Leo and the others.
The only hope left for the King Riku Army
is the Toy Soldier!
Once known as "The Legend"
throughout Dressrosa,
his true identity is close to being revealed!
Next on One Piece:
"The Last Light of Hope!
The Secret of Our Commander!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!