The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Oh!
The wind stopped again.
Just when we should be rushing
straight for Little Garden, too.
We're temporarily stopped again.
Time is running out as we speak, too...
Don't worry.
I know we need to get to Alabasta
as soon as possible, but...
Alright! Let's fish! Fish!
Hey, anyone seen the bait?
Bait? Oh, the stuff in there? I ate it.
You ate it?! Those were bugs, you know!
Yeah? They taste good!
Don't eat stuff like that!
Now what?! We can't fish now
that you've eaten our bait!
Use this, then!
We can't catch anything with that!
Really? We can't?
Then how about him?
Oh. That sounds okay.
--Hey, you! Come here!
--Get back here, bait!
Dammit, you guys! Knock it off!
But can't you guys be
a little worried, at least?!
Worried about what?
Oh! Nami-san is lovely
when she's angry, too!
Honestly, now!
But it's strange.
For someone with a
30 million-Berry bounty,
he doesn't seem that
terrible of a person at all...
Yeah, it might be hard to imagine,
but he's beaten many big names.
Arlong, the fishman who was
bent on ruling the East Blue...
Pirate Fleet Commodore, Don Krieg...
Captain Kuro, an unknown pirate
notorious for his cunning methods.
You forgot one.
A navy freak who wields a huge axe-hand.
Oh! Axe-Hand Morgan!
Axe-Hand Morgan?
I've heard of him before.
I heard he's a navy captain
who's feared in the East Blue
for his overwhelming domination.
You're saying he beat even him?!
Oh! The old axe-hand guy!
That reminds me, I wonder what
that guy with him is up to now...
I wonder if he's still
at that navy base...
Who's "he"?
Yeah! His name's Coby!
He's my friend!
"Try Hard, Coby!
Coby-Meppo's Struggles in the Navy"
Sub-Lieutenant!
Preparations for departure are complete!
"Justice"
I see.
All ships, move out!
Yes, sir!
Luffy-san! How are you?
It's me! Coby!
After we parted ways back then,
I've worked my hardest!
There were plenty of hardships,
but now I've achieved my
dream of being a navy officer!
C-Captain Morgan!
Coby...
Go to Hell, Coby!
Luffy-san!
Heya, Coby!
Gum-Gum...
...Tornado!
Wow! So pretty!
Oww!
I was dreaming!
What the hell?!
Quit screwing around, you!
--Shut up!
--Quiet!
Go to sleep, you idiot chore boys!
"Chore Boy"
At any rate, Luffy-san,
I'm now working at the navy base!
Captain Morgan's son Helmeppo-san
was given chore duty, too!
--Hey! Quit slackin' off!
--Oww...
Hey, chore boys! Wash the windows
when you're done cleaning!
Yes, sir!
And don't forget to
clean up in the mess hall!
Eh?! What about our meal?!
You're obviously not
gonna finish before lunch!
You can eat after
you've finished everything!
Eh?! But I'm starving to death here!
Helmeppo-san!
Helmeppo! Coby!
Yes, sir!
You're both aware neither of you
were qualified to join the navy...
...yet you were given special
permission to join as chore boys, right?
It's not like you let us join, though!
Yes, sir! Of course! If there's
anything I can do, I'll do it!
Just give the order!
No... just making sure you realize that.
Work hard, now!
Yes, sir! You can count on us!
We'll also be honored to do your laundry!
--Are you an idiot?!
--Eh?
You don't need to go out of
your way for even more work!
But we are chore boys,
after all! Okay! Work! Work!
"We"?
If you wanna work that badly,
you can do it yourself!
One! Two! Three! Four!
I can't stand this. Forget Coby--
why do I hafta be a chore boy?!
How I wish I could go back to then...
Helmeppo-sama. Your cocoa, sir.
Oww!
Dammit! Are you trying to scald me?!
No, sir! I-I'm very sorry, sir!
Who do you think I am?!
I'm Helmeppo-sama, only son of
the great Navy Captain Morgan!
Yes, sir! Helmeppo-sama!
Man, things were good back then!
Dammit! This is all
that Straw Hat's fault!
He stripped Dad of his
position as a navy captain!
It's all his fault!
It's all because of Straw Hat that
I'm stuck doing this crap now!
Helmeppo-san.
What do you want?!
Don't touch me all friendly-like!
I'm sorry. But I wanted to tell
you something, as a friend...
Friend?! Why would
me and you be friends?!
Well, we are both chore boys...
I'm not the kind of guy who
does chores in a place like this!
If it hadn't been for Straw Hat...
It's not good to blame Luffy-san
for everything like that.
Blaming your fate on others
won't solve anything.
Wouldn't you agree that's
the sign of a weakling?
W-What?!
For a long time, you lived your
life using your father's power.
But from here on out,
we need to face forward
and search for our dreams on our own!
What are you...
I have a dream!
Someday, I will be a navy officer
who cracks down on bad guys!
How can you be like that?!
A wimp like you, being a navy
officer?! That'll never happen!
It will!
After seeing how Luffy-san lives
his life, I made up my mind!
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
I've decided to be it, so if I die
fighting for that, that's fine with me!
So I decided to be like Luffy-san
and put my life on the line
to strive for my ambition!
You see? So let's both
work hard together!
Screw you!
You, lecturing me?! Since when
are you that high and mighty?!
What could you possibly learn
from that despicable Straw Hat?!
Don't talk bad about Luffy-san!
I haven't said anything that's wrong!
Even if that were true,
you still piss me off!
Helmeppo-san!
Please come to your senses!
Like you're anyone to talk!
--Take this!
--Wake up!
What is it?! What's going on?!
Sir! The chore boys
are fighting on the roof!
What are you gawking for?!
Stop them already!
You two!
W-We're sorry!
Eh? That explosion earlier
was you guys' doing?
Did they kick you out
of the navy after that?
Thank you for the food.
No, we managed to
avoid being kicked out.
We had to agree to work
for free for 50 years, though.
Being kicked out
would've been much better.
Cheer up, you two!
Oh, yeah! Look at this!
"Straw Hat Luffy Wreaks
Havoc in Loguetown!
Manages a Baffling Escape
from Captain Smoker!"
Luffy-san!
This means Luffy-san
headed for the Grand Line!
At last, he's taken a big step
toward realizing his dream!
Attention!
I will now fill you in
on our current mission!
--Hey!
--Whadya want?!
D-Dad...
Former Navy Captain Morgan is
to be sent to Navy Headquarters
to face a court martial for the
crimes of military exploitation
and the tormenting of civilians!
His transfer and delivery to
Vice-Admiral Garp is today's mission!
I am Navy Captain "Axe-Hand" Morgan!
You rankless, low-status scum
will kneel before me!
There's no getting around it, huh?
He should get court-martialed
or whatever else.
He does get what he deserves and all...
But to be honest,
I still respected him anyways.
My dad...
...was my idol.
But I guess he did take
things too far, huh?
Damn it!
Why?!
Tell me, do you think
they'll execute him?
T-That's...
Maybe there's no getting
around that either, huh?
Given how my dad is...
Helmeppo-san...
All hands on deck!
Fall in!
--It's Vice-Admiral Garp!
--It's Garp the Fist!
So he's Navy Headquarters
Vice-Admiral Garp the Fist!
The hero of the seas who
travels all over the Grand Line!
Vice-Admiral Garp! Thank you
for coming all this way personally!
We hereby deliver Morgan to you!
--Dad...
--Stop, Helmeppo-san!
Umm... Vice-Admiral Garp?
Vice-Admiral Garp!
Quiet!
I hear you.
I've been up for five days now...
Thank you for your hard work, sir!
No, I've been going for a
new doughnut-eating record...
Sir?
But the lack of sleep and rest has
gotten me a bit drowsy at 842...
This geezer's a joke.
Morgan! Vice-Admiral Garp is a
leading figure at Navy Headquarters!
Old man. Cut the sleeping act.
Don't move!
Move and I'll hack this chore boy
up and feed him to the sharks!
D-D-Dad!
Please stop this!
Helmeppo-san is your own son!
Son?! I don't need a son!
What I want is freedom!
His life means nothing to me!
I'll toss him into a pool
of blood if I have to!
D-Dad...
H-Help me!
So long, fools!
Helmeppo-san!
Ready the cannon!
Load! Aim!
Target-- 16 degrees starboard!
Distance-- 8,263! Ready!
P-Please wait!
--That's dangerous!
--What're you doing?!
P-Please don't shoot! My friend...
My friend's onboard!
Move.
No!
Then I'll cut you down!
--Stop, chore boy!
--Don't go against regulations!
No! Helmeppo-san is my...
...my...
...friend!
That fool. Stirring up trouble, huh?
You will pay for this.
That's much better than
just abandoning my friend!
Please! I'll go capture him myself!
You idiot! Come back!
There's no way you can catch him!
Let's let him go.
He's either quite the fool, or...
What do we do?!
What's with all the racket?
I'm finally awake...
Vice-Admiral Garp! I thought
for sure you'd been done in!
Huh?! Someone's been done in?!
I didn't see it because I was asleep!
Who was wounded?!
Me?
I'm free!
Just you watch! The world will
kneel down before me once again!
Today marks the new start of
the newly reborn Morgan Kingdom!
Now! Set our course to the west!
What're you doing?!
I said set our course to the west!
No!
I'll have no part in this!
He covered for me after this happened!
Even when getting kicked out of
the navy would destroy his dream!
He's protecting me, regardless of that!
I can do it, too!
Dad! I'm going to capture you!
Just give up--
Are you stupid?! Who do you
think you're talkin' to, huh?!
What can a piece of
useless scum do to me?!
Do as you're told, and I'll make
things nice for ya. So be quiet and--
Shut the hell up, Dad!
Dammit!
Know your place, you pathetic insect!
As if I'd ever listen to you!
I'm the one who decides how I live!
Quit getting the wrong idea!
What can scum like you possibly do?!
He isn't alone!
--You!
--M-M-Morgan!
Please give yourself up!
As a member of the navy forces,
I'm going to capture you!
Pathetic! Pathetic! Pathetic!
What can a couple of insects do?!
Get in my way and I'll
chop you both into pieces!
I'm sorry it turned out this way
after you came to save me...
What are you talking about?
We're friends!
Coby...
Plus, I've made up my mind!
I've decided to live for my beliefs!
Damn it...
A-And if I die fighting...
...if I die fighting for that,
that's fine with me!
You wanna die that badly, huh?!
I'm not going to die!
Not until I've become a
navy officer! But, when...
When I do die...
...it'll be...
...while I'm fighting!
Playtime is over!
Coby!
You stupid idiot! Let Coby go! Coby!
You damn insects
aren't even worth killing.
Never show yourself to me again!
Morgan!
I'll let you go for today!
But someday I will surpass you!
Someday, I will catch you!
Just you wait!
Please forgive my poor supervision!
Allowing the prisoner to escape
is the biggest blunder of my life!
We're very sorry, sir!
After what's happened,
these two will be kicked out for life!
What truly lost causes you are.
I doubt anyone anywhere
would take you in now.
And you'd only burden everyone
if we turned you loose...
You leave me no choice.
Come with me to Navy Headquarters!
Vice-Admiral! You're going to
take them with you to Navy HQ?!
Is that bad?
N-No, not exactly...
Are you two against it?
If you want to run away,
now's your chance.
Though I have no intention
of letting you say no, anyway.
My, oh, my.
What an odd day this has been!
And that's how we wound up heading
for the Grand Line, Luffy-san.
I'm sure the day will come
when we meet again!
You've got me!
Ah, gentle song
Make it there for us
After a wave washed away
that little sand castle
You looked up at the passing
clouds with a sad smile
If you find the world is full of enemies,
I've got your back
Don't lose faith
You've got me!
Ah, my love
I'll hold you in my arms forever
You've got me!
Oh! Here we go! Check it out!
What is it? Oh, this is a navy photo!
That's no ordinary guy in it!
Know who it is?!
--Whoa, it's Coby!
--Coby? Who's that?
My friend!
--He's gonna be a navy softener!
--You mean "officer"!
Man, talk about being careless...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Coby-Meppo's Resolve!
Vice-Admiral Garp's Parental Affection"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!