Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa
but Law has been captured by Doflamingo.
Luffy snuck into the Royal Palace
to take back Law.
Meanwhile, the toys who turned
back to their original forms
channel their anger towards Doflamingo.
Who are those bastards?!
--Look! He's a Doflamingo operative!
--Thank you for turning us into toys!
Take him down together with the factory!
The fighting competition
came to a surprising end
and the mystery man who were disguised as Lucy
finally disclosed his identity.
Who are you really?
Me?
My name is Sabo.
We're members of the Revolutionary Army.
What? Then, the first Lucy, too?!
The first Lucy has a bounty of 400 million.
He's the man who'll become
the King of the Pirates someday!
Straw Hat Luffy!
A pirate?!
Yeah, he's my brother. Take good care of him!
At the same time, Luffy finally comes face-to-face
with Doflamingo. However...
Tra-guy!
I'm here to save you!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Oh, the stone guy!
Pica!
I never thought I'd be taken in like this.
Mingo's alive!
It's a difficult situation.
I have no choice but to use the "Birdcage."
The Birdcage?!
Right, Law?
"The Devil's Trap!
A Dressrosa Extermination Plan!"
Where's Doflamingo?!
Take everything away from him!
Destroy the factory as well!
THE SMILE FACTORY
What should we do?!
The ex-toys are coming to...
...raid the factory!
Well...
Nobody can get in here
unless they have a key to the door!
This factory means everything
to the Young Master!
Even if the ceiling collapses,
there won't be a single scratch
because the buildings are
made of Sea Prism Stone.
And more importantly...
Those two top executives are on guard now!
It's no use!
Lock!
Sticky-Sticky Chain!
Don't push your luck, you scum!
Stick-Stickem!
Nobody can take down those two!
This factory has
an impregnable two-pronged defense!
We need to do something immediately.
Creepy!
How are you still alive, Doflamingo?!
Do you want me to teach you...
...how to kill a person?
Soldier!
Brother Kyros!
This is how you do it.
Kyros!
Straw Hat!
There are two Young Masters!
Pentachromatic Strings!
Sorry! I dropped my guard!
Gum-Gum...
Armament!
...Jet Gatling!
Luffyland!
What is that clone?!
That hurts!
It's like a marionette made of strings!
I've never seen such a technique!
King Riku.
Do you remember the feeling you had
on that night 10 years ago?
The day you sliced up your dear citizens
and burned down peaceful towns.
Please stop!
If there's no preventing me
hurting the citizens...
I'd rather be dead!
Somebody, please...
...kill me!
I still have nightmares of it every night!
Yes, I remember it! So what?!
The tragedy that will unfold soon
will not be small-scale like that.
Don't be ridiculous!
What are you planning?!
I don't ever want to see such...
Now it's time to let you guys go.
Pica!
Throw these nuisances out!
Doflamingo!
Don't cause harm to...
...this country anymore!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
Now, let's bring an end to everything.
He threw us out into
the garden of the Rampart Tower!
We can't get near Doflamingo
as long as Pica is there!
I-It's started...!
The Birdcage!
Captain, what's that?!
How do I know?!
Let's get off of the island now!
Even if we stay here and hurl
our anger at Doflamingo,
we'll just be crushed in return!
Captain! Watch out! Something's there!
Ouch!
A-Are they blades?
What are these bars?
It didn't work! We can't break it down!
What the hell is that?!
The Birdcage?
What do you mean by that, Tra-guy?!
Before the truth behind
this country is exposed,
Doflamingo is going to...
...kill everyone on the island!
What?!
There's a fence all over as far as I can see!
Where is the exit?!
What is that-dara?
Vice Admiral Bastille!
I can't reach the Headquarters!
The same here!
I can't make contact with the base!
We haven't reported anything yet!
This must be...
Hey! What did you shoot somebody's house?!
I-I didn't want to! I can't control my body!
Hey! Stop!
Wh-What the...?! M-My body's...
Daddy!
Stop me! Please duck, everybody!
Parasite String!
Help!
What the hell is going on-dara?!
Sir, I have report!
There are people causing
harm to others randomly
in different parts of Dressrosa!
Some of us Navy soldiers
are running wild, too!
If nothing is done, many citizens will die!
What is it this time?!
Th-The King's Plateau is sinking down!
H-H-Hey! The ground is descending!
What's going on?!
It's Pica!
Since he can merge with stones,
he can even shift the geography!
The Royal Palace is going somewhere!
Stop, Royal Palace!
The factory is going up!
What?! What the hell is happening here?!
Somebody!
Please stop me!
The plateau of the Flower Field is...
...rising up and pulling in the whole town!
Clank.
Citizens and guests of Dressrosa.
I could have reigned over you all
with terror from the start.
After finding out the truth,
I bet a great number of you want
to kill me now.
That's why I prepared a game for you.
It's a game to kill me.
I'm in the Royal Palace. I won't run or hide.
If you can take my life,
the game ends there, of course.
But there is another way to finish the game.
Here is how. You kill all the
people that I'm going to name now.
Also, I will award a large prize
for killing each one of them.
Kill or get killed.
Everyone in this country will become hunters!
The only way for you to survive is...
to kill somebody!
The all-out battle at the Colosseum was
only a beginning!
Now, the whole of Dressrosa has
become a battlefield and the
horrifying, life-or-death game is on!
Faced with an extreme situation where
citizens turn violent and try to kill him,
Luffy moves to take down Doflamingo!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The 500 Million Berry Man! Target: Usoland!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!