iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Usopp knocked Sugar out
and freed the toys who had been forced to labor as slaves
but Doflamingo confined everybody in the country in the Birdcage.
Now, let's bring an end to everything.
I-It's started...!
The Birdcage!
Doflamingo is going to...
...kill everyone on the island!
"The 500 Million Berry Man!
Target: Usoland!"
Damn! It's as steady as rock!
Move aside!
How about this?!
How's that?!
Daddy!
Somebody! Stop me!
Nobody's gonna come to help.
Nobody can get out of this Birdcage.
Hello? Hello?!
You can't make contact with
anyone out there.
You're all going to die
and no one out there will know it.
--Your neighbors who are running wild...
--Don't! Daddy!
--...will keep harming others randomly.
--Somebody, please stop me!
Or I'm gonna kill my own kids!
It doesn't matter if it's their family or close friends
or citizens who they swore to protect.
Don't do it!
I can't control my body!
Somebody, please! Stop me!
Get away from me! Everybody!
Issho-san!
Even if you run or hide,
there is no safe place in the cage.
The terror of the Birdcage will go on for days.
It's a matter of which happens sooner.
You all die or you finish the game.
Damn that Doflamingo!
You can't anticipate his next move!
I can't believe it!
The factory went up and is gone now!
--But this is definitely a good chance for us!
--We can get out!
--We finally can get out from underground!
--Thank you, God Usopp!
Advance!
Robin-dono!
Kin'emon!
I'm glad that you're okay!
A-An iron breast-band?!
This is quite a foreign culture.
Love it!
R-Robin-senpai, let me be your slave!
I mean, can I ask you something?
Th-That guy's nose...
It looks like Sniper King-senpai's,
who is known for shooting out the flag on the Tower of Law!
It's him. His name is Usopp.
There he is!
And Robin-senpai was moved by
the action of her pirate group...
...that turned the world against them
in order to save one of their friends!
That makes them
the Enies Lobby Shoot-out Duo!
Yes! Yes! Oh, yes!
What are you excited for?! You geek!
Shut your mouth!
I got my arm broken by this fool?!
Alright, I hand them over to you.
Although they're little, they're quite good warriors.
Thank you, Topknot-land!
We found them passed out
in a hallway at the Palace!
I guess they laid their lives on the line
for the commander.
Cub-san! Rampo! I'm proud of you all!
Somebody, stop me!
My body's out of control!
Somebody!
This is exactly like the incident
on that night 10 years ago!
Now...
I know!
On that night,
King Riku-sama was... the King Riku Army was...
...manipulated by...
...manipulated by Doflamingo!!
Scream! Hate! Suffer!
You people are innocent victims!
Help...
Stop me!
Stop it... Doflamingo!
Think!
You either come to kill me or
side with us Don Quixote Family
and punish the 12 fools who rebel against me.
If you make the wrong decision,
the game will not end.
I'll pay 100 million berries for each star rating!
100 million berries?!
These are the criminals in Dressrosa!
First, the One-stars...
REBECCA
A CONVICT GLADIATOR OF THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
(KING RIKU'S GRANDDAUGHTER)
NICO ROBIN - A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
"DEMON CHILD"
FOXFIRE KIN'EMON
- A SAMURAI FROM THE WANO KINGDOM
VIOLA - THE FORMER PRINCESS OF DRESSROSA
CYBORG FRANKY - A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
Next, the Two-stars...
KYROS - THE FORMER ARMY COMMANDER OF DRESSROSA
PIRATE HUNTER ZORO
- A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
A-Army Commander Kyros!
I forgot about him, the invincible gladiator!
There are pirates, too! It's the Straw Hats!
I didn't know the executive of the Family, Violet, was Princess Viola!
And as for key figures of each group,
I give them three stars!
SABO - THE CHIEF OF STAFF OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
STRAW HAT LUFFY - A PIRATE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE STRAW HATS
TRAFALGAR LAW - THE CAPTAIN OF "THE HEART PIRATES"
THE WARLORD(TENTATIVE), "SURGEON OF DEATH"
RIKU DOLDO III - THE FORMER KING OF DRESSROSA
300 million!
Law and Straw Hat...
Their pirate alliance has just startled the world!
King Riku!
King Riku-sama... He was alive!
There's a big gun from the Revolutionary Army!
He's the Chief of Staff!
--They knew about you already!
--I'm a target, too?!
Wh-What a relief.
They haven't found out about me.
Plus, there is the man who
pissed me off the most today!
It's all his fault that you people have to
play such a bloody game!
The one who kills him will get...
...500 million berries!
"GOD" USOPP - A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
500 million!
I don't have to work for the rest of my life!
Five?!!
F... F... Five...
Oh... Oh no, Usoland is...
The Five-star!
There are two One-stars
and one Three-star there!
Sabo-kun, what should we do?
Let's go above ground! Everybody, run!
God Usopp! I'm sorry but I need to kill you!
The Five-star! 500 million!
Th-They were worshiping me
until a few minutes ago!
Damn! Please run!
Yes, sir!
Robin-dono!
I'm gonna go look for Kanjuro so excuse me!
Be careful!
There's one, too!
The One-star samurai! 100 million berries!
This is so annoying!
Th-The Little Person told me
there's a junkyard down there!
Are you really there, Kanjuro?!
--100 million berries is mine!
--Okay, let's just go!
He fell! The samurai fell down into the hole!
You have no time to wonder what to do.
People are falling and
towns are burning moment by moment.
Either you kill me...
...or kill the 12 criminals.
Now the game is on!
What should we do?!
We just found out that
King Riku-sama was innocent!
If we citizens all act together,
maybe we can take down Doflamingo...
It's not just him!
In order to kill Doflamingo,
we have to fight the 2000 soldiers of the Doflamingo Family!
What are we supposed to do then?
Even King Riku-sama is in the 12 criminal list!
Are we gonna do wrong by the innocent king again?
I think we don't have to kill them!
We can just take them into custody!
Just 12 of them!
We have no choice! Let's fight!
--Yeah!
--You're right!
One of the 12 criminals is
knocked out over here.
What?!
Where did Cyborg Franky go?
He was down on the ground.
I'm back on my feet
with backup cola for destroying the factory!
Look! There's one of the Straw Hats!
Wait!
You guys are the ex-toys who were saved by Usopp, aren't you?!
It's nothing personal!
One-star, 100 million berries, Cyborg Franky!
100 million is mine!
Bring it on!
How dare you guys be blinded by money!
If you think you can bring me down, try it!
Silly big talkers!
Th-There's the criminal!
One of the criminals is here!
Let's go!
Catch him, everybody!
Forget about us and just shoot!
Cut it out, guys!
I have no business with you town people!
Shoot already!
Shoot!
I have no choice.
You'll have to try harder!
We've made up our mind!
We've got to do it!
There's no end if I fight them one by one!
This would do!
Usopp did his part so it's my turn!
I'm gonna break the factory into pieces!
Hey hey, the factory went up on its own!
It's Pica.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Trebol!
--What?
--Doffy?
Diamante, I didn't know you are there, too.
Y-Yes, I am.
Doffy, about Sugar...
Both of you, come back to the Palace!
We'll talk later. Okay?!
Clank.
Wait!
Barrier!
Stop following us!
Go on! To the ground above!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
--Zoro?
--Yeah.
--Where are you now?
--Robin?
I'm with Luffy and the others.
We're on, what they call, the King's Plateau.
Things are getting messy, aren't they?
Is this Robin?!
Did you see it?!
Mingo's such a jerk, isn't he?!
But Usopp's bit was hilarious!
What did you say, Luffy?!
Rebecca was also on the list.
I wonder if she's alright.
Rebecca is...
I'm here! Lucy?!
Oh! It's good that you're there!
The soldier is here...
Oh?
Where did the soldier go?
What?!
Don't tell me he is...
It's the criminal!
Kill him!
Soldier-san?! He turned back to a human, too, didn't he?!
Tell me, Lucy, what kind of a man is he?!
What kind of a man?!
What are you talking about?!
That one-legged soldier was...
...your father!
He's the old man the statue is of!
I... I couldn't protect her!
I'm sorry!
I couldn't protect your mother!
Although I couldn't protect your mother,
I'm gonna protect you to the end, with my life!
Until the day you are filled with happiness,
I will always be by your side!
I thought so...
Run, Rebecca!
I'm gonna save you now, Rebecca!
Soldier-san is a brave man
He will always be by your side
Happy Birthday, Rebecca!
Let me teach you how to fight.
There's no need since I have you.
I'm gonna teach you how to not get hurt!
Humans' instincts are much better than that!
Let it all out!
Believe in your human power!
I'm a toy.
I don't know how long my body's gonna last!
Stand up, Rebecca!
Be strong!
I'm happy for you!
The soldier guy has gone somewhere now
but listen to me, Rebecca!
Don't cry yet!
I won't let the soldier die!
You have to be safe, too!
I feel bad that I couldn't let you have
the Flare-Flare Fruit that you wanted.
But instead,
I promise I'll kick Doflamingo's ass for you!
So stay with my friends!
I'm gonna bring an end to
this stupid game in no time!
So survive! Okay?!
Uh-huh!
Wait for me, Mingo!
Along with Law and Zoro, Luffy is on the move!
The three single-mindedly make a dash
for the Royal Palace to confront Doflamingo,
but are surrounded by executives of the Family -
Machvise, Señor, Dellinger,
and rowdy pirates who are looking to
claim their prize,
and find themselves caught in a deadly battle!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Breaking through Enemy Lines!
Luffy and Zoro Launch the Counter-Attack!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!