Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
They freed the toys who had been forced to
labor as slaves
but Doflamingo trapped everybody in the country
in the Birdcage
and put prices on the heads
of Luffy and 11 others.
Now, those of you who rebel
against our family...
What?
I'm gonna fight you!
His voice! It's so high!
Run!
Run! It's gonna crush you up!
Luffy!
Luffy!!
"Gathering into a Powerful Front!
Luffy and a Group of Brutal Warriors!"
What?! What?!
M-My hand...
--My hand - it's slipping!
--What?!
I won't let you fall!
Usoland!
Th-Thank you, Leo!
That was close.
But what was that?
What caused the big shake?
I can't believe it...
I'm scared!
The town got squashed.
If he throws another one,
it'll be dangerous to be here!
Let's run!
To where?!
His fist can reach the edge of the town!
With a single blow...
Luffy! Law!
Where are you?!
Hey!
Zoro!
We're up here! Up here!
Luffy!
I got hanged!
Let me down now!
Get off of me now!
Sorry, sorry!
What's wrong with you?!
Trying to hurt me?!
--Huh?
--Don't give me "Huh?"!
Boy, how reckless can you be?
Laughing at Pica's voice means death.
Look how far we've got!
Where are we?
I don't know.
I think we got even farther away
from the Royal Palace.
Damn that stone assimilation human!
He ended up being even bigger than Oars!
If only I knew how to beat him...
Straw Hat.
Cabbage!
You're Pirate Hunter Zoro, aren't you?
And Trafalgar...
...Law!
Give me back...
...my glory, you scoundrels
of the Worst Generation!
What are you doing?! He's with me now!
No, I'm not!
What?! Do you still hold
a grudge against me?!
No, I'm not gonna go after
you Straw Hats anymore.
Because one of your crew,
God Usopp, saved my life!
Usopp did?
That's right! I won't ever
forget the brave image of him
when he saved hundreds, sacrificing his life!
Although I didn't see it.
Well, I'm happy when
somebody says nice things about my friends.
Oh yeah!
Trafalgar.
This is your hat, isn't it?
I found it in front of the Colosseum.
Let me put it on you.
Come closer, now!
I don't trust you!
Well, who cares. I'm busy now anyway.
Do you wanna know why I'm busy?
No.
All right, I'll tell you if you insist!
I've decided to kill Doflamingo to
return you guys the favor!
What?!
Leave the rest to me and go hide somewhere...
No thanks! I'm gonna do it!
I have to return Rebecca the favor
for buying me lunch!
Your reason to fight was food?!
Cut it out! I know you're trying to fool me!
You plan on stealing more attention
by killing Doflamingo, don't you?!
The spotlight?!
What are you talking about?!
Think about it.
If you take down a vicious pirate like Doflamingo,
newspapers won't leave you alone!
A flood of people will come to hear your story
from morning 'til night!
"Hello, superstar!"
Did you call me "superstar"? Oh, please!
"What do you want?"
"Cavendish-san! What do you think of
the situation regarding pirates in recent years?"
"Oh? You're there, aren't you?!
Cavendish-san?!"
What's wrong? I'm right in front of you!
"You are?! But I can't see you
because you're so bright!"
Is it too shiny for you?! I'm sorry!
But I can't hide my brilliance!
"Wow! You really are a star!"
Alright.
Let's go.
Now, burn my image into your mind as
much as you want! I am a superstar!
Let's see!
I don't see Straw Hat's dead body!
Maybe, it's been completely destroyed
or it got blown away.
Or he got away.
Where did you go? Straw Hat!
His voice! It's so high!
Find him! Let me know if he's still alive!
I won't let him reach Doffy!
Luffy, you know that strange guy we just met?
Oh, you mean Cabbage?
Cabbage?
Are you kidding? Is that a name?
I met him at the Colosseum.
There were a whole bunch of
strange people besides him!
Oh yeah?
There they are!
One 200-million and two 300-millions!
Don't let them get away!
Take this!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
Two-Sword Style!
Rhino Cycle!
There they are!
One Two-star and two Three-stars!
We got more!
Hey, Luffy!
If we fight them all, it'll take forever!
--Let's go!
--Okay!
There you are, Straw Hat!
Get out of my way!
Don't stand in my way!
--Get out of my way!
--That voice is...
Wait, Garp's grandson!
DON CHIN JAO - THE HAPPOSUI ARMY (A GANG)
SAI - THE LEADER OF THE
HAPPOSUI ARMY (A GANG)
We've been looking for you, you bastard!
BOO - THE VICE LEADER OF
THE HAPPOSUI ARMY (A GANG)
You can't get away from us!
Ugh! I thought so!
--Wait!
--Oh no! Run!
Huh? What's the matter?!
Why are you running?!
They are all persistent!
--Wait!
--They just won't give up!
Why can't you wait?!
Head-Arms!
I said wait, Garp's grandson...
Don't get me wrong, Garp's grandson.
I don't hold a grudge against
your family anymore.
What? Really?
We originally came to this country to
take down Doflamingo's business.
We don't care about prizes!
We don't work for
such a small amount of money!
I was saved by not just you
but one of your crew, God Usopp.
--Usopp saved you?
--Indeed.
Therefore, I have made
up my mind to return you
and God Usopp the favor
by taking down Doflamingo.
Don't do it!
I'm gonna kick Doflamingo's ass!
What did you just say?!
I said "Don't do it"!
Because I'm gonna do it!
What?!
Are you going to disregard my kindness?!
HAJRUDIN - A WARRIOR OF ELBAPH
There you are! Straw Hat Luffy!
Oh! You!
Let's just forget what happened in the match!
For my pride as a warrior of Elbaph,
I will kill Doflamingo and return you guys the favor!
--Now it's you...
--Cut it out!
We of the Prodence Kingdom have...
ELIZABELLO II - THE KING OF PRODENCE
...long been in debt to King Riku!
I will bring down Doflamingo!
DAGAMA - A MILITARY TACTICIAN
Th-That's what he says!
We don't want any prize!
No, we are the ones who will kill that jerk!
JEET AND ABDULLAH
The heavenly light shone down on God!
It's hard to forget after all!
Let me make a confession!
Wait, wait!
ORLUMBUS - A COMMODORE OF A FLEET
If you're talking about Doflamingo,
I will take him down!
"DESTRUCTION CANNON" IDEO
Destruction is my repayment!
SULEIMAN
It's my job to execute someone!
BLUE GILLY - THE LONGFEET TRIBE
No! I will take out Doflamingo!
Where are all these idiots coming from?
Don't forget about me!
Here comes the annoying one.
Hey, do you guys really wanna...
You have to leave the task of
killing Doflamingo up to us!
I can't back out on that!
I need to repay my debt!
What the hell is going on here?!
Okay, how about this?!
We will take down Doflamingo!
And you guys will back us up!
No way! I will take down Doflamingo! Huh?!
I'll do it!
No good... There are too many egos.
Guys...
All of you! That's enough!
I said I will kick Doflamingo's ass!
What did you say?!
We said we'll return the
favor - don't you get it?!
Why don't you shut up or I will kill you,
you dimwitted savior!
That's right! Back off...
I will do it!
I will destroy him!
I am the executioner!
Duty!
Popularity!
Pride!
King Riku!
Our God!
A spear?
--There they are!
--Guys, let us help you!
One 200-million and two 300-millions!
They are the ex-toys who were locked
up underground with us, aren't they?
You're right. They certainly are.
What shameless assholes!
Catch them!
Go to hell! You ungrateful bastards!
--Let's go.
--Okay.
Moocy!
A bull?
I got an idea!
I see a shadow behind the smoke!
Oh, n-no!
A-A bull?
Go!
There they are! Pica-sama, I found them!
It's the Straw Hats!
They came back!
Don't let them get away!
They're riding a bull!
The three of them from earlier...
And four, five...
Six...
Seven!
Wait, Straw Hat!
Stop following me, I said!
Th-They are...
...increasing in number!
I will take down Doflamingo!
Enough! If you guys get in my way,
I won't hesitate to slice you all up to kill him myself!
Don't be so selfish!
We are the ones who'll do it!
No way! It's me!
No, me!
Luffy, what should we do about these fools?
Stop following us! I will
kick Doflamingo's ass!
No, I'll do it!
--How did they get so many
guys on their side suddenly?!
--How do I know?!
They were the competitors from the Colosseum!
P-Pica-sama?!
What's going on?
He's moving!
He's aiming at us!
I'm gonna bring him down!
No, I'm gonna do it! Don't get in my way!
That's absurd! Leave it up to me!
You boneheads! Stop talking shit!
What an unfitting voice!
It's impossible! That voice!
Three or three-hundred,
it doesn't matter to me!
Here it comes!
Count on me!
I'm gonna crush you all at once!
I'm right behind you!
Hasshoken Secret Technique!
Drill Dragon...
Although I'm not fully charged...
A lite version of...
...King...
...Punch!
...Nail!
Damn you!
Pica-sama's arm!
You did it! Grandpa!
That's my king!
We're gonna take down
Doflamingo just like this!
Stop following us!
Shut up, you idiotic savior!
What did you say?!
The group of ruffians led by Luffy is
on their way to the Royal Palace!
However, giant Pica relentlessly throws down
his fist on them and blocks their way!
When everyone thinks it's all over,
just before Pica's devastating attacks,
Luffy finally shows his
stunning ultimate technique!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Steady Progress! Luffy's Army vs. Pica!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!