iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
They freed the toys who had been forced to
labor as slaves
but Doflamingo trapped everybody in the country
in the Birdcage
and put prices on the heads
of Luffy and 11 others.
Cien Fleurs!
Spider Net!
Bartolomeo-san! Hack-san!
We can climb up from here!
I'm gonna crush you all at once!
Hasshoken Secret Technique!
Drill Dragon...
King...
...Punch!
...Nail!
Damn you!
"Steady Progress!
Luffy's Army vs. Pica!"
Pica-sama!
--What a big piece of shit!
--There is nothing that my drill head can't grind!
Run!
These are nothing against my drill head!
I got it back thanks to him.
That was close!
Go Moocy! To the Palace!
Don't get hit!
We're counting on you, Moocy!
Hey! I told you not to come with me!
Get off of Moocy!
Whoa, don't say that! Please!
Straw Hat-san! Please let us!
Moocy! We're counting on you!
Where did he go?! Straw Hat!
Hey! Don't let them through!
They're heading to the Palace!
Outta our way!
Get out of our way!
Sai and Boo?!
In the name of the Happosui Army,
we'll repay our debt!
I'm gonna fight you guys!
Ideo the champion fighter?!
Don't let Straw Hat get away!
You better pay attention!
Destruction Cannon!
If you wanna stop me,
bring out some stronger guys!
What's wrong with these guys?!
C-Commodore Orlumbus!
You're in my way! Commodore...
...Hug!
Shoot Straw Hat!
Next, I'm gonna execute you!
--Why are they teaming up?!
--Execution is my repayment!
Wait, Hajrudin! If you kill Straw Hat,
you'll get a lot of money!
That's just a pittance!
I almost had my pride stolen
but was saved by God Usopp!
I can truly win my pride back,
only by repaying my debt!
--I will take down Doflamingo!
--No, I will!
--No, it's me!
--No, me!
I said it's me!
Cabbage!
I realized my destiny again.
I get a chance to bring down a Warlord.
I can get the better of
these annoying rookies all at once!
There'll be stories about me
in the newspapers everyday!
I'm destined to be a top star!
"Ah! When Cavendish-sama is
on the front page of the newspaper,
it looks as gorgeous as a work of art!"
Oh yeah? How about having me on all pages,
not just the front page?
"That's a good idea!
Only you could come up with that!"
Well, the problem is
whether they can take a good picture of me.
Because I'm brighter than
a camera flash, so...!
--Go away!
--Shut up!
Good-bye!
Now! Shoot!
Blade of Beauty, Swan Lake!
Catch all the criminals and
bring an end to this game!
There they come!
What?!
--Go to sleep, weaklings!
--Do you want me to kick you to death first?!
--You guys are not strong enough!
--What?!
You need another 100 years of training to get strong enough
to repay your debt!
I will take down Doflamingo!
No, I'll take him down!
I'll get all the attention!
Let me return them the favor!
Don't follow me, I said! Go away!
--Back off, idiot!
--You back off, shithead!
Execution!
It's my chance!
It's not your chance!
It's my chance to become a top star!
I said "Go away"!
I will kick Mingo's ass!
What is wrong with these fools?!
Look up!
He's gonna throw another one!
Straw Hat!!
--How annoying!
--I'll take him down again and again!
Don't do it, guys!
Even if you break his arm again,
he can restore it!
If you can't figure out how his power works,
it's just a waste of your energy!
Then, what should we do?
You're a military tactician, aren't you?!
Can't you come up with some tactics?
I'd say...
Run!!
You're a tactician, aren't you?!
Come up with a better strategy!
Shut up!
Retreat is a viable strategy! Just run!
Dammit! This is nothing!
This is it! Prepare to be crushed to death!
Straw Hat!!
--It's impossible to run through him head on!
--Maybe, we should just take a detour!
He's really blocking our way!
We can't get to the Palace
unless we stop him!
Hey! Where did Straw Hat go?!
--I can't see him anywhere!
--Maybe he got crushed along with the bull!
Where are you, Straw Hat?!
What's that?!
There he is!
Yeehaw!
We're on the fast track! Yeah!
What?! He's climbing up his arm!
Keep going! Moocy!
--Can't believe it!
--Is he crazy?! That fool!
He's making a bigger scene than me!
I can't believe it!
Let's get to the Palace like this!
That's right! Run, bull, run!
Hey.
Yes?
--Cut the "Run, bull, run" crap!
--Yes?
--Get off! You're making it harder for Moocy to run!
--Oh, yes.
Excuse us for not introducing ourselves sooner.
I'm Jeet and the big guy behind me is...
I'm Abdullah.
--Did I ask your names?
--Whoa-whoa!
Take it easy, sir!
Hey!
I said "Get off"!
Straw Hat-san...
--Straw Hat!
--He's pissed!!
I won't let you go any closer to Doffy!
Oh! His arm!
Straw Hat! He has nowhere to hide
as long as he's on the giant's arm!
Straw Hat-san?!
Third Gear!
Armament Hardening!
It's massive! We're finished!
We have nowhere to run!
There comes the punch!
He can't ward it off in the air!
It's gonna hit him!
Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Magnum!
He did it!
He's breaking apart?!
Pica-sama!
Yeah!
Those infamous strong men
who came out of the Colosseum are...
...heading to the Palace where Doflamingo is,
along with Straw Hat.
I see.
I knew those notorious scoundrels
wouldn't play by the rules but...
...I didn't expect them to join forces.
Excuse me.
Could I borrow that for a while?
What?
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring... Clank.
Vice Admiral Bastille!
There is an emergency call!
I can't answer them all at once-dara!
We keep getting calls from soldiers
who got blown away to distant places by Pica!
Vice Admiral Bastille!
There is an emergency call for you!
Who's that?! Can't this wait?!
I-It's... It's me.
I-Issho-san?!
Sir! How can I help you?! Where are you now?!
Tough competitors from the Colosseum
have allied and are on the move, I heard.
The whole town is in chaos now
and they're running wild
together! It's the worst-dara!
No, actually, it's favorable for us.
Wh-What do you mean-dara?!
Vice Admirals all over the island,
I need reinforcements as soon as possible.
It's time for us to take action.
Meet me at the foot of the Royal Palace!
There he is!
Show yourself, Kyros!
The game won't be over until
we catch all of you criminals!
I have a family!
I beg you! Let me catch you!
I still have a long way to go, to the palace!
Somebody, stop me!
I can't control my body!
I can't stand it anymore!
This must be a nightmare!
We have to relive the tragedy
from a decade ago?!
I will take back Dressrosa at any cost!
THE OLD KING'S PLATEAU
Guys!
We're almost there at the King's Plateau!
--Hurry up, everybody!
--We're almost there, Usoland!
--I'm counting on you all!
--Okay!
--Are you okay, Rebecca?
--Yes, I am, Robin-san!
What's wrong with that guy?
I'm so pleased!
I'm being helped by
Robin-senpai's very hands now!
I feel like I'm dreaming!
I'm gonna climb up to the top gratefully!
Again, what's wrong with him?!
Nice! How nice! It's so soft! I'm so happy!
And I'll see Luffy-senpai
and Zoro-senpai up there!
We gotta kill all the criminals!
Everybody, hurry up! They're coming!
What?!
--We see a lot of money!
--Yeah!
Rebecca!
100 million!
Nico Robin!
God Usopp!
500 million!
The total is...
700 million berries!
Let's go!
--Help!
--Climb up at full speed!
I got 100 million berries!
Dammit! Rebecca-sama!
Oh no!
--Slap!
--What?!
What the hell is this?!
I'm not gonna let you harm that girl!
Strong and beautiful!
Only Robin-senpai could do it!
Hey, Bartolomeo! Put up a barrier!
--Robin-senpai, you're the best!
--You're not listening!
--Are you okay, Rebecca-sama?
--Thank you!
--We're all here now, aren't we?
--Robin-san, there are still some pursuers!
Once we get to the top, they're all ours!
We're done with the net now.
We better put it away.
Oh?
--Yes!
--Sorry.
Oh my Big Sis-sama!
Pica-sama!
--Only you could do it, Straw Hat-san!
--Thank you for your work!
Alright!
Let's go straight to the Palace!
Yes, sir!
No, I didn't say that to you guys!
I said it to Moocy!
Luffy! The head you just
shattered was just a stone!
What?!
What we're running on is just a stone shell!
We've lost him again?!
Where is he?
I know he hasn't gone far.
He looks pretty pissed!
What?! Where?! Where is he?!
His real body is right there!
I see something!
What?! That's the stone man?!
This is the first time we've seen him
in a human-like figure!
He has a massive sword!
Turn away!
If you can't turn away, stop!
It's too late!
The bull is flying!
After all, his voice is a riot!
Straw Hat!
Here he comes again!
--I'll see you later!
--What?!
Yeah, leave it up to me!
Cool!
Get out of my way!
Only friends of God himself could do this!
Zoro, I'm counting on you!
I'm gonna go kick Doflamingo's ass!
Got it, Captain!
I have business with Straw Hat! Go away!
Our captain has no business with
a worthless rock like you!
I'm all you've got. Live with it!
You soprano-voiced dumb-ass!
Zoro faces Pica, who has taken his true form!
All the battles involving the Straw Hats
and the others begin to intensify,
Law shares his true feelings,
which up until now have been a mystery!
The stunning truth about
the hostile relationship
between Doflamingo and
Law is finally revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Shocking Confession! Law's Soulful Vow!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!