Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
On top of that, he put prices
on the heads of Luffy and
11 others, and now they're being
hunted by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
Is everybody okay?!
We all came to save you!
Diaper Bombs!
Nipple Light Special!
Don't worry, long-nosed goblin man!
They were having trouble so...
I made a net for them!
Why did you do such a thing, you fool?!
--They're coming to get me!
--Was it unnecessary?!
Princess Mansherry, where are you?
There was a room...
There you are, Mansherry!
"Invincible!
A Gruesome Army of Headcracker Dolls!"
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
Oh, those are...
...the Executives of the Doflamingo Family!
Watch out. Don't let them see you.
Okay!
We're almost at the Flower Field
on the fourth level!
If we can see Luffy and the others there,
we can hand over the key to Tra-guy-kun's cuffs.
I can... I can see Luffy-senpai soon!
Luffy-senpai!
Oh, Bartolomeo!
I've been waiting for you!
What? Y-You've been waiting for me?
L-Luffy-senpai has been waiting for me!
I can't help being emotional!
Hey, where are you going?
--What?
--Are you okay?
Y-Yes. I'm sorry to be late.
Well, I wasn't worried a bit.
What?
Because you're my friend!
F-Friend?!
Friend... Friend... Friend...
I don't care what happens anymore...
Why are you crying?
Never you mind.
It has to do with the treasure in my heart.
Everybody! You're getting so much better at using
the Tontatta Airlines' Jumping Service!
--Leo! Can you hear me?
--Yes, Viola-sama!
--I found Princess Mansherry!
--What?! Really?!
The Palace!
Princess Mansherry's in the Palace!
Great! Where in the Palace?
The small room at
the back of the chapel...
Remember?
--Chapel...
--The back...
A small...
...room?
I remember now!
The naughty room!
Yes! That's it!
What's wrong?
I just remembered Scarlet-sama.
Yeah...
My mother?
When we used to go to the Palace,
we were mischievous with Viola-sama
and got scolded by King Riku-sama!
He wants you to stay in here
and think about what you've done.
No! No! Let me out!
Not until King Riku-sama allows it!
What? But it's almost dinner time!
Until King Riku-sama permits it,
you can't eat!
Wait!
Viola-sama!
While Viola-sama is locked up,
we gotta think about what we've done
in this naughty room.
Leo! Cub! Inhel!
But it's good that we have each other!
--Why?
--It's sad to be all alone!
You're right! This room is bleak so...
But...
Oh, I'm hungry.
Yes...
--Big Sis!
--Scarlet-sama!
Did you get scolded again?
You never learn.
It's not my fault!
Leo and those two broke a plate!
You told us we could "break" it!
No! I said you could "touch" it!
Huh?!
I'll come and apologize with you later.
Really?!
Yes. Anyway, aren't you hungry?
We are!
Then, let's eat these together!
Thank you!
We all loved Scarlet-sama so much...!
Uh-huh!
She was always kind and gentle to us...
I still remember the naughty room well!
Thank you for the information!
The Palace is now the enemy's headquarters.
Be careful, Leo!
Roger that!
We'll save our princess at any cost!
Clank.
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
THE THIRD LEVEL - LUFFY AND THE OTHERS
Alright! Those creepy dolls are gone!
Let's go!
Cabbage! Get on already!
Why're you guys getting on before me!
Dodge, Farul!
Horse!
Is it still alive?!
You bastard!
Gum-Gum Jet Pistol!
Farul!
Stay with me!
What a powerful jaw!
It crushed his head!
Don't die on me, Farul!
What the... I blew a hole in its stomach!
You monster!
How could you do this to Farul?!
Blade of Beauty! Round Table!
What?!
Are they invincible?!
Those toys...! Don't tell me...!
You...
I-It's humiliating for us samurai
to get hit on the head!
I'd rather take responsibility for providing
the enemies a net and commit hara-kiri!
You're such a pain!
I said I'd forgive you with just a few bruises!
Hold out, Kanjuro! Bear with it!
What you've done was that sinful!
But, Usopp-dono,
why should I get hit, too?
You two are collectively responsible.
Is that...
What's wrong?
You still looking for something, Viola?
Sugar is awake now!
What?!
Hey! What are you talking about?!
Sugar had been...
...completely knocked out
with my Special Facial Jack in the Box
and it seemed like
she wouldn't wake up for a couple days...
The Straw Hats and the others...
They don't know her, do they?!
Or her ability.
Sugar is totally recovered!
Straw Hat and the others are in danger!
What?!
What?
E-Everybody with a long nose, stay away!
Everyone with a long nose, drop dead!
What?! I thought you'd be hungry
so I brought...
...these.
What?!
They're just sausages.
Don't bring me stick-shaped things!
Snacks must be grapes!
Are you an idiot?!
Turn into a Headcracker Doll like the others and go fight!
I feel bad for Young Master-sama...
I'll turn everyone in this country...
...into toys again!
First, that damn, annoying long-nose
and his clan!
The Straw Hats!
If Sugar uses her ability,
the people and the soldiers of Dressrosa
will get turned into toys again!
Oh no!
Usopp-dono, is it that serious a problem?!
It sent chills down my spine
when I realized Robin had been turned into a toy, too, earlier!
I didn't even realize
I had forgotten about her!
If Sugar touches Luffy,
I'll forget about him like that!
Your friend disappears
and you won't even know it!
I can't take it!
That'll send chills down on
my spine, too...
I won't let that happen!
Can't we tell them through the Transponder Snail?
I've been calling them
but they haven't noticed!
The net-climbers are
getting pretty close, too!
Catch God Usopp and King Riku!
I have no option left now!
I'll shoot her from here!
But, Usopp-dono,
shooting her from this far is...
...impossible!
I can barely see the Palace
with my naked eye.
And the enemy is behind the wall.
I can't even see her!
No matter how tough, I gotta do it!
We'll assist you!
Yeah, if I fail, Sugar will put up her guard
and there will be no second chance!
It's gonna take a lot of precision
to get her with one shot for sure!
With your Clairvoyance,
tell me Sugar's location in detail!
Yes, count on me!
All right, now...
Help!
Halt!
About face!
Yes, sir!
Huh?! Why are we obeying him?!
Armsmorphosis!
Flying Disc Girl!
Humph! Bring it on!
I'll accept the onslaught from all of your techniques!
What?!
Did you say "I'll accept all of you"?
I, the former leader of the Happosui Army, will fight you!
You young squirt!
Don't call me "young squirt,"
you shit-bag twerp!
Shit-ba"g" twerp! There's the...
..."G"!
You called me a "shit-bag twerp"?!
They're...!
We're flying over the third level, Rebecca!
Yes, Robin-san!
The Flower Field is on the next level!
What?
Something's flying towards us
from below!
The real Straw Hats are beyond my imagination as I thought...
Rooster-kun, watch out!
Pop Baller!
Rooster-kun!
This is the Pop-Pop Fruit power!
Oh no! My Yellow Cubs...
Robin-san!
I can't believe there's a group
that is trying to get to the Palace like that!
It's Gladius!
Pop...
Diez Fleurs!
Rebecca, take the key to the Flower Field!
I'll be fine!
Robin-san!
Gum-Gum...
...UFO!
Dammit! If only I had the key to these cuffs,
I could take care of them all!
What? Something's falling from above!
Ouch!
I wasn't paying attention...
--Crest Head!
--That must be Luffy-senpai!
Cien Fleurs!
Wing!
Robin!
Luffy! Tra-guy-kun!
You guys are here!
Nico-ya, where's the key?!
Give it to me now!
--Rebecca has the key...
--What?!
She's heading for the Flower Field
on the fourth level!
Rebecca...
She got away...
Well, she's just one little tramp.
I know she can't do anything
even if she can get to the Palace.
I'll go after her and kill her later.
You bastard!
It's you!
My name is Gladius.
I'm gonna take care of you all first.
--Leave them in my hands.
--Yeah!
What?
Luffy! Tra-guy-kun!
And Soldier-san, too!
Just go now!
To the Flower Field on the fourth level!
That's right!
Robin?!
Rebecca's waiting for you!
Just go!
Okay.
Got it!
Clashing fiercely with Fujitora,
Sabo tries to figure out the admiral's true motive!
Meanwhile, Robin, Bartolomeo, and Cavendish,
placing their hopes in Luffy,
stand against Gladius' vicious attacks with their all their might
and clear the path for taking down Doflamingo!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Risking Their Lives! Luffy is the Trump Card for Victory!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!