Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
On top of that, he put prices on
the heads of Luffy and 11 others,
and now they're being hunted
by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
All right!
Let's go and kick Mingo's ass!
Wait!
What?!
Doflamingo isn't someone
that you can beat just by force of will alone.
You need to cool down.
What?! How can I cool down
after getting this far?!
I'm saying, if you don't,
you can't defeat him!
I promised Rebecca!
Stopping here won't change anything!
Law and Straw Hat have shown up
in the yard...
...nearby the pool.
--Roger that.
--Clank.
I spent such a long time,
increasing their number little by little.
Those tens of thousands of toy slaves.
But that idiot...
...brought it all to naught in an instant!
Not yet, Kanjuro?! We have no time!
It's almost done!
Revenge is easy.
Just touch them with this hand.
Straw Hats...
Now I'll bring...
...your existences...
...to naught!
"One Shot One Kill!
The Man Who Will Save Dressrosa!"
Okay, this is it! It's done!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Usopp-dono.
--It's a work after my own heart.
--Oh, it's done?!
Looks good! Well done, well done!
O-Oh yeah?
To me, it kind of looks terrible again...
Terrible but fine!
I'll use it!
Keep going, keep going!
Don't fall!
Catch the king!
It's done!
That's your ammunition?!
Yes, I'll call it "Bagworm"!
It's the special attack we need
to take down Sugar!
Viola!
I'm counting on your Clairvoyance.
Tell me every move Sugar makes.
Okay.
Can you really do it
with only her Clairvoyance?
I have no other options.
Sugar is already on the move.
I'm a sniper!
Covering someone is what I do best!
Shoot an enemy without being seen
to protect my friend!
Viola. I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Sugar's walking towards those two!
Okay!
--Captain Tank! Hack!
--Yes, King Riku-sama!
Give me a hand! We'll protect Usopp-kun!
Father-sama!
The people are getting really close.
Everybody's confused.
They might come after me, too.
Stop! Please!
But don't hurt anyone.
That's very hard.
But we've got to do it.
Yes,
us hurting our people is
exactly what Doflamingo wants.
All we need to do now is
buy time for the launch.
Old king man, thanks!
Usopp-kun!
Sugar is getting closer to those two!
Now, she can see them!
Keep your eye on her!
Made it!
There!
King Riku!
Viola-sama!
Kin'emon!
God Usopp!
Catch them all and
hand them over to Doflamingo!
--Coming!
--Yeah!
Listen, don't hurt anyone!
Now they're here!
--We have to stop them, too!
--Okay!
THE ROYAL PALACE - THE POOL GARDEN
"Kicking someone's ass" is your answer
to everything!
What's wrong with that?!
It's easier that way!
Neither Trafalgar Law nor
Monkey D. Luffy know me.
It's easy to approach them.
What the...
Sugar came out into the yard!
The time has come!
Excuse me, help!
Why is a kid here?
Dad! Mom! Where are you?!
Don't tell me she's lost.
In such a place? No way!
--Are you lost?
--Don't pay attention to her.
I don't like this man!
Let's go.
It's dangerous here
so hide somewhere.
No! Don't leave me alone!
Luffy!
Everyone, listen! None of us will run!
--Stop right there!
--Father-sama!
Guys, come to your senses!
I won't let you get near Usopp-dono
at any cost!
Stop! Hold it, hold it!
--Stay focused!
--I'm sorry!
Tell me the exact location of the yard!
See the windows on the upper
part of the Rampart Tower?
Yeah.
I see Straw Hat and Law
in the first window right of the center.
There are iron bars on the window.
How many bars are there?
One vertical bar and
three horizontal bars.
The length from the ground
of the yard to the bottom
of the window is about 1.2 meters.
That's about Sugar's height.
How big is the bottom pane
of the window?
50 wide by 40 high.
It's about the size of the ammo...
Where is Sugar now?
She's still behind the post.
Leave her.
Help, please!
Sorry, we've got to get going.
No! Don't leave me!
You can have these!
What?
Sugar is gonna get between
the two any minute.
Get out of our way!
Everybody, stop!
The target is behind the wall...
If I miss, we'll lose Luffy!
You can have these. They're good!
What?! Is it okay?!
Uh-huh!
Forget it!
What's your problem?!
She said I can have some!
Sugar came into the center of the pane!
She's approaching them!
Usopp-kun?!
I-I can't...
...stop shaking!
Dammit!!
What?
Luffy!!
I'll hit her no matter what!
Hey, Luffy!
The seas without you,
I don't ever wanna see that!
Who will save this country?!
You'll see it, Sugar!
I won't let you guys...
...have it all your way!
What's... going on?
I see the aurac
...of their presences!
There's Luffy!
Here I go!
Super Grown-Up Great Black Kabuto!
Special Long-Range Attack! Bagworm!
The wind is blowing from west to east...
Wind force scale: 4.
A slight tailwind.
We got him!
Two...
One...
The first booster, Exploding Star!
Slight ascent, then,
release the rear section.
Two seconds later,
ignite the second booster.
The outer-cover comes off
and the ammo goes horizontally.
It's gonna go through the lower left side of
the window on the Rampart Tower!
It passes through the wall
and goes straight!
Straight to the target!
What?
It trails off a little but
that special ammo is...
...meant to retraumatize the enemy!
AAAAARGH!
Luffy, you don't even have to notice...
If you're all right,
just go ahead!
But, Usopp-dono, what are you
going to do with this drawing?
Can you turn it into a real object?
An object?
Do it! It's gonna be an ammunition!
Sugar-sama!
Oh no! She passed out again!
What?!
They stopped!
--Why're they going down themselves?!
--The toys...
What happened?
I'm amazed, Usopp-kun...
You're such a brilliant sniper!
Viola-sama?
You did it!
You brought down Sugar!
Usopp-kun!
Did he really?! I can't believe it!
--I'm stunned!
--Did he really do it?!
Great...
How are they?
They are both okay.
Sugar-sama!
Let's go!
We're here, Mingo!
They've just made it there!
To the top floor of the Palace
where the decisive battle will take place!
I see...
You did it, Luffy!
Let me just make sure.
Just in case, I'm wrong.
You two,
what did you come here for?
To kick your ass!
The same here!
I'm disappointed...
Luffy and Law finally come face-to-face with
their sworn enemy, Doflamingo!
Provoking the two cunningly and
leading them around by the nose,
Doflamingo launches vicious attacks
against them manipulating Bellamy,
and when Luffy's anger hits its peak,
Luffy and Law strike a
blow with all their might!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Anger Erupts! Luffy and Law's Ultimate Stratagem!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!