Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
On top of that, he put prices on
the heads of Luffy and 11 others,
and now they're being hunted
by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
However, Sugar closes in on Luffy
and Law with her evil intention...
Neither Trafalgar Law nor
Monkey D. Luffy know me.
It's easy to approach them.
Hey, Luffy!
The seas without you,
I don't ever wanna see that!
I see them!
Special Long-Range Attack! Bagworm!
What?
Sugar-sama!
Oh no! She passed out again!
If you're all right,
just go ahead!
We're here, Mingo!
Let me just make sure.
Just in case, I'm wrong.
You two, what did you come here for?
To kick your ass!
The same here!
I'm disappointed...
"Anger Erupts!
Luffy and Law's Ultimate Stratagem!"
What?!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 3
I thought they were giant toys...
...but each of them was actually
made up of eight people.
They turned their own soldiers into toys?!
How could they do that to their own people?!
No way...
Sugar passed out again?!
Sugar-sama!
Sugar-sama, stay with us!
Sugar-sama!!
It was terrible!
We thought we'd live as toys
for the rest of our lives!
That wouldn't be!
We were gonna turn you back
as soon as the battle ended, of course.
Th-That's what I thought!
--Good to hear that!
--I'm relieved!
Of course, we didn't even remember...
...their existences.
All right!
My barrier is fully recharged!
I won't let you guys ascend any farther!
You think you got the better of me
just because the toys are gone?!
That groundless confidence of yours,
I'll smash it into pieces!
I won't let you get in Luffy's way!
I'm gonna take down an Executive of
the Don Quixote Family
and become even more popular!
THE TOP FLOOR OF THE ROYAL PALACE
Bellamy!
Do you care about him?
I thought you two had a fight
in Mock Town.
When did you guys become friends?
Hey! Hey!
When?! When?!
Hey! When? When?
When?! Hey, hey!
You're such a delusional dumbass!
Listen. The era where pirates
dream about things is over!
Forget about the past!
Let go of Bellamy!
That's...
...up to the winner to decide!
This fool came to get killed by me.
Right, Bellamy?
You entered the competition at the Colosseum
to become an Executive of my Family.
But you got defeated pathetically.
That's more than enough reason to be killed
but I gave you another chance.
Which was, if you kill Straw Hat,
I'll make you an Executive.
But you failed again so you shall be killed.
Don't you think so, Bellamy?
I'm gonna get on board Doflamingo's
ship to ride through
the "wild wave" that will
come sooner or later.
I'm done picking on you.
Doflamingo has been my pirate hero
since I was a kid.
I can't betray Doflamingo!
I look up to him!
This is how you take
responsibility, isn't it?
Bellamy.
You idolized me of your own will
and got desperate when things
didn't go as you'd wished.
People can't change their nature.
No matter how far you go,
you're just a cheap thug.
Bellamy!
What are you saying?!
Bellamy has changed!
It's okay now...
Just...
...kill me... already...
Hey, Straw Hat-ya!
Let go of Bellamy!
Mingo!!
Sorry, Bellamy!!
Didn't we agree on this earlier?
Straw Hat-ya! If you show
your anger or hatred,
you're giving the enemy what he wants!
Hold back! Stirring our emotions is...
...his tactic.
If you lose your cool, you could get killed.
Like I almost did in the first battle.
Doflamingo is
an ironhearted, ruthless man.
He's always looking for
a chance to get you!
In the face of your dying friend...
You kicked him! Didn't you? Yes!
You just kicked him!
You idiot!
What did you say?!
Don't listen to him!
How dare you say I'm ironhearted!
Law, I'm not as ironhearted as you think.
I'm pretty mad.
Think what you guys have done.
First, you began by destroying
the SAD manufacturing machine.
Then, you laid your hands on
Vergo and Monet
and kidnapped Caesar.
Later, here in Dressrosa,
you freed the toys throughout the country.
Your associates are trying to destroy the SMILE factory
even now!
I've had it enough already!
I'm smiling just because
I can't get any madder!
And what is worse, you think you can kill me.
It's been disastrous since
you guys came along.
Feels like I'm reliving the despair of
13 years ago!
If that hadn't happened,
I wouldn't have shown up
in front of you like this!
If that hadn't happened,
you would've been here as the third Corazon!
Black Knight!
The clone again?!
Then, I'll fight...
...the real one!
Bellamy?!
Hey, why're you doing this, Bellamy?!
I said sorry for what I did!
Straw Hat-ya!
He's being manipulated!
I'm sorry, Straw Hat...
Please...
...stop me!
Commodore...
...Hug!
A lite version of King Punch!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
THE COLOSSEUM ARMY VS THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
Destruction Cannon!
Guillotine High-Heel!
Your Destruction Cannon can
destroy anything, right?
Ah! I love it, too!
Destruction!
Ton, ton...
Ten-Ton Vise!!
You're my target!
What?!
I'll knock you out!
Barrier-Barrier! Barrier Crush!
Mil Fleurs!
Gigantesco Mano!
Stomp!
Blade of Beauty! Round Table!
Señor!
THE SMILE FACTORY
Come on!
Great!
That's pointless...
I thought I felt a gentle breeze.
No!
--So hard-boiled!
--So cool, Señor!
You're too tough!
You bring it on this time!
Give me more than that...
That won't work against me at all!
I thought a caterpillar was crawling
on my cheek!
--He's awesome!
--Fraland!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 4
I don't know how you know him but...
...if you wanna stop him,
you gotta knock him out!
Just do so! Straw Hat!
I can't do that!
You're my friend!
You're gonna die soon...
Not a bad way to die, huh?
Do you remember
what I told you once, Law?
The weak have no choice about how they die!
That bastard!
We came this far
but you still don't fight us yourself?!
Tra-guy!
I'm gonna kick his ass now!
He's pissing me off!
Idiot! I told you it's our ultimate stratagem!
I also told you not to get heated!
I'm gonna do it now! Gum-Gum...
You fool!
I'll teach you a lesson later!
He's going to attack Law!
Are you going nuts, Straw Hat?!
This is fun!
Room!
Shambles!
...Red Hawk!
Doffy!
Radio Knife.
Straw Hat-ya! You're the worst!
You, too, are...
...from that generation!
Pulling off their tricky stratagem,
Luffy and Law go on an offensive!
However, when Doflamingo,
who's anger hits its peak,
launches horrific counterattacks
and corners the two again,
Luffy and Law learn
the shocking truth of the Warlord Doflamingo!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Noble Family! The True
Identity of Doflamingo!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!