Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along with the entire island.
On top of that, he put prices on
the heads of Luffy and 11 others,
and now they're being hunted
by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with
Doflamingo at the Royal Palace!
Octopus Stamp!
Law's secret motive behind this fight was...
And I'm still here thanks to Cora-san!
I'm grateful!
Because I can take you
all down with this power!
Law and Doflamingo.
Their relationship began 16 years ago...
Knowing his days were numbered,
Law came to join the Don Quixote Family.
There, he met the silent,
child-hating Corazon.
There he is! Corazon!
My parents, young sister,
and everybody from the church were dead
and that idiot is alive - it's not fair!
They won't know if I keep quiet.
Nobody cares...
...if a scumbag goes missing!
"A Celestial Dragon!
Doffy's Stormy Past!"
SPIDER MILES - A PORT TOWN IN THE NORTH BLUE
16 YEARS AGO
They're a Celestial Dragon family!
Kill them!
They're "former" Celestial Dragons!
The Navy won't do anything
even if we kill them!
The admirals won't come, either!
Great! I got a chance to retaliate!
I thought I'd have to bear it silently all my life!
--Break all their bones with a hammer!
--Shoot a thousand arrows!
No! Don't kill them so easily!
Keep them alive long enough
to make them suffer and suffer!
Yeah! No slap-on-the-wrist!
No! I wanna get my revenge on them now!
Listen, you jerks!
My sons were only five
and two years old...
And all they did was cut across the
path of the Celestial Dragons...
But just for that reason,
they got killed!
My enslaved daughter came
home looking horrible
and without speaking a word,
she killed herself three days later!
I was once your slave!
And my eyes...
Because of you jerks...
Give me back my wife!
You guys don't give a damn about our lives!
Because of the Heavenly
Tribute we pay to you fools,
my country was destroyed by famine!
Have you ever been hungry?!
Everyone became skin and bones, and died!
You guys are like gods, aren't you?!
You're different from humans, right?
Then, I bet this won't kill you!
--Doffy!
--Brother!
Dammit!
H-How dare you treat us humans...
worse than worms!
Do you know what it is like to
be in pain or grief or agony?!
Hey, Celestial Dragons!!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring...
Ring, ring... Clank.
What do you want?
Law did it?
Okay.
Clank.
THE HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS - 33 YEARS AGO
Are you sure, St. Homing?!
I thought you'd be the
last person to do that!
You're saying you give
up your status as a god
and reduce yourself to a human?!
ST. DON QUIXOTE HOMING
THE WORLD NOBLE (CELESTIAL DRAGON)
I am a human. Since I was born.
Are you saying we are too-eh?!
That's sacrilege!
Who do you think we Celestial Dragons are?!
Traitor! You've always been heretical!
He's right, Traitor!
I don't care what you think.
Humans are wonderful.
It's way more satisfying to
live as a human.
That's how I think.
--Eek! What did you say?!
--So rude-eh!
Get out of Mariejois now!
We can't take you farther than here.
We're at the north end.
A non-member nation of the World Government.
An adequate house and assets
are ready for you there.
Thank you. That's all we need.
Now, I'll collect
your Celestial Dragon ID chips.
Let's live a humble life here,
all four of us as a family.
We need to unpack first.
Father! Where are the slaves-eh?
Let the slaves put away stuff-eh.
If there aren't any,
let's go buy some-eh.
Doffy. Rocinante.
We have to teach you from scratch.
You look great, Doffy.
No!
I don't wanna wear these!
I look like a slave-eh!
Stop.
No, Father, I don't want them-eh!
I'll stink if I wear these-eh!
Doffy, we're gonna live
as humans from now on.
Humans?
We'll lead a life far richer than
the life in Mariejois.
What I mean by "rich" is
not having so many things.
It's about heart.
Here are your two apples.
Excuse me.
I would like to purchase some food.
Oh? You don't look familiar.
Yes. I moved here from Mariejois recently.
My name is Don Quixote Homing.
What?!
M-Mariejois...
A-Are you a Celestial Dragon?
I've cast that title aside.
I am a human from now on.
We want to become friends with you all.
Hey!
Why don't you fall down on your knees?!
You fools are disrespectful!
You just cut across in front of me, didn't you?
Somebody, get a gun!
Who do you think I am?!
Hey, you idiots!
Where are the Celestial Dragons?!
--Find them!
--Hang them up!
Father, why don't they fall down
on their knees-eh?
They're not in here! They must've run!
Find them! I don't think
they got too far yet!
Don't kill them!
Keep them alive and let them suffer!
Yeah!
Get several centuries worth of revenge
out of that family!
Yeah!
--Wait!
--Don't let them get away!
Doffy!
Father! Why do they come after us-eh?!
We should be thankful
to be out of the rain here at least.
People around here haven't
heard about us yet.
--Let's stay here for a while...
--No!
How can I live in such a dirty place-eh?!
There are bugs inside the house!
The smell here makes me sick-eh!
Find the family!
They should still be around here!
Kill them as soon as you find them!
We gotta run! Now!
I couldn't expect it'd turn out this bad.
I was too optimistic.
Please! I'll do anything!
Just my wife and children are fine.
Would you let them go back to Mariejois?!
If we stay here, we all get killed!
That was your choice-eh.
You can't take back something you gave up.
Don't ever call me again!
You're no more than a human!
W-Wait! I beg you!
Clank.
You bread thieves!
Father! For the first time in my life,
I feel pain-eh!
Father!
For the first time in my life,
I'm hungry-eh!
Eat fast, Rocy!
Somebody's gonna come!
Mother, we brought you some food-eh!
Doffy. Rocy.
Mother!
I'm sorry...
I don't feel quite...
...well...
Father...
Mother is dead-eh!
We got them!!
Pardon my boys! Just take me!!
Please! I'm begging you!
Father!
You idiot!
Look what you've done-eh!!
Young Master-sama, we caught Law!
I guess he suddenly decided to escape.
Dammit! Let go of me!
He was already at the port-in.
They'll start torturing him
for stabbing Cora-san-dasuyan!
But Law is a poor boy...
What?!
Corazon...!
Damn! He didn't die!
Then, will I get killed for nothing?!
I shut Buffalo's mouth
by buying him an ice cream
but he told Doflamingo himself!
I'm sure the blade went through his body!
How can he act like he's fine?!
Law...
I called you in for just one thing.
I decided to welcome you to the
Doflamingo Family officially.
What?
The Family-in!
Because you went through
such a horrible experience,
you got that incomparable,
hateful look in your eyes.
You have the "quality."
He sees potential in your future!
Young Master-sama is a visionary man!
Doesn't he know
what I did to Corazon yet?
Why? He can tell him by writing...
What is he up to?
Even if he sees future potential in me,
I will die in three years anyway!
That depends on your luck!
Luck?
We specialize in the black market.
And we handle the Devil Fruits, too.
And some of those Fruits have
powers that are beyond human knowledge.
There might be a Fruit
that could cure your disease.
Devil Fruits?
If you're lucky,
your life could be saved by
a Devil Fruit we come across
in the three years you have left.
I will train you to become my
right-hand man 10 years from now.
What's wrong?
ENEMY
--What?
--An enemy hurt you?
Did you take care of him?
I FINISHED HIM OFF
That's good. Get it treated, okay?
Did he just... cover up for me?
What is he thinking, really?!
Towards Reverse Mountain in the southeast,
we'll keep moving our base
and expanding our business.
TWO YEARS LATER
We told you our real names!
So? I'm not interested!
You're so uncool! You're no fun!
Even if I have fun, I'll die anyway.
You have quite a lot of white parts now.
I don't know if
I can live another year...
I may die sooner than I calculated.
That aside, if you have a real name,
tell us-dasuyan!
Or I'll tell the Young Master
you stabbed Cora-san two years ago!
Yeah, we will!
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
Huh?
I shouldn't tell that name
to anybody, actually.
I don't go by a code name like you two
so it's just a little longer.
"D." is a secret name,
"Water" is a true name.
For generations, my family...
--How boring! This is not fun at all.
--Yeah-dasuyan.
You guys asked me repeatedly!
H-Hey, let go of me!
What the... Corazon!
What do you want?! Hey!
Oh, he's gonna get beaten again.
Cora-san looked scarier than usual.
What do you want, Corazon?!
Do you wanna fight?!
What are you doing?! Bring it on!
What you said before, was it true?
What?
Huh? Oh? Who is it?!
The secret name "D"...
If it's true, you need to get out of here.
Get away from Doffy!
Law! You shouldn't be around him!
As Law's moment of death approaches,
he and Corazon set off on a journey
to look for a cure for his disease.
After the long, painful journey,
Corazon starts pouring out his heart in tears
which deepens the bond between the two!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Rocky Road! Law and
Corazon's Journey of Life!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!