Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage along with the entire island.
Corazon,
in order to cure Law's White Lead Disease,
took him out and went around various hospitals
for six months.
What are you gonna do to me?! Hey!
You're still a rude little boy...
...and hearing you say "I'll die soon" is...
...heartbreaking...
You... stabbed me... that day but...
...it didn't hurt at all!
I know you were the one who was in pain!
You poor thing!
Law!
So this is it!
It's over, Straw Hat!
Go to hell!
"The Time is Ticking Down!
Seize the Op-Op Fruit!"
Tsk! It didn't cut it up!
It's too bad!
Tra-guy!
I shouldn't be wasting my time here
any longer!
What will you do then?
If it can't be cut by a sword,
how about this?!
It's my turn!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--Hey, Cora-san! Cora-san!
--I like how it sounds. Call me again!
Cut it out!
Don't be shy!
Just pick it up! The Snail!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
It's me, Corazon.
Corazon, you're there, aren't you?
It's been six months since you two left.
Is Law with you?
Doflamingo!
I see. I'm glad both of you are okay.
Have you found a good doctor?
I thought so.
Bring Law and come back to the ship.
We might be able to cure the disease.
I got information about the Op-Op Fruit.
Offered a huge amount of money
by the Navy,
some stupid pirates who don't know its value
will accept a tradeoff, it seems.
The Government must be pulling the strings
behind the scenes.
It's risky but we'll seize it.
Once we get it,
because of the nature of its power,
the person I trust the most should eat it.
You eat it, Corazon.
And cure Law's disease.
Clank.
What do you guys think?
Even including Tsuru who often smelled out where we were
and came after us,
the Navy hasn't showed their face at all
in the past six months.
Six months that Corazon was away.
Are you saying that
he was tipping the Navy off before?
It could be just a coincidence.
I hope so.
I don't want to distrust him...
He's my biological brother.
It's good news! Law!
You have a chance to survive!
Forget about foolish doctors!
If we can get the Op-Op Fruit,
we'd be able to cure your White Lead Disease!
What's the Op-Op Fruit?
It gives you the ability to
modify human bodies!
You can perform miraculous operations
and cure even unknown diseases with it!
I don't believe in that magic crap...
No! It's no magic!
You need medical knowledge!
I know that you're the son of a doctor
who was trusted by the people of Flevance!
Since the time you were able to understand,
you were learning medical knowledge and techniques,
weren't you?!
Yeah but...
what does it have to do with this?!
So, it's perfect for you to eat it!
Me?!
Doflamingo said you should eat it!
A person will die
if he eats two Devil Fruits.
Doffy said that because he doesn't know
that I'm a Devil Fruit eater.
You and I...
We won't go back to the Family!
What?
I decided so when I noticed
this journey would take longer than I thought.
I think Doffy knows that
I'm a traitor by now.
But he didn't sound like it.
He said you should eat it...
There is another reason for Doffy to say
he wants me to eat the Op-Op Fruit!
Doffy...
Since I won't refuse you,
you're looking to have eternal life
in exchange for my life, aren't you?
I'll get killed if I go back!
Listen, we'll get a jump on Doffy and the others
and steal the Op-Op Fruit!
You eat the Fruit!
When you get cured,
let's go hide somewhere!
Prepare to set sail!
We'll get the Op-Op Fruit at any cost!
--Clank.
--"Rice crackers"!
"Rice-cracker pellets"! It's me.
Rosinante! It's been a while.
I've been worried about you!
Hey, Garp!
Why don't you go out for a sec?!
What?! I just brought you senbei crackers!
Make green tea for me!
Vice Admiral Garp...
Now isn't a good time, Sengoku-san?
Get out! Idiot!
I gotta work! W-O-R-K!
NAVY
Humph!
How dare he treat me like a nuisance! Sengoku!
Oh, Kuzan!
Do you wanna eat senbei crackers with me?
Um... Can I talk?
Yeah, sorry. Go ahead.
Do you have a deal regarding
the Op-Op Fruit?
H-How did you know?!
My brother knew it.
What?! But it's top secret!
Cora-san must be talking to...
I wanna know those pirates' activities.
I don't think we can find them
before the trade...
Even if Doflamingo is looking to
steal the Op-Op Fruit before the trade?
Is it true?!
Oh? Hm?
I kind of feel dizzy...
When and where will the trade be?
Three weeks from now,
at Rubeck in the North Blue.
Rubeck...
I'll meet up with Doffy and the others
at Swallow Island three days before the handoff.
Three days before, huh?
So I guess all of the Family members
will wait for the fight there for sure.
That's a good tip.
That'll be it for Doflamingo!
We'll ambush at Swallow Island
and catch the Donquixote Family
in one fell swoop!
You stay away from the island!
I was planning on it.
The list of all Doffy's business partners
and the big names
connected with him behind the scenes,
I'll give it to you sometime soon.
I think it's enough for you to uncover...
the dark side of the North Blue.
Okay. Thank you.
Clank.
Hey, Law. Are you ready?
We gotta sail out...
Law!
Law! Hey! You gotta be kidding!
Stay with me!
Not now! We finally got a chance!
It's not been three years yet!
I thought you still had time left according to your calculation!
Oh no! He has a very high fever!
What should I do?!
Doctors are all useless!
Oh yeah! Let's give him some water!
Dammit!
What am I supposed to do?!
Tell me, Law!
Please make it!
Stay alive for another three weeks!
Give me a chance!!
THREE DAYS BEFORE THE TRADE
Dammit! Why does it have
to be so choppy now?!
Cora-san...
Huh? What's wrong, Law?!
The Government knew that we would die
but they kept making us dig up White Lead, for money!
My family... and the people of Flevance...
The Government killed them!
So if you're a Navy soldier allied with them,
tell me the truth.
That's absurd! I'm not a Navy soldier!
Good!
In fact... You need to realize -
Stealing the Op-Op Fruit means...
...we'll make enemies of everybody...
Doflamingo, the Navy, and the Government!
We'll be chased by all of them!
You better be prepared to fight to live!
MINION ISLAND
Have you found the pirates, Sengoku-san?
Yeah, east of Rubeck
where we'll have a trade,
there's Minion Island which has a ghost town.
Looks like that's where their hideout is.
Diez Barrels is the pirate's name.
Sounds familiar?
Yeah, he's a former Navy officer...
That's right.
Our look-out ship is staking out
Minion Island now.
It's all as Sengoku-san said.
Meanwhile, at Swallow Island
where you and Doflamingo were going to meet up,
there are two warships.
I don't think anyone can see here...
I won't let Doflamingo steal the Op-Op Fruit!
Law, it won't be long. Wait here...
Drie! Booze! Bring more booze!
Right away.
How much do you think
this one fruit would cost?
They offered five billion!
How ridiculous!
Did the Government go nuts?!
Once we got that much money,
there's no reason for us to be pirates!
Right, right!
It may sound too simple but...
...once a doctor eats this,
he'll become a famous doctor
in great demand all over the world.
There was a legendary doctor who ate this
and cured intractable or rare diseases...
...by performing miraculous operations,
they say.
But it has nothing to do with us!
--Yeah, getting money is way better!
--That's right!
Look at this, Law!
This will cause anything I interact with
to not make any noise!
Calm!
NO SOUND!
That face...
NO SOUND
The direction of his eyes!
Stinks!
See? You heard nothing, right?!
What is that ability good for?!
It's not even cool!
Baby 5's Arms-Arms is
much better than that!
Damn! You're right!
I wish I had that power!
But no one can have a quiet sleep like me...
Whatever!
What was that quake?!
Captain! Th-There wasn't any noise
but the compound's exploded!
What?! That can't be happening!
The treasure house is on fire!
Put out the fire now!
What's going on?!
Is there an invader?!
--The lights went off!
--Pieces of glass are falling onto us!
The lamps! The lamps are broken!
Somebody! Somebody put on a light...
Hurry up and put on a light!
Somebody's here!
NO SOUND
--What the...
--Is that... what that guy did?!
I got it, Law! It's the Op-Op Fruit!
Your disease will be cured!
--What the...?!
--Who's this?! He freaked me out!
Where did he tumble down from?
Hey!
A guy in a black coat stole the Op-Op Fruit!
Don't let him get away!
A guy in a black coat?!
It's him!!
Law, I can't take you with me from here.
I know it's hard but...
wait here for a while.
I'll be back in no time.
With the Op-Op Fruit!
Corazon seized the Op-Op Fruit.
But when he reaches to Law,
his body has already exceeded its limit.
To save Corazon,
Law desperately looks for help
but when a Navy soldier
shows up in front of him,
the wheel of fortune begins to spin out of control!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Moment of Resolution! Corazon's Farewell Smile!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!