Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo!
Law's secret motive behind this fight...
I'm grateful!
Because I can take you
all down with this power!
What's the Op-Op Fruit?
It gives you the ability to
modify human bodies!
You can perform miraculous operations
and cure even unknown diseases with it!
Listen, we'll get a jump on Doffy
and the others and steal the Op-Op Fruit!
Coming to Minion Island along with Law,
Corazon raided the hideout
of the pirate - Barrels
and managed to steal the Op-Op Fruit.
However...
NO SOUND
I got it, Law! It's the Op-Op Fruit!
Your disease will be cured!
What the...?!
Who's this?! He freaked me out!
Hey! A guy in a black coat
stole the Op-Op Fruit!
It's him!!
"The Moment of Resolution!
Corazon's Farewell Smile!"
SWALLOW ISLAND - THE RENDEZVOUS POINT OF
THE DONQUIXOTE FAMILY ~ CORAZON
Don't let your guard down.
Our enemy is Doflamingo!
Yes, ma'am!
Sengoku, that fool...
TSURU
A VICE ADMIRAL OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Where did he get the information
to deploy us like this?
--Vice Admiral Tsuru!
--Hm?
We got a call from the look-out ship
at Minion Island!
MINION ISLAND
THE ISLAND WHERE THE PIRATE BARRELS HIDES
Barrels' hideout is on fire?
Yes! Some of us are heading
to see what's going on!
Idiot!
Once they find you guys,
the deal will be off!
Check the coastal area now
and tell me if you see someone suspicious!
Yes, ma'am!
THE GHOST TOWN
THE PIRATES' HIDEOUT
Hurry up and put out the fire!
Captain Barrels!
You okay?
Let go of me!
Forget about my wounds!
It's a five-billion berry deal!
Get back the Op-Op Fruit!
Cora-san...
Good. You are okay.
Silence.
Look! It's the Op-Op Fruit!
The building is on fire and I heard some gunshots
so I thought maybe something happened to you...
Hey! That's beside the point!
You gotta cheer up!
This Devil Fruit will save your life!
But even if I eat it,
you don't know if it will cure my disease...
What are you talking about?!
It will!
--Now, eat it! Here! Eat it quickly!
--What are you doing...?!
Gross!
There! Chew it like this!
Chew it up and swallow it down!
H-Hey, Cora-san!
I wasn't even ready to become a...
...Devil Fruit eater!
Cora-san? H-Hey!
It's good...
You can... cure yourself now...
We have outsmarted Doflamingo...
We won...
What's wrong, Cora-san?
Are you just tired?
What?!
Wait a minute!
You're covered in blood!
Cora-san, did you get shot?!
Yeah, I made a little blunder...
Damn!
What are you doing, Cora-san?!
Oh yeah!
Get better! Get better!
Get better!!
Stop bleeding! Stop!!
--Op-Op power! Heal him!
--That's foolish of you...
I told you the ability doesn't work like magic.
What am I supposed to do, then?!
You... got shot because of me,
didn't you?!
I said it's not like that...
I just messed up...
Law... I'll be alright!
These wounds won't kill me...
Cora-san!
But I want to stanch the bleeding
for a while...
Listen carefully, Law.
We sure did get the Op-Op Fruit.
But it won't stop
Doflamingo running wild yet!
I'm sorry to use you when you're weakened
but I need you to do me a favor.
I saw a Navy look-out ship
off the west coast of the island...
I want you to hand this over to them...
All the Navy soldiers will know what it is
once they see this cylinder.
This one small package will save...
...a far-off kingdom called Dressrosa.
A kingdom? But I hate the Navy...
You're the son of a doctor, aren't you?
You'll be able to save more than just sick people from now on, Law.
Don't get so bent out of shape.
As soon as you finish delivering this,
let's get off of this island!
And let's travel all around the world,
just you and I!
The Navy soldiers...
He's all by himself!
Hey, take this!
Oh, it must be a secret letter.
I bet somebody asked you to deliver it.
Thank you.
I'll keep it. Don't worry.
By the way, little boy,
you sound so weak...
Can I trust you?
Yeah, if you're talking about the letter,
I'll take responsibility and...
I need you to help someone!
H-He got shot and he's dying!
Please! Save him!
I don't want him to die at any cost!
He got shot... because of me!
Cora-san!
He said he's gonna give you first aid!
Vergo!
Corazon?! What are you doing here?!
Huh? Did you just talk?!
Oh no! Don't tell me his secret mission is...
You two know each other?
Vergo... Is he...
Vergo?
He's a strong man who's currently separated
from the Family on a secret mission.
The details of the mission have been kept secret even from the Family members.
You have no business with him.
Don't! That's...
So Vergo's mission is to infiltrate the Navy!
How unlucky!
There are thousands of Navy soldiers
and of all of them, he got the letter!
Understood. Rosinante!
Give it back to me!
Cora-san!!
Rosinante!
Stop it!
You! You! Dammit!
You! You! You! You!
You're the Vergo guy, aren't you?!
The Vergo guy?
So I guess
you're Law from the White Town.
I heard about you.
I heard you two went missing.
You have no sense of propriety!
If you know that I'm your great senpai, you call me...
"Vergo-san"!
Law!
You wrote down
a fair amount of information in here.
If the Navy got this kind of letter,
that'd be it for the Family!
Likewise for our future plans and everything!
Is the kid more important to you
than the Family?!
The second Corazon!
I can't believe we had a rat like you in our Family!
When you were eight, you went missing one day.
And you came back to us again...
...14 years later!
It was enough to be skeptical about you!
But merely because you're his brother,
Doffy didn't distrust you!
You should know what's coming,
shouldn't you, Rosinante?!
Please stop...
Cora-san... He's gonna die!
Stop it, Vergo!!
Whoa-whoa,
you haven't killed them, have you?
They're still breathing...
Just barely though.
So, what do you know?
Corazon was the Navy's spy
and he was with the Family in order to frame you!
Be careful. They must know all of your plans!
Where are you now, Doffy?
I was watching the rendezvous spot, Swallow Island,
from a distance earlier and two warships came.
That's when I became convinced.
My once-lovely young brother shows me his teeth.
And it reminded me...
...that you guys are...
...the only "family" I got!
Sadly, what I thought was true, it seems.
We just landed at
Minion Island where you guys are.
But it was a bit too late...
We arrived and saw Barrels' underlings
running around saying the Devil Fruit got stolen.
It must be Corazon!
If he's there, don't let him go anywhere!
He has the Op-Op Fruit!
Okay...
Tsk! Those fools...!
Oh, did they run?
Well, no worries.
As long as they're in the town...
I won't let them get away.
What's that?! Something's coming down!
What the hell?!
What's going on
on this island?!
This ain't good!
Ouch!
--These strings are like blades!
--They're solid, too!
Damn! We can't get out!
Cora-san, what happened to us...
Oh, where is Vergo...?
What's that?
That's one of Doffy's abilities, I suppose.
I've never seen it before but
there's one thing I know.
We have nowhere to run.
What?
Somebody! Stop me!
Using the Parasite String in the cage, huh...
Yeah, this is like hell...
Cora-san, what's going on?
Maybe I can let Law get away, just him...
I have no chance to survive now but...
will you remember me even after I die?
I'll die with a smile so...
Because... if you think of me someday,
I'd rather you remember my smile.
Law, we gotta get going.
Let's go!
As Corazon gets driven into the corner by Donquixote Family,
he finally faces Doflamingo.
When Corazon takes a chance risking his life,
a single bullet is shot at him
which starts the young Law
on a path towards freedom.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Advance, Law! The Kindhearted Man's Final Fight!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!