Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Law, Doflamingo, and his brother Corazon.
Their relationship began years ago...
Look! It's the Op-Op Fruit!
--Now, eat it! Here! Eat it quickly!
--What are you doing...?!
Gross!
There! Chew it like this!
Chew it up and swallow it down!
It must be Corazon!
If he's there, don't let him go anywhere!
He has the Op-Op Fruit!
We have nowhere to run.
Maybe I can let Law get away, just him...
I have no chance to survive now but...
will you remember me even after I die?
I'll die with a smile so...
Because... if you think of me someday,
I'd rather you remember my smile.
Law, we gotta get going.
Let's go!
"Advance, Law!
The Kindhearted Man's Final Fight!"
No! Don't do it!
I don't know what's going on!
Suddenly, the town is surrounded by
some kind of a giant cage!
We can't get in!
And as hard as it is to believe,
in the cage,
it seems the pirates had a falling out
and they're killing each other!
Drie!
Where are you going? Help me!
Can't you do something about the cage?!
Hey! Don't go!
It's an enemy raid!
It's the Donquixote Family!
Drie!
Damn! Where did that brat go?!
He isn't there when I need him the most!
He's stronger than anybody but has no guts!
Doflamingo!
It was you guys who stole
the Op-Op Fruit, wasn't it?!
If it were so,
I wouldn't have to go through all this!
How dare you let it be stolen,
you drunken idiot!
This is a treasure house-in!
Hey, carry all the treasures out carefully!
This is great-in!
Not bad, not bad!
They've got quite a lot!
Stop fooling around, you guys!
Look for Corazon!
Buffalo!
How's your search from up there?!
It's all burnt - I don't think
there are any survivors-dasuyan!
Bzz...
I picked up a message!
We took a boy into protective
custody at the coast.
We'll keep searching to see
if there are other victims!
They said the Navy took someone
into protective custody!
What are you doing?!
Get your lazy ass in gear and find Corazon!
--Oh, Okay!
--Okay-dasuyan!
Corazon, that fool...
Where is he hiding?
Or has he already dropped dead?!
Doffy. This is our boss.
Everyone got knocked out?!
That must be "Haki"!
Brother, don't!
Brother!!
Why did you also take away the power I had?!
Do you want me to give you...
the strength to take revenge?
We can't undo what you've done now!
I'm going back to the Holyland
by taking your head!
Doflamingo. Rosinante.
I'm sorry that you had to have...
...a father like me.
You!
Doffy!
I think they found Corazon!
Law. This is a blind spot for the pirates.
They'll never find you. Stay still!
Corazon went that way!
Lao G! This way!
--Come on! Follow me!
--I'll crush you-in!
Oh? I can't open it!
Something is on it!
Cora-san!
Where are you aiming at?!
Corazon!
Vipera Glaive!
Sticky Launcher!
I got you!
Diamante!
Oh yeah!
Ouch...
You jerk!
Why have you been pretending
that you can't talk?!
Because I got nothing to talk about...
with you fools.
Screw you!
How dare you make a fool of the Young Master!
It's unforgivable! I won't forgive you!
That's too much, Gladius!
He'll die before the Young Master gets here.
It's no problem!
He was trying to force an all-out war
between us and the Navy today!
What a sinful bastard!
Cora-san!
Hey! The Young Master's here!
It's been six months.
Corazon.
Young Master!
You have no place to go?
Then, do you wanna come with me?
Marine Code 01746.
Commander Rosinante of
the Navy Headquarters.
Donquixote Family, captain, Doflamingo.
I have been undercover
to prevent a future tragedy of your doing.
I am a Navy soldier!
I'm sorry that I lied you...
I lied because I didn't want you to hate me.
Why are you bringing it up now?!
I already...
...knew it!
You fool! Do you think it'll help you
to apologize now?!
Stop telling those insipid jokes and...
...answer these two questions!
Where's the Op-Op Fruit?! Where's Law?!
The Devil Fruit...
The Op-Op Fruit... I let Law eat it!
He's a Devil Fruit eater now!
He managed to get out of the cage.
I bet he's been taken into protective custody
by a look-out ship from the Navy HQ by now.
You can't touch him now!
Young Master-sama!
We heard the Navy said on the radio earlier
they took a boy under their care!
Why didn't you report that sooner?!
--I rushed here even if I don't look like it-dasuyan!
--I'm sorry!
A boy?
What a strange coincidence!
Law is here!
Check into that quickly!
I'll undo the Birdcage!
This is an unbelievably great coincidence!
As I thought, Law,
something compels you to stay alive.
Saviors keep descending upon you
one after another.
Prepare to set sail!
If what he said was true,
we'll sink the Navy's look-out ship
and get Law back!
Don't.
Why would you wanna go after Law?
Why would I wanna go after Law?
If he ate the Op-Op Fruit,
he needs to be educated
in order to die for me!
Boy... You've done tons
of unnecessary things!
Why do you wanna get in my way?!
Why do I have to kill another
member of my biological family?!
Cora-san, are you sure you'll be alright?!
I know you can't shoot me...
You're so much like your father!
You told me you'll be alright,
didn't you?!
Listen, Law.
Pirates can't resist taking treasure boxes
to their ships whenever they find them.
That means if you stay in here,
you'll definitely have a chance
to get out of the cage.
Don't miss it.
What about you, Cora-san?!
You silly...
Doffy wants you and the Op-Op power.
Doffy and I are brothers by blood.
Of course, he'd get pissed at me
but I'm sure he won't kill me.
Calm.
This will cause anything you interact with
to not make any noise.
Alright, see you in the next town.
Hey, Law.
I love you!
This isn't what you told me, Cora-san!
You said he won't kill you!
Law won't obey you! Doffy...
Affected by White Lead Disease,
he was doomed to die in three years.
But he got over it.
He's not the same Law...
...who lost track of himself and came
to visit a crazy pirate that day.
There is nothing he can gain from you
since you're like a child of destruction!
Leave him alone now!
He is free!!
Say it again!
Who did you call a monster?!
Whoa! He tripped
and he's on fire at the same time!
--See? You had a quiet sleep, didn't you?!
--Cut it out!
I love you!
Not yet...
I'm gonna stay alive for a little bit more...
Pull the ship over here!
Because if I die now...
the spell I cast on you
will be broken instantly...
and your voice and noise you make...
...will be heard throughout the island.
Go, Law...
Quietly... without being noticed...
Go farther... and farther...
There is nothing to bind you down anymore...
Whether it's the iron border
barrier of the White Town
or a short life expectancy...
Nothing and no one will limit you.
TSURU
It's Tsuru's warship! Dammit!
You are...
...free now...
Fire!
Sacrificing his own life,
Cora-san paved Law's path to the future.
Law inherits his wish and
to become truly free,
he fires a shot on behalf of Cora-san, who
couldn't take a shot on that fateful day,
aiming straight at Doflamingo!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To Be Free! Law's Injection Shot Blasts!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!