Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Law, Doflamingo, and his brother Corazon.
Their relationship began 16 years ago...
Having a very short time to live,
Law jumped into the Donquixote Family
and with Corazon's help, he managed
to eat the Op-Op Fruit, however...
Not yet...
I'm gonna stay alive for a little bit more...
Because if I die now...
the spell I cast on you
will be broken instantly...
and your voice and noise you make...
...will be heard throughout the island.
Go, Law...
Quietly... without being noticed...
Go farther... and farther...
There is nothing to bind you down anymore...
Whether it's the iron border
barrier of the White Town
or a short life expectancy...
Nothing and no one will limit you.
You are...
...free now...
TSURU
"To Be Free!
Law's Injection Shot Blasts!"
What's the matter? Is that it?
You were just playing
into my hands after all!
You can't get away from me!
I came to see you...
...on my own will!
"Will"?
I told you!
I'm here to settle things
up from 13 years ago!
To attain that man's long-cherished ambition!
That's what I meant when I said
you were just playing into my hands, Law!
The crap that you call "your own will"
or your freedom...
They're all mine!
Shut up!
Cora-san...
There is nothing he can gain from you
since you're like a child of destruction!
Leave him alone now!
He is free!!
When I truly become free will be...
...when I fulfill your dream!
Room!
It's when I stop Doflamingo!
Here I go, Fake-mingo!
Gum-Gum...
Pentachromatic Strings!
Bullet String!
Damn!
Gum-Gum Jet...
Stop it, please!
Release Bellamy already!
You bastard!
Armament Hardening!
What do you think of Monkey D. Luffy?!
I didn't know that you were...
...a Celestial Dragon until today!
Shambles!
What do you think of "D."?!
It's none of...
...your concern!
So are you saying Straw Hat Luffy was
led by destiny
and come to kill me,
who has godly blood in my veins?!
How idiotic!
In some places, there are people
who call the Family of "D."...
"Sworn enemy of the gods"!
I'm a "D." too!
How is the war situation, Viola?
In the decisive battle
at the top floor of the Palace,
Straw Hat has been thrown
down to the lower level
and Law cannot measure up against Doflamingo.
The battles in this country
can be divided into three major parts.
The plateau - location of the Royal Palace.
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
The statue of Pica.
THE STATUE OF PICA
The SMILE factory.
THE SMILE FACTORY
Put out the fire!
Don't do it!
Restrain those who are rampaging!
As long as the battle continues,
the number of victims keep rising.
V-Viola.
How many executives of the Donquixote Family
are left?
There are still many of them.
One of the major battle areas -
the SMILE factory, the executive
who's protecting there is...
THE SMILE FACTORY
...the free-swimming human, Señor Pink!
In the second zone, the statue of Pica,
there is the top executive...
THE STATUE OF PICA
The stone assimilation human, Pica!
And the third part is
at the plateau - location of the Royal Palace.
On its top floor, there are...
...the current king of Dressrosa
and the string human, Doflamingo!
And the chief of staff,
the mucus human, Trebol!
In the Sunflower Field on the fourth level,
THE ROYAL PALACE - THE FOURTH LEVEL
there's the hero of the Colosseum
and the flag human,
Diamante!
The rupture human who leads his underlings
on the third level is...
THE THIRD LEVEL
Gladius!
There are four executives
on the second level.
THE SECOND LEVEL
The half Fighting Fish Fish-Man, Dellinger!
The Geo-Fist user,
Lao G!
The super weight human,
Machvise!
The full-body weapon human,
Baby 5!
There are still 10
who are ranked higher than executives but...
What a nice breeze.
Don't tell me you...
The breeze is hurting my eyes.
Oh! So hard-boiled!
In most of the battles,
everyone's heavily injured already!
The end of the battle is...
...not too far away!
THE ROYAL PALACE - THE FIRST FLOOR
You can't get away now.
Pentachromatic Strings!
Hey!
Just attack already!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE
ROYAL PALACE THE FOURTH LEVEL
Father-sama!
How annoying...
Army Bandera!
What?! The ground is...!
How do you like it?!
The ground ripples like a flag!
Seems hard to even just stand there!
Clutch!
Rebecca...
I let her go on her own but is she okay?
It's a battlefield of monsters
above this point!
Go ahead, Robin-senpai!
What?
I know how you feel!
Leave this place in my hands!
Rooster-kun!
Now, go on!
Okay!
Pierna Fleurs!
What an honor!
I'm protecting Robin-senpai!
I'm like the Straw Hats fighting
at Enies Lobby!
Just kidding! How presumptuous I am!
I'm sorry!
Boy! How you guys attack puts me to sleep!
Get ready, Gladius!
THE THIRD LEVEL
THE SECOND LEVEL
Destruction Cannon!
Missed me!
Ten-Ton...
...Vise!
I'll shoot...
...through your heart!
I was right!
You just...
...did it again!
Lao G!
INSIDE THE ROYAL PALACE
We're on our way!
Princess Mansherry!
THE STATUE OF PICA
Three-Sword Style!
108-Pound Phoenix!
That asshole... He always escapes!
IN FRONT OF THE PLATEAU -
LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
--Run!
--The building is gonna collapse!
Fire Fist!
Are you okay?
Yes! Thank you very much!
Hey mister, thank you!
--Get to somewhere safe! Go!
--Okay!
There's no such place...
The end of the battle is...
...not too far away!
However, even if their battles
against the executives wrap up,
if they can't take down Doflamingo,
the fates of the people who are
in the Birdcage won't be changed!
Are you saying we must leave the fate
of this country to those pirates?!
You're a "D."?!
Is it your secret name?!
You're destined to be here!
Is that what you're saying?!
I'm reassembled!
You think you can stop me
because you're a "D."?!
The Family of "D." is
the sworn enemy of the gods?!
That's just a superstition!
Whoa-whoa, Doffy, watch out!
You're in the range of Law's power!
Injection...
...Shot!
Cora-san was fully aware of it.
If I can defeat you just with my name,
it would've been so easy.
But that was just the catalyst.
I know you can't shoot me...
You're so much like your father!
I'm here...
I love you!
...because the kindhearted Cora-san
couldn't pull the trigger that day!
I'm only here to pull it on his behalf!
With his passion for the
memory of the late Cora-san,
Law keeps launching attacks
with his emotions laid bare.
However, when Doflamingo on the receiving end of
those fierce attacks,
puts a fearless smile on his face,
a horrendous counterattack pushes Law into
an abyss of despair!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Intense Battle! Law vs. Doflamingo!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!