Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
That's enough, Bellamy. I set you free.
Like you have always been.
I'll kick Mingo's ass for you, too!
Wait!
Do you remember this technique?
Here I go! Straw Hat!
Spring...
...Hopper!
Drill Dragon...
...Nail!
Young Master... I'm sorry!
Damn you, unfledged monkey!
You "g"oofy monkey! There's the...
..."G"!
Call me chieftain!
"The Man's Pride!
Bellamy's Last Charge!"
Th-This is serious...
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
Lao G-sama got taken down!
How destructive...
I heard that name before.
The Happosui Army from Kano.
I'll keep it in mind.
Anyone can become our enemy anytime.
Old man! Hey, old man!
Don't die! Old man!
Then, I'll reserve two ceremonial halls, honey!
Ceremonial halls?! Honey?!
For the wedding and...
...the funeral...
Not dead yet!
Like I said, the way you laugh is weird!
Stop it!
What?!
What's wrong with laughing while having fun?
Charlestone!
Who are you targeting?!
Tsk! He escaped!
One-trick pony fool!
I don't like it...
Do you want me to assist you,
Pirate Hunter?
It's you.
My name is Elizabello.
King Riku is an old friend of mine!
So this country belongs to my friend!
My King Punch is a trump card
that I can resort to once an hour.
Did you figure out the stone man's ability?
I did long ago.
Then, leave him to me.
Thanks but I will take him down.
You better save your "trump card."
We still don't know what's to come.
I'll save it as you say!
That stone jerk! What is he up to?!
Hm? What are you gonna do? What are you gonna do?
THE 4TH LEVEL - THE SUNFLOWER FIELD
The ground is rippling like a flag!
How pathetic! Why don't you grovel in the dirt?!
Toy Soldier!
I thought so! It's all connected!
The toy soldier who was crying and screaming
like a fool that day...
That was you!
Scarlet!!
You're the late Scarlet's husband
and Rebecca's father.
This is great!
There's nothing between us but hate, eh, Kyros?!
That's right!
That's why I came here!
Oh, oops... That was a good move!
But it's a steel cape. Watch out!
Vipera Glaive!
Rebecca!
Father-sama!
Kyros!
There...
What are you gonna do, Toy Soldier?
He keeps targeting me...!
Father-sama! I'll fight, too!
Yeah! Fight, Rebecca! I'll kill you!
I wanna see Kyros lose
both his wife and daughter!
Father-sama!
It's okay, Rebecca! Let me protect you!
I want to atone for Scarlet's death, too!
Let me compensate for teaching you how to fight!
I've been living with regret and shame for it
until today!
Since I got turned back into a human now,
I'll never let my daughter swing a sword!
You're okay, now.
Here, drink this.
Thank you very much!
Hey! Somebody!
Somebody! Help me!
My friends are stuck in the cage at the Colosseum!
--Take me there.
--What?
There are trapped prisoners, right?
Y-Yeah... This way!
Luffy...
THE ROYAL PALACE - THE FIRST FLOOR
You got stronger but I got stronger, too!
This technique is far more destructive than
it used to be!
Hey, you!
You're gonna die if you move around that much!
Shut up! Stop worrying about your enemy!
I know now! That I admired the wrong man!
And how pathetic I am!
Forget about the past!
Let go of Bellamy!
That's...
...up to the winner to decide!
This fool came to get killed by me.
Right, Bellamy?
But turning around on the man
that I chose to admire
because I couldn't get the response that I wanted,
is so disgraceful!
I know I'm an idiot but even an idiot has his principles
that he must stick to!
Straw Hat! This'll be my last fight!
You gotta go along with me on this!
Stop, Bellamy!
Shut up! This is...
This is my way of settling things!
There's no reason for me to accept such a fight!
A reason to accept a fight, huh...
Listen.
The era where pirates dream about things is over!
The big hidden treasure, One Piece...!
Those idiots who are blinded by dream treasure don't
notice the treasure around them.
They're misled by those illusions and die.
That's just drivel by losers!
When I see idiots chasing after dreams like that,
I get disgusted!
Luffy!
Get out!
Get outta this town!
Luffy! Zoro!
Forget the promise, beat them up already!
Zoro...
Don't take them on, no matter what happens.
You were like that at that time, too!
But...
If there's no reason to accept it, fine!
Just stand there!
If you still think...
...my determination is cheap!
THE ROYAL PALACE - THE SUIT CHAMBER
How long will you keep up with
this pathetic little revenge game, Law?
So pathetic! You're so pathetic!
You never learn!
Do you wanna lose another arm?
All right.
I won't kill you right off.
I'll take time and torment you...
Trebol!
He gives you over to me!
I've been willing to give you one or both of my arms
from the beginning!
He's really stupid! This jerk!
Pentachromatic Strings!
Room!
Counter Shock!
What?!
Thank you for that one, you shitty brat!
Fallbright!
I'll send you to meet Corazon, Law.
Stop, Bellamy!
Come to think of it,
he's still not coming yet. Straw Hat.
How can you be so relaxed
in a situation like this?
Law!
Hey, stop it!
Doflamingo said he sets me free!
Do you know what it means?!
I got fired from the Family!
That's a good thing! Mingo betrayed you!
So I should side with you now?!
I told you!
I can't betray my principles like that!
Principles that even an idiot like me must stick to!
Bellamy!
Sticky Launcher!
He's still alive.
Hey, hey, hey, Law.
Don't you think you have to give up by now?
You better rest now, Law.
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 3
Stand up, Gladius!
Why are you crawling, slinking around?
I'm very close to total victory...
Now, fight me, Gladius!
Don't push your luck.
What the...
No! Don't tell me you... Gladius-sama!
The whole ground is inflating!
You know what'll happen, don't you?
You've been setting all of these up!
--It's dangerous!
--Run!
Hey, Bartolomeo!
Everything'll blow up along with the ground!
Let me get inside of your barrier!
--No way!
--What?!
If I open it, Robin-senpai and I'll be in danger,
plus, the enemies will enter, too.
No, open it! I'm on your side!
Gladius-sama!
We'll be caught up in it, too...
--It'll be fine. Because you guys are elite, right?
--What?!
Open it!
Pop Rock...
...Fest!
Goodbye, Cavendish.
While Robin and the others carry on
the heated offensive-and-defensive battle against Gladius,
Dellinger, the executive, joins in,
changing the tide of the battle.
When it seems like
they can't avoid falling into a deadly crisis,
the sleeping weapon, Hakuba, awakens and
an extreme-speed battle begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Strong Wind and a Surge! Hakuba vs. Dellinger!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!