Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
I know I'm an idiot but even an idiot has
his principles that he must stick to!
Straw Hat! This'll be my last fight!
You gotta go along with me on this!
Sticky Launcher!
He's still alive.
Hey, hey, hey, Law.
Don't you think you have to give up by now?
You better rest now, Law.
I'm very close to total victory...
Now, fight me, Gladius!
Don't push your luck.
What the...
No! Don't tell me you... Gladius-sama!
The whole ground is inflating!
You know what'll happen, don't you?
You've been setting all of these up!
--It's dangerous!
--Run!
Hey, Bartolomeo! Everything'll
blow up along with the ground!
Let me get inside of your barrier!
--No way!
--What?!
If I open it, Robin-senpai and I'll be in danger,
plus, the enemies will enter, too.
No, open it! I'm on your side!
Gladius-sama!
We'll be caught up in it, too...
--It'll be fine. Because you guys are elite, right?
--What?!
Open it!
Pop Rock...
...Fest!
"A Strong Wind and a Surge!
Hakuba vs. Dellinger!"
Goodbye, Cavendish.
If you were outside,
it would've killed you instantly.
You jerk! If you were gonna let me in,
why didn't do so right away!
I thought I was gonna die!
What's wrong with you?!
Is that how you thank someone who saved you?!
I was covering you before that!
You gotta thank me, too!
What?!
I've had enough!
I've gotta keep fighting!
Let me out!
What?! Now I let you in
and you wanna get out?!
Since you came in, why don't you
stay for a while, you selfish fool?!
Is this an inn?!
Offense must come after defense!
That's how it should be!
I won't let you in next time!
Let me in again when I'm in danger!
You're such an inflexible idiot!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Why should I put up a barrier for you, jerk?!
Oh yeah, Robin-senpai!
Oh, great! She's alright!
I'll be there, Rebecca! Stay safe!
What a cunning tramp! Nico Robin!
I won't let you get in the way
of the top executives anymore!
Catapult Pop!
Barrier-bility: Racket!
But I won't let you get
in Robin-senpai's way!
That fool! He's alive!
Advance! Robin-senpai! Go, go!
Crest Head-kun!
Thank you!
S-She made a gesture with her eye,
a.k.a. a wink!
I'm sooo grateful!
Did it mean, "Good job, Crest Head-kun!
You can become my slave if you want"?!
No no, you're being too presumptuous, Bartolomeo!
You're asking for too much!
Buuut!
I'm starting to feel so high!
Cavendish! You were in the barrier, too?!
Too bad, Gladius! Blade of Beauty, Blue...
Bracchium...
Gladius-sama!!
Bartolomeo!
Barrier Bulls!
The barrier is charging at us!
Robin-senpai! Your eye gesture is something
worth risking life for, to a man!
Stop, Bartolomeo! Can't you see I'm here?!
Sorry, Cabbage!
But there's a reason I can't stop!
What is it?!
I'm feeling... so high!
I don't care!
Feeling higher and higher, and
I'm running out of control!
What are you talking about,
you fool?! Stop now!
I can't!
Dellinger!
Haven't you cleaned up the second level yet?!
Gladius! What are you doing?!
It'll be over here soon!
Come and help on the third level!
Nico Robin is trying to make her way up!
My hands are full with these two idiots!
Ah! Roger! Sounds like fun!
I told you to...
...pay attention!
Boy... You're so persistent, you Longarm!
I thought your body structure was odd.
You have something past your shoulders.
You got a hole in your damn stomach
so why don't you drop dead already, Mr. Champion Fighter?
I can't do that!
You gotta have a sense of duty and obligation
in a man's world!
I don't wanna let down the guys
who got defeated already!
Oh! That doesn't sound like you.
Cut the crap!
What happened to you all of a sudden?
Oh no... You're so persistent.
If you played dead or something,
I would've spared your life.
How will getting on your feet help?!
Maybe I can buy some time.
Until Straw Hat beats the
hell out of Doflamingo,
we'll try to keep you guys from
getting in his way!
We'll do it together!
There is no victory in this world,
that somebody can win all by himself, brat!
So you guys are trying to score a victory
by sacrificing your lives.
That's something losers would do!
The strong don't heed obligations!
I'm no ordinary human, either.
Don't underestimate my Fighting Fish lineage!
Gladius! I'm here!
Where are you?!
Gladius!
Dellinger! Stay on the lower level!
It's dangerous here!
We have a troublesome enemy!
Oh! That doesn't sound like you!
Gladius! Nobody can trouble us
when we fight together...
Dellinger!
What...
What the hell is this...
Wh-What's going on?!
Wh... Who are you?
You are...
Damn! Dellinger...
What the... What has just happened?!
That shitty brat with horns
and all the other enemy soldiers...
He took down all of them...
There's a scary-looking guy
on the other side of the barrier!
Wh-Who is that person?
He looks like the cabbage guy
but his face looks totally different!
This is exactly the same
situation as what happened in the
Block D match at the Colosseum.
I-I can't believe this!
Everybody's collapsed!
Is he the one who did it?
Those outfits are undoubtedly Cavendish's.
But the face looks undoubtedly
somebody-else-ish!
So what-kinda-vendish is he?
I-It scared me!
He was so fast and I couldn't see him!
Who the hell are you?!
Hey! Aren't you Cabbage?
Look at you!
You can't cut my barrier with a sword!
Nice try, huh?! Huh?!
Ha! No matter how fast you can move,
it's useless against my ability!
See, look! When I'm crossing my fingers like this,
nobody can break the barrier!
No! There's a hole!
What are you thinking?!
What happened to you?!
If you carry your jokes too far...
Hey! Who did you just take glance at?!
Don't do anything stupid! Hey! Hey!
Don't!!
Don't go after Robin-senpai!
Oh! Robin-senpai!
I'm relieved! I'm so relieved!!
It's no use.
No matter how quick you are.
You became very evil-looking.
Cabbage-kun.
Do you want something from me?
Falling into the massive trap that
Gladius, the rupture human, set up,
Robin is in an inescapable fix!
To save his idol who is
in a desperate situation,
Bartolomeo who is covered all over with wounds,
risks his own life and
launches a deadly attack!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Barrier-Barrier! Homage Holy Fist Strikes!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!