Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
The strong don't heed obligations!
Don't underestimate my Fighting Fish lineage!
There's a scary-looking guy
on the other side of the barrier!
It's no use.
No matter how quick you are.
You became very evil-looking.
Cabbage-kun.
Do you want something from me?
"Barrier-Barrier!
Homage Holy Fist Strikes!"
I'm worrying about Rebecca
and I have to get up there now.
Wow! Cool! She stopped him!!
Dobin-senpai!
I knew it was too presumptuous
for a weakling like me
to try to protect you!
Seems like you're not gonna stay quiet.
Wait, Hakuba!
I didn't allow you to emerge!
Sorry, Nico Robin. I almost cut you.
So that was Hakuba that
everybody is talking about.
Your alter-ego...
That's right...
He's bad news...
He just goes and attacks people at random...
Not just your limbs...!
I will chop up your entire body, Nico Robin!
I will cut up everything!
Go away, Hakuba!
I won't let you take control!
Shut up! Stay asleep, Cavendish!
You don't know the meaning of this fight!
I'll take care of this!
I'll rip up everything!
There's no point if I don't do it!
Don't care! I'll let them
see a pool of blood!
What?! I won't let you do such a thing!
It's like two people having a conversation!
Does he have a split personality?!
I will!
I will do it!
No, I will!
No, me!
I will, I will, I will!
--I will!
I will!
I will! I will!
He's half-and-half!
Uggh! Shut up, Hakuba!
I'm the only Cavendish!
You were half-and-half just a minute ago!
Hey! I said you were half-and-half!
Okay, it's all right now, Nico Robin...
Why don't you let go of me?
Are you telling me to
trust you after seeing that?!
What?!
Let's settle this while you're at it.
I'll blow you up along with the wall!
You can't just get away by flying somewhere!
Don't think you can get away in one piece!
That bastard!
He'll rupture us along with the wall!
We need to get down for now, Nico Robin!
No! Something could happen to Rebecca
while I'm doing that...
Leave it in my hands!
I won't let him harm Robin-senpai!
Good judgment.
Yes, if you take me down,
you can stop the rupture of the wall.
Pop Hair!
This is nothing!
What's this?! It went numb!
--Those hairs are poison needles.
--What?!
--Bartolomeo!
--Crest Head-kun!
Damn! I let my guard down!
I'm a Pop-Pop Fruit eater.
In other words,
I'm a rupture human from head to toe.
If you do something to me,
my body will burst up
and tens of thousands of
times more poison needles
like the ones that just caught you...
...will pierce through those two up there!
But if you don't take me down,
you can't stop the rupture of the wall.
What are you gonna do?
The explosion of my body will be so powerful
that you can't survive, of course.
What?!
It means, either way,
Robin-senpai will get harmed!
You're a fast learner, Bartolomeo.
Think, Bartolomeo!
What is my priority to protect now?!
That's obviously...
...Robin-senpai's body!
I can't let Robin-senpai fall from there!
To stop the rupture of the wall,
I must take that hedgehog down but...
then, tons of poison needles
will hit Robin-senpai!
What should I do? Think!
Think harder, Bartolomeo!
Doesn't matter if it's up or down!
Just let go of me and run!
Oh yeah!
There is somebody expendable
by Robin-senpai's side!
Hey, Cabbage!
I'll bring down the hedgehog here so...
...you protect Robin-senpai
using your whole body as a shield!
Hey...
Hey, Cabbage!
Shut up, Crest Head!
That bad one is taking over now!
He's so useless even at this crucial moment!
Robin-senpai is in danger from all sides!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
Oh yeah!
Are you coming to attack, Bartolomeo?!
I can only put up one barrier at a time!
That's the drawback but it won't matter!
Robin-senpai!
If I can save you, I won't hesitate!
Barrier Ball!
Blow up as much as you like!
We're in the unbreakable barrier!
This fool...!
I'll give you the finishing blow!
Crest Head-kun! Don't tell me you...?!
Are you willing to sacrifice yourself?!
You idiot!
Fashion Pop!
Crest Head-kun!!
That serves you right, Hedgehog!
This will stop the rupture of the wall!
Robin... senpai...
I did it! I saved Robin-senpai
successfully...
Nice try, you dumbass...
You missed by just a few centimeters...
It wasn't my throat that you stabbed.
It was my shoulder.
I-I missed the crucial spot?!
He was inflated and
I sure couldn't tell if it was
his neck or shoulder but...
Dammit!
You're a Devil Fruit eater, too,
so you know the deal.
As long as I'm conscious...
The rupture of the wall won't stop!
Watch as your friends getting blown away!
Damn! How stupid am I?!
Nico Robin, I'm sorry!
I brought Hakuba under control!
I'm Cavendish now!
But I left half of me as Hakuba.
Let go of me! I will kill you!
I'll let you escape to the Sunflower Field
with Hakuba's quickness!
I'll use Hakuba's capability!
We have no other options! Let go of me!
Trust me!
Which of him is this?!
No time to think!
Hurry up!
It's over.
D-Don't!!
Pop Rock...
...Super Arena!
Robin-senpai!!
I like this barrier thing...
Look.
Both of them are completely...
Huh?!
Why did you stop me?!
It's your own body!
If so, why don't you...
...listen to me every now and then?!
Cien Fleurs! Spider Net!
You stopped Hakuba's sword for me,
didn't you, Cabbage-kun?
You're a complicated man.
No way!
How could they escape that rupture?!
I'm so relieved... Robin-senpai...
I couldn't save the one I had to save
so what am I doing here?!
If it were him...
If it were Luffy-senpai, he would have...
I'm the man who'll be King of the Pirates!!
I'm still alive after all. I got lucky.
Monkey D. Luffy! The Straw Hats!
His bounty went up again!
He's pulling ahead rapidly!
The Gum-Gum Fruit techniques are like this?
Luffy-senpai!
Go home now!
Don't tell me it's... Luffy-senpai?!
Gum-Gum...
...Thor...
Non-Drill Dragon...
...Elephant Gun!
...Non-Nail!
Yeah!
He's so strong!
I wasn't wrong about him!
Luffy-senpai is the man who'll become the
King of the Pirates someday for sure!
Compared to him,
I should be ashamed of myself!
Homage Holy Fist!
Luffy-senpai...
My skills aren't good enough now
but I'll become stronger and stronger and...
Barrier-Barrier...
Surely someday,
I'll become a man who can help you!!
...Pistol!
I barely won with my senpai's power...
Anyway, I'll never team up with...
...such a troublesome guy!
It's quite noisy down there, too.
On an unstable battlefield like this,
even a gladiator from the
Colosseum would totter and fall!
Right, Rebecca?
Vipera Glaive!
Don't!
Run, Rebecca!
You can't defend yourself from it!
Butterfly flowers that divert attacks!
Mil Fleurs!
Butterfly Orchid!
Robin-san!
That tramp...
Robiland!
Your mission is accomplished, Rebecca.
Thank you for delivering the key.
I'll protect you from now!
With their executives getting
defeated one after another,
the Donquixote Family starts
getting driven into the corner!
However, Giolla put a hideous
secret maneuver in motion,
which will resuscitate all the executives!
With this great danger that will turn
the tide of the battle closing in,
the little warrior Leo's
courageous fight begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Healing Princess! Save Mansherry!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!