Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Butterfly flowers that divert attacks!
Mil Fleurs!
Butterfly Orchid!
Robin-san!
Thank you for delivering the key.
I'll protect you from now!
"The Healing Princess!
Save Mansherry!"
LEVEL 4 - THE SUNFLOWER FIELD
You annoying tramp! Nico Robin!
Don't you think your opponents are
a little too disadvantaged?
Disadvantaged? Whoa-whoa...
Are you thinking this is a fair competition or something?
I'm executing them here, Nico Robin!
I think you have that backwards.
Commander-san,
you no longer need to look over your shoulder!
I'll stay with Rebecca!
Thank you! I'm so appreciative!
I couldn't hold myself back from...
…becoming furious!
What are you guys doing?!
Show us mercy!
W-We're just carrying away the corpse of a defeated man!
Please let us go!
He's not dead yet!
No! Even if it takes a couple days for him to wake up,
we want to treat him at least!
Please! Show some samurai-like mercy!
Please! Have mercy!
I'm begging you!
All right! Just go already!
Thank you very much!
Boy...
Humph! He's pushing his luck! That idiot!
We'll teach him a lesson! He'll regret this!
THE FIRST FLOOR OF THE ROYAL PALACE
AT THE BACK OF THE CHAPEL
--Bring Dellinger-sama now!
--Hurry up!
--You idiot!
--Put him on the stretcher now!
Ow, ow, ow...
You guys!
How could you treat...
...an executive of the Family so poorly?
What in the world are you thinking?!
GIOLLA
A ♣ EXECUTIVE OF THE DONQUIXOTE FAMILY
So sorry!
We're truly sorry!
It's forgiven since you
apologize so genuinely!
What?!
No way!
I won't forgive you like that!
I call this work "Penance"!
Oh, it's beautiful!
You all! Put it somewhere people in
the palace can see!
Yes, ma'am!
Anyway... I can't believe the executives
are getting defeated one after another...
Giolla-sama!
I've just gotten word they'll carry in
Gladius-sama soon!
Even Gladius?!
I have to get things going as soon as I can!
Bring it to me!
Yes, ma'am! Right away!
What will she do?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--It's from the factory!
--Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
THE SMILE FACTORY
Oh, Señor!
So hard-boiled!
Ouch!
Señor!
It's connected!
Viola-sama! This is the factory team!
What's going on with Princess Mansherry
and Leo's group?!
I hope the modest and kindhearted princess is
not having a hard time...
Can't help worrying...
Well, things just took
a turn for the worse...
The worse?!
Did something happen to her?!
Wait a moment!
I'll call Leo now so stay on the line!
Leo, can you hear me?
Oh, Viola-sama!
It's Leo!
We're on our way up the Rampart Tower now!
We'll reach the chapel in the Palace soon!
Leo, you have to hustle!
Mansherry is caught by Giolla
and is being forced to use her ability!
What?! That's very bad!
Oh no! Hurry up, Leo!
There they are! The Little People!
THE RAMPART TOWER
UNDERNEATH THE ROYAL PALACE
They're coming up!
Shoot, shoot!
THE STAIRWAY TO THE ROYAL PALACE
Damn! They move like rats!
Bring a bomb!
I'll blow them away along with the stairway!
We'll get there in a super hurry!
Hang on a little bit
more! Princess Mansherry!
Do what I say already!
You little princess!
I can't do it anymore...
MANSHERRY
THE TONTATTA TRIBE -
CHIEF TONTA'S DAUGHTER (PRINCESS)
Let me go back to Greenbit!
I can't help you anymore!
Shut up! Who did you call Boa Hancock?!
I-I didn't say... even a
single word like that...
Don't be such a baby!
It's time to exercise your ability! Look!
Those executives that've been brought down!
The people who fought against our executives,
however...
Even though they gained victories,
they're terribly injured.
If you resuscitate the executives
with your Heal-Heal Fruit power,
all of the enemies will have no choice
but to face death!
There'll be a big upset
in the battle situation!
Now,
use the ability that recovered
Sugar earlier again!
Take out the Watering Can
filled with magic water!
Now! Now!
Now!
I happened to know something.
You people are bad people who
trouble King Riku-sama.
King Doflamingo is lying to us.
So what?!
You're nothing but the Tontatta Tribe!
I don't want to cure bad people anymore!
So...
So cute!
Cute!
Don't get fooled like that!
Who did you call
the once-in-a-millennium beauty?!
Again, I didn't say anything like that...
Now!
Help!
Well then...
you don't mind if something happens
to your friends at the factory, do you?
I-If I heal your people's wounds,
they will harm somebody again, won't they?!
Don't give me lip!
I'll squeeze the power out of you whatever it takes!
Help me! Leo!
Shoot!
I got a hit!
Cub-san!
Cub-san?!
Leo! What happened to him?!
Don't stop!
Go ahead, Leo!
I'll catch up with you soon! I'm okay!
I got it!
Let's get the second rat!
What?! Where did it go?!
Take out the Watering Can already!
That hurts! You're hurting me!
What happened to me?
His wounds got healed!
I think the Little Person's
teardrop fell on him...
Her teardrop?
Oh, so that's how it works!
I see, little princess.
I guess you can heal wounds
with your tears, too.
Then, cry!
Cry more!
No!
Come on! Shed more healing tears!
It hurts! Help!
Leo, hurry up!
Right away!
What's wrong, Viola?!
Giolla noticed
Mansherry's tears can heal wounds!
What?!
She's beating her cruelly
to make her shed tears!
What?!
Princess!
I, Mouji, will come save you now!
It's no use!
We have to count on Leo and Cub-san for now!
The princess of the Tontattas has power
to heal?!
She's a Heal-Heal Fruit eater.
The basis of its power is
healing wounds of living things.
No wonder the enemy wants it!
That's right!
Giolla is trying to resuscitate the defeated executives
using that power now!
If she succeeds, there'll be a crisis!
What?!
That means, no matter how many times we beat them,
they'll come back endlessly!
There'll be... no end, will there?
This is gonna be awful!
--Leo, we're counting on you!
--Cub-san, go for it!
D-Don't tell me...
...Sugar is there, is she?
She is!
Whaaat?!
Turn into a toy!
They're coming back?!
You've got to be kidding!
All of our efforts will come to naught!
That's right!
You can do it! Leo!
Go! Take back the princess!
That's right!
No!
There it is! The naughty room!
I found her!
Leo!
Princess!
You're too late!
Catch him!
Now, come back!
Executives of the Donquixote Family!
Round 2 starts!
Leo!
Outta my way!
You take care of Giolla!
Beetle...
...Uppercut!
What?!
Sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew!
Sew!
Sew...
Sew, sew, sew, sew, sew!
I'll line them up and try again!
There's no need!
Sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew!
Sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew...
What?!
I'll sew you all up together
so you'll never get separated!
What the hell is this?!
Haute Couture!
Patch Work!
What?!
L... Leo came...
Leo came to save me...
He's like a prince!
Art... it... is...
He made it! That was really close!
R-Really?!
Ninja Woman-dono!
No one has been revived
and he finished off Giolla!
Small person! Great job!
Mansherry has been saved!
Yeah!
Princess!
THROB! THROB!
Leo! I was scared...
Princess! You gained some weight again.
THE TONTATTA PRINCESS - PRINCESS MANSHERRY
RESCUED
The same old...
THE ROYAL PALACE
Y-Your body is all beaten up so...
...if you keep fighting,
you really are gonna die!
You just keep taking hits without trying to attack
and still...
you worry about your enemy!
How confident you are!
But I'm sure even you must've gone through
some unexpected event...
...that shattered your confidence!
Even if I die, if I can take you down,
maybe I can remain in Doflamingo's memory
even a little bit!
Señor Pink's life-changing meeting with
his beloved woman,
and his entire melancholic, romantic,
eventful life are revealed
as the fight between Franky and Señor,
each staking their lives on the line, comes to a climax!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Manly Duel! Señor's Elegy of Love!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!