Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Let me go back to Greenbit!
Don't give me lip!
I'll squeeze the power out of you whatever it takes!
Help me! Leo!
Now, come back!
Executives of the Donquixote Family!
There's no need!
I'll sew you all up together
so you'll never get separated!
Haute Couture!
Patch Work!
What?!
If you keep fighting, you
really are gonna die!
Even if I die, if I can take you down,
maybe I can remain in Doflamingo's memory
even a little bit!
"The Manly Duel!
Señor's Elegy of Love!"
That jerk isn't worth risking your life!
That's something I decide myself!
There's no need for us to stay here!
Let's go back to Viola-sama and the others!
You're right.
Leo!
I hurt my leg.
You can carry me on your back if you want!
Carrying me in your arms is also okay!
Here we go again! You're acting like a baby!
If you really got hurt,
you can heal yourself!
You've always been a good runner
so let's just run to get out of here!
Explode!
Then, I'll stay here!
What?!
Here we go! You're being so fussy!
I didn't ask you to help me!
Grr! How dare you say such a thing!
Do you want me to leave you here
for real?!
Bah!
Just carry her on your back already!
We gotta go!
It hurts...
Humph!
Honestly! You're selfish, capricious,
and short-tempered!
You're really a troublesome princess!
Leo's back...
She's nice to everyone besides him.
Why doesn't he get it? Leo...
We have a problem!
They took Mansherry away!
Catch the Little People!
They went that way! Don't let them get away!
Wh-What a shame...
But this is a crisis!
I have to let the Young Master know!
The Young Master includes
Mansherry's ultimate technique in his plan.
Her ability to restore things
in exchange for shortening her life!
Even if something happens
to the SMILE factory,
as long as we have the Heal-Heal
Fruit power on our side,
we can restore it. That must be what he thinks!
If nothing is done, the... the...
The factory will be destroyed!
Señor! Defend the factory at all cost!
Franky...
No! Dodge, Señor!
...Strong...
...Hammer!
Oh! He dove into the ground again!
Fraland! He's gonna do it again!
Dodge!
Meow-Meow...
...Suplex!
Oh! Señor!
Señor couldn't stay on his feet, either…
Neither of them can keep this up!
Fraland!
I know you can dodge that attack, Fraland!
You've taken that same attack 30 times in a row now!
Why?!
Stay out of this, Tontattas.
Yeah...
Señor has gotten the same punch 30 times, too...
Why is that?!
When somebody offers you a drink at a bar,
if you're truly a man,
you can't pull your glass away!
What?! Then, don't tell me you were...
This guy is one staunch dude. So I'm...
...not willing to shy away from his attacks!
I'll receive all of his attacks
and still win at the end!
That's my Strong-style!
I know you can't help being worried
but this is a manly fight!
I'll win it at any cost so just you watch!
I won't let you guys become
their slaves again!
Fraland!
You make me drunker than some cheap bar, kid.
Don't forget what you just said!
I'm not...
...that young now so let me finish
this up with my next attack.
Señor! Can I say one thing before that?!
You're far away! Way too far away!
You know what I mean!
You said you'll receive all of my attacks!
If you're as manly as your
word, take this and...
...try staying alive!
They went outside!
Let's witness this manly fight to the end!
Señor!
If you can get on your feet again by any chance,
it's my loss!
I'll receive your final
attack with my entire body!
All right!
He's swimming through the wall of the tower!
What is he up to?!
Unluckily, today's weather
isn't so good but...
...if I can keep flying upwards,
I can see Russian...
Russian?
Yeah... I have a son named Gimlet, too.
But unfortunately, gravity persists.
I can't keep flying.
Hey! What are you talking about?!
Cyborg, your back is flesh
and blood, isn't it?
You son of a gun! You knew it - that's why...
Now, stop talking!
Or you'll bite your own tongue off!
Even if Fraland is tough,
if he gets dropped from that height...
Fraland!
Meow-Meow Suplex!
Baby...
...Buster!
Fraland!
Oh! He did it!
You gave me your word...
...so it's my turn now!
You got me there.
Sorry, Young Master.
Franky...
...Iron Boxing!
He shows no mercy.
It's like a rain of punches.
It was like this, huh?
Russian...
The day that I met you
and the day that you stopped smiling...
They were both nights of pouring rain
like this...
I wasn't expecting rain, were you?
I'm all wet!
You're soaking wet. What's so funny?
I like... rain.
--Do you like it?
--What?
Rain.
Things that I don't like? Hmm...
Oh, pirates! I hate them to death!
What do you do for a living? Tell me.
I-I work at a bank.
I see...
Is it you? Welcome home!
Boy... You bought something again?!
Let me see it!
Oh, it's cute!
Thank you, honey!
Hey, what else did you buy?
Oh, this is cute, too!
Move!
Honey!
Hey, honey, what should we name him?
How about…
Gimlet.
I love that name!
Honey!
Where did he go?
Oh, what's wrong? Good boy, good boy.
What am I supposed to do?
Oh, please don't cry!
What?
Gimlet died?
A week ago today,
the day you left without notice,
his temperature went up suddenly
and I took him to hospital
but he couldn't make it!
--You're a liar!
--What?
You're a liar!
I called the bank repeatedly but they said
they don't have an employee like you!
Please! Tell me the truth!
What do you really do for a living?!
What kind of money are we're living on?!
Say it!
Hey! Can't you tell me?!
You're not worthy to be a father anymore!
Get out of my way!
W-Wait!
Wait! Russian! It's still stormy outside!
Don't bother me!
Stop following me!
It's not what you think, Russian...
The reason I can't tell you everything is...
Pirates! I hate them to death!
Russian!
Where are you?!
Russian!!
Russian...
Ring, ring, ring...
Because of the rain,
there was a mudslide right above your wife
and she was caught.
Her condition is quite serious and...
In a vegetative state?
Yes, she is unconscious and...
...I'm afraid if she stays like that,
she'll never be able to
demonstrate her feelings again.
I don't know how long
her body can last, either...
If only you hadn't met a guy like me,
you would've...
Thank you, honey!
I'm sorry!
I didn't wanna lose you...
So I lied!
We see that man often these days...
--I heard he's taking care of his wife.
--Oh...
He's coming to see her
everyday bringing flowers...
I'm envious.
--But she is...
--What?
I wanna hear her response...
I wanna hear her voice...
Once more...
I want her smile.
Russian, look.
I found the same bonnet
that Gimlet used to wear!
Don't you think this looks like him?
Since he resembled me.
Once more...
Please smile!
I-I'm sorry! I've gone way out of line...
If someone sees me wearing this...
Once more...
Russian...!
As the top executive Diamante's
merciless attacks rain down on him,
Kyros gets driven to the verge of death!
But just as Diamante, the man
who killed his wife in the past,
is about to take his beloved
daughter Rebecca away from him,
the undefeated warrior Kyros'
unyielding spirit flares!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Stardust of Death! Diamante's Storm of Vicious Attacks!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!