Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
I'm sorry!
I didn't wanna lose you... So I lied!
Russian, look.
I found the same bonnet that Gimlet used to wear!
Don't you think this looks like him?
Since he resembled me.
Once more... Please smile!
I-I'm sorry! I've gone way out of line...
If someone sees me wearing this...
"Stardust of Death!
Diamante's Storm of Vicious Attacks!"
Good morning, Russian.
That's so cool, old man!
He lost his son and
his wife got in a big accident.
No wonder his spirit has broken...
Pink! What the hell has happened to
your sense of fashion?!
Hey! You're trying to be funny, aren't you?!
What happened to your luxury suits?
That's embarrassin"g"! There's the "G"!
I'm going out.
--Look! There goes a pervert!
--A pervert is passing by!
Disgusting!
Don't walk around wearing that!
Oh, please! He's so creepy.
He's still wearing that?
Oh! There's a freak!
Hey! No!
I'm sorry, Russian! I'm late!
Russian...
Hey, honey, what should we name him?
How about...
Gimlet.
I love that name!
Russian...
To me,
these outfits are worth more than
any expensive suit.
Because only while I'm wearing these,
you smile...
I wasn't expecting rain, were you?
I'm all wet!
You're soaking wet. What's so funny?
I like... rain.
Do you like it?
Rain.
Seems like the rain that you liked so much...
...stopped.
Honey!
Señor!
Fraland!
That's pathetic...
What are you thinking of, crying?
Brother.
If we see each other again someday somewhere,
let's have a drink.
And tell me...
...about the woman named Russian.
THE BATTLE AT THE SMILE FACTORY
THE WINNER - FRANKY
Now, you guys! Are you all ready?!
Yeah!!
This damn factory that gave
you Tontattas a hard time!
Destroy it!!
Let's go!
Thank you, Fraland!
Tontattas, good luck...
I'll leave all the mess
up there in your hands...
Luffy...
Help the injured first! Call the rescue team!
Yes, sir!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
Showtime!
Now, let's have showtime together!
You got to show me already!
The image of a father and a daughter
dying miserably together!
Half Moon...
...Glaive!
Kyros!
I thought you were furious earlier...
...forgetting your place!
Did you think that I'm just a talented matador
who can make things ripple?!
Don't think that you'd be the strongest
in the Colosseum's history forever!
I have a solid strength.
The current hero of the Colosseum is
me, Diamante-sama!
I don't care about the title!
But I can make things ripple as well!
Army Bandera!
Father-sama!
Nice try! You almost got me!
Can't be helped!
You've been running around
the country all day today
and fighting while protecting your daughter's life
on this wavering ground!
With just one leg! If you
were an ordinary person,
you would've been unable to move already!
Father-sama...
Viola-sama, how's Kyros-sama doing now?
He's totally exhausted...
Brother Kyros is almost
reaching his limit, too.
Please avenge Scarlet-sama...
You don't have to concern yourself about
my having one leg!
Oh?
If I wanted to use it as an excuse,
I wouldn't have come to this battlefield!
I dedicated my missing leg to someone
I owed a lot to and I'm proud of it!
Okay. Then, I don't have to hesitate
to strike your weak point!
It's too boring for me to just deliver a
final blow to the already-fatigued you!
How about a game?!
The last showtime!
--Those are...
--...Confetti?
That's right! They look
like just paper but they're
actually something that I made to ripple.
Now, I'll undo my power.
Ripple Release!
Spiked iron balls!
Look how beautiful they are!
It's like stardust!
--Robin-san!
--I guess we have nowhere to hide.
Robiland! Please protect Rebecca!
Commander-san, you're in danger, too!
I'm going to be fine!
I bet you're upset. You know what's coming.
Yes, those are stardust that
can kill an entire army!
It's extremely difficult to stay alive!
I'm glad we're at the Sunflower Field!
Mil Fleurs!
You're blooming beautifully, I'm sorry!
Struggle as you like!
Adios!
Death Enjambre!
Flower Umbrella!
That was close!
Oh, she handles it quite well.
Pay attention!
Kyros!
An army that gets defeated by an attack
like this mustn't be that good!
That's so crazy!
He's smacking away every
single spiked iron ball!
Don't tell me he can even
avoid getting wet in rain!
Dammit!
Father-sama!!
Look out for what's falling onto you, Kyros!
How silly are you to stumble now?
Damn you, Diamante! I'll never forgive you!
No, Rebecca! There are still iron balls!
Father-sama!!
This is the gun that I shot
your wife Scarlet with!
You should be happy!
You'll get killed with my gun like your wife!
I won't forgive you!
I won't forgive you! Diamante!
Well said, Rebecca! Don't forgive me!
Fight me! I'll kill you with these hands!
Like your mother!
Let go of me, Robin-san! I gotta kill him!
How long will it last?!
The Flower Umbrella can't take it anymore!
Diamante!!
No way...
This is my fight! Rebecca!
Drop...
...your sword!
For a decade, you...
Father-sama!
Get under the umbrella! You'll die!
...have followed your mother's wish!!
My mother said I shouldn't hurt anyone!
I'm gonna teach you how to not get hurt!
Fight, Rebecca!
She has never hurt anybody
and she won it all by letting
opponents fall out of the ring!
She has never been defeated!
You can't even cut your enemy
and you call yourself a winner?!
Shed your blood, Rebecca!
You coward!
That was a horrible match!
You brought shame to all of us gladiators!
--Drop dead, Rebecca!
--A corrupted family!
You foul-blooded wench!
You've been fighting in the Colosseum
but you still haven't hurt anybody!
Your hands are still clean!
Those are the hands...
...in which your mother
Scarlet's spirit lives!
Mother-sama...
There's no need to bathe
those hands with the blood
of a devil like him after all these years!
Rebecca!
I won't let you wield a sword!
His entire body assailed by
countless deadly iron balls,
Kyros reaches his limit!
But when he thinks of the pain and grief
that Doflamingo caused to the citizens,
and gets filled with resentment,
his wholehearted attack which will
tear up the misfortune
of Dressrosa is launched!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Trueno Bastardo! Kyros' Furious Strike!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!