Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Meanwhile, Zoro and Pica, too, are...
This is Donquixote's country!
That bastard!
Is he going to kill the king?!
I'll save you now! My friend, King Riku!
Wait a sec, you king of somewhere!
Hey!
Give me two minutes.
Is King Riku there?!
Plan 5.
Fly in the sky and chop him up!!!
Let's do that!
"A Decisive Battle in Midair!
Zoro's New Special Secret Technique Blasts!"
--If nothing is done...
--Grandfather-sama and the others will...
Sniper King-senpai! Run!
Pirate Hunter!
How long will you make me wait?!
Hey, Director!
Huh? If you mean Commodore, that's me.
Whatever! You threw a person
like a bombshell earlier, didn't you?!
Prepare yourself, King Riku!
Pica-sama!
Just go ahead and crush up
King Riku and God Usopp!
--I won't let him do it!
--Shoot! Shoot!
--R-Retreat!
--Run!
Stop it!
Your target is me, isn't it?!
Don't create any more havoc!
Tank! Get everyone out of here!
Yes, sir!
Everyone! Get out of here now!
Get off of this plateau!
King Riku-sama, you need to leave now!
Hurry up, Father-sama!
Viola! Tank!
Take everyone and go down now!
His target is me! Go!
That's why you need to run, King Riku-sama!
Please hurry!
No! If everyone else can get away
while he's targeting me,
that's fine!
Your Majesty...
I see! Then, I'll do as you like!
His palm is as wide as a town!
What the hell?
Pirate Hunter, Orlumbus!
What are you gonna do?!
You're really sure about this?!
This technique isn't meant
for throwing someone safely!
Just do it already! We don't have time!
I'll crush you up along
with the King's Plateau!
That jerk!
He's only going for people
who aren't willing to fight!
--You ready?!
--Yeah!
King Riku! You're not a king!
You're not cut out to be a king, either!
Commodore...
Your Majesty, if you won't
run, neither will we!
--Your Majesty!
King Riku! Did you clear up the
decade-long misunderstanding
and win back your popularity?
Why did you come back?! Run! Now!
How cheesy!
A pacifist like you...
...couldn't protect a country!
Did you forget that?!
A country is all about armed might!
A guy who can't destroy
an enemy of his country...
...is not qualified to be king!
I'll pulverize you along
with your cheap ideal!
King Riku!!
Th-The town is falling onto us!
...Killer...
...Bowling!
You're right!
I couldn't protect the
country so I'm incompetent!
I'll never sit on the throne again!
King Riku-sama!
But...
...I tried my best to be a good man!
The nine mountains and eight seas,
...constitute one world!
A thousand of them form a small chiliocosm!
And when I gather and cube that chiliocosm,
there's nothing I can't cut!
Three-Sword Style Secret Technique!
To be a good man?!
If you say I'm not allowed to live
without committing a murder,
I'd rather choose to die voluntarily!
There's no future for a mass-killing nation!
Your Majesty! You're our only king!
That's why the good can't make history!
Because they will die like you!
The Billion-fold World...
...Trichiliocosm!
Good! He got away into the upper body!
Roronoa!
Zoro!!
Dead stones...
Active stones...
No matter how many pieces they divide into,
his main body will definitely...
...be in one of them!
It won't be divided up!
Whaaat?!
There's no ground he can
get away to, in midair!
Come on out, Pica!
How long are you gonna stay hiding?!
By cornering me,
you think you already win?!
You think you can beat me if you
can cut those stones, don't you?!
I won't get cut when I'm clad in Haki!
Haki, huh?
If I knock you off from here, you'll lose!
Only if your Haki is stronger than mine!
Of course, mine's stronger!
You're no match for me!
Do you know what they call people like you?
Frog in the well...
Know how big the world is.
Oni... Giri!
There's no way that it's this far...
The world's strongest!
Why aren't you withdrawing?
I'd rather die.
Kid!
State your name.
Roronoa Zoro.
I'll remember it.
I haven't seen anyone like
you in a while, strong one.
Thus, as a swordsman's courtesy,
I'll sink you using the world's
strongest Black Blade.
Three-Sword Style Secret Technique!
Three Thousand Worlds!
I lost...
I never imagined I'd ever lose...
It's still too early for you to die.
My name is Dracule Mihawk!
Learn about yourself!
Learn about the world!
And become strong!
Try to surpass me! Roronoa Zoro!
I don't have time to stumble over you here!
Cut that crap!
The nine mountains and eight seas...
There's nothing I can't cut!
Go to hell!
Roronoa Zoro!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Stop causing innocent people trouble!
Zoro-senpai!!
Doro!
Pirate Hunter... saved
my friend, King Riku...
But, it's falling onto us anyway!
We're gonna die!!
Help! Boro!!
Your turn!
King...
...Punch!
W-We've been saved!
That brat... He used my King Punch...
...to clean up the stones! How rude!
He'll regret this!
PLAN 5
ACCOMPLISHED
Good work!
ZORO VS. PICA
THE WINNER
ZORO
One of the top executives
- Pica finally falls,
and only Doflamingo and Trebol remain!
However, while everyone is placing
all their hopes on Luffy,
Bellamy stands in his way putting his pride as a man on the line!
The two men now clash,
having their minds racing with emotion!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"So Long! Bellamy's Farewell Blow!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!