Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Meanwhile, Zoro goes after Pica
who is closing in on King Riku...
Commodore...
...Killer...
...Bowling!
The nine mountains and eight seas,
...constitute one world!
A thousand of them form a small chiliocosm!
And when I gather and cube that chiliocosm,
there's nothing I can't cut!
Three-Sword Style Secret Technique!
The Billion-fold World...
...Trichiliocosm!
The nine mountains and eight seas...
There's nothing I can't cut!
Go to hell!
Three Thousand Worlds!
But, it's falling onto us anyway!
King...
...Punch!
Good work!
"So Long!
Bellamy's Farewell Blow!"
Has your sword ever broken?
Well, maybe, several times...
You broke mine, too!
If you were clad in Haki,
it wouldn't have broken,
even if it's the same sword.
You must feel ashamed of
having even a nicked edge.
Every sword could become the Black Blade.
Black Blade?
Until you master it, no drinking.
What?!
No nicks on the edge.
Zoro! Zoro, are you alright?!
Of course, I am!
Did anybody get hurt?
No, thanks to you, Issho-san!
King...
...Punch!
The debris is falling onto us!
--Get away now!
--Run!
Issho-san...
--Now, evacuate the people quickly...
--Y-Yes, sir!
--Run!
--Hurry up before it's too late!
Just run!
Everyone! Retreat!
Issho-san! The evacuation is complete!
Okay.
Thanks to you, Issho-san, for
letting them float temporarily,
we have no casualties.
Luckily, we had set downtown
as an evacuation zone, too.
That's good.
Did you see it?!
That giant statue got cut completely in half!
Does it mean the top
executive got taken down?!
Pica-sama got taken down!
He's that strong but he didn't
enter the competition...
What a humble guy.
That strong man works under Garp's grandson?
He's good!
We managed to protect King Riku in
the end so I'll let it go but...
Zodo-senpai!
--King Riku-sama!
--I'm glad!
What? The factory is...!
The factory that came out
of the ground exploded!
What's going on?!
--Let's go for one more!
--Yeah!
There!
Yeah!
Blow it to bits!
The factory that made us suffer!
We'll never be fooled and
forced to work again!
Hey, hey, Pica got taken down
and the factory got blown away, Doffy.
But the losers will come back!
The factory will be rebuilt!
Just keep being excited over nothing!
We have the Heal-Heal Fruit power eater,
Mansherry on our side!
Rebecca-sama!
Robiland! Are you okay?!
Commander!
You must be Commander Kyros!
Yeah! So you rescued the princess, Leo!
You look so gallant!
You're looking just like the statue!
It's the other way around.
Oh, you're hurt so bad!
I'll heal you right away!
Wait!
You must be Princess Mansherry.
I heard a lot about your power
but there must be a limitation for it.
Don't use it on me.
But you're bleeding all over!
I'm fine. I'm conscious, as well.
Most importantly, I'm glad that you're okay.
It must've been tough.
If you're willing to use your power,
there are people who need
it all over the country!
What?! This is...
Is this Dressrosa?!
I heard so much about the situation
from Leo and the others
but I didn't expect it was this bad...
But looks like they destroyed
the factory successfully.
The battle is coming to a crucial point now!
Inhel and the others, they pulled it off!
This country has been taken over
by Doflamingo's trap.
Whether we can restore it
to King Riku's hands...
...or we let it fall as a
hopeless country again...
Our hope is in the hands of some pirates now!
Pirates?
At the top of...
...that Royal Palace...
Luffyland... Lawland...
Those two are our last resort.
Luffy... Tra-guy-kun...
Lucy...
I just got into the Rampart Tower.
Something bad is gonna happen, it seems.
Sabo-kun, can't you get here? Where are you?
I'm helping trapped prisoners run
at the Colosseum.
That place is too far from here.
There aren't that many things
that you can handle by yourself, are there?
If I could handle it, I
wouldn't have called you!
It might affect Luffy-kun!
--I'll be right out!
--Boy!
Zoro! Are you alright?!
Zoro! Do you need a hand?!
I'm okay! I didn't get a scratch!
That's great!
Zoro! Thank you! I thought that was it!
Zoro-dono! Well done!
Pirate, thank you!
I couldn't believe my eyes
when I saw you cutting that giant statue
with your swords!
Wait a sec, you guys!
You'd better wait to get excited
until that suffocating cage disappears!
It's still there, which means
the key man hasn't got taken down yet.
Stop! Stop, Bellamy!
Stop!!
Bellamy! Why...
Why do you wanna go that far?!
You are...
You are fooled and used by Mingo!
He said he set you free but...
That's enough, Bellamy. I set you free.
Like you have always been.
You didn't run, and fight me to death...
He knew that's what you would do, didn't he?!
I think so! But so what?!
I respect that man!
If he at least recognizes how I die,
I can't ask for more!
Don't lie! You just have no choice!
Because you're a man!
If you know that much, shut up and fight!
But you'll die for nothing!
No, I can't ask for more.
If I'll be sent to kingdom come...
...by another man that I admire!
Straw Hat...
Hey, Straw Hat! Where're you going?!
The sky!
What are you saying?!
Bellamy has changed!
You've changed, Bellamy.
You're my friend!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
Straw Hat!
If you're not gonna accept my
challenge to a duel, I'll just...
...kill you!
I'll kill you!
Prepare yourself, Straw Hat!
I'll end this with this one blow!
Why are you just standing there?!
Take a fighting pose, you coward!
If by any chance,
you know how to throw a punch!
Mingo!
Straw Hat!
Go to hell!
So long, Straw Hat!
Thank you for saying that I'm your friend!
I know now! That I admired the wrong man!
And how pathetic I am!
I know I'm an idiot
but even an idiot has his principles
that he must stick to!
Doflamingo!!
The beast is roaring.
Just come on up here.
I'm sure he'll be surprised, Law.
When he sees your dead body...
Even though he's on the verge of death,
Law continues trying to get his revenge
but after the ruthless Doflamingo's
bullets riddle his body,
he finally meets his end!
When Luffy who witnesses that
horrific outcome roars with anger,
the final battle in Dressrosa begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Law Dies! Luffy's Raging Onslaught!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!