Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
Their allies have been bringing down
the executives of the Donquixote
Family one after another.
Luffy and Law's fight against Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace is about
to come to a climax, too.
This country has been taken over
by Doflamingo's trap.
Whether we can restore it
to King Riku's hands...
...or we let it fall as a
hopeless country again...
Our hope is in the hands of some pirates now!
Pirates?
Lucy...
I respect that man!
If he at least recognizes how I die,
I can't ask for more!
Don't lie! You just have no choice!
Because you're a man!
If you know that much, shut up and fight!
But you'll die for nothing!
No, I can't ask for more.
If I'll be sent to kingdom come...
...by another man that I admire!
So long, Straw Hat!
Thank you for saying that I'm your friend!
Doflamingo!!
The beast is roaring.
Just come on up here.
I'm sure he'll be surprised, Law.
"Law Dies!
Luffy's Raging Onslaught!"
Straw Hat has just taken down Bellamy...
That brings the number
of the tough enemies of
the Donquixote Family down to two.
There are only two left;
the top executive and the chief of staff,
Trebol, and the boss of the Family,
Donquixote Doflamingo!
As Roronoa Zoro said,
we can't lower our guard
but the tide is turning for us in a big way!
Almost...
A little more to go and
this nightmare will end!
No!
What's the matter, Viola-sama?
Viola?
Our force has been reduced as well!
What?!
"Our force" means one of us got taken down?!
Who in the world could it be?!
It's Trafalgar Law!
What?!
Can't believe it! Law-dono?!
I'm sure he'll be surprised, Law.
When he sees your dead body...
A FEW MINUTES AGO AT THE ROYAL PALACE
Sticky Launcher!
You better rest now, Law.
You must've learned enough.
The difference in our strengths
that you can't make up no matter
what kind of cheap trick you play.
You're no match even for me alone.
Why would you want to
challenge the two of us?
Straw Hat won't make it up here that easily.
If he had the nerve to beat up
his "friend" right off the bat,
he could've saved you but...
He's such a naive idiot so...
...it's no use laying your hopes on him!
No use! No use!
You're really a poor soul.
You were born in the hellish White Town...
In your youth, your future
seemed just plain darkness...
Then you met my young brother,
Corazon, and...
...he extended your life expectancy but...
...you've been holding a grudge against me
as if you're the ghost of him
and living to get your revenge.
What a fool!
For a man who is already dead,
you've honed your skills,
allied with Straw Hat, and
even come to Dressrosa...
What an astounding obsession...
But...
...it's over now.
What a worthless 13 years you've spent.
I feel sorry for you.
Your death is inevitable.
Die in vain like a dog!
But, if you're gonna die anyway,
wouldn't you rather make something out of it?
It's meaningful for both of us.
I'm only gonna say this once so listen carefully,
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
Perform the Perpetual Youth Surgery
which is the ultimate Op-Op
technique on me and...
...die.
In exchange, I'll grant
your wish, whatever it is.
Oh, that's great!
Whatever it is?
That's right.
If you really mean it,
it is a good idea.
It's meaningful for both of us.
All right. I'm in!
You're a very understanding man!
Finally, Doffy can have eternal life...
Then,
bring Cora-san back to
life for me, right now!
When you finish with that,
go lick all the butts of the people in this country!
No match for you?
It's no use laying my hopes?
No kidding!
It's you who is not seeing
the picture, Doflamingo!
The Straw Hats have worked so
many miracles up until today.
You can't take down Straw Hat-ya!
You can't take back Caesar from him as well!
Law! How could you say such a thing to Doffy!
It's your future that's hanging by a hair...
What an idiot!
You never stop rebelling against me!
The letters on your back... "Corazon"?
Who are you aiming the satire at?!
First of all, your pirate group
is called the Heart Pirates!
Who are you aiming the satire at?!
You don't even sit on the Heart seat
then why are you bearing
the mark of the Heart?!
Law!
How irritating!
Law... Corazon... This is it...
No one else will succeed
your stupid obsession...
Your curse has been broken now!!
Tra-guy died? You've got to be kidding!
After getting riddled by so
many bullets, he can't be...
King Riku-sama.
If we're in an unpredictable situation,
it's even more necessary for us
to save the citizens who are in danger.
--Yes, sir! Let's go!
--I-I'll go, too!
--I'll go with you, too!
--Me, too!
All right! Let's go down to the town now!
It's not too late to minimize casualties!
Yeah! Even though we can't fight,
there are things we can do!
Yeah! Let's go!
Doffy...
Well, it's okay.
We can get hold of the Op-Op Fruit again.
Yeah, you're right.
Then, all there is left to do is...
Take care...
...of everything.
Doflamingo!!
There you are!
You're late, Straw Hat.
Since I emancipated him,
Bellamy became free, didn't he?
Don't play dumb! You knew full well!
That he wasn't gonna run away!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Spiderweb!
I see. So Bellamy didn't run away.
What's so funny?!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Gatling!
Break White!
Oh, shoot!
Hey, Tra-guy!
Why are you bleeding so much?!
What happened to your arm?
Hey!
Stay with me! Tra-guy! Hey!
Tra-guy!!
He's dead... It's obvious.
You're lying!
I'm not. It seemed like he trusted
you so much but what a shame.
He said you can work miracles.
Can you, Straw Hat?
I didn't think you were that strong
when I fought you, though...
Now, bring it on! There are the two of us!
How dare you bastards!
Gum-Gum...
Pentachromatic Strings!
...Battle-Axe!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Whip!
Armament Hardening!
What the hell is that?
Gum-Gum...
...Spring Bullet!
You almost got me.
Is there something wrong?
No...
Wait! Stay where you are!
What?
--I hear something.
--Wh-What is it?
What?
What's wrong?
No, it was just my imagination.
No, it is moving!
--Oh, please...
--The wall of strings is...
Shrinking!
I'll let you follow Law in death shortly.
Let's bring an end to this game.
Mingo!!
--Wait.
--What?
Listen carefully, Straw Hat-ya.
Doflamingo's cold-blooded extermination
plan is finally put in motion!
The shrinking wall of strings cuts up Dressrosa!
There is only one hour left!
When it seems like every
hope has been dashed,
a tenacious attack that takes a
one-and-only chance, rings out!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Blade of Tenacity! The
Gamma Knife Counterattack!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!