Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current king Doflamingo's agenda, they were
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Gum-Gum...
Go to hell! Together with Law!
Shambles!
You're the one that'll perish! Doflamingo!
This operation will destroy you
from inside your body!
Gamma Knife!
Doffy! You're a king!
Don't fall on your knees anymore!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp!
Doffy!!
That bastard is my responsibility...!
Room!
Cora-san...
I finally can attain your ambition!
It's over. Doflamingo!
"A Collision of Haki!
Luffy vs. Doflamingo!"
You have no chance to survive now.
The Gamma Knife destroys your internal organs
without an external wound.
When a doctor says so, there's no doubt!
Law!
You fool! What did you do to Doffy?!
Don't get in his way!
You just...
...gathered up people who were convenient for you
and called it a Family.
And your biological younger brother, Cora-san,
who tried to stop your rampage, got...
He is free!!
Yeah, that was a shame...
He betrayed me and
even pointed a gun at me...
You knew!
That Cora-san wasn't gonna pull the trigger!
I could pull it.
I bet so.
You're the same as me.
I wanna destroy everything that I see!
Towns, houses, people...
I wanna destroy them all!
Yeah, whatever you say.
But on that day,
...you were the one who was supposed to die!
Law, I have something to say
that's as evil as you think I am.
Corazon was a drag and an eyesore to me.
He started to have a cheesy sense of justice
and let out his worthless feelings.
He was an incompetent man.
When I killed him that day,
it was a great load off my mind...
Counter Shock!
Go to hell, you demon!
Doffy!
Tra-guy!
Hey! Stay with me!
Oh, Straw Hat-ya...
You don't have to worry about me.
More importantly, how's Doflamingo...?
That's our king!
H-How is it possible?
If I have enough time,
I can apply first aid to myself.
Inside my body now,
strings are repairing my inner organs.
What?!
How smartly you can use your ability
is important.
It's a bit different from recovery, though.
Thank you for your suicide attack.
What?!
Sticky-Sticky Chain!
Stop!
Stick-Stickem!
I can stop your breath at least.
Damn!
Damn...
How dare you stop me?!
I was just looking to smash up Law's head!
What?!
The Color of the Supreme King, colliding?!
He uses it, too?!
What?! What the hell is going on?!
Straw Hat-ya...
He can use it as I thought!
You're the man who was chosen by heaven!
Do you want me to give you...
the strength to take revenge?
People who I wanna kill...
There are tons of them!
Straw Hat!
You're not good enough
to compete with Doffy!
What happened to you?
--Don't forgive them!
--Kill them!
Great! I got a chance to retaliate!
I thought I'd have to bear it silently all my life!
--Doffy!
--Brother!
Help!
My children are innocent!
Aim all your arrows at me!
Please! Don't harm my children!
It hurts, Father!
I can't take it anymore!
I'll get even...
I'll get even with you idiots!
Brother...
I'm not gonna die!
I'm gonna survive no matter what you do to me
and I will...
I will come kill
every single one of you jerks!!
Wh-Wh...
What?!
Everyone got knocked out?!
Yeah.
That must be "Haki"!
Haki?
And on top of that,
that's the Haki of the Color of the Supreme King!
That's the proof that
you have the quality of a king.
Doflamingo!
You're the man who was chosen by heaven!
Now,
if you're a man,
you'd better put yourself to a test.
Are there any people who you wanna kill?
Do you want me to give you...
the strength to take revenge?
People who I wanna kill...
There are tons of them!
Why did you also take away the power I had?!
We can't undo what you've done now!
I'm going back to the Holyland
by taking your head!
Doflamingo. Rosinante.
I'm sorry that you had to have...
...a father like me.
Doffy's different!
He's of a totally different caliber!
His birth nurtured madness in him!
His fate fed him anger!
And they changed this man
into a perfect demon!
No less, the ultimate evil!
Doffy is...
...the true king who was chosen by heaven!
So what?!
Mingo!!
Doffy is a charismatic evil.
Go to hell!
Mingo!!
Gum-Gum...
Doffy's madness will...
...destroy everything!
...Eagle...
...Bazooka!
Athlete!
Don't get in my way!
Straw Hat!
Luffy clashes with Trebol,
the last top executive standing!
However, none of his attacks with Haki of the Color of Arms work against Trebol,
and he gets driven into a corner!
When Trebol exercises his secret technique which will
burn up everything, Luffy and Law are pushed to the extremes!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Unassailable! The Stunning Secret of Trebol!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!