Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
H-How is it possible?
Inside my body now,
strings are repairing my inner organs.
How smartly you can use your ability is important.
What?! The Color of the Supreme King, colliding?!
He uses it, too?!
Go to hell!
Mingo!!
Gum-Gum...
Doffy's madness will...
...destroy everything!
...Eagle...
...Bazooka!
Athlete!
Don't get in my way!
Straw Hat!
"Unassailable!
The Stunning Secret of Trebol!"
Stick-Stickem!
What's this?!
You idiot! Don't think a weakling like you can beat Doffy!
Damn! Let go of me! You bastard!
Just wait here struggling!
We'll kill you in turn!
First,
Law, we'll start with you.
Now, Doffy, I'll stall Straw Hat.
Crush Law's head while you have a chance.
Hey! Don't do it, Mingo!
Fight me! Tra-guy can't move even one millimeter now!
I said "In turn"...
Shut up! This jerk is so icky!
I'm sticky!
Oh, you got me...
...or not! Not a chance!
It's no use!
What?! Why's that?!
I thought I could hit a Logia eater with the Color of Arms!
Well, now, do you think my power is the Logia type?
Either way, that crap doesn't work against me!
You rubber idiot!
Straw Hat-ya!
He's right - it's no use.
He's a papier-mâché bastard!
P-P-Papier-mâché?!
More than anything,
I didn't want to sit on the Heart throne
because I didn't want to be grouped together with idiots like them!
I-Idiots?!
Did you call us top executives idiots?!
Seems like you still can talk.
What're you saying, you half-dead moron?!
We top executives are
the foundation of the Family!
I'll never forgive anyone for making fun of us!
Stick-Stickem...
...Launcher!
Stop! Tra-guy can't even move!
Law, you bastard!
I gotta teach this brat something!
Move, Doffy!
Listen, Law!
Doffy will always be the absolute king!
But...
...there is no gap between him
and us current top executives!
That's because...
...one day 30-something years ago,
we four picked up this immense gift
that fell from heaven!
We gave him power and brought him up
to be a charismatic force for evil!
Everyone got knocked out?!
That must be "Haki"!
The Haki of the Color of the Supreme King!
You're the man who was chosen by heaven!
Do you want me to give you...
the strength to take revenge?
I'm going back to the Holyland
by taking your head!
You almost got killed
in the Holyland of Mariejois?!
Even bringing them your father's head?!
But I'm glad that you came back alive!
It's a miracle!
Doffy...
Doffy, you have the quality of a king.
We swear to support you in everything.
Doffy, in return, let us have a dream!
Now, Doffy...
Hm? What's the matter, Doffy?
What is that wound?
Some hoodlum did this. I wish he'd die.
Okay. I got it.
What the hell do you want?
Hey, hey, is it you who hurt Doffy?
Oh, that brat!
I just teased him a little bit!
He just hurt that kid a little bit!
Ow! Ow!
What's wrong with you bastards?!
We are the Donquixote Family.
No... You got to be kidding!
Don't do it!
He passed out!
Wh-What's with this brat?!
Doffy likes your turf.
We need you guys to go away.
P-Please don't kill me...
Help!
Adios!
What happened?!
Did somebody hurt you again?
No, I just fell because the road was uneven.
An uneven road?! Which town was it?
Oh, I see. This needs to be fixed.
It's a butterfly!
The Doflamingo Family!
Listen, Doffy.
You're a king.
No one must be allowed to rebel against you.
You're the man who will...
...become the king of the sea someday!
We set up Doffy as a king
and showed our dignity to our subordinates!
But Doffy and we four have been thinking of
the Family equally and
brought it to its present level!
Like a true family!
Understand, Law?!
Do you remember that
my mucus is flammable?
I can shut your annoying mouth up instantly...
A true family?
Equally?
It's only you guys who are thinking
like that, Trebol.
His own ambition is everything to him.
He doesn't give a damn about you guys!
What... What did you say?!
How pathetic.
To me, even you, who acts like you're the chief of staff, only look like...
...Doflamingo's foolish puppet!
F-F-Foolish puppet?!
I won't forgive you!
Hey! Don't fall for it, Trebol!
Room!
You're inside the Room!
This brat was barely alive already but I
restrained his movement with my mucus in addition!
What can he do in these circumstances?!
I'm not gonna blow it up!
I'll shut your smart-ass mouth
in the cruelest way I can think of!
Now, open your mouth!
Stop!
You insolent brat!
I'll shove this into your throat
and impale you!
I'm not gonna blow it up!
I'll shut your smart-ass mouth
in the cruelest way I can think of!
Now, open your mouth!
Stop!
You insolent brat!
I'll shove this into your throat
and impale you!
Stop!
I'm a captain of a ship, too!
If I leave both you and Doflamingo
in Straw Hat-ya's hands,
I'll lose my prestige!
You can't even move! What can you do?!
You damn worm!
Go to hell!
Takt!
What're you...?!
The arm?!
Sterben Blade!
Something wrong, Leo?
THE SMILE FACTORY
What's the matter, you guys?
You turned to the town all of a sudden.
I-I don't know why but...
...it feels like a huge load has been
lifted off my chest...
Hey! We don't have time for that nonsense!
We finished destroying the factory!
Now let's run from the approaching Birdcage!
We gotta hurry or...
What?! What happened?!
Blood! He got slashed and bled!
What?! What the hell is that?!
A slim guy came out of the mucus!
This is why my punch got through his body!
Damn you, Law...
What an idiot!
I can't believe you used...
...your disembodied arm...!
How annoying...!
When it comes to this...
Law...
You die with me!
Oh no! He's gonna set fire!
I'll take you along!
The Royal Palace burst into flames!
What's going on?!
Wh-What happened this time?!
Luffy!
Hey, Viola! What's going on at the Royal Palace?!
One of the executives, Trebol got defeated!
Is Luffy okay?!
Doflamingo!
Straw Hat!
--Great! He's alive!
--Yes!
It makes Doflamingo the only one remaining!
Luffy! Doflamingo!
Luffyland!
Is he all right?
We got to back him up somehow!
Yeah!
You'd better not do anything.
You might give him trouble to be honest.
Look! Even Trafalgar Law who has
the same title of Warlord as Doflamingo, is...
…in quite bad shape!
Lawland!
Luffy!
Luffy! Hand me Tra-guy-kun!
Robin! That'll help!
Take him! Tra-guy cornered Mingo enough already!
Oh no! His arm...!
Cien Fleurs! Spider Net!
Lawland's arm is...
How could they do this?!
Tra-guy-kun, stay with me!
Nico Robin!
Don't do anything unnecessary!
He's still breathing.
He hasn't been dismissed yet.
Doflamingo!
That jerk! He's still going for Tra-guy!
Here's a finisher!
Gum-Gum...
Bullet String!
...Hawk Whip!
Damn!
Robiland!
Tra-guy! Robin!
Carrying on Law's ambition and with everybody's hopes
on his shoulders, Luffy fights!
Doflamingo's powerful techniques squarely target him!
Red Hawk blasts!
While time is ticking away until all people
in Dressrosa get wiped out,
the all-out decisive battle
between the two now begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Anger Erupts! I Will Take Everything upon Myself!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!