Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
The executives of the Donquixote
Family have been taken down
one after another, after hard
battles, by the Straw Hats,
and finally, there is only Doflamingo left!
The time has come for a one-on-one duel
between Luffy and Doflamingo
that shakes up Dressrosa!
I'm a captain of a ship, too!
If I leave both you and Doflamingo
in Straw Hat-ya's hands,
I'll lose my prestige!
You can't even move! What can you do?!
You damn worm!
Go to hell!
Takt!
What're you...?!
The arm?!
Sterben Blade!
I can't believe you used...
...your disembodied arm...!
How annoying...!
When it comes to this...
Law...
You die with me!
Oh no! He's gonna set fire!
I'll take you along!
Look! Even Trafalgar Law who has
the same title of Warlord
as Doflamingo, is...
...in quite bad shape!
Lawland!
Luffy! Hand me Tra-guy-kun!
Robin! That'll help!
Take him! Tra-guy cornered
Mingo enough already!
Oh no! His arm...!
Cien Fleurs! Spider Net!
Lawland's arm is...
How could they do this?!
Tra-guy-kun, stay with me!
Nico Robin!
Don't do anything unnecessary!
He's still breathing.
He hasn't been dismissed yet.
Doflamingo!
That jerk! He's still going for Tra-guy!
Here's a finisher!
Gum-Gum...
Bullet String!
...Hawk Whip!
Damn!
Robiland!
Tra-guy! Robin!
"Anger Erupts!
I Will Take Everything upon Myself!"
Precious Metal Axe!
Cabbage-kun!
I'm sorry. I'd been sleeping
until a while ago.
Hasn't this all been settled yet, Straw Hat?!
Cabbage!
Take everyone and get off of this plateau!
No way!
Since I stand before Doflamingo here,
I wanna land at least one blow, too!
I leave everybody in your hands!
L...
Leave them in my hands?!
Trust...
Respect...
Popularity!
Straw Hat is my fan.
My fan is asking me a favor!
I can't turn it down!
I know Bartolomeo is on the lower level!
Let's go down there now using his ability!
Can you treat him somehow, Leo?!
The cut is ragged!
If I can manage to sew them together...
Then,
I can heal him with my Watering Can!
Thank you, Princess Mansherry!
In any case, we'd better
go down now as Lucy said!
That was kick-ass!
How he took down Pica was awesome!
Hey, Bartolomeo!
Make stairs with your barrier!
Zoro-senpai!
Forever!
Are you even listening, you fool!
I don't take orders from
strange, dual-natured creeps!
Make stairs for Nico Robin
and the others! Hurry up!
Oh, is it for Robin-senpai?!
That's enough.
Straw Hat.
Law is suffering because he can't die.
It's better to put him out of his misery.
If that's what you wanna do,
do it after you beat me!
Seems like you're quite wasted away already.
So are you!
I don't think such destructive attacks by Tra-guy
would leave you unscathed!
Bazooka!
You surely move fast but...
...you're lacking heaviness!
Overheat!
This brings back memories!
Ever since you drove that ill-famed Crocodile
to be stripped of the title,
I've been keeping an eye on you!
Crocodile got defeated?
By a captain from the Navy Headquarters?
You gotta be kidding. There must be a catch.
Look! It's got to be him!
His bounty jumped up!
Find out about this pirate group.
I've never heard their name.
Monkey... "D."?!
And the Paramount War in which
you fell from the sky!
I can't believe you survived
and made it this far!
Wait!
You woke up, Trafalgar!
Leave me... here!
What are you saying?!
For past 13 years...
I've been living just to kill Doflamingo!
I've done... everything I can!
I have to leave the rest to Straw Hat-ya!
If he's gonna win,
I wanna see it through with my own eyes here!
If he loses, I need to be here and...
...die along with him!
I...
...got him involved in this conflict...
I gotta see it through with my own eyes here!
Leave me!
Trafalgar...
Tra-guy-kun...
Captains of allied pirate groups
have to be on an equal footing.
Luffy is here...
...of his own free will.
He doesn't fight if he has no will to.
Leave me here!
I'm begging you!
I don't think I can talk you out of it...
Nico Robin, you go ahead.
Cabbage-kun!
Robin-senpai! I will help you now!
Barrier-bility:
Stairs!
I can't listen to a suicidal wish.
I'll stay here, too.
You need to come to terms with it.
If you're gonna die,
it's got to be after me.
Robin-senpai!
Come down now!
Robin-san!
Bartolomeo made us stairs!
Go.
You can wear this.
You have to go, Nico Robin.
Let me look after him.
Thank you, Cabbage-kun.
Robiland!
We'll stay here, too!
We can't leave
the wounded Lawland here like that.
What should we do?! What should we do?!
What can we do to stop it?!
Zoro-dono, where are you going?!
--It's dangerous!
--You guys! Come with me!
Hey, Zoro!
Seems like he has some kind of idea.
Let's go!
Mingo!
Where did it come from?!
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
Damn! How about this?!
Third Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Magnum!
You're wide open!
So you don't wanna
let Law's attack go to waste, huh?
How long will it take you...
...to take me down?
By a one-hour time limit, I mean...
...the Birdcage will take that long
to completely collapse.
I'm sure there are people
who have a leg problem.
There are also bedridden old people
and babies at the breast.
Who will fall victim first?
After 30 minutes,
people start dying somewhere.
After 40 minutes, we will hear screams here.
After 50 minutes,
the whole country will be covered in red
as if tomatoes have been crushed.
After an hour,
there will be no voice whatsoever.
I know what will happen to Dressrosa
is none of your concern but...
...people who are going to die will
hold a grudge against you guys.
If only you guys hadn't come here,
Dressrosa could have been peaceful!
Cut the crap! It was only on the surface!
You see unlucky people everywhere
in the world.
If you try to save them all, there's no end.
You're just a passing pirate.
Are you trying to be a hero?
How dare you get in my way!
No! You got in my way!
You made my friends cry and
made my crewmates mad!
But you still haven't fallen
so I will take everything upon myself!
I won't let anybody die!
You and the Birdcage are standing in my way!
Fourth...
...Gear!
Luffy's secret stratagem, the new,
strongest-ever special technique finally blasts!
Luffy's ability, that has evolved
unimaginably in power, speed, and
everything, overwhelms Doflamingo!
A breathtaking fierce onslaught
to turn the whole thing around, begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Fourth Gear! The Phenomenal Bounce-Man!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!