Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along with the entire island.
The executives of the Donquixote Family have been taken down
one after another, after hard battles, by the Straw Hats,
and finally, there is only Doflamingo left!
The time has come for a one-on-one duel
between Luffy and Doflamingo that shakes up Dressrosa!
Muscle Balloon!
Fourth...
...Gear...
...Bounce-Man!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong...
...Gun!
Rhino Schneider!
Athlete!
Armored but still rubbery?!
It won't work!
Damn!
Enough! Fall on the ground already!
Gum-Gum...
...Culverin!
Everybody, listen.
I'm...
...the former king of Dressrosa - Riku Doldo III.
Wh-What is it?
The Donquixote Family
that we thought nobody could match has...
...almost been wiped out by the hands of the tough warriors
who only happened to be here in this country!
All of the Family's executives are
already taken down!
Really?!
The only enemy there is left to beat...
...is the current king of Dressrosa - Doflamingo!
And the one who is fighting him is
the pirate - Straw Hat Luffy!
I believe he is the man
who will destroy the Birdcage for us!
Whether he wins or loses,
it'll only take several dozen minutes!
I don't want any one of you to get crushed
by the constriction of the country!
Keep running!
Even if you run out of breath!
Or even if your leg breaks!
Just for several dozen minutes,
try to survive!
There is hope!
Please don't give up!
"Luffy!
An All-Out Leo Bazooka!"
He's right!
Yeah!
Don't give up!
Run!
Hurry up! Run to the downtown!
I gotta live! For my baby's sake, too!
There's still hope!
Believe!
That guy will save this country!
There's no time to lose!
It won't work!
Tsk! He's so tenacious!
Damn! The strings are in my way
and I can't get near!
I gotta hurry...
Mingo!
Damn!
Break White!
That was close!
You're annoying!
It's time for you to drop dead.
I'm running out of time!
Fall to the ground! Straw Hat!
The whole town is turning into strings!
Billow-White!
Mingo!
Get blown away!
Damn brat!
Mingo!
You little squirt! Don't put on airs!
This is it!
Gum-Gum...
...Leo Bazooka!
D... D...
Doflamingo!
H-He did it!
He really took down Doflamingo!
That's...
That guy... Don't tell me he's...
Those moves!
The body that stretches like rubber!
Yeah, it's no mistake!
He did it!
Dressrosa has been saved now!
The rubber ball!
No, he isn't just a rubber ball.
According to King Riku-sama, he is...
...the pirate - Straw Hat Luffy!
Lucy the gladiator!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
No, wait a minute...
His face looks scarier and his body is rounder
than the guy on the newspaper.
--Is it really him?!
--What?
Are you Straw Hat Luffy?!
What? Yeah.
I heard he's like an eight-meter-tall monster.
--He's not more than four meters tall.
--That means he's a fake?
Hey, rubber ball.
Are you Straw Hat himself?
You guys are bugging me!
Why do you keep bouncing up and down?
Can't you stop?
I can't.
Hey, what was that?!
I just heard something loud!
Viola?
Straw Hat... won!
You sure?!
Amazing!
How destructive that was!
There's no way he's still alive!
Hey, look up in the sky!
It's no good.
The Birdcage isn't gone!
No way...
That means Doflamingo is...
Not dead yet.
Straw Hat-ya...
Damn! One more strike!
Gum-Gum...
H-Hey, what's the matter, Straw Hat Luffy?!
Jesus Burgess!
Why was he here at the Palace?!
No kidding! He jumped down!
I can't believe how far he can jump!
Hello? Sabo-kun?
Come in! Hello?!
That bastard Straw Hat is barely alive!
Now's my chance!
What?! That's...
The captain of the first ship of
Emperor Blackbeard's pirate group -
"Champ" Burgess!
Wait for me!
I'll kill you and rob it from you now!
The Gum-Gum Fruit!
--Are you okay?
--Don't.
Don't go near him blindly. He's a pirate, too.
You don't know what he's thinking.
How could you say that?!
He fought against Doflamingo for us!
She's right!
At least, he isn't our enemy!
Still, I can't trust him!
He's a pirate like Doflamingo is!
But...
...King Riku-sama said he is our hope!
Hey you! Is the battle over?!
What happened to Doflamingo?!
Doflamingo is still alive!
Get away from the town!
The fight between the pirates is still going on!
We'll get caught up! Get away!
Even the downtown is in danger!
The Birdcage is closing in!
There's no place to run!
Min... go...
Doflamingo strikes back against Luffy
who used up all his energy and can't even move!
It takes ten minutes for his Haki to be regained,
and an intense battle begins
to protect the incapacitated Luffy during that time from
Doflamingo, who has become the embodiment of anger itself!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Flame Dragon King! Protect Luffy's Life!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!