Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
However, by the actions of the Straw Hats,
the executives of the Donquixote Family
have been taken down one after another,
and Doflamingo alone remains.
But he launched a counterattack,
making the Birdcage constrict,
in order to kill all the
people in the country.
As the moment of Dressrosa's
destruction closes in,
Luffy has used up all his energy
and become incapacitated.
What are you doing, Zoro-dono?!
Trying to stop it with your swords?!
It isn't something you can stop
by just pushing!
It's just the ability of one person!
There's no rational reason for
me to believe I can't stop it!
Push the factory!
Push!
Push! Push!
Now, let's do it, guys!
My barrier will never break! Push!
Follow Zoro-senpai!
T... T-T-Trafalgar Law!
Will he regain his Haki?
O-Oh, the thing is...
He told me that he needs ten minutes
and now we've got three minutes
and twenty seconds to go!
There is no time to lose.
I'll take him under my care from here.
You can do it, Dressrosa!
"As Long as We Breathe!
Stop the Deadly Birdcage!"
The Birdcage is closing in on us!
--Oh? Huh?
--Hey, can you move?
Y-Yeah.
Why?! The injured are
recovering one after another!
Who cares why?
Let's just run!
Hey, wait a minute!
Listen to what I have to say!
What is it, Hundredth-Degree Hack?!
No! I'm behind him!
--The Five-star, God Usopp!
--What kind of crime did he commit?!
--Shut up! We don't have time!
--Oh, okay!
Listen, guys! Those of you who are strong,
go to the east and west side of the town!
My friends are pushing the Birdcage there!
Please help them!
Go help people who are pushing the Birdcage?
It's impossible to stop that thing!
Yeah, we have no chance!
No chance?
Stop making excuses! Trust my friends!
The god is angry!
We got it!
Are you okay?
Oh, what a pain...
I wonder if they're really heading off
to push the Birdcage.
Viola, use your Clairvoyance and...
Oh? Oh? Where did she go?
She was here until a minute ago.
Anyway, we don't have time.
Let's go ask other islanders, too.
We've got to hold out until Luffy comes back!
Straw Hat!
All of your "shields" have been broken!
Show yourself already!
Too bad for you. This "shield" is...
...still alive.
Get your dirty hands off me!
Not yet... Not yet!
We'll keep you busy until Lucy comes back!
I don't mind! Just stab him like this!
You scum never learn!
Prepare to die a second death!
Straw Hat! I'm here! Come on out!
Hey, we've come all the way! Let us through!
The Birdcage is right there!
They say there's danger ahead
and we can barely advance, too!
People all over the country gathered
here at once and we can't even move!
Oh, please...
Everybody! Don't stay here!
Advance towards the plateau -
location of the Royal Palace!
You're Rebecca!
We gotta run there?!
Is it really safe?!
Yes!
The center of the Birdcage is moving
towards there!
Please hurry up! It's dangerous here!
Okay! I take your word for it!
Me, too!
--Me, too!
--Let's go!
Did you hear that?! The plateau!
Run towards the plateau!
Everybody! Evacuate to the plateau
- location of the Royal Palace!
The downtown area is a battlefield
and it's dangerous!
We don't have time! Just go!
--Run!
--Hurry up!
Everybody! Don't abandon hope!
There are people who haven't given up yet!
There are people who are trying
desperately to stop the Birdcage!
You go guide citizens
to the plateau - location of the Royal Palace!
We'll take this one!
Come on! Hurry up!
Thank you, Rebecca!
They're all trying so hard
to stop the Birdcage!
But if the Birdcage is something
that'll never stop, no matter their strength,
all of their efforts will be wasted!
I know I'm no match for him but...
But everybody's fighting desperately!
I've got to do something, too!
Father-sama!
When push comes to shove, I'll...
...kill Doflamingo!
What?
Viola-san!
Rebecca! Why are you here?!
Viola-san, I...
Don't be silly!
If I let you die, I can't face Brother Kyros
or my late sister!
Walk away!
So, what did you come to see me for, Viola?
The Donquixote Family is about
to be obliterated.
If I do nothing to take responsibility
as a former executive, it's too selfish.
No!
Either I will die, or you will!
Doffy!
You're very passionate, Violet!
Viola-san!
THE SMILE FACTORY
You gotta push more! Push harder!
Okay!
The Birdcage will definitely stop!
Keep pushing!
We got it!
IN FRONT OF THE BIRDCAGE
- NEAR THE SMILE FACTORY
How is it?!
It's slowing down... I think!
Now that you mention it,
it seems like it's slowing down!
No! It hasn't changed at all!
Stop grumbling and just push!
Why are you here?!
Oh no... I don't know who
it is because I can't see.
That jerk! He's the last
person we wanted to see now!
Damn!
It's hard to walk away from foolish people.
Although my ability is limited,
let me help you, if even a bit!
Procession - halt!
--Give support to those unknown people pushing the cage!
--Yes, sir!
The Navy!
Oh, we got so much help!
It's encouraging!
--Those of you who can't use Haki, head for the factory!
--Yes, sir!
Huh? The Navy?!
Push the Birdcage!
Run!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Nothing'll change if we just keep running!
I'm gonna push it, too!
Oh! Hey!
--Push!
--Okay!
Damn! I'll push, too!
--I have the greatest muscular strength here!
--Yeah, that's the spirit!
No, I do!
--We're gonna push it, too!
--We wanna protect our own country at least!
Let's push it together!
All right! Guys!
Give it everything you've got!
Yeah!
SEVIO
There they are!
Warriors! Let us push, too!
--Just do it already!
--Yeah!
--We'll do it, too!
--We can't just let it cut us without doing anything!
--I'm sorry, everybody! Help us!
--Yeah! Let's work together!
--Here we go, guys!
--Yeah!
Let's do it!
Yeah!
Push!!
It's not working! It's not stopping!
It's too early to give up!
I trust Zoro-senpai!
We'll stop the Birdcage at any cost!
Push!!
It stopped...
The Birdcage...
Wow! I can't believe it!
The Birdcage stopped!
It's gonna move again!
But it did stop for a moment.
So it's stoppable!
Doro-senpai is as awesome as ever!
The Birdcage... stopped?!
That way, we can buy time
until Straw Hat comes back.
Damn fools...
Keep pushing!
Let's stall the contraction of the Birdcage!
Stay focused!
Hold on! More!
What? King Riku-sama?!
Army Commander Tank?!
Good job!
If it weren't for you people,
we would've lost thousands already!
Screw this Birdcage!
People are meant to be free! Keep pushing!
Okay!
More!
Push the Birdcage back!
No matter how many seconds you buy,
it's useless.
Nothing has changed.
You think so?
Hierro Lagrima!
Tearwhales!
That's enough! Viola-san!
Viola-san!
Did you think...
...I'll hesitate just because
we spent a decade together as a Family, Violet?
Hesitate to kill you?
I don't criticize my associates
for their mistakes.
But I don't condone betrayals.
Now, next up is...
Look at her, Violet!
Rebecca!
Viola-san... My body is moving on its own...!
Poor girl. She's scared.
No!
Don't...
Now, come this way!
Stop it! Don't involve Rebecca!
What am I... going to do?!
Viola-san!
Rebecca!
No! I don't wanna do this!
Now, kill her...
Viola-san!
Why am I doing this?!
Rebecca!
I-I don't wanna do this!
Viola-san!
It's starting to slice up
the old King's Plateau!
Damn! It stopped once!
If it keeps constricting,
people will start dying one after another!
--Don't give up! Keep pushing!
--Stall it even for a second!
How long till Lucy comes back?!
Let me see...
The Birdcage slowed down
but it will close completely in...
...60 seconds.
And also, 60 seconds to go
until Lucy's comeback!
The Birdcage has started
shredding the King's Plateau!
While the voices of the people rise in prayer
for Luffy, their only hope,
as Dressrosa crumbles,
Rebecca's sword, manipulated
by the hands of Doflamingo,
hangs precariously over Viola's body!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Dead or Alive! A Fateful Countdown!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!