Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
However, by the actions of the Straw Hats,
the executives of the Donquixote Family
have been taken down one after another,
and Doflamingo alone remains.
I don't criticize my associates
for their mistakes.
But I don't condone betrayals.
Rebecca!
Viola-san... My body is moving on its own...!
Doflamingo has caused the
Birdcage to constrict
in order to kill all the
people in the country.
As the moment of Dressrosa's
destruction closes in,
Luffy has used up all his energy
and become incapacitated.
I need ten minutes...
Ten minutes?
If I regain my Haki, I'm sure I
can finish him off with one blow!
Hey, if we give you ten minutes,
will you get us out of the Birdcage?!
I promise!
"Dead or Alive!
A Fateful Countdown!"
Don't fall behind! Hurry up!
Here! Take my hand!
Come up here on the plateau!
It stopped once!
We can hold it back again and again!
Guys, give it everything you've got!
Now is the time to reward Luffy-dono
for his hard fighting!
We're samurai of the Land of Wano!
Show them what we Navy are made of!
Stop the cage!
Every time these hands and feet back down,
our defeat in this battle
and sure demise inch closer!
Prepare yourselves and keep hanging on!
Shut up! You're distracting us!
You don't have to tell us!
This very moment is the time to fight!
That's the spirit, guys!
Keep pushing with all your might!
Okay, honey!
Don't cling to me!
Yeah...
I have no intention of
making this place my grave!
I have a goal I want to achieve!
If that's so,
until our bodies are broken,
let's make the greatest
effort of our lifetimes!
Please... Please be safe...
As many lives as possible...
Are you okay?
Stay with us!
Stop it! Don't involve Rebecca!
What am I... going to do?!
Viola-san!
Rebecca!
Now, kill her...
Viola-san! Why am I doing this?!
Rebecca!
No!
No! I don't wanna cut Viola-san!
Doflamingo!
No!!
Alright, everyone!
It won't be much longer!
Wh-Who's talking?!
--Who is it?! Now isn't the time!
--Where is he speaking from?!
Our star will return!
Oh! Hey! There he is!
You're the announcer from
the Colosseum, Gyats!
--How long have you been there?!
--What are you up to?!
Everyone, do you remember?!
Now isn't the time to fool around!
The country is on the verge of destruction!
You're not King Riku-sama!
Yes, I know you remember!
What?!
About that funny and bold star
who burst onto the scene...
...in the tournament at the
Corrida Colosseum today!
Star?!
Don't tell me he's talking about...
...me!
Hey, I told you I'd stay here with you
but do you mind if I go now?
Trafal...
Gagh! Law! He's gone!
What?! Where did he go?!
I remember!
He tamed the killer bull
that everybody feared
and mowed down the towering Giant!
He even knocked down the
living legend, Don Chin Jao!
He's the little gladiator
who made the Colosseum...
I mean, the whole of Dressrosa
bubble over with excitement!
I've never before seen anyone fight so freely
and make a competition
as thrilling as he did!
I was watching that!
He's talking about that guy, isn't he?!
--I saw it at the Colosseum!
--I watched it on a screen in the town!
His name is...
...Lucy!
So what?! He's just a gladiator!
Lucy...
Help me, Lucy...
Yes! He's Lucy!
But that was just his temporary alias!
His real name is...
The pirate - Straw Hat...
...Luffy!
What?!
What?! That's who Lucy was under his mask?!
That's the guy King Riku-sama
mentioned earlier!
Since we've been fooled by
and been under the control of a pirate,
maybe it's hard for us
to trust another pirate!
But...
...he's different from the Donquixote Family
who appeared in disguise
as heroes on that night a decade ago!
Straw Hat Luffy is someone
that the real king,
King Riku-sama, called "our hope"!
He fought Doflamingo earlier
to within an inch of defeat!
That little boy did that?!
He sure was very strong
at the Colosseum but...
I want to believe!
What?!
I want to trust him!
Me, too!
We ended up like this because
we couldn't trust King
Riku-sama a decade ago!
This time, I'll trust!
--That guy...
--Lucy will...
...Save...
...Our country!
He's now knocked out
after getting hurt in the battle but...
...it's not over yet!
Dance with joy, Dressrosa!
Lucy...
...promised me!
That he'll knock out Doflamingo...
...with a single blow!
Knock him out with a single blow, huh?
What a big talker!
That's what I'd expect from Luffy-senpai!
That's so Luffy!
You've got to do it. Otherwise, we
can't hold out much longer, Luffy!
--That's great!
--Lucy!
Are you listening,
Doflamingo?!
You...
...puppeteered our king, deceived the world,
and stayed here in Dressrosa as a false king!
This is the place where you'll receive...
...your punishment!
Gyats!
I see everything you're up to, Doflamingo!
Come get me if you want!
Stay away from Viola-sama and Rebecca-sama!
With all your efforts, we successfully
delayed the constriction of the Birdcage!
It won't be long before
Lucy, the star who was born
in the Colosseum, comes back!
Hold on until that moment!!
Luffy-senpai! Here we go!
Hajrudin!
D-Damn... Not now...
What the...
The injured who recovered earlier
are collapsing again!
--Time's up.
--What?!
The effect of the Dandelixers
on those who got it first, is wearing off.
It's not gonna work twice!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Because my ability isn't good enough,
it's like I gave them a glimpse
of happiness for a moment,
and then, disappointed them! It's terrible!
No, Princess Mansherry!
We don't know how many people
would've been killed by the Birdcage
if it weren't for the Dandelixers!
But...
--Look!
--What?
You worked a miracle!
Oh, please! What weaklings!
People in the back take the collapsed ones' places!
Get more people!
Okay!
We'll hold out at any cost!
Until Lucy gets rid of the Birdcage!
Yeah!
They've stalled it enough!
Luffyland will take over from there
and get rid of the Birdcage!
Finally! Lucy will come back in ten seconds!
He should be listening somewhere!
Call out the name of the star!
Lucy! Lucy!...
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!...
Three seconds to go!
Two!
Enough already!
Gyats-san!
Lucy! Lucy!
Don't stop! Keep calling out!
One!
How absurd...
Go to hell, Doflamingo!
Our star Lucy will...
...drop you with a single blow!
Zero!
What?! Where's Lucy?!
Straw Hat isn't coming back!
It quieted down finally.
Viola, it's your turn to go quiet...
Forever!
No!!
Viola-san!
Close your eyes, Rebecca!
You don't have to see a thing!
This is a bad dream!
No matter what happens, forget everything!
I won't hold a grudge against you so...
just forget it!
No!!
It's not your fault at all!
I'm sorry, Rebecca!
This will leave a deep scar in your mind!
No!!
Go!
There he is!
Lucy!
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!...
Luffy comes back and
enters a final battle against Doflamingo!
The formidable Doflamingo
tries to manipulate people
and continue his reign over them,
but when Luffy launches Fourth Gear's
most powerful attack
with a soulful scream, Dressrosa's fate is finally settled!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Attack on a Celestial! Luffy's
King Kong Gun of Anger!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!