Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
governed by the Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo.
DOFLAMINGO FALLS
They took down the executives of
the Donquixote Family one after another.
And finally, Luffy brought down Doflamingo!
"The Birth of the Legend!
The Adventures of the Revolutionary Warrior Sabo!"
A HILL IN CARTA - A TOWN IN THE EAST OF DRESSROSA
KYROS' HOUSE
So you've been living on top of a hill.
It was convenient for me and Scarlet.
Sorry but my place is not as good as the Palace.
It'll do.
There's one for each. Help yourself.
Law-dono.
Who is this man that you brought here earlier?
He's somebody Straw Hat-ya knows.
I picked him up.
I'm sorry but I'm gonna turn in first.
If you're hungry,
you can eat anything in the house.
I think there's only dried meat though.
When Luffy wakes up, it'd be gone in a second.
Meat... Meat...
Hey, you fell asleep so quickly!
You, too?!
You fell asleep in an instant, too.
I'm sure everybody was tired.
I guess they're not gonna wake up for a while.
We should let them have a good rest now.
Boy, he has no booze here...
Who is it?!
Here!
Sabo!
Yo!
You know him?
He's Luffy's... brother!
What?!
So you know him from the Revolutionary Army?
Yes.
Luffy...
Robin, you don't have to wake him up.
I just came to see his face before I leave.
Are you leaving the country already?
Yeah. Because some troublesome people are
headed back here.
Who are they?
CP-0.
They played a part in Doflamingo's deception.
They're targeting us!
Dressrosa will get crowded in a day or two.
You guys should leave as soon as possible, too.
Thank you for telling us.
Either way,
we're not gonna stay here for long.
And what's more, I didn't know he
had another brotherbesides Ace.
You're right. I've never heard of it.
I bet so.
I think it surprised Luffy the most.
What do you mean by that?
I was presumed dead for a long time.
I was always with Luffy and Ace
when I was a kid.
We ran around like wild
and had it hard because of that old man, Garp.
And we dreamed about becoming pirates...
We exchanged cups of sake
to become brothers.
But I got involved in an accident one day.
I mean, an incident.
D-Do you know...
12 YEARS AGO - SABO (10 YEARS OLD)
that there will be a fire in the Gray Terminal tonight?
We all have to keep quiet about the plan!
We're special!
Ace! Luffy!
There's something wrong with this town!
Everybody's crazy!
Even though they know that people will die soon,
they act normally and even smile!
I don't wanna stay here!
I gotta tell them quickly!
Ace! Luffy! Run!
What happened to you, boy?
This town smells worse than Gray Terminal.
It smells like rotten people!
If I stay here... I'll never be free!
Ace... Luffy...
I wish I could see you.
This place is like a birdcage!
I don't think I can stand living in this country
filled with stale air.
What is freedom?
Where can I find it?
What a nice day!
It's perfect for setting sail!
The ship is huge!
How rude is that!
Damn! The ship is on fire!
Why did they shoot me like that?
Saint Jalmack!
There is a child on the ship!
When someone flies a black flag,
he's a pirate regardless of who he is.
But most importantly...
A commoner shouldn't cross
the path of my ship!!
Ace... Luffy...
Help me... Somebody...
Help...
He's late! He's too late!
I wonder what he's doing!
Ivankov-san, please relax!
I'm so frustrated and...
My head's gonna explode...
Explode...
What?!
Or not!
That was a joke?!
Heehaw!
You're late, Dragon!
You kept us waiting for so long!
Sorry.
Oh, hey, that's...
That's awful...
Hey, treat him! Hurry up! It's urgent!
Call the ship's doctor! Now!
He woke up!
Don't surprise him.
I wasn't gonna do that!
Boy! How rude!
Oh?
Where am I?
You're on board our ship.
It says Sabo on your possessions.
Is it your name?
Sabo...
I don't know.
You don't know?
What's your name, then?
No idea...
Don't tell me he's...
Probably...
He doesn't remember a thing?
Yes, even his own name...
I first met him
at the Highland of the Goa Kingdom.
I'm sure he's one of the nobles from there.
Then, let's take him home.
Search for his parents...
No...
I don't wanna go back!
Why?!
I don't know!
But...
...that's the last thing I want!
But we can't have you on this ship forever!
We have things to do!
In that case!
In that case, just take me someplace else!
You're just a kid! Don't be ridiculous!
I'm begging you!
What should we do, Dragon?
You're not gonna run into the Navy here.
And we've already called in a town doctor, too.
Oh, thank you!
What about booze?
We'll hold a banquet at a later date.
What? We have to wait?
Sorry...
We'll sleep in a huddle here tonight.
Wait a sec!
Cabbage! Are you gonna sleep here, too?!
Of course, I am!
Why don't you just go to sleep, too?
Somebody! Bring me a chain! A strong one!
Or we'll see a monster!
Wh-What are you doing?! Bartolomeo!
Now we can have a good sleep!
Is that how you joined the Revolutionary Army?
Sort of.
One thing that I knew for sure was
that I didn't wanna go back to my parents at any price.
Other than that, I didn't remember a thing.
BALTIGO
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S GENERAL HEADQUARTERS
Lower your center of gravity!
There's no point in
keeping those who can't fight with us!
This will soften my muscles.
Where are you going, Sabo?! Stop for a sec!
I'm gonna go train myself!
How's that kid?
Even though he lost his memory,
his body remembers how he used to move.
I don't know what he'd been doing before
but obviously, he has a lot of experience in fighting.
I bet he used to be quite a naughty kid.
I already don't know what to do with him.
You haven't won yet!
What?
Kuma-san's next? Here I go!
Damn!
We gotta go out to sea someday...
...and live as we like.
Freer than anyone else.
Uh-huh!
Let's go out to sea at 17!
And we will become... pirates!
Peel these, too!
10 YEARS AGO - SABO (12 YEARS OLD)
What?!
You want some?
Take it seriously!
I'm orrwy!
Sabo-kun!
Sabo!
Oh?
Oh, boy...
Although it was just training,
he fought bravely against the higher-ups.
You just wait! I'll make my name soon!
FIVE YEARS AGO - ACE (17 YEARS OLD)
Good luck, Ace!
A BATTLEFIELD IN SOME COUNTRY
Fire!
No, I can't reach them!
The arrangement was they'll open the front gate, wasn't it?
Those who snuck in first - what are they doing?
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
I'll figure something out!
Sabo! Where are you?!
Clank.
Is that it?!
SABO (17 YEARS OLD)
Sabo-kun!
Sabo!
He's pushing it too far again!
What's with him?!
Shoot him up!
Why can't we hit him?!
Follow Sabo!
Sabo-kun, we freed the citizens and our allies
who were captive!
We'll leave the rest up to you!
All right!
Clank.
Stop!
You can't get away!
He's all by himself! How idiotic!
Here it is.
Dragon Claw Fist!
Dragon...
...Breath!
You've gone too far, Sabo-kun.
Achieving such a feat at your age
is really something.
It won't be so long before
you lead the Revolutionary Army.
Oh yeah. I heard a rookie who refused to join
the Seven Warlords is around your age.
Oh, you mean "Fire Fist"?
"Fire Fist"?
I heard he's a very hot-blooded guy.
Well, I wonder how much he can do
in the New World...
If I'm correct, his name is Portgas D.--
Ace.
That's right, Ace! Oh, you knew!
No, d-did I say something?
You've lost your memory again?
TWO YEARS AGO
LUFFY (17 YEARS OLD)
What nice day for setting sail!
You don't know who you're messing with.
Look at this technique
I've been training for 10 years!
SABO (20 YEARS OLD)
So you'd lost your memory until two years ago?
Yeah...
If it was that serious,
how did you get your memory back?
Ace helped me.
That's what I think now.
FIRE FIST ACE DIES
The timing couldn't be any worse than that
but...
...that was why...
...he awakened my memory.
The Paramount War in Marineford
that became legend.
What happened to Sabo when Ace died?
And what did he have on his mind
when he showed up in front of Luffy?
That shocking truth and the story of
the brothers' strong bond will finally be revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Brothers' Bond!
The Untold Story Behind Luffy and Sabo's Reunion!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!