Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa governed by
the Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo.
They took down the executives of
the Donquixote Family one after another.
And finally, Luffy brought down Doflamingo!
So you'd lost your memory
until two years ago?
Yeah...
If it was that serious,
how did you get your memory back?
Ace helped me.
That's what I think now.
FIRE FIST ACE DIES
The timing couldn't be any
worse than that but...
...that was why...
...he awakened my memory.
"The Brothers' Bond!
The Untold Story Behind Luffy and Sabo's Reunion!"
TWO YEARS AGO - SABO (20 YEARS OLD)
Sabo!
Sabo-kun!
There you are!
Something wrong?
No, I was just looking out at the sea.
Yeah?
We're back in Baltigo
for the first time in a month.
I hope everybody's doing fine.
Yeah, we've been tied up with missions.
Let's make a report to Dragon-san first.
BALTIGO
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S GENERAL HEADQUARTERS
It's so hectic.
Oh, Chief of Staff! You
came at the right time!
Come to the situation room now!
The Paramount War between the Navy
and the Whitebeard Pirates has ended!
Whitebeard lost?!
So, one of the Four Emperors has
been taken down...
The Navy has a lot of casualties, too.
Seems like it was a hard battle as expected.
What about Ivan-san?! Is she alright?!
It doesn't say she died or anything.
The ones who died in the war were...
...the Emperor - Whitebeard...
And...
...Fire Fist Ace!
But more importantly, Dragon-san, look...
Is it true?!
Is Straw Hat Luffy your son?!
Hm? Yes, he is.
What?!
FIRE FIST ACE DIES
I'm gonna become a pirate...
...and defeat others and become infamous!
It'll be the only proof of my life!
It doesn't matter if all the people in the world
reject me or despise me!
I'll become a great pirate
and show them what I can do!
Sabo-kun, what's wrong?!
You're acting strange!
I can't believe that Ace
was Gold Roger's son...
He was the biggest threat to the Navy
so they wanted to get rid of him at any cost.
Did you guys know?!
They say Akainu punched a hole right
through his body!
We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
Brothers? Really?!
When we become pirates,
we might not be on the same ship
but our brotherhood will always be with us!
Wherever you are, whatever you do,
we'll always be bonded together!
So from now on,
we're brothers!
Yeah!!
Are you alright, Sabo?!
--Sabo-kun!
--Sabo!
Now I know!
The one who died wasn't
some unknown pirate...
He wasn't just some threat in the Pirate Era
that needed to be eliminated!
Ace is my...
...brother!
I'm not gonna run from anybody!
I'm not gonna lose to anyone!
--The chief woke up!
--Really?! That's great!
I thought you were gonna die! Sabo-kun!
You had quite a high fever, Sabo.
You've been sleeping for three straight days!
And I've been worrying!
What?! You got your memory back?!
Yeah, I remember everything now.
Including who I am and
why I left home and sailed out to sea.
I see. That's good.
Are you gonna quit
the Revolutionary Army, then?!
No, I'm not.
--Is Dragon-san still here?
--He is.
I need to talk to him.
At that moment, I felt Ace said to me,
"You're Sabo.
You're Luffy's and my brother."
That's why I...
Wait a sec!
What do you want?! Don't interrupt now!
You...
What?
Why did you finish the bottle?! It's empty!
How dare you eat all the meat as well!
I can't listen to such a
story without drinking!
Whoa-whoa, both of you...
Well, we don't need alcohol
but we'll be in trouble without food
when Luffy wakes up.
All of our crew eat so much!
I'll go and get groceries
later with Kin'emon.
Thank you!
Get some booze, too.
Luffy's friends are funny.
You'll never get bored.
Hey, I wanna hear the rest already!
Okay.
I finally... managed to get here... Ace.
Look at this. Luffy started to make his way
to become the King of the Pirates again.
That's our younger brother!
THE STRAW HATS ARE BACK
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Sabo-kun?
I want you to ask the entire
Revolutionary Army a favor.
There's a Devil Fruit that
I want to get at any cost.
But Luffy-senpai,
what about the Flare-Flare Fruit?
I wanna keep it out of
the hands of a few people
but I don't have a choice!
My friend's gonna die!
I promise you I will win the Flare-Flare Fruit
so you can go out without worry!
Thanks! I appreciate it!
I won't let you have the Flare-Flare Fruit.
"Straw Hat Luffy"!
Hey, hey, hey! Where you from?!
You can't talk to Luffy-senpai so casually!
He is the legendary pirate
"Fire Fist" Ace-sama's brother
and he will become the King of
the Pirates one day, you idiot!
I've known that from way back.
What's your problem?!
You can't just appear out of nowhere
and say you won't let me have the fruit!
It's me, Luffy.
What do you mean "It's me"?!
Listen! The Flare-Flare Fruit
is a keepsake from Ace!
If you want it, you're my enemy!
And you called me "Luffy" but...
...look at this beard!
I'm Lucy!
You think I can't tell my brother's face
just because he's in disguise?
"Brother"?!
Listen, the only people who
can call me their brother
are the late Ace and
the guy who died much earlier...
D-Died...
Sabo!!
I don't believe you!
We stole a bottle of sake from Dadan
and made a toast...
Sabo?!
What the...
Where have you been all this time?!
I thought you were dead!
Thank you, Luffy!
I'm glad that you're alive!
But Sabo, I...
I let Ace get killed in front of me...
I know! Even though Ace died, I'm...
...so happy that you survived!
I almost helplessly lost both of my brothers!
If you had also died,
I would've been left on my own!
Thank you!
Thank you for being alive, Luffy!
Can I eat the Flare-Flare Fruit?
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
That'd be nice!
That's the only option we've got!
Luffy... He's laughing.
I wonder what kind of a dream he's having.
--I'm leaving now.
--Already?
I got to see his face so...
Here, I made a Vivre Card
of Luffy's just in case.
Oh, when did you have time for that?
I'll take a piece of it.
All right. Luffy might be a
bit much for you to handle,
but take good care of him.
Yeah! You can count on us!
It's natural for a big brother to worry
about his bungling kid brother.
He might be a bit much for you to handle,
but take good care of 'im.
He said the same thing Ace said.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Is this Sabo? This is Hack.
Yeah, I just left the
house. I'll be back soon.
Roger that.
So how was it? Luffy-kun was quite...
Clank.
Why did he hang up?! That selfish jerk!
Whoa-whoa! Hack-san!
What is it? Could you look at it?
It's "one"...
I see... The only side that
would be in Straw Hat's favor -
that's what we agreed on, isn't it?
Yes, it is but...
Then, he won this one.
We won't arrest him tonight.
You can't determine that
with a die roll! Issho-san!
We ran across the entire country
and finally found where he is!
You lashed out against
Fleet Admiral Sakazuki like that!
If you wanna take down Law and
Straw Hat, now's the chance!
Maynard-san!
A man shouldn't grumble like that
after a die has been cast.
You're pathetic.
THE ROYAL PALACE
Did anybody see Lucy after that?
--No, nobody did.
--I wanna say "Thank you" to him at least!
There's already quite a fuss out there.
Even if they truly are pirates or criminals,
they're our saviors without question.
Grandfather-sama!
Rebecca...
Father-sama, Lucy,
and the others aren't here at the Palace!
Yeah but don't worry. I
got a call from Kyros.
They're together.
Okay.
That aside...
Rebecca.
If I go back to being a king again,
you'll be a princess, you know?
What?
Can we depart anytime?
Yeah, anytime.
All right! Once we go back to Baltigo,
I gotta tell Dragon-san so much about Luffy!
It was...
...really nice to see you again!
Let's hurry up!
Sanji, Nami, and the others who were
being chased by Big Mom's ship,
have already been on a whole
new adventure on the strangest island ever!
At the same time,
in front of Kid and the others who
are aiming to defeat the Four Emperors,
a pirate who is known as the
strongest among all creatures
on land, sea, and air, descends from the sky!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Strongest Creature!
One of the Four Emperors - Kaido, King of the Beasts!"
Ifm gonna be the King of the Pirates!