Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
governed by the Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo.
They took down the executives of
the Donquixote Family one after another.
And finally, Luffy brought down Doflamingo!
Let's hurry up!
"The Strongest Creature!
One of the Four Emperors - Kaido, King of the Beasts!"
His brother was just here but
he's sleeping peacefully, totally unaware.
He'll be disappointed when he wakes up.
What a nice brother...
Damn! I can barely fix myself...
Do you want me to help you?
He really is a nice brother.
Did we wake you?
Oh, were you listening to Sabo's story?
Yes, from about halfway through.
We must've been speaking...
...quieter than our captain's snoring.
Should we wake him up?
No, let him sleep as much as he likes.
I brought him here for just that reason.
Zoroland, maybe there is alcohol
in the cellar under the kitchen floor.
What?! You think so?!
No matter how much I thank Luffyland,
it could never be enough.
There's no way of knowing how much he
encouraged the people of Dressrosa.
This country will change.
Thanks to all of you, of course.
The pain from the wounds that
you're all suffering from...
...is the result of injuries you sustained
on behalf of us, the citizens of Dressrosa.
We have to repay you somehow.
Do you wanna have a drink?
Aren't you gonna sleep?
--Am I disturbing you?
--No.
I wanna spar with you someday.
I can't believe a famous swordsman
such as you said that...
What an honor.
Maybe someday when our wounds heal...
Yeah.
You can have the rest.
Thanks.
Well, it was mine to begin with...
I'll take a rest, too.
Give me some meat...
Rebecca...
Soldier-san!
Rebecca.
I saw the list in the Colosseum.
You entered the competition as I thought.
I told you not to!
I...
I'll do it! I'll win it!
Soldier-san!
So...
So... Hey, can we live together?!
Now, the so-called Twirly Hat Crew
who headed for Zou,
a mysterious island in the New World, is...
Everyone!
I want you to take him and head for Zou!
The Twirly Hat Crew took Caesar,
the scientist from Punk Hazard
who ate the Gas-Gas Fruit, with them...
...as they set out to meet
Luffy and the others at Zou.
But they were targeted by Big Mom, one
of the Four emperors, on their way.
Her desire was to capture Caesar.
I don't wanna get caught by Big Mom!
Because I...
...swindled research funds from them!
We can't let anyone take
you anyway so shut up!
You go ahead and sail for Zou!
Damn!
After all the struggle
to shake up Big Mom's ship...!
Why did you wanna get into trouble again?!
You have no choice! Just do it!
Don't tell me what to do!
We have no time for grumbling!
How dare you kick me?!
I'm saying it for the sake of you guys!
Don't stick your nose in their business!
We should've waited on the ship quietly!
You're pretty stupid to be
rushing ahead like this!
Shut up and do what I say!
Are you gonna do it?!
Or do you just want your
heart to be crushed?!
Fine! But I won't forget this!
It was the right call to come ashore!
We can still save them! We need your help!
In that case,
why don't you treat me more nicely...
Did you say something?!
Stop taunting me with that!
Hurry up, Caesar!
I said "Don't tell me
what to do"! You raccoon!
I'm a reindeer!
What's the difference?!
Shut up! Just hurry up!
If they die because of you,
I'll make you pay for it!
We need your help!
It's hard to run here!
I can't believe we got separated
from Sanji-san and the others...
We're in trouble!
We paid too much attention
to the mystery girl.
Oh, watch out! Nami-san!
--Watch out! I gotta save myself!
--What?!
No, how could you?!
How could you?! How could you?!
Thank you, Brook.
Onami! They're coming!
Yeehaw!
What?!
Is this it, invaders?
Hey! Where did you hide that girl?!
How did you guys invade the island?!
Answer me! This place is quite atypical...
What?! What's going on?!
What is it this time?!
It's a Rain-Ruption!
Again?!
What?!
Get down!
What is that?!
Rain?! No! It's a huge water spray!
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming,
it's coming! It's coming this way!
--No!
Go away!
I'll protect you no matter what!
No!!
Nami-san!
Momonosuke-san!
Help me!!
Help me, too!
Boy! You Devil Fruit eaters
are such pains in the butt!
I'm sorry that I couldn't protect you!
I won't let you get away! You damn invaders!
Come on! Brace up!
Thank you as always...
You, too, Momo!
Thank you...
When in doubt...
Just kill!
--Brook!
--Bonekichi!
I finally managed to protect you!
Leave the rest up to me!
Tsk! How arrogant!
Sheep's Horn!
What?!
--What are those arms?!
--Bonekichi!
Take this!
Soul Parade!
Wow! Bonekichi, that's awesome!
What kind of ability is that?
Brook!
--Keep stalling him like that!
--What?!
Diable! Mouton...
...Mallet!
Sheepshead-sama!
Sanji-kun!
Oh, Nami-san!
Who are you people?!
Who are you people... Oh!
What?! How creepy!
Gin-Rummy-sama!
Guys! Retreat!
Sheepshead-sama has been taken down!
What?!
But we haven't found the samurai yet!
Although we cornered them this far,
he didn't show himself!
The samurai's not here! Tell him so!
Yes, ma'am!
Hey, look at that!
The water's draining away...
What was that all about?
It's a strange island.
I hope that girl's okay, too...
She moves quicker than
us so she'll be alright.
You're right.
Hey! Guys!
Get over here now!
That's Chopperemon!
From the forest down below!
Let's go now! There's no time to lose!
THE KID PIRATES' SAFE HOUSE
What was that?
What happened?!
Captain! There's a massive hole!
--A hole?
--Something landed!
--Arm yourselves!
--Yeah!
That's it!
It sure is big.
Where did it fall from?
Who in the world did this?!
Hey, doesn't it look like
the shape of a human?
I once heard...
...a legend about a Sky Island
where some monster lives...
...somewhere in the sky around here.
Have you ever heard that?
Are you saying that
it was pushed off of a Sky Island?!
Captain Kid!
One of our ships was capsized by the impact!
What?!
Damn it all! Who did this?!
The strong live and the weak die.
That is just how this world is.
A few minutes ago...
A SKY ISLAND - THE RUINED
CITY OF BALLOON TERMINAL
What are you doing?
Let's leave him alone, Monk!
He must be insane!
We're at a height of 10,000 meters...
He was looking for a place to die.
If he's serious, why bother to stop him?
To sum up his life,
he had been defeated seven times as a pirate
and was captured
by the Navy or his enemies 18 times.
He underwent torture repeatedly
and had been living as a criminal.
He wanted to kill himself...
...by jumping off a Sky Island
which is rather out of the ordinary...
That's what led up to this.
It bears repeating.
He challenged the Navy and the
Four Emperors single-handedly
and was captured 18 times;
sentenced to death 40 times.
When he was hanged, the chain broke.
When he was sent to a guillotine,
the blade shattered.
When sentenced to impalement,
the spear crumbled.
Consequently, he sank
nine giant prison ships.
That means no one could kill him.
Even himself.
What is it this time?!
What is that monster?!
Damn! My head hurts!
I guess it's hard to die.
I survived again!
He managed to pull off dying...
That old man, Whitebeard...
The man looking for a place to die -
Kaido, King of the Beasts.
"If it's one-on-one, Kaido will win."
That's what people say.
On land, sea, and air, he
is a pirate who is known
as the strongest creature
among all living things.
I have no choice now, do I?!
Dammit!
Hurry up, Joker!
Make preparations for the final battle!
I don't care if this boring
world is destroyed!
Let's start the greatest war
the world has ever seen!
Dressrosa celebrates King Rikufs
restoration to the throne
after a decade and the debut
of their new princess, Rebecca.
However, when the Navyfs heavyweights,
"Inspector General" Sengoku
and "Great Advisor" Tsuru,
show up in front of Fujitora,
the die that will determine Luffy
and the others' fate is cast!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Fujitora Takes Action! The
Complete Siege of the Straw Hats!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!