Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and brought down the Warlord -
Donquixote Doflamingo.
Now, peace has returned to Dressrosa.
Do you think he doesn't wanna live with me?!
Am I annoying to him?!
How do I know?! Think for yourself!
I gotta leave this country already!
I only came here to ask
"Are you really okay with things this way?"!
Of course not!
I'm not okay with it!
Then, do you wanna come with me?!
Uh-huh! I do!
"The Bond Between Father and Daughter!
Kyros and Rebecca!"
A pirate is a pirate after all!
I'll never trust a pirate again!
I thought that you were a hero!
Catch Lucy!
Let go of Rebecca-sama!
Free her!
You can't get away!
Catch Lucy!
They're so persistent!
Our target is Straw Hat!
What now, Lucy?!
Charge!
--Let's go!
--Okay!
Capture him!
Aim carefully!
Oops! Oh no!
It's Sea Prism Stone!
Are you okay, Lucy?!
Lucy!
It came off!
That's it! Straw Hat!
Give up the princess without a fight!
Lucy!
--Get on!
--Okay!
Catch him!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
Gatling!
Son of a...!
No!
Lucy!
--Whoa! What's going on?!
--Lucy?!
--That's my meat!
--I'm sorry!
Rebecca!
I'll leave you behind the hill and lure them away!
So go off on your own!
The whole nation is trying to protect you!
If you get caught, they'll take you back to the Palace!
Be careful!
Uh-huh! But where should I go?!
Soldier is at the small house
in the Flower Field!
The Flower Field?!
Okay, I got it!
You gotta hurry or he'll be gone.
Thank you!
Thank you for everything, Lucy!
Okay! But don't worry about it!
Her name is Rebecca.
Kyros, hold her in your arms.
She's your daughter!
I shouldn't touch such an innocent thing!
My hands are tainted!
I don't wanna taint her!
You're like an angel, Rebecca!
I'll be watching over you!
I'll always be by your side!
How cute she is! How cute she is!
You're crying again!
Scarlet.
I fulfilled my role.
Forgive me for telling a lie about your husband.
I did it all so that Rebecca can live a happy life.
I need to hurry!
Mother-sama!
Mother-sama, I picked so many flowers!
--Wow, Rebecca!
--Would you like to have one?
Thank you. I would like to.
And this is from your mother to you!
Would you like to have one?
Thank you!
We sold all the flowers today!
Yes, we did. Maybe people bought them
because you're so cute!
You helped your mother!
Good girl, Rebecca!
I'm gonna go to the palace!
Alright, Scarlet? Rebecca?
Father-sama!
I... I couldn't protect her!
I'm sorry!
I couldn't protect your mother!
Although I couldn't protect your mother,
I'm gonna protect you to the end,
with my life!
I want my mother!
I don't like you, Soldier-san,
because you couldn't protect my mother!
Soldier-san!
Isn't this warmer?
Yes, it's much warmer!
Soldier-san is a brave man
He will always be by your side
Don't go...
I... haven't told you... told you anything yet!
Rebecca...
I want to live with you one day,
in the same house.
Soldier-san!
Let me teach you how to fight.
My mother said I shouldn't hurt anyone!
I'm gonna teach you how to not get hurt!
Stand up, Rebecca!
You have to become stronger!
Because you were a member of the royal family,
you've been running around,
getting insulted for a decade.
That's why, this time...
I want you to have your chance at happiness
as a member of the royal family.
I can't stay here, either.
Rebecca!
Don't lie!
Oh, about the letter?
I wasn't lying!
I really was...
...a worthless guy who fought all the time
in the past.
And whatever the reason was,
I really killed people.
So...
I'm not a daughter of some prince!
I don't know anyone like that!
It doesn't matter if he killed hundreds of people
or how tainted his hands are!
I only have one father!
I'm Kyros' daughter!
Don't lie!
Until the day you are filled with happiness,
I will always be by your side!
Stay by my side like you promised, Soldier-san!
I-Is it okay with you that I'm your father?!
Yeah! Let's live together!
Dad!
Yeah... Yeah...
Rebecca will never come back here,
Father-sama.
Viola... I thought so.
Yes. That's what she wants.
I'm sorry, Viola-san!
But could you take my place and become a princess?!
I'm sorry, Viola!
Big Sis-sama?!
This is the second time in my life
that someone asked me such an odd favor.
I see. Rebecca is really like her mother.
Luffy isn't here yet?!
Trafalgar Law's not here, either!
THE RUINS OF THE FOREST TOWN - CARTA
THE EAST PORT
What are both of our bosses doing?!
There are some enemies that can't be held back
even by us...
That's...
Fujitora!
The unwanted one's here!
Luffy-senpai, hurry up!
"Fools rush in where angels fear to tread"-dara!
I've already sent reinforcements
to the east port where Straw Hat's heading!
The warships on the sea
and Issho-san will pincer them!
And we'll catch the Straw Hats and the other criminals
in one fell swoop-dara!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What should we do?!
We only have one choice!
Zoro-senpai!
You and your friends should stand back!
Leave it...
...Up to us!
Hey! What happened to the reinforcements
for the east port-dara?!
Yes, sir!
Well, most of the units became incapacitatedc
What do you mean-dara?!
The bullets and gunpowder are missing
from their rifles!
And all their other weapons like
swords, pistols, axes, spears, and knives...
...went missing, too!
They must've been stolen...
And at the port,
the warships are stuck together
as if they got sewn to one another
so they can't sail out!
How could the iron be sewn together?!
Cut the string! Cut it!
But we don't have a knife!
Meanwhile, the soldiers who suddenly collapsed
are still paralyzed...
What are you doing, you idiots?!
I'm sorry!
Are you gonna let the Straw Hats and the other criminals walk away?!
Do something!
W-We'll do our best!
Is it really okay to get this much healing properties today,
Mouji?
The donors will be paralyzed
if we take too much out of them...
It's okay! We got permission!
From Kyros-sama.
Just do as I say, Princess!
Okay! Then, I won't hesitate!
We still have so many heavily-injured people!
I know you're in the middle of it
but we gotta go...
It'll be finished soon!
THROB
Then, I'll wait!
According to the citizens,
all these strange occurrences are
the work of fairies.
You fool! Cut the fairy crap-dara!
I-I-I-I'm sorry!
B-Barrier!
Will your barrier work?!
If it were breakable,
it wouldn't be called a barrier!
Keep holding on
until Luffy-senpai and Trafalgar come!
Yeah!
Are they fighting?!
NAVY BRAND RICE CRACKERS
Want some rice crackers?
No thanks. Just start talking.
A boy with White Lead Disease?!
So there was a survivor
from the White Town?!
He hates everything in this world.
Feels like I'm watching my older brother
when he was a kid.
I feel sorry for him but there's no way to
cure White Lead Disease.
Don't get involved too much
or you'll give yourself away.
Yes, I know.
I'm here to stop my brother.
Doflamingo is a violent man.
I'm not gonna let him go to Dressrosa.
One day, a Navy soldier died.
He was someone special to me.
I met him when he was a kid
and I thought of him as my son.
He was honest and
had a stronger sense of justice than anyone.
So he was a subordinate that I could trust as well.
But he lied to me just once in his lifetime.
Do you have a deal regarding
the Op-Op Fruit?
My brother knew it.
What?! But it's top secret!
Cora-san must be talking to...
That'll be it for Doflamingo!
We'll ambush at Swallow Island
and catch the Donquixote Family
in one fell swoop!
You stay away from the island!
I was planning on it.
This is the landing unit.
There is an executive of the Donquixote Family
among the dead.
His code name: Corazon.
JUSTICE OVER ALL
I've sent a picture of him.
Could you confirm?
Rosinante!
Why were you there on the island?!
He betrayed me.
But he must've had a reason.
Four things were lost during that incident.
The Barrels Pirates. My subordinate.
The Op-Op Fruit.
And the boy who was with the Donquixote Family
at the time
who was suffering from White Lead Disease!
Yeah, that's me!
Admiral Fujitora, with his overwhelming strength,
stands in the way of the Straw Hats and the others who are trying to escape!
But Luffy fights against him with all his power
and his firm resolve to become the King of the Pirates!
When the two men's inflexible determinations collide
with each other, their all-out special attacks crackle!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Men's Pride! Luffy vs. Fujitora, Head-to-Head!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!