I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
It's awesome!
So this is the back of the elephant!
To meet up with Sanji,
Nami, Chopper, and Brook,
Luffy and the others set foot on Zou
and encountered the Mink Tribe
who are known for disliking humans.
What the...?!
Wait! Stop, Carrot!
Here comes something else!
Forget about them-teia!
More importantly, we have an
invader in the Whale Forest!
They're the Mink Tribe!
Oh?! I-Isn't that outfit...
...Nami's?!
Hey! Sanji! Nami!
Chopper! Brook! Momo!
Where are you?!
Oh, and the gas guy.
Well, forget about him.
Hey! Somebody, respond!
"A Battle Begins!
Luffy vs. the Mink Tribe!"
Oh? What's this place?
It's huge!
If I climb on it, I think I can
get a good view of this island!
Hey! Sanji! Nami!
Chopper! Brook! Momo!
Where are you?!
What is that weapon?
I felt a shock for a moment!
We have an invader in the Whale Forest?!
Yes, we're in trouble!
The Guardians will be mad!
An animal?! A human?!
H-Hey, you!
Where did you get that outfit?!
What did you do to Nami?!
Are they a cannibal tribe?
Don't say such a scary thing!
What are you? A monster?!
I'm sorry! Don't eat me!
Look how high she can jump!
Do all of them have physical
abilities like that?!
How is it?!
Do you see something, Carrot?!
I do! Maybe it's a little too late!
On the other side of Kurau City,
there's a disturbance in the Whale Forest!
I thought so! Let's go, Warney!
Get on, Carrot!
Okay!
We don't have time to
transport you-teia guys!
Do as I say!
Go through the Rightrump Forest to your right
and turn left at a deep dark swamp!
And you'll reach the Rightflank Forest!
You'll find the corpse of
your-teia friend there!
C-Corpse?!
Wait at the Rightflank Forest!
We'll be there later!
Y-You've got to be kidding!
Please tell me you're kidding!
Do you think they-teia are gonna be okay?
--Those were the Straw Hats.
--What?
They-teia are gonna be shocked.
It's a shame but there's nothing we can do.
What's done is done.
The one who just invaded the Whale Forest
is probably a pirate, Straw Hat Luffy.
He's their-teia captain but I'm sure
the Guardians will show no mercy!
They were killed!
She said there's a corpse -
which means they weren't cannibalized.
That's not the problem! Cut it out!
Calm down!
Old "Spiral Eyebrows" is with them.
He won't let anyone be killed.
Yeah. They're not gonna
be killed that easily!
This must be a trick to make
us upset and submissive!
You're right. I can't believe it.
How can I calm down?!
I mean, didn't you hear what she said?!
She said "corpse," okay?!
They must've killed Nami and the others
and ripped off their clothes!
Are they the only tribe
living on this island?
Are they really a cannibal tribe?
We need to check these things out.
Why are you so obsessed
with cannibal tribes?!
We have to find out
if they're our enemies or not.
You're right but I'm scared!
First, we have to collect information.
Tra-guy-kun.
Your friends must be here, right?
Yeah.
--Is there any way to make contact?
--No.
I didn't even expect to see them again.
But now I remember.
I forgot that I had a Vivre Card.
It belongs to our navigator, Bepo.
Oh yeah, you had a talking
polar bear in your crew!
Is he a Mink too?!
Yeah.
This is where he came from.
But he didn't remember much
about this island.
Because he left the island
when he was little.
Can we trust him?!
For instance, just for instance, you know,
he might become aware of his nature
as a member of the cannibal tribe!
You have a pretty wild imagination too!
I've known him for a decade.
We can trust him.
If you wanna get reliable information,
let's head straight.
Oh, I looked around from up there before!
If we go straight, there'll be a town!
We don't know who are there!
Are we gonna be okay?!
The cannibal tribe might be there.
It's better than going along
with the unknown animal.
Let's follow him.
IN THE WHALE FOREST
Gum-Gum...
Moo Golova!
...Bell!
Why isn't Electro having any effect?!
What's wrong with you-gara?!
How can you be unhurt after
getting that attack?!
That didn't work
because I'm made of rubber.
Rubber?
It's my turn!
Gum-Gum...
...Bell!
That's...
Yeah, that's Straw Hat!
That's it! Stop right there!
I know him!
Even if you know him, he's an invader!
I guess we gotta stop you by force!
Don't get in our way!
No! Jean Bart!
--Damn! This is too much to handle!
--He's too strong!
Keep napping.
I'm gonna knock you down!
Come on!
Oh no!
When Roddy gets mad like that,
no one can stop him!
Bring it on!
That's enough, Guardians!
A fluttering object!
A banana!
Yeah! I got a banana!
RODDY - A BULL MINK
THE WHALE FOREST GUARDIANS
BB (BLACKBACK) - A GORILLA MINK
Yum! Yum, yum, yum...
So this is how you handle them.
A dog?
WANDA - A DOG MINK
THE BATTLEBEAST TRIBE
You-teia are Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
I'm Wanda.
CARROT - A RABBIT MINK
THE BATTLEBEAST TRIBE
She's Carrot.
And a rabbit.
We won't do anything to you
so stop resisting.
There are a bunch of strange
creatures in this country.
It's like having a ton of Choppers.
Do you know me?
Of course.
What's with them?!
I didn't even do anything
but they attacked me!
That's because you-teia invaded the
forest where you mustn't enter.
Oh! Wh-What are you doing?!
The Guardians eject
invaders from this forest.
That's their job.
So I wasn't allowed to enter?
No, you weren't.
Guardians!
We'll take him out of here!
Please forgive him!
For Wanda's sake...
Let's retreat, Roddy!
BB!
Pedro!
Everyone, retreat!
What?!
Was I surrounded?
I didn't sense them at all.
Just be thankful this wasn't a moonlit night.
Straw Hat! It's been a while!
Hey, Straw Hat, don't you remember us?
We took care of you after the Paramount War!
I'm shocked!
Oh! You're the talking
bear from Tra-guy's crew!
Tra-guy?!
No, we work under Trafalgar Law!
BEPO - NAVIGATOR OF THE HEART PIRATES
THE GUARDIANS' HELPER
The Heart Pirates!
That's what I said.
No, you didn't!
Well, we've been reading newspapers!
There was a whole bunch of surprising news!
--We're allied, aren't we?
--Is our captain here too?
Yeah, Tra-guy's here!
You got it wrong again! Who is that?!
Tra-guy is Law.
Oh yeah? I didn't know that.
So our captain, he's here! Yeah!
Captain, I can't wait to see you!
KURAU CITY AT THE CENTER
OF THE ELEPHANT'S BACK
I guess there's no doubt
that it was attacked.
This city could have as many as
several hundred thousand residents
but not a single person is here.
It's dangerous!
This country's dangerous!
Let's get out!
As soon as we find Sanji and the others!
It's dangerous!
This place is really dangerous!
There are signs that people
were just here until recently.
It must've just happened.
This destruction happened
not so long ago, either.
We shouldn't be out in the open like this!
The enemies must be around here still!
They'll get us! They'll
get us! They'll get us!
Is this a device for torture?
We can't even tell
whether the enemies are humans or not.
Franky! Don't get too far...
What are those scratches?!
There are so many claw marks.
Yeah, what are those?!
Hey, come see this.
It's a giant footstep.
Do you think it's an elephant?
This city is dangerous!
We'd better get out...
What the hell is that?!
Did some monsters and beasts attack
the Minks' country?
But looking at those claw marks,
it might be internal discord.
One thing is for sure.
This country was suddenly ruined
only one or two weeks ago.
Th-Then Sanji and everyone else...
were involved in it?!
Ruined?
That's why no one's there.
This centuries-old country's name is
Mokomo Dukedom.
When I trace my memories back
to just a half-month ago,
I can see everyone's happy face.
This country was ruined by...
...Jack!
Jack...
Oh! What is it?!
What the...?!
What's going on?!
There'll be a Rain-Ruption!
Climb a tree!
A Rain-Ruption?!
Get on Warney!
I'll take you to the Rightflank!
Your friends are there!
Great! So Sanji and the others are there!
What's wrong?!
They're all there, aren't they?!
With a heavy Rain-Ruption falling from above,
Luffy, Wanda, and the others head
desperately for the Rightflank Forest!
When a hidden Mink fortress finally
reveals itself in a thick fog,
Luffy finally gets to see
Nami and everybody again!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Garchu! The Straw Hats Reunite!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!