I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
Luffy and the rest met
Wanda and Carrot from the Mink Tribe
and were guided to the place
called the Rightflank Fortress.
There, they finally reunited
with Nami and the others.
And by 10 days ago,
most of the country had been destroyed.
But on that day,
Nami and the others arrived here.
That can only be described as a miracle!
If not for their courage
and Chopper's medical expertise,
every single person in the Mokomo Dukedom
would've been helplessly killed...
I know it's just happened and it still hurts
so if you don't wanna talk
about it, that's fine but...
No, I'll tell you everything.
You-teia people have the
right to know everything.
Wanda! Duke Dogstorm said
he'd like to see the saviors!
Okay, I'll be right up!
You-teia guys, will you come with me?!
"A Threat Descends!
The Beast Pirates, Jack!"
Captain!
You came for us!
I missed you!
All the members of the
Heart Pirates are here!
Bepo, do you wanna squash him?
What?
Sorry, sorry!
Captain, I'm so amazed to know
that you beat Doflamingo!
No, that's Straw Hat-ya's...
We have a lot to catch up on!
Let's go deeper into the forest!
Okay.
THE RIGHTFLANK FORTRESS
Going through this passage is the shortest way to
get to Duke-sama's sanatorium.
That's curious. Do those fruits emit light?
That's right.
They light up the darkness of the night.
Oh, that's interesting!
There are other things
in the fortress that...
--What's wrong?
--One of you is missing.
What?!
Boy! Where did Luffy go?!
Oh?
What are you doing, Luffy?!
Look at these grapes!
They're growing everywhere!
I can drink as much as I like!
Come join me! It's very sweet!
Are you gonna drink more?!
I'm already full!
Come back here now!
Okay!
See! I knew that'd happen!
Oh man, that was good!
I like this place!
I'm so happy to hear that.
Although, we don't usually use this place.
The capital of the Mokomo Dukedom was...
...Kurau City which you-teia people saw.
Vibrant and bustling.
That's what it was like in Kurau City.
Neigh!
We got some good ones today!
I ran fast and picked up the ones that...
...the morning Rain-Ruption provided!
It's all fresh today!
--Oink! Here you go!
--What? That's too many...
Well, you always shop at our store.
So that's a treat for you.
Little guy. Thank you for
shopping with us! Oink!
Uh-huh!
It's been a while.
Oh, did you gain some weight?
You got fatter too!
Garchu! I'm so glad that
both of us are doing fine!
Hi! It's a lovely day, isn't it?
It is! Drop in for a cup of tea later.
I'm getting a little bit drowsy...
Kurau City was peaceful and relaxed.
People were leading normal lives.
They were talking with their friends,
loving their families,
and enjoying the blessings of nature.
But it happened half a month ago.
What in the world happened?!
By the time we got here,
the city was completely destroyed.
As if a storm had just swept through.
It was 17 days ago to be exact.
Yes, the first time in a month and a half
since Bepo and the others arrived,
the visitor's bell rang
all over the Mokomo Dukedom.
But that was...
...the seldom-heard Raiding Bell!
I gotta warn everybody!
No! Don't tell me...
What's that bell?
That's the Raiding Bell!
--What?!
--Raiding?!
No wonder a young lady like
you-gara doesn't know.
It rarely rings.
The gate has been broken down! It's pirates!
Kick them out!
Something stinks.
That horrible smell is getting stronger!
Cutting up the forest along the way,
the enemy invaded our peaceful city.
Feeling such unusual movement,
Zunesha roared!
Who were they?! What did they want?!
If our vicious enemies want
something that we don't have,
how can we give it to them?
A mammoth?!
Why's that prehistoric animal here?!
Alright, give him to us now!
I know you have a warrior from the
Land of Wano named Raizo here!
Raizo?
Is that what your enemies wanted
and you people didn't have?
A warrior from the Land of Wano? Raizo?
We don't know such a person!
D-Don't mess with this country! Get out!
So it was real!
The unknown country of the Mink Tribe!
You silly animals talk a lot!
Identify yourselves!
Who are you-gara people?!
Who do you think
you're asking to identify themselves?!
This man right here is...
...the infamous Emperor
Kaido-sama's right-hand man!
One of the three henchmen
who are called "Disasters"!
JACK THE DROUGHT
A PROMINENT MEMBER OF THE BEAST PIRATES
THE CAPTAIN OF THE MAMMOTH
Jack the Drought-sama!
The land that he passed through...
...will be destroyed -
ruined as if a drought occurred.
Now, hand over Raizo,
the warrior from the Land of Wano, to us!
You don't want your quiet life
in which you can hold your kid...
SHEEPSHEAD
THE HEADLINER OF THE GIFTERS,
THE BEAST PIRATES
...to be threatened!
How can we hand over someone who...
Or do you wanna fight?! Huh?!
We definitely don't want to fight.
Mon-ji!
However, we need you to listen to us
in order to come to an agreement.
We can't hand over someone who isn't here.
Jack-san, we Minks don't lie.
What was the name of the person?
Raizo!
Yes, if you want to look for this Raizo,
you can go from door to door...
He has no mercy
even for women, children, or elderly people!
That infernal monster!
He's not going to listen to us!
Are we here to talk, Gin-Rummy?
No, Jack-sama.
We're here to capture a samurai.
Raizo is not a samurai, you idiot!
He's a ninja!
Cut it out, Sheepshead-sama!
Samurai is a general term for
all kinds of warriors from the Land of Wano!
Either way is okay!
Samurai and ninja aren't the same!
I only have one demand!
Bring Raizo here!
M-Mammoth?!
Hey, Usopp! She said it was a mammoth!
What?! Is that what you
find most interesting?!
She mentioned the Four Emperors!
So it was Kaido's subordinates
who attacked this country.
That's right.
We don't know anyone named Raizo!
Stop asking for the impossible!
We really don't know!
How can we tell you
about someone we don't even know?!
Then, search the length and breadth
of the country! Pleasures!
My boy!
Silly kid! Show them how merciless we can be!
Ouch!
What the...
You squirt!
Get him!
Ouch!
What are you guys doing?
Ow!
What's with them?!
How pathetic they are!
We have no weaklings in this country!
All of us Minks are born
to be gifted fighters!
Even a baby knows how to defend himself!
You-gara people, do you think you can
fight all the people in this country?
We even have highly-trained Musketeers
whose abilities are beyond words!
If we fight, both of our
troops will get hurt!
If you want to look for someone,
could you at least have a talk with
the duke of our country?
A talk?
I refuse!
Gifters! Come forward!
Okay!
What's with their-gara bodies?!
Alright! Destroy the country
and find the samurai!
We have no choice.
Let's fight, everyone!
They didn't listen to us at all
and the fight began.
The peaceful Kurau City was...
...instantly turned into a battlefield!
So that's why everybody moved to
the Rightflank Fortress here.
That's right.
Those who could walk
helped those who couldn't
and carried them here.
Hey. So in the end,
you don't know why that Jack guy was
looking for the samurai, do you?
No. We also don't know
how they-teia got to this island
or what made them think
that the samurai was here.
I bet the mammoth was so big!
Don't get excited!
Now isn't the time for that!
Oh, it's a suspension bridge!
Hey, Luffy!
What are you doing?! Hey! Stop!
We're gonna fall! We're gonna fall!
Hey, stop, you idiot!
Get your hands off of it!
Oh, that was fun!
No, it wasn't!
Let's keep going.
We'll get to Duke-sama's sanatorium soon.
By listening to Wanda-san's story,
you know why I said "samurai" and "Land
of Wano" are taboo now, don't you?
You're right.
What bad people!
So if you use those words,
you'll anger them and make them hate you.
So, anyway...
The ninja that Kin'emon was
talking about isn't here!
What a letdown!
What?
The Gifters, a creepy group
of Devil Fruit eaters,
and the Musketeers, an elite
corps of the Mink Tribes,
are thrown into a deadly struggle!
However, when it seems like they are helpless
before the overwhelmingly strong Jack,
the mightiest warrior of
the Minks finally shows up!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The King of the Day! Duke Dogstorm Appears!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!