I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
Kurau City was peaceful and relaxed.
People were leading normal lives.
They were talking with their friends,
loving their families,
and enjoying the blessings of nature.
But it happened half a month ago.
The gate has been broken down! It's pirates!
Kick them out!
This man right here is...
...the infamous Emperor
Kaido-sama's right-hand man!
One of the three henchmen
who are called "Disasters"!
Jack the Drought-sama!
I only have one demand!
Bring Raizo here!
How pathetic they are!
We have no weaklings in this country!
All of us Minks are born
to be gifted fighters!
If we fight, both of our
troops will get hurt!
If you want to look for someone,
could you at least have a talk with
the duke of our country?
I refuse!
Gifters! Come forward!
Okay!
They didn't listen to us at all
and the fight began.
The peaceful Kurau City was...
...instantly turned into a battlefield!
By listening to Wanda-san's
story, you know why I said
"samurai" and "Land of Wano"
are taboo now, don't you?
You're right.
So if you use those words,
you'll anger them and make them hate you.
So, anyway...
The ninja that Kin'emon was talking about isn't here!
What a letdown!
What?
"The King of the Day!
Duke Dogstorm Appears!"
Ninja?
Bone-Bone Chop!
Chop! Chop! Chop!
By "ninja," you mean
a warrior from the Land of Wano?
You-teia, do you know something?
We're just teaching him a lesson about minkship!
So never mind!
Garchu! Garchu!
But I'm sure I heard him
say "ninja" just now.
No, no, he definitely
didn't say such a thing!
Oh, "kanja (patient)"!
He was asking how the patient is doing!
The patient?
Oh, I heard him wrong!
You-teia people are kind!
You care about our Duke-sama so much!
Of course, we do!
Ni... Ni...
Garchu!
It doesn't hurt at all...
And are we almost there
at the patient's house?
Yes, I see Duke-sama's sanatorium already.
Thank you for coming with me.
I'll tell you the rest of the story later.
DUKE DOGSTORM'S SANATORIUM
We're sorry, Shishilian-sama!
Please forgive us!
Shishilian-sama is raging out of control!
What's going on?
Shishilian-dono! What's the matter?!
Oh, Wanda!
They-gara kept saying sweet things so...
...I just pushed them off the cliff!
FULL-POWER SHISHILIAN (A LION MINK)
THE CAPTAIN OF THE DOGSTORM MUSKETEERS
Generosity!
Love! Romance! Babies!
Sugar! Honey!
Don't ever talk about sweet stuff
in my presence!
Or I'll bite out your windpipe!
Now, climb up here without help!
He's so strict but very cool!
Alright, stand up.
He's doing this to us because he loves us.
I know.
This is his way of trying to train cowards like us.
He's so generous!
What did you just say?!
What?!
How could you talk about such sappy stuff
like love or generosity...
...so soon after I told you not to!?
But still, he's cool...
We're sorry!
We'll never say anything sweet again!
--All right then!
--Shishilian-dono.
What?!
They-teia are the Straw Hats.
Thank you for saving my country!
I'll be indebted to you forever!
Shishilian-dono puts all
his power into everything.
What an annoying lion.
Who is your-gara captain?!
I am.
Oh!
So you-gara are Nami and the others' captain!
Great! I couldn't wait to see you!
Garchu!
I thank you, really, from the bottom of my heart!
Ow, ow, ow, ow! It's hot!
The duke is expecting you!
You can go in! Hurry up!
What's wrong with him?!
Luffy and everybody!
He's huge!
DUKE DOGSTORM
THE KING OF THE DAY, THE MOKOMO DUKEDOM
Duke-sama! I'm glad that you're okay!
Wanda. I'm sorry to make you worry.
So you-gara people are the Straw Hats?
Yeah.
You saved us in every way.
Thank you very much.
I heard my crew saved your people
but I haven't gotten to hear the whole story yet.
Well, you-gara and the rest saved us too,
Straw Hat Luffy-kun.
Anyway, I bet you're strong!
I mean, really strong!
What?! That's rude!
Duke-sama is the mightiest warrior in the country!
Hey, stop.
That's not what you call a loser.
You're not a loser!
The enemies were surely troublesome
but we had the upper hand!
He's drooling!
I know how you feel! He-teia saved us too!
What a delicious-looking savior.
You're not fully recovered yet so...
--not now.
--Not now or ever!
Oh, come on! A little won't hurt!
"A little" could kill me!
You don't know how much I got sucked on and chewed on
the past few days!
Well, let's not talk about the loss.
You-gara, that straw hat
looks quite good on you.
I was once...
Oh, I can't remember who it was!
That cat...
Master Cat Viper.
I was once traveling across the seas
with that one.
Shanks who is one of the Four Emperors now
was wearing that kind of hat then.
What?!
Old man, do you know Shanks?! How?!
I got this hat from him and...
He fell asleep!
It's already six o'clock.
It's only six! He's not a kid!
Hey, wake up!
Tell me how you know Shanks!
Hey! Hey!
Stop it, Luffy! He's still injured!
Like I mentioned earlier,
the Mokomo Dukedom is governed by two rulers all the time.
Duke Dogstorm is the official ruler but...
...Master Cat Viper who guards the old sacred Whale Forest
possesses the same right.
What does it have to do
with him falling asleep?!
I said "Stop"!
They really don't like each other.
When they come face to face,
they might try to kill one another.
--Kill one another?!
--Why?!
I don't know why.
I heard they used to be best friends.
But they're both well-respected kings
so even if they fight, it'll be an equal match.
They had too many fights
and they don't even wanna face each other now.
So one of them, from six in the morning
to six in the evening with the sun
and another from six in the evening
to six in the morning with the moon.
That's how they split their living hours.
They hate each other that much?
I didn't realize the
doctors were sleeping too!
All of the people in this fortress
should be sleeping now.
I'm getting tired. Grr...
You are...
Shishilian! Always at full power!
You don't have to yell! I hear you!
The day-and-night shifts
are affecting us too.
The people of the city are active
during the day.
And the people of the forest...
...are nocturnal...
At full power...
He fell asleep.
They're funny!
We've always lived
with the custom of having two rulers.
Even during the recent battle.
The fight between Jack's group and us in Kurau City
was intensifying.
Where is the samurai?!
Give us Raizo!
Get out of this country!
Find him!
I know Raizo is in this country!
Spit it out! Where is Raizo?!
Find him!
Stop!
Don't destroy the city anymore!
If nothing is done...
Where's the samurai?!
I don't know! I really don't know!
Then, go to hell.
Here come the Musketeers!
Great! Let them-gara handle it!
Everyone else, just step back!
Minimize damage!
THE MUSKETEERS
Try to disarm them!
--Let's go!
--Okay!
What's wrong with them-teia?
So creepy!
There are some odd warriors here.
--Is that a race we don't know?!
--They-teia have strange abilities!
Watch out for those with black horns!
--Where is Raizo?!
--We don't have such a person here!
Wolf Grip!
His hand turned into a wolf!
Go to hell!
Wanda!
You-gara, step back!
Shishilian-dono!
THE THREE DOGSTORM MUSKETEERS
The Three Musketeers!
All available Musketeers,
lead the citizens to the forest!
Alright! Let's evacuate to the forest!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
I'll beat the hell out of them at full power!
Who are they?!
Dammit, you monster!
Duke Dogstorm!
Duke-sama!
Duke-sama came to save us!
Duke Dogstorm!
You're Jack, aren't you?
Stop this vandalization and violence now!
You must be the ruler of this country!
Electro sparks the fire away!
The Rain-Ruption pours down!
When Duke Dogstorm and the
Musketeers are desperately
fighting a defensive war to stop Jack,
the other raging ruler runs through the forest at dusk,
roaring with anger!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The King of the Night! Master Cat Viper Emerges!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!