kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
It's awesome!
So this is the back of the elephant!
They met the Mink Tribe and
reunited with Nami and the others
at the Rightflank Fortress.
Then they were guided to the sanatorium
where Duke Dogstorm, the King of the
Day of the Mokomo Dukedom, rests.
Duke Dogstorm is the official ruler but...
...Master Cat Viper who guards the
old sacred Whale Forest
possesses the same right.
They really don't like each other.
They had too many fights
and they don't even wanna
face each other now.
So one of them, from six in the morning
to six in the evening with the sun
and another from six in the evening
to six in the morning with the moon.
That's how they split their living hours.
The day-and-night shifts
are affecting us too.
The people of the city are active
during the day.
And the people of the forest...
...are nocturnal...
We've always lived
with the custom of having two rulers.
Even during the recent battle.
Dammit, you monster!
Duke Dogstorm!
Duke-sama!
Duke-sama came to save us!
You're Jack, aren't you?
Stop this vandalization and violence now!
You must be the ruler of this country!
"The King of the Night!
Master Cat Viper Emerges!"
Duke-sama!
So you are...
Indeed. I am the ruler of the Mokomo Dukedom!
Stop this vandalization and violence now!
I swear that the person you-gara
people are looking for isn't here!
It's no use! This is a senseless fight!
You silly animal!
How many times do we have to tell you?! Huh?!
If you don't want us to destroy your country,
just give us the samurai already!
And how many times do we
have to tell you-gara?!
That person is not here!
Not here! Not here! Not here!!
Look all over the country
and bring him here, I said!
That's impossible!
That's enough!
We'll kill them all!
Destroy everything in the country!
Understood!
In that case, we'll just fight back!
Wait!
What'll you do by yourself?!
What?!
Duke-sama!
Why did you drop your sword?!
We're not gonna resist!
You can search the country or the island...
...for that samurai, all you want!
So stop the destruction!
This country has a glorious history!
I refuse!
Duke-sama, run!
Duke-sama!
That's our Jack-sama!
You bastard! How dare you kill Duke-sama!
Calm down, Wanda!
Shishilian-dono!
Whoa-whoa! What's with that dog?!
He withstood Jack-sama's attack!
That's our Duke Dogstorm!
I didn't know they had such a strong guy!
I thought this was a
fairyland of fuzzy animals!
Screw you!
Our boss, Jack-sama
is a great pirate renowned
throughout the New World!
The bounty on his head is...
...one billion berries!
So just because you're a little strong,
don't think you can push your luck!
This underling sure is obnoxious.
Please!
It's a false accusation!
We're not hiding the samurai!
Let me make it clear!
We'll call off our attack as
soon as we get the samurai!
If you don't have him, it's your own fault!
That doesn't make any sense.
Let me tell you one more thing.
I like destroying stuff.
This is certainly a disaster!
All we can do is try to take down the
enemy leader and stop the battle now!
Kill them all!
Let's go!
What a tough guy.
That won't work.
I'm gonna crush you up!
That's how he broke open
the gate to Kurau City!
I'll take that challenge!
Duke Dogstorm, he's awesome!
He's strong like I thought!
But the enemy gave even
the mightiest warrior in
this country and the Three
Musketeers a hard time...
Jack the Drought! Sounds super bad.
He didn't listen to what
others had to say at all.
What a pain.
He's got a billion-berry bounty.
That's twice Luffy's, you know!
How strong this Jack guy is!
Doesn't matter!
I'll kick his ass someday!
And how did the battle go?
It got more intense from there.
That won't work!
Hyena Grip!
S-Shishilian-dono!
Leave it to us - the Three Musketeers!
Screw the Three Musketeers!
We the Gifters Grip Trio will...
...Beat you all to bits!
How dare you do that to our people!
If it's a three-on-three battle,
we the Three Musketeers will...
Win! Win! Win!
That's our Shishilian-dono!
He said "three-on-three"
but he took them down single-handedly!
So cool!
Here comes a Rain-Ruption!
--Musketeers, herd the Warneys!
--Yes, sir!
What the...
Sheepshead-sama! Look at that!
Rain? A big splash of water
is falling towards us!
He is as steady as rock
even with the Rain-Ruption.
Grab my hand!
It's the blessed rain!
We can turn the tables now!
What an unbelievable amount of rainfall!
Don't be intimidated by such rain!
Take their alligators!
Thanks to the Rain-Ruption,
we briefly gained the upper hand,
but once the water drained away,
they came back again.
Damn you monster!
That's Master Cat Viper's roar!
The Fool of the Night woke up!
Let's retreat, Musketeers!
--What?!
--Aren't we gonna fight with them?
No, the day-and-night shifts are working.
We can stay on the offensive
without giving them a break.
You're right!
Jack!
Don't think you-gara are
the only unreasonable man here!
Anywhere you go, you can find a fool!
PROTECT
It's my country when the moon is up!
I won't let any invaders get away!
THE GUARDIANS
Don't think you can get out of here alive!
--It's giant!
--A cat monster!
Jack-sama!
Master, the city is...
Never mind! I heard what's going on.
You came looking for a warrior
from the Land of Wano, didn't you?
I wouldn't let any samurai
step onto the island!
If they come in,
I'd be the first to bite them to death!
I'm Cat Viper!
The man who waits for the dawn of the world!
MASTER CAT VIPER
(THE KING OF THE NIGHT)
THE WARDEN OF THE WHALE FOREST
Jack-sama!
It must be the ancient version
of the Elephant-Elephant Fruit.
You ate such a rare fruit!
They've still got this many soldiers.
You fools are about to experience a terror
that you've never known before!
You should've withdrawn
while the dog was treating you nicely!
Master!
We have just as many soldiers
as some major countries!
And then there's us too!
Bepo!
You-gara guys are still under my care!
You don't need to fight!
It's not gonna work that way, Master!
Although I became a pirate,
this is still my home!
--To us...
--...It's our friend's home!
Don't speak as if you're full-fledged.
I'll destroy everything!
We'll fight back!
Jack, Dogstorm, and Cat
Viper put on a display
of animalistic savagery
beyond human understanding!
When it seems like the Minks have seized
a slim chance of winning
after their deadly struggle,
Jack impatiently executes
a horrifying secret plan!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Exterminated Capital!
The Twirly Hat Crew Arrive!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!