The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
We made it!
Ah! So that's the second island
in the Grand Line-- Little Garden!
W-What's with this island?!
Collier Shoot!
L-Little Garden?!
W-What's so little...
...about this island?!
This is an island of ancient times.
It's stuck in the age of the dinosaurs!
The duel has continued for 100 years now.
I've forgotten the reason for it.
But that doesn't matter, anyway.
Then why?!
Pride!
Man, he's huge...
This is Elbaf, the god of war's...
...judgment!
I didn't have his divine protection.
Who is it?! Come out!
You guys spoiled
the old giant guys' duel!
I'm gonna beat you up!
It's no use!
Your friends are going
to become my works of art!
Luffy!
Ahh. Such nice tea...
Luffy! What are you doing?!
Such... nice... tea...
Luffy!
What are you doing, you idiot?!
It's over for all of you.
This is my ultimate ability!
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
"Time to Fight Back!
Usopp's Quick Thinking and Fire Star!"
What an idiot! He missed his
target and hit his own friend!
Where'd his bullets go?!
Breeze Breath Bomb!
I forgot to mention it,
but my breath explodes.
Dammit! This is insane!
He had no bullets?!
Karoo! You alright?!
Hey! You come to your senses?!
Y-Yeah...
I'm awake! Thanks!
That attack was meant to burn
his clothes and the trap on it
to undo the mental manipulation!
I've had enough of that paint!
I refuse to let anyone else die!
Now I'm mad!
It's definitely weird. Damn weird.
Why hasn't anyone come
back after all this time?
Something must've happened to
Nami-san, Vivi-chan, and the rest.
In which case, this is no time to
be getting ready to cook a lizard!
Nami-san! Vivi-chan!
Hey! Say something! I love you!
What's this?
So what if you're mad?
Just look at your friends now!
So what?! They're still alive!
Are they, now?
All they need now is some
of Miss Golden Week's paint
and they'll be exceptional wax figures!
You're too late, Straw Hat!
That's correct!
You're not only late, but now you
can experience even more despair!
Move out!
Candle...
...Champion!
What's that?
It's said he once took down a
42 million-Berry bounty with this.
It's Mr. 3's ultimate artistic talent.
Now, Miss Golden Week!
Perform an artistic paint job on me!
Can I take a break after that?
Yes, of course! I'd actually
prefer you to stay out of this!
Like this, I am invincible!
This armor is as hard as iron,
and wrapped around me like velvet!
My form now...
...has no flaws!
S-So cool!
This is no time to be admiring him! Fight!
Alright! Gum-Gum...
--Paint job complete!
--Now, then!
...Pistol!
Champ Fight! Harvest Field!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
It's no use!
Not good! The guy's so solid
his attacks don't work!
Damn! The wax haze!
Wax?
Yeah! Why didn't I realize it?!
The fact it turns into
a mist means it can melt!
Luffy! Fire melts this guy's wax!
No matter how hard it is,
wax is still wax!
Zoro and all the others
hardened only moments ago!
We can save them!
What?! For reals?!
Yeah, for reals.
Don't admit that to them!
But even if you realize that now,
you have neither time
nor a chance of winning!
30 more seconds at most!
After that, their hearts
will completely stop!
As we speak, they're
probably writhing in pain
with what little consciousness
they have left
as they experience
the terror of dying!
We don't need 30 seconds!
I'll save them now!
Special Attack: Fire--
Breeze Breath Bomb!
Usopp!
Did you not hear him say you
have no chance of winning?
Dammit! There's no time!
Give it up!
Listen... Take this rope...
Oh? This looks like fun!
Whatcha planning?
Can I join in, too?
Karoo! Run!
Run!
Just run around all the candlesticks!
Everything you try is pointless!
Pardon me.
Crescendo Stone!
How many kilograms
can you endure, I wonder...
10 kilograms...
100 kilograms...
200 kilograms...
300 kilograms!
Damn nimble bird!
Give it up! Give it up!
They've become my works of art!
I don't think so!
I won't let you have their lives!
If fire can melt them,
then I'll use this fire!
Don't pull! Stop!
Luffy! That small flame
won't do it fast enough!
Light Karoo's rope on fire!
The bird's rope?!
It's a special rope...
...soaked in oil!
--Okay! Everyone! Wake up!
--Hey! Wait! Stop!
It'll be a little hot, but endure it...
Stop!
Oww! Hot! Hot!
What a big fire!
Are they gonna be alright?!
Curse you... Curse you, Straw Hat!
How dare you destroy
my Candle Service Set?!
You'll pay for this!
I won't let you get away, you jerks!
Damn it! How dare you mock us?!
Now you've done it!
Playtime is over!
I'm going to shatter that
neck of yours into pieces!
Special Attack:
10,000 Kilogram Guillotine!
This is bad!
That was hot! Couldn't you
have done it a different way?
Don't be fussy!
Just be thankful you were saved!
You're right. Thanks!
This doesn't seem real... We're alive!
The wax melted.
What a pain! We can't afford to
screw up our mission any further!
Mr. 5!
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
Fool! I've shown several times
that explosives don't work on me!
I'm an "explosive man"!
You took the bait!
So sorry! I'm a liar, you see!
That wasn't an Exploding Star!
It was a Special Tabasco Star!
Spicy!
I already proved its
effectiveness the hard way!
Damn you pirates!
How dare you make a mockery of me?!
Time to blow up in a full-body explosion!
There won't even be bone fragments left!
No! Stop!
Usopp!
No! I'm sorry! I won't do it anymore!
Flaming Oni...
...Giri!
Flaming swords aren't too shabby.
Zoro!
Yo. Good to see you're alive.
Yeah.
Master...
That leaves two foes left.
Bird!
Don't let them get away with this!
Real men don't spoil people's fights!
How good of you to come!
Welcome to my Wax-Wax Manor!
What is this?!
Well, then. Can you tell where I am?
It would appear you picked a
fight with the wrong people!
We're the most intellectual
team in all of Baroque Works!
A brute-force buffoon like you who
acts on instinct cannot catch us!
I am Mr. 3. I carry out all
assignments given to me flawlessly.
Now, then! Step forward!
The moment your back is
turned to me, I'll stab you...
...right through the heart.
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
How... did you know...
...I was here?
A hunch.
Afternoons are definitely
best with Earl Grey.
Hold on, now!
This is no time for me to be
drinking tea all fancy-like!
Nami-san and the others might
be waiting for me to help them!
Still, though. What's such a
relaxing place doing in the jungle?
What's that?
Oh...
It's a Transponder Snail.
Heya. You've called the Damn Restaurant.
You want reservations?
Quit fooling around, dumbass.
Aren't you a bit late with your report?
Oh? Report?
And who might I be talking to?
It's me.
Mr. 0.
The world is awfully big
so even if there is treasure somewhere,
the odds are astronomical
So relying on dumb luck
won't get you anywhere
So even...
...if someone stops me or
laughs at me from the shadows
the ship will continue forward
Bon voyage!
Forget about them!
I know I'm a fool, but I gotta go
The crazier the dream,
the cooler the ambition
I know I'm a fool, but I'm gonna fight
The farther the sea,
the more heavenly it surely is
Do everything you can, and you'll
get a little nearer to any horizon
--I got my hands on this...
--An Eternal Pose to Alabasta!
--Yes!
--Now we can set sail!
Alright, everyone!
Let's have a rice cracker party!
Oh, no! We only have three left!
We can't have a rice cracker party!
You know this is no time for that!
Let's go, Captain! We don't
have time to be lounging around!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Farewell, Giant Island!
Head for Alabasta"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!