I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
They met the Mink Tribe who live there
The group listened to all the details of the battle
between the Minks and...
...the Beast Pirates led
by Jack, Emperor Kaido's
subordinate, that happened a half month ago.
Then, they learned Sanji was taken by
them two days ago, to a tea party...
...where his wedding with Emperor
Big Mom's daughter will take place.
This is my problem.
I'll be back.
Tell them "Hi" for me.
The Vinsmoke Family is,
well, to put it simply,
a family of assassins!
"Luffy's Decision!
Sanji on the Brink of Quitting!"
Sanji-kun is from a family of assassins?!
I don't know what you're talking
about and I don't care!
Grr! I'm sure you don't!
What we wanna know is
whether he'll come back or not!
He can get married if he wants!
But we don't wanna become Big
Mom's subordinates because of it!
So if they get married,
you guys become my subordinates!
Ouch!
Pekoms, are you okay?
--Luffy, you're funny!
--Understood, Lion Viper?!
Tell Big Mom so!
Watch what you say, you brat!
Or I'll destroy you!
Grr!
I owe you guys but don't push your luck!
Mama is one of the Four Emperors of the sea!
Uh-huh.
This is bad for my wound.
You have pretty eyes.
Shut up!
Well, either way,
he can't escape the marriage.
Why?!
Just like Black-Foot has gone to attend it,
no one can turn down an invitation
to Mama's tea party on any account.
If anybody turns it down,
he'll get himself...
...quite a shocking present.
Because he put Mama to shame.
A present?
It's not the kind of present you want.
He'll receive the decapitated head of a person
who was close to him!
A head?!
It could be a head of someone
from the Straw Hats...
...or someone from the restaurant
in the East Blue.
Oh, it could be someone
from the Kamabakka Kingdom.
No...
Hey!
How do you guys know about all those things?!
That's what power can do, Straw Hat!
What he was told at that
time must have been...
When someone as powerful as that makes
a threat, it's definitely not idle.
Who can fight it?
That's how powerful the Four Emperors are!
There's really nothing you can do about it!
That's why Sanji-kun had no choice but to go!
There's one other thing.
Let me ease your worry, my saviors.
You guys will not become
her subordinates. Grr!
It's a political marriage.
Mama always forms a connection with
those who'll become her subordinates.
So this marriage is a ritual to form a
connection between the Vinsmoke
Family and the Charlotte Family.
It's got nothing to do with you guys.
Do you want me to break it down for you more?
From the moment they get married,
Black-Foot Sanji will no longer
be part of your crew!
That's totally unacceptable!
Sanji's my friend!
But he's Vinsmoke's son first!
Don't get mad at me! Grr!
I know Sanji will refuse such a marriage!
In the face of Mama
and the vicious Vinsmoke Family?
Well, I wonder if he can manage
to stay alive after he refuses.
What do you mean?!
Hey, Lion Viper!
What are you gonna do now?!
I'll go back to Mama after I get well.
He thinks he killed me,
that son of a gun - Bege!
But he can't get away with it!
Then, take me with you!
Luffy!
--Nami, I'm gonna go by myself.
--What?
Like Robin and the others said,
if we go together, it'd
seem like we want a war.
We don't have time for that.
I'll go by myself!
If I go with him, maybe I can sneak into the tea party
and ruin the wedding.
Screw you!
Are you asking me to harbor an enemy?!
Oh, sounds like fun!
Carrot, this is serious!
Okay, it's a deal!
H-Hey!
Ouch!
I'll get Chopper! Get well already!
You're not at liberty to decide that!
Ow, ow... Hey!
Wait, Straw Hat!
Zoro, you're here!
Did you hear all that?!
Just barely.
You're worried about Sanji, aren't you?
I'll kick you, fool!
I told you to forget about that idiot!
Hey!
Luffy! Zoro! How's Pekoms doing?!
Oh, Chopper!
He's crying from pain and banging
his head against a wall and yelling!
Cure him now!
Those are crazy symptoms!
I'll check him right away!
Well, he can move around which
means he's fine, I guess.
You're right.
Garchu! Baron Corpse!
What? Hey!
--Garchu! Garchu!
--Hey!
Hey, stop! No! Hey!
Garchu!
You look so delicious, Baron Corpse!
Help me! I'm in a bigger state
of emergency than anyone else!
No, don't just watch and laugh!
Oh! You-gara are Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?!
I couldn't wait to meet you!
What?! Why did you follow us?! Get rest!
I just got better!
No, you didn't!
He's huge! Is that Cat Viper?!
He's a cat monster!
A Garchu of thanks!
Cat Viper's spouting blood!
Hey, what are you doing, cat monster!?
Stay with me! Cat Viper!
He's really big! And so fluffy, too!
The cat monster!
Get off of him, Luffy!
He may not look it but he's heavily injured!
What's going on?
I'm out of blood!
Bring me some blood quick!
Okay, Dr. Chopper.
Th-Th-Th-Thank...
What's wrong, Chopper?!
Cat monster, stand up! I'll cut you up!
Whoa-whoa, he's injured.
Who cares!
I'll run him through all nine of his lives!
No, don't!
Oh, Tra-guy!
Oh! Are they your friends?!
Yeah, I came to introduce them to you.
They're my crew - 20 in total!
It's nice to make your
acquaintance! Straw Hat!
THE HEART PIRATES
Yeah!
We need to talk.
What?! Is that it?!
Slighted! Slighted!
Slighted! Slighted! Slighted!
We feel slighted, Captain!
We're pirate allies, aren't we?!
Introduce us to the Straw Hats properly!
He's right, Captain!
We're just allies.
We don't necessarily have to get friendly.
Stay with me, Cat Viper!
Help me...
What?! Black-Foot-ya went to see Big Mom?!
Uh-huh.
How in the world could that happen?!
Don't worry!
I'm gonna go take him back!
So could you wait to fight
Kaido a little bit?!
That's not my call!
It's only a matter of time
before Kaido comes after us!
I thought we could hide ourselves
here in Zou for a while
but they know where it is.
Even if their target is us
next, what do you think
will happen to this country
if it's attacked again?!
How kind of you!
Since when were they there?!
Garchu!
You-gara guys, are you really pirates?!
Thank you for caring about us
on top of saving us!
Thank you! Garchu!
Garchu, Baron Corpse!
I can't take it anymore...
Oh, Pekoms, are you hurt?
--Yeah...
--Well, who cares!
Oh, you came around!
Stay quiet this time!
Okay, let's have a banquet!
Bring drinks and food!
Why, Cat Viper?!
I'm in!
No!
Banquet!
We're gonna have the greatest
night of our lives!
Cheers!
Yummy!
Oh yeah?!
Grill more! Our saviors are hungry!
--Let's keep grilling!
--Yeah!
Cheers!
Master!
Here is the main dish!
Lasagna-meow!
Wow! Yum-yum!
Don't be shy!
You-gara guys, enjoy the
Whale Forest's Special
Lasagna as much as you like!
Yeah! I'll have some!
Yummy!
You're right! This is quite good!
Yeah? Let me have it!
Oh?
It feels like I'm forgetting
something important...
Well, never mind!
Seems like Luffy-san and the others are
completely forgetting about it.
But we mature adults must
get our act together.
That's right.
This country doesn't want them.
Yeah! Under no circumstances
should a samurai enter!
After all, Raizo-san, the
person Kin'emon-san and
Kanjuro-san are looking for,
isn't here so there's no point.
In addition, because of that,
the millennium-old city was ruined!
Bring Raizo here!
Where's the warrior from the Land of Wano?
They call us saviors and thank us.
So we absolutely can't tell them
that we actually have some samurai friends.
If they find out that
Kin'emon and the others were
going to use this island
as their rendezvous point,
even the cheerful Minks would be pissed off.
I don't wanna fight them
after we got to know each other!
Let's keep guard all night long
to prevent Kin'emon and Kanjuro from entering.
We'll be in trouble if we
get tired and fall asleep.
Let's take turns. I'll go first.
No, I'll go first.
No, I'll keep guard!
--Let's do it together then.
--Okay.
THE NEXT MORNING
Well... Well, well, well,
it's still dark so it's before dawn.
We made it!
That's right! We finally made it!
Oh boy, it was a disaster
but all's well that ends well.
I'm sure Luffy-dono and everybody
are worried about us.
I feel bad.
Yes, they must've been waiting for us!
Well done, Torasaburo.
Tora (tiger)?!
Oh, I didn't know this animal was a tiger!
That's right! Nekozaemon should be happy
that his efforts weren't for nothing.
Alright, that's enough.
Revert to a painting!
But monkey fellow,
you didn't tell us anything after all.
I just wanna know
if a warrior named Raizo is...
I-I don't know anything-saru!
What's the matter? You look pale...
Oh, hey, wait! Where are you going?!
We can't look for Raizo on our own!
Wait, monkey fellow!
We need you to take us around!
Hey!
Wait!
Monkey fellow!
Oh no-saru! Samurai are here-saru!
I gotta let them know as soon as possible!
Samurai are here-saru!
The emergency bell rings
all over Zou once again!
Cat Viper and Dogstorm rush
towards Kin'emon and Kanjuro!
The Mink Tribe who are badly bruised
after getting their country ruined
because of some unknown samurai,
vent their unbridled emotions
against the two samurai!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Volatile Situation! The Dog
and the Cat and the Samurai!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!