kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
Oh no-saru! Samurai are here-saru!
I gotta let them know as soon as possible!
Samurai are here-saru!
"A Volatile Situation!
The Dog and the Cat and the Samurai!"
No! I fell asleep!
Hey, both of you, wake up!
Wake up!
We have a problem!
Kin'emon and Kanjuro must've arrived already!
What?!
Is it morning already?!
--Look.
--That drawing is...
Ryunosuke.
No! The one next to it!
It's a new drawing by Kanjuro!
--When did it appear?!
--While we were sleeping!
What kind of a pathetic animal is this?
I don't know for sure but
I think it's a tiger.
A tiger?!
Who cares?!
If they meet the Minks and say
they're looking for Raizo,
it's gonna be messy!
Right! Because of some samurai
named Raizo who isn't even here,
the Mokomo Dukedom was destroyed!
Anyway, we have to stop those two!
--Yeah!
--Let's go!
Hurry up-saru! Hurry up-saru!
This is serious-saru! This is serious-saru!
Samurai-saru!
Samurai are here-saru!
Bariete's ringing the bell!
Samurai-saru!
Samurai are here-saru!
Move! Get out of my way!
Out of my way!
Shishilian.
Let's go to the city!
Tell everyone who is capable to follow me!
Yes, sir!
Duke-sama! Your Warney is ready!
Listen, everyone!
Do as you've been told!
Shishilian-dono, what have we been told?!
We haven't been told anything!
All able-bodied people in the fortress,
go into action!
Follow Duke-sama along with me, Shishilian!
Of course, at full speed!
Let's go!
Yeah!
--Master!
--Pedro!
This is an extremely serious matter!
Don't fall behind!
Yeah!
Samurai! Two samurai appeared!
Follow Master!
Luffy, wake up!
Wake up!
Yeah, I can eat more!
Hey, Luffy!
You're still half sleep! Just wake up!
By the way, that bell is very noisy.
It's been ringing constantly.
Isn't it a bell to tell
everyone they have a visitor?
They must be welcoming us!
That's certainly possible!
But Law-dono was saying that...
...the inhabitants of Zou who don't like humans
are actually the Mink Tribe.
Yes, is that what people are saying?
I can't understand why.
If that's what people
are saying these days...
Who is it?!
Father! Kanjuro!
Momonosuke!
Kanjuro! So you're all right!
Ah, I'm sorry to make you worry.
I'm relieved!
Now, why are you here alone?
Where are Luffy-dono and everybody?
Actually, I haven't been at ease
since we came to this country
so I've been sleeping in a room by myself.
--Oh no!
--You poor thing.
And when I woke up, nobody was there
so I came looking for someone.
I see. Then come with us.
I guess they're assembling to welcome us!
There's no mistake!
Why?! Why?! Why?!
Why should I be running this early in the morning?!
I told you! Kin'emon and...
What was his name?!
Kanjuro!
Yes! Those two arrived!
They say two samurai appeared
and the whole country is in a great uproar!
Master Cat Viper headed for the city
leading the Guardians!
Another welcome banquet?!
I wouldn't mind having one for two consecutive days!
No, they've got a score to settle!
Of course, they do!
They were wrongly accused of hiding a samurai
and almost died!
Where are they?!
We'll find them right away!
People across the country
keep rolling into the city...
Pedro! Can you see them?!
What's wrong?!
This is no good.
Can't you find the samurai yet?!
We're on the hunt now!
--Find them as soon as possible!
--Yes, sir!
Master, please pull back!
--Pull back?!
--Hurry up!
Humph! What are you talking about?!
What?! Duke Dogstorm!
I'll pretend I didn't see him.
Please. Just keep going.
Oh...
Oh no! The two ran into each other!
You-gara...
Oh, shoot!
--Master!
--Duke-sama!
Please don't do it, Master!
Duke-sama! Please calm down!
Is it a fight?
That's...
What are you doing?!
Man! That was...
...Really close!
You three, take my advice
and go back to the Sunny now!
Oh, they're fighting!
Boy! If you go out there now,
it'd be like pouring gasoline on a fire!
How many years has it been, cat monster?
You've become even more monstrous.
What about you-gara?
You've lost one of your legs.
--What should we do?!
--Somebody, please stop them!
Where is Raizo?!
Give us Raizo!
I know Raizo is in this country!
We don't have such a person here!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Search through the country as you please!
We don't have a samurai...
I wonder if you'll say goodbye to this leg first,
or tell us where the samurai is.
Let's try it, "Dog King."
Then, there is no way
for me to save this leg.
You-gara got your hand chopped off.
You can't fight anymore.
The most you can do is eat lasagna.
Say it! Where's the samurai?!
How can I tell you the whereabouts
of someone who isn't here?!
A person from the Land of
Wano has no business here!
Then, we have no choice but...
...to kill these guys one by one.
All you can do is use poison gas
and attack the weakened men!
You cowards!
Oh no! This guy's trying to break the chains!
Is the gas really working?!
Immobilize his arms!
Yeah, you'd better do that!
If you have time to harm my people,
point your spear at me!
No... Master!
I'll take all of those crappy spears myself!
Master!
It's a shame that
you-gara have only lost one of your legs!
I wouldn't mind if you were dead.
One king is enough for the country!
Please stop, both of you!
Then let's send one of us to kingdom come!
You-gara must die!
A dog and a cat?!
Hey!
I heard about it before
but they're really strong!
Hey, wait!
Stop fighting!
Hey, you idiot! What are you doing?!
That's...
...a samurai!
See?! They found you!
Run, Kin'emon! They're gonna kill you!
--Momo-chan!
--Hey, let go of me! Please!
What are you gonna do?!
Momo, stay away!
Kanjuro! Why did you guys come out?!
Run! Now!
Cat Viper! Dogstorm! Wait a minute!
They really mean no harm!
People from the country of Zou!
I'm a retainer of the Kozuki Clan from
the Land of Wano, named Kin'emon!
I'm here to look for my comrade
named Raizo who is a warrior
from the same country!
Has he been here?!
Well, this country was destroyed
because he wasn't here!
Luffy!
Yeah!
--It's not looking good.
--Shoot! Should we fight?!
We've been expecting you.
I don't know Raizo! I swear to god!
If the man you're talking about is here,
you can take my life!
Raizo-dono is...
...safe!
Oh, he's safe! I'm relieved!
Whoa, wait a minute!
Hey, was Raizo here all this time?!
Did you all know?!
Y-Y-Y...
You all almost died!
The millennium-old city was ruined!
I'm sorry that we kept it a secret
from you-gara guys too.
The Land of Wano's Kozuki Clan
and we have been like a family since way back.
No matter what will be ruined,
we'd never sell out our friends!
A mysterious shadow in the dark night,
which runs with a rhythm!
He sneakily throws an 8-pointed shuriken,
and his mutable short
sword will cut down evil!
With these dreams of being a
ninja which all boys share,
Raizo the ninja finally shows himself!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Third One! Raizo of the
Mist, the Ninja, Appears!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!