I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
They met the Mink Tribe who live there
and listened to all the
details of the battle between
the Minks and
the Beast Pirates led by Jack, Emperor Kaido's subordinate,
that happened a half month ago,
and they also learned Sanji
was taken to a wedding
of himself and Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Then...
Stop fighting!
Hey, you idiot! What are you doing?!
People from the country of Zou!
I'm a retainer of the Kozuki Clan from
the Land of Wano, named Kin'emon!
I'm here to look for my comrade named Raizo
who is a warrior from the same country!
Has he been here?!
Well, this country was destroyed
because he wasn't here!
Raizo-dono is...
...safe!
Y-Y-Y...
You all almost died!
The Land of Wano's Kozuki Clan
and we have been like a family since way back.
No matter what will be ruined,
we'd never sell out our friends!
"The Third One!
Raizo of the Mist, the Ninja, Appears!"
JACK DIES!
THE PROMINENT MEMBER OF THE BEAST PIRATES
"Emperor Kaido's right-hand
man, Jack the Drought,"
"suspected of trading fire with
the Navy that was transporting
Doflamingo and presumed dead"?
That's bullshit!
--Hey!
--Yes, sir!
What do you think? Am I dead?
N-No! Definitely not!
You're alive, Jack-sama!
Too slow...
Why's this ship this slow?!
Go faster!
Yes, sir!
I'm deeply grateful to you all!
It's not a big deal! Don't mention it!
Thank you!
And now, as proof, I offer you this!
Yes, that's certainly the
same Kozuki Clan crest
that Duke-sama, Master and Raizo-san have!
Kozuki...
I can't believe they know each other!
I was really prepared for a
clash against the Minks! Jeez!
We were trying to keep the samurai a secret.
We were just beating our
bones against the wall.
I mean, heads.
It couldn't be helped.
They couldn't have told the whole story even to us.
You're right.
She just said the doggy and the kitty
have the same crest.
Maybe, their bond is far
stronger than we realize.
But Dogstorm, Cat Viper...
It is surprising to see you two
alive and well here!
Death would've been a relief to us.
But we thought if we trust the words
from that day and wait here...
Yeah, then we would get
to see you-gara guys one day!
Hey, cat monster!
What do you want, dog?!
I was talking to Kin'emon!
Don't interrupt as you please!
I was just thinking Kin'emon must be
sick of talking to you-gara
so I tactfully took over!
What did you say?!
Oh, here we go again!
I thought they were cooled down.
Well, when they're both present,
it's not gonna be peaceful.
Why do they hate each other so much?!
--You-gara served your purpose! Get lost!
--You get lost!
Please stop, both of you!
Our long-awaited guests have just arrived!
Stop fighting! Dogstorm! Cat Viper!
You two used to be such good friends!
Why have you been fighting like
you wanna kill each other?!
Because...
I forbid you to ever fight again!
It's even more inexcusable
if it's because of my father!
It would make my father sad
to see you two like this...
Oden-sama...
Momo?
Did you say it'd make your father sad?
But Kin'emon's right here.
Don't tell me...
I'm sorry!
Momonosuke-sama! I'm ashamed of myself!
You're absolutely right!
--What?!
--Duke-sama!
I can't believe Master's bowing his head!
Would that child be...
Momonosuke-sama is right!
Sama?
Hey, did you just use "sama"
when you mentioned Momonosuke?
Seems like it wasn't just
the Minks who had a secret.
Please forgive me for lying to you all, too!
To tell you the truth,
Momonosuke-sama and I are...
...not father and son!
What?!
This man right here is the heir to...
...Kozuki Oden-sama, great daimyo
of Kuri in the Land of Wano!
KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
THE HEIR TO THE DAIMYO OF KURI IN THE LAND OF WANO
His name is Kozuki Momonosuke-sama!
That means for all of us including
Dogstorm and Cat Viper,
he's our lord!
What?! Usopp!
What in the world is going on?!
What lord?! I don't understand!
The dog, the cat, Kin'emon
and Kanjuro are retainers
and Momo must be their master but...
I don't understand either!
So he's the heir of the Kozuki Family
and Oden-dono's son!
How could I miss that?!
Is Momo someone important?
If they're heading the list of his retainers,
he could be quite a powerful lord.
Along the way, if his true identity was revealed,
we could've attracted more enemies
so we pretended as if we were father and son.
Although we trusted you all,
we never had a good chance to tell you.
Sorry.
So you're not father and son.
But they're alike. They're both perverts.
I'm sorry that I was lying!
I'm actually an important figure!
Yes, and a pervert.
No, I'm not!
Whatever!
What do you mean by that?!
Bow down, Luffy!
No way! Why do we have to change our behavior
just because you're an
important person?! Idiot!
M-Momonosuke-sama!
You're afraid of heights
and you have no guts!
We samurai aren't afraid of anything!
How rude!
--You coward!
--What an insolent fellow!
Here we go again.
He saved our lives but...
You can't ask a pirate to be humble.
Momonosuke-sama's getting
distracted so that's good.
So frustrating, Onami!
Luffy is a terrible guy!
Oh, there, there.
Stay away from her, Momonosuke-sama!
You damn brat!
Hey!
Say, Momo-chan,
if your father is a lord, there must be
treasure in his castle, isn't that right?
Cut it out!
You're really a bad person!
It's only been a few months since...
Their-gara cheeriness must be helping him.
Momonosuke won!
You got me, Momo!
Yeah, because I'm a samurai!
Let's make a truce, cat.
If we keep dwelling in the past,
we'll make Momonosuke-sama suffer.
Okay, for the sake of our lord!
I'll communicate with you-gara
but won't connect with you-gara!
That's a deal!
Oh! Look at that!
Those two are... No way!
It's a miracle!
Our two kings made up!
The King of the Day and the King of the Night
finally...
How amazing the Kozuki Family's power is!
It makes me cry!
Dr. Miyagi! You're hopping too much!
This is, indeed, another miracle!
What happened to them suddenly?
--They're getting excited over something.
--Yeah.
It's beautiful.
It's a rainbow!
Let's climb the whale.
If you learn which vines to take,
you can reach the top.
So Raizo's here?!
--Yeah.
--Ya-hoo!
--Nin-nin!
Can't wait to see the ninja! Nin-nin!
I get to see a ninja! Nin-nin!
The Watery Escape Technique! Nin-nin!
I still don't feel well, Kin'emon.
You can wait at the bottom if you want,
Momonosuke-sama.
As we get closer to the whale,
the voice I hear is getting louder.
You have a similar ability to Oden-sama.
There was another man
who used to say something like that.
I was just thinking about the same thing.
Oh, I can't believe there's an entrance here!
On the tail of the Whale Tree?!
No one would notice!
And it's a hidden door
so it's impossible to find.
Let's go.
This place is cool!
Me first!
Hey! Don't go too fast!
Bye!
Wait!
It's a long flight of stairs so be careful.
Is that...
That's Raizo's voice.
What?! The ninja?!
Ninja!
Ninja! Ninja! Ninja!
--Ya-hoo! Where's the ninja?!
--Ninja! Ninja!
Here we are.
He-gara is the ninja, Raizo.
Ninja! Nin...
There you are, Cat Viper!
You! Why didn't you just
hand me over to them?!
RAIZO OF THE MIST - A NINJA
FROM THE LAND OF WANO
Everyone that brought me food here...
...was injured!
They told me the country is okay,
but is it true?!
If it's a lie, I, Raizo, will hate you!
What?!
He's nothing like we expected!
The King of the Pirates - Gold Roger,
the man who once attained everything
this world has to offer,
left behind the legendary
treasure of One Piece.
When Luffy finds a new Ponegliff,
the road to becoming the King
of the Pirates will be revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Red Stone! A Guide to the One Piece!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!