I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
In the tall Whale Tree on
the back of the elephant...
...lay one of the Road Ponegliffs
that hint at the location of the hidden Raftel.
The Kozuki Clan from the Land of Wano,
who created all the Ponegliffs...
...were Momonosuke's ancestors.
However, knowledge of how
to read and write the ancient
text written on those stones...
...was cut off at Momonosuke's
father, Kozuki Oden's generation
before it was passed down to Momonosuke.
Let's join hands!
We're allies!
Taking down Kaido and opening
up the Land of Wano.
To achieve the same goal,
they formed the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai
Alliance.
We met Tra-guy-kun and came to Zou
following the Vivre Card by chance
and found the Road Ponegliff
which points the location of Raftel by accident.
But according to Crocus-san
at the Twin Capes,
if you track logs,
every route will come to one in the end.
I'd always imagined that's Raftel.
Yes, I understand.
If you're interested where logs will lead you,
go see it yourself.
There is definitely a route on
which all of those three needles
point in the same direction
- towards one specific place.
However, you-gara people have
already left on a journey
which lies beyond that point.
What? What do you mean?
You're supposed to find out about
something for the first time
at the end of the route.
Find out the truth about
the Ponegliffs and the ancient script.
Find out about the civilization
that created those and the existence
of the hidden last island Raftel!
When Roger got there,
he had to do everything all over again.
Don't worry! You're on the right track.
Just keep going!
But for now, we have so many things
to do before fighting Kaido!
We need to prepare.
Like I told you before,
we're trying to recruit
samurai who will fight with
us in the Land of Wano now!
In the meantime, we've got
someone we need to see!
It's always good to have more reinforcements.
Who is it?
He is the former 1st division commander of
the Whitebeard Pirates...
Marco the Phoenix!
"The Nightmare Returns!
The Invincible Jack's Fierce Attack!"
Marco?
Yeah.
Really?
--I didn't expect to hear that name here.
--Marco... Marco...
Oh! So you guys are friendly with him!
That's good to know!
If he can back us up,
that's going to be a tremendous help!
No but wait a minute.
In the event a year ago, they...
Well, don't expect too much.
Even if we can find him,
there's only a little hope.
Marco... Marco...
I'm sure I know him...
You must've met him
in the Paramount War at Marineford!
Marco... Who was it?
Don't you remember?
He was Whitebeard's right hand!
They say he ate a very
rare type of Devil Fruit!
What? Rare?
He looks like a pineapple.
Oh, that guy!
1st division commander - Marco!
Thanks! You saved me!
Don't mention it!
Yeah, he was really strong!
Oh? Then why is there only a little hope?
--That's because there was this war.
--A war?
Yeah, it was a major clash between the
remnants of the Whitebeard
Pirates led by Marco
and the Blackbeard Pirates!
It's been a year since
the so-called Grudge War,
but we haven't heard about what happened to
the commanders yet.
If he's alive,
I think I know where he would be.
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Did they fight against Blackbeard?!
They did.
Both sides had reinforcements.
It was quite a large-scale battle.
And Marco and the others
suffered a crushing defeat.
Blackbeard came to be recognized
as one of the Four Emperors after the war.
I didn't know that.
Damn, Blackbeard!
That was a major incident!
You really have no idea about
what had happened
while you were under training.
Jimbei told me.
In the Paramount War,
after I passed out,
the Whitebeard Pirates saved my life.
I'm not gonna let you kill him!
Move out of my way!
The war is not over yet!
Take Ace's brother with you, Jimbei!
All right!
Straw Hat's life is how
Ace's life will live on!
We will protect him at any cost
on behalf of Ace!
If we let him die,
it's a dishonor to the Whitebeard Pirates!
I wanna see him again and thank him.
So just like Kin'emon,
we need time to prepare too.
Okay, got it!
Then, let's split up for now!
We will round up allies
and plot a strategy in the Land of Wano.
Are you gonna be okay there?
I thought you guys are being
targeted by the shogun.
We're fully aware of the risk.
But we're worried about our comrades there.
The Land of Wano is occupied by Kaido now,
right?
Your chances of encountering the
Beast Pirates are high and isn't it
hard to even enter the country?
Can't you do something with your ninjutsu?
It'd be hard to use it against everyone.
I see.
If you come on our submarine,
you'll be safe while traveling.
Oh, are you sure, Law-dono?!
--We'd like that!
--Please take us!
And...
...if you know a place to hide
on the island, you'll be alright.
I'll go look for Marco with my subordinates.
Our final targets are the shogun and Kaido.
If Kin'emon and the others
are headed there first,
we'd better meet up in the Land of Wano.
Let's make Kin'emon's Vivre Card.
Okay! It's a deal!
Uh-huh, understood.
Don't get lost, guys.
Look who's talking.
There he is! Raizo-dono!
Good to see you again!
What?
I'm glad that you're okay!
Raizo-san!
Y-You guys...?
--Let's have a celebratory banquet.
--It's ready!
A celebratory banquet?
What are we celebrating?!
Raizo-san's safety and...
The reconciliation of the two kings and...
The Kozuki Clan for reuniting safely!
Oh my!
Wh-What are you talking about?!
You damn Minks!
Sorry for locking you up!
We wanted to save you-gara
from Jack and the others!
Raizo-san!
We tied up your hands - did we hurt you?
Don't ask me about my hands!
You guys are way more wounded than I am!
How annoying!
Ninpo!
I-love-you Technique!
Raizo-dono!
Nin! Nin! Nin! Nin!
All right! Let's have a banquet!
Banquet! Banquet! Banquet! Banquet! Banquet!
Wait, Luffy!
We've already had a banquet!
Let's get going!
It's gonna be too late to save Sanji-kun!
What?! Are you coming?!
Of course, I'm coming with you!
I feel responsible.
Besides, do you think you can travel the sea
of the New World without a navigator?
I'm coming too! Pekoms is heavily injured!
He needs a doctor!
Plus,
who is going to play music
when you guys feel down?
Let's go and meet Master Cat Viper
Who needs that?
Hey! Don't exclude me!
We both allowed them take Sanji-san!
Kin'emon, do you mind if I take them with me?
You don't need my permission!
They're your crew!
And no one can stop someone
who is trying to save his friend!
I wish I could come along!
I'm in debt to Sanji-dono!
I'm sorry!
Now it's getting hard to sneak in.
Get out of there as soon as
you screw up the wedding!
We're gonna go along with Kin'emon
so you take care of Sanji!
--Uh-huh!
--Count on us!
Oh, Luffy.
Robin, are you gonna go with them?!
In case you find a Ponegliff,
can you take a rubbing for me?
--Okay!
--So light-hearted!
I'll do research on the Ponegliff that Kaido has
in the Land of Wano too.
Great!
Alright! Is that all for now?
Let's have a banquet!
Hm? What's wrong?
What is it?!
Is that...
What?! What?!
--Again!
--It's going the other way now.
The whole island is shaking!
Zunesha is crying out!
What's going on?!
Who's Zunesha?!
Huh? You're standing on it!
Oh! It's the elephant's name!
It's a big quake!
It's never happened before!
Who is it?! Whose voice is that?!
Oh no!
Room!
Shambles!
Captain!
Run! It's gonna collapse!
Strong Right!
Get away from the building!
--Hold onto the tree!
--Okay!
This way!
Hurry up now!
Thank you!
Who is it?! Who's talking?!
My bone's gonna break, break, break!
My bones go crack, crack, crack, crack!
Momonosuke-sama! Are you hurt?!
What's happening to Zunesha?!
If you're there...
Wh-Who is it?!
--I hear the voice again!
--Momonosuke-sama!
Luffy, what's wrong?!
"What's wrong"?!
You hear it too, right?!
Huh?! Hear what?!
Can't you hear it?!
--No way!
--Can he-gara hear it too?!
Hurry up!
Who the hell are you?!
It's the loudest ever!
Fire!
It's starting to work!
No wonder.
Normal elephants are panicked
by just one bee.
Take a good look at its body.
If it's really been living for a millennium,
its skin must've gotten weak!
Is it a living legend?
No! It's just an old animal!
Concentrate fire on its left foreleg!
More volleys!
Keep shooting!
If we can make it bend its knees
and it brings its face closer,
we can finish it off as we like!
I'd like to gouge its eyes out
and cut out its tongue!
Maybe we can cut its stomach up from within!
Hurry!
Give me an order!
If you are there!
Give you an order to do what?!
Answer me! Who are you?!
The giant elephant and
the ultra-giant elephant!
Jack and Zunesha's greatest-ever
battle is now on!
When Luffy and Momonosuke hear
the mysterious voice again
in the country of Zou, submerged in chaos,
an earth-shattering blow
with a howl strikes the sea of the New World!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Battle to Defend Zou! Luffy and Zunesha!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!