kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
Who is it?! Whose voice is that?!
If you're there...
Hurry up!
Who the hell are you?!
Give me an order!
Give you an order to do what?!
Answer me! Who are you?!
"A Battle to Defend Zou!
Luffy and Zunesha!"
Come on!
Answer me! Who are you?!
Hey, Luffy!
Who are you talking to?!
We can't hear anything!
I can only hear his voice!
He's not listening to me
and I have no idea who it is!
--What do you mean?!
--What the hell is going on?!
Gol D. Roger...
And Oden-sama as well.
I heard they experienced the same thing.
They heard a loud voice
but they couldn't get it to respond.
What?
Gold Roger?
Just run!
Thank you!
Everyone! Gather together in one spot!
Get away from buildings!
Flower Shuriken!
--Wow! That's our ninja!
--That's our ninja!
What is it?! What's happening?!
What's going on?
Cat.
Yeah, I guess something is happening
to Zunesha.
Momonosuke-sama!
We have to get away from here!
Momonosuke-sama! What's wrong?!
--Momonosuke-sama!
--Are you okay?! Momonosuke-sama!
Momonosuke-sama! Momonosuke-sama!
Momonosuke-sama!
What is this?
My head! My head... h-hurts!
This is...!
It's Jack!
Jack?!
Did he say Jack?!
Fire!
Fire! Keep firing!
Go! Shoot it to death!
Jack is...
Jack is attacking the elephant!
There are five powerful-looking
ships at nine o'clock!
--Zunesha is under attack?!
--As I thought, Jack wasn't dead.
Momo! How do you know that?!
I don't know... I just saw it!
You saw?
It... It came to my mind...
I'm scared!
Momo...
Zunesha's cry and this quake...
Yes, it makes sense.
Damn Jack!
How dare he attack Zunesha!
But if he's alive, that's good for us!
Let's fight back!
Guardians!
--Musketeers!
--Yes, sir!
Send out the ships!
Return fire against Jack on the water!
Okay!
Get to the ships! At full speed!
Let's defeat Jack this time!
Momonosuke-sama!
--Hang on! Don't move!
--Watch out for buildings!
This is painful!
If I collapse,
it would put all of you in danger!
The one behind the voice is...
...this...
...elephant!
The one behind the voice is...
...this...
...elephant!
You mean Zunesha?!
Momonosuke-sama! What's going on?!
Momo-chan?
Again!
A long time ago, I...
A long time ago,
the elephant committed a crime...
And now... all he is
allowed... to do is... walk.
He has been... obeying that order.
Thus...
Shoot it up! Blow it away!
Thus, give me permission for once!
Finish it off! Kill the elephant!
That worked! It's gonna collapse!
Hell yeah!
Order me!
To fight!
Grab on to something! Anything is fine!
For once!
Give me permission!
The elephant is... asking for permission!
He needs someone to... order him to fight!
Zunesha does?!
Kin'emon! Kanjuro!
What am I supposed to do?!
Momo!
You tell him!
I have a feeling that your voice will reach him!
But...
If they bring down the elephant,
we'll all end up in the sea!
But how loud should I be...
Just shout it out!
Or the elephant's gonna die!
A little more to go!
Hurry up, Momo!
The elephant's really gonna die!
Do it now!
Elephant!!
Don't give up, elephant!
You can't fall down!
Make Jack...
Make Jack go away!!
Understood!
What's going on?!
What happened?
--What the hell?!
--The elephant moved suddenly!
What is this force?
What is it gonna do?!
Trunk!
Jack-sama, our ship has
been thrown into the air!
It's out of control!
Oh...
Oh no-saru!
It quieted down.
What happened?!
I don't know. I don't see anything
or hear the voice now.
You too, Luffy?
Yeah, come to think of it,
I don't hear anything now.
Momonosuke-sama, are you okay?!
I'm not surprised.
It'd been so intense all this time.
This is serious-saru!
I have... I have a report-saru!
Oh, really?!
So Zunesha used his own trunk?
That's right-saru! With a single blow!
This elephant is strong.
I can't believe it.
I'd never thought Zunesha has a mind of his own.
Furthermore, we can even
communicate with him.
Did Oden-sama know
about Momonosuke-sama's ability?
Hey, Jack is a Devil Fruit eater, right?
If he fell into the water, he must be...
Yeah, that means he's dead!
Hey!
What's wrong?
You guys still look serious.
We're stunned at this sudden occurrence.
First, we gotta find out
how Jack was able to get here.
Otherwise, this place will no longer be safe.
I see. Well, good luck with that.
It'd be cool if this elephant becomes our ally.
That's easy for you to say.
Now, we're gonna go
so can we have lots of food?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
What do you want?
They say that communication with Jack
has been lost suddenly!
Kaido-san!
Dr. Chopper takes action to save Zunesha!
Using Zoro and Brook's sword skills,
Robin's Flower-Flower Fruit ability,
and Usopp and Franky's techniques,
an unprecedented major
treatment project begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Save Zunesha! The Straw
Hat's Rescue Operation!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!