I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go, Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible? Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani? mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
We have a problem!
What's wrong, Musatobi?!
Don't tell me Jack is back again!
N-No! It's not about Jack!
One of Zunesha's forelegs is...
It looks really terrible...
The wound is so large and deep...
In order to treat the elephant who was shot by Jack's clan,
Luffy and the rest took action.
I'm sure it's unbearably painful
but he's staying calm and letting us treat him.
--Hang on tight!
--Don't get shaken off!
I'm gonna be blown off!
Luffy!
Cien Fleurs - Spider Net!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Now, everyone, climb up!
--We're okay now!
--Robin!
Hey!
Lion Viper!
"Saying Goodbye and Descending from the Elephant!
Setting Out to Take Back Sanji!"
Clip it right there and we're done.
We're done too!
The medical knowledge of the now-named Sakura Kingdom
and the pharmaceutical knowledge of the Birdie Kingdom.
It's really incredible!
The bleeding has stopped.
You did great!
I prepared more than enough medicine
so you'll be okay!
Only Dr. Chopper could've done it!
It's really amazing!
S-Such compliments...
...don't make me happy,
you fools!
Like you taught us,
we'll try to remove the bandages on a regular basis
to see how the wound is.
Good.
But even just changing the bandages is painstaking.
We'll be careful.
Yeah! Leave it to us!
We'll protect Zunesha!
Yeah!
You're all so dependable!
Zunesha is our millennium-old land!
We might've gotten too comfortable and forgotten about it
because it's always been there since we were born.
Today, we were reminded.
We were reminded that we're always kept alive
by this great lifeform.
And it will come to an end one day.
If Zunesha, our land, has free will,
I want to ask him this now.
"You have been walking for a thousand years.
Where are you heading?"
KURAU CITY, MOKOMO DUKEDOM
You want to stay? Here in Zou?
Uh-huh.
What are you going to do here?
I actually don't know what to do but...
For once!
Give me permission!
Make Jack go away!!
Understood!
If it's possible,
I want to talk with him once again!
With Zunesha!
With the one who has been living for a millennium!
Why could he hear my voice?
Maybe he knows something about the Kozuki Clan!
--What?
--Momonosuke-sama!
I understand but there are people waiting for us
in the Land of Wano...
That's all right, Kin'emon.
Dogstorm!
I've been thinking I still have to
protect this country from the threat of Kaido.
We don't know yet how Jack could make it here twice
so we mustn't let down our guard.
We can't all get into the Land of Wano
at once anyway.
I think I'll stay here for a while.
I'll bring Momonosuke-sama with me later.
Understood. Thank you.
Cat Viper made my Vivre Card earlier.
Give this to everyone.
Now, let's split up into four groups.
First, the group that will search for Marco the Phoenix,
the former 1st division commander of the Whitebeard Pirates.
CAT VIPER TEAM - THE SEARCH FOR MARCO
Cat Viper's group!
Second, the group that will stay here on Zou
and join us later.
DOGSTORM TEAM - ZOU
Dogstorm's group!
Third, the group that will head for the Whole Cake Island
to take back Sanji-dono.
LUFFY TEAM - THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Luffy's group!
And the rest of us will go back to the Land of Wano,
round up allies, and plot a strategy while waiting for everyone.
KIN'EMON TEAM - THE LAND OF WANO
We're the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance!
Our objective is to subdue Emperor Kaido
and the shogun of the Land of Wano!
You can get there by following the Vivre Card,
but the problem is how we communicate.
In other countries, they use a snail to...
I mean, it's this big and if you speak into it,
someone at a distance will...
--Oh, you mean the Transponder Snail.
--Oh, that.
But in this country,
we're not accustomed to using them.
If you want a Transponder Snail,
I saw a wild one in the forest.
If you want one, I can set it up for you.
It's easy.
--What?
--E-Easy?
THE WHALE FOREST
Hey!
THE OUTSKIRTS OF THE GUARDIANS' DWELLING
Lion Viper's house is collapsed!
Hey, Lion Viper!
Are you okay?! Answer me!
Lion Viper! Where are you?!
I'm here! Grr!
Where are you?!
Look down!
Ac
A turtle?!
Step back!
Boy! What was the quake all about?!
How can I get a good rest?! Grr!
So you're Turtle Viper!
Okay, so not only do you not remember my name,
but you also forgot that I'm a lion! Grr!
How did you survive?!
The room is all destroyed!
Of course, I could survive!
I ate the Turtle-Turtle Fruit!
And my shell is as hard as a diamond!
Why aren't you listening?!
Chopper said he'll take responsibility
for treating you.
I see! You're not gonna
respond to the diamond part? Grr!
Ow, ow, ow!
But I appreciate his care.
I owe you guys a lot.
What?
What?!
What?!!
So let's go see Big Mom!
What?!
Wait, you bastard!
Don't you get it? I'm fatally injured now!
Hey! I'm injured! You've got to stop...
It's insane! I can't believe this!
You're the worst person to have debts to!
While I'm away,
work together and protect Zunesha, you-gara guys!
Count on us, Master!
Master.
Pedro.
Sanji saved this country.
And he was kidnapped in this country.
Even though the team has to be small,
we will fail in our duty...
...if no one from the Mink Tribe other than Pekoms
accompanies them.
You-gara, do you want to go along with Luffy?
I do!
Don't try to get the jump on the rest, Pedro!
That is a role that...
...we the Three Dogstorm Musketeers are
prepared to take on!
Back off, Shishilian!
A noisy guy like you is the least suitable for the job!
I'm not noisy!
Let me go!
I was with the Straw Hats the whole time!
Let me go too as an assistant to Dr. Chopper!
Wanda! Tristan!
We befriended Luffy after we fought him,
Pedro-san!
BB! Roddy!
Nami likes to sleep on my stomach!
That won't do them any good, Pastor Yomo!
I wanna chew on Baron Corpse's bones forever!
--Me too!
That's just your own goal! Shut up, dogs!
--I wanna go!
Maybe I can help them in some way!
I wanna go too!
--Me too!
--Let me go!
--I'll go!
--I wanna go too!
All right!
I understand how you all feel!
But you have to...
...let Pedro handle it!
Why, Master?!
Because Pekoms will be there.
Only Pedro can get him-gara under control!
I wish I could go!
Something is going on over there.
I called the last one "perfect" but...
...the new one surpasses that easily!
I incorporated
the growth capability of Pop Green
and got Franky's help
for the surface treatment.
It's not too much to say
that it's the greatest invention of the century...
You listening, Nami?!
If I squeeze here...
That was close!
Hey! What are you...
It's a little too long, Usopp!
Listen to my instruction! You extended it too far!
You need some practice!
That's a new Climate Baton which you can extend
as you like with slight variations in handling!
I see!
I incorporated all the gadgets from Weatheria
that I got from you in Sabaody.
But just one thing...
You said to me in Sabaody...
It's like a magic wand!
I didn't understand what it meant.
It fits to my hand! It's easy to twirl!
--So it's up to you to decide.
--This is great, Usopp!
Wh-Wh-Wh...
What an advanced ninjutsu that is!
It's nice!
This sure is the culmination of
Weatheria's science of weather!
The Sorcerer's Climate Baton that I wanted!
Oh yeah?!
Thanks, Usopp!
Don't mention it!
I just thought, for the future, you might need a weapon
that'll make you feel safe if only a little!
Now, about the cost...
Mirage Tempo!
Don't try to run!
THE MAIN GATE OF ZOU
In the end, it's the six of us.
It's nice to have you, Peropero!
It's Pedro. I won't bother you.
Wh-Why's Big Bro Pedro coming, Grr?
I'll come along as someone who's known you-gara well
for a long time.
What do you mean by that?! Grr!
Garchu!
It was really nice meeting you-teia guys!
You too! Garchu!
Nami! Take care!
Thanks! You too, Wanda!
We still wanna come with you, Baron Corpse!
I-I'm very flattered but no thanks,
dog ladies and gentlemen!
Thank you very much for everything.
Dr. Chopper. Please take care.
Uh-huh!
Take care, Dr. Chopper.
Listen. We know him.
He could be dancing around like that
being happy about his marriage.
No way!
But I can't deny it!
Well, it's gonna be okay!
Alright, Luffy-dono!
We'll be waiting for you in the Land of Wano!
Good luck, Luffy!
Take care!
Let us know if something happens.
I'll make a weapon to destroy Kaido!
I'll round up the samurai in the Land of Wano!
Now, I'll help you descend from the elephant.
That's okay, Kanjuro!
Bye!
Ya-hoo!
Leave Sanji in our hands!
What?!
See you in the Land of Wano!
--Okay!
--Don't get caught by Big Mom!
She's the emperor of the sea!
Yeah! See you!
Ya-hoo!
Thus, the Sanji retrieval team led by Luffy...
...sets out for the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom, who Luffy picked a fight with, waits.
Meanwhile, at the desert kingdom Alabasta
in the Grand Line...
Father-sama, hurry up!
Wait, Vivi.
Why are you in such a good mood?
Because it's been a while
since I went out to sea!
The princess of the desert kingdom who once traveled and
cried together with the Straw Hats!
And the Mermaid Princess who holds
a promise with Luffy in her mind!
It is time for them to set sail, each with their own dreams, for
the Reverie where kings from all around the world get together!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To the Reverie! Princess Vivi and Princess Shirahoshi!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!