kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others split into four teams,
each on different missions.
The Sanji retrieval team led by Luffy set out for
the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom waits.
See you in the Land of Wano!
--Okay!
--Don't get caught by Big Mom!
She's the emperor of the sea!
Yeah! See you!
Ya-hoo!
"To the Reverie!
Princess Vivi and Princess Shirahoshi!"
THE KINGDOM OF SAND - ALABASTA KINGDOM
Your Majesty!
All aboard!
Is that...
That's Vivi-sama!
Vivi-sama!
NEFELTARI VIVI - THE PRINCESS
OF ALABASTA KINGDOM
Have a nice trip!
--Vivi-sama!
--Your Majesty!
Everyone! See you!
Hey, Koza.
Vivi-chan looked very excited.
I guess her pirate spirit is back.
Just when I was thinking
she had become more like a princess.
Yes, this is Hina. We just left Alabasta.
We'll get the Nefeltari
Family to Mariejois safely.
"BLACK CAGE" HINA - A NAVY HQ REAR ADMIRAL
Hina-sama, accept these flowers!
I picked them for you!
I don't want them.
Django! Fullbody!
Go to your positions now!
Yes, ma'am!
Vivi-sama! Vivi-sama!
It's dangerous, Vivi-sama!
Please come down from there right now!
Vivi-sama!
What a nice sea breeze...
I wonder if I can see them again...
All right!
At any rate, no matter what happens,
this thing on our left arm is
the sign of our friendship!
I wanna kick Crocodile's ass!
You hope nobody dies in this fight.
None of the citizens, and none of us!
Even when a million people are going wild.
Don't you think that's too soft-hearted?
And what's wrong with thinking that?
What's wrong with not wanting people to die?!
People die.
Stop talking like that!
Say that again and I'll make you pay!
The people of this kingdom
haven't done anything wrong!
So why do people have to die...
...when it's all Crocodile's fault?!
Then why are you putting
your life on the line?!
Just one look at this kingdom
and even I can tell...
Tell what?!
...what most needs to be done!
As if putting your single
life on the line is enough!
Then what should I be putting on the line?!
I don't have anything else
that I can put on the line...
At least try putting all of our lives
on the line together!
Aren't we friends?!
Let me tell you something...
You can't save this country.
Goodbye, Princess...
Crocodile!!
Luffy-san!
Just in time.
My voice... no longer reaches anyone...
At this rate, the country will...
Don't worry.
Your voice is heard by us.
Yes...!
I won't... lose again!
Please... stop fighting!
Gum-Gum...
...Storm!
I see...
Then all we have to do...
is beat up that Crocodile, right?
Luffy-san...
He won!!
When our enemy's already gone...
Don't shed... any more blood...
Please stop fighting!
Please don't fight... any more...!!
Vivi's voice has reached everyone...
Since our nightmares are... all over...
The rain falling right now...
will fall again as it used to...
THE EASTERN HARBOR - TAMARISK
Let's go. It's past noon.
There's no way that she didn't come!
Let's get out and look for
her! She's definitely here!
Hey, this is bad!
The Navy is after us again!
Give up, Luffy.
Her case is different from ours.
Everyone!
Vivi!
Karoo!
Vivi-chan!
Let's go back! Better hurry!
The Navy is right there, too!
I came to say goodbye!
What did she just...?
I'd like to go on more adventures,
but there's no ignoring...
that I love this country!
So I can't go!
I see!
I...
This will do!
I will remain here...
It's a sign of our friendship!
But if we ever meet again someday...
will you call me your friend again?!
You'll forever be our...
Idiot!
Don't reply! The Navy has noticed Vivi.
If we prove she's connected with us,
she'll become a criminal.
Let's part without saying anything.
No matter what happens, this thing on our left arm
is the sign of our friendship!
Some strange bird might come and kidnap you.
What would you do then?!
What if a sniper's targeting you from somewhere
or a meteor falls out of the sky?!
You worry too much.
Vivi-sama was once a pirate.
Are you out of your mind, Pell?!
We have the Navy next to us!
Don't push yourself, Your Majesty.
If you don't feel well,
we'll head back right away.
No, I'm fine.
Ever since I met Nico Robin,
NEFELTARI COBRA - THE
KING OF ALABASTA KINGDOM
I've wanted to ask the World
Government about something.
About the Ponegliffs?
Mm-hm. I'm going to attend the upcoming Reverie
no matter what!
If I have a chance, I want to know...
...what some king of the Nefeltari Family did to the world
many years ago.
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh...
Hey! That's enough, Vivi-sama!
Father-sama, how are you?
Not very good.
Maybe I only have a very short time to live.
I wish my daughter to
take a husband already...
That's not fair!
You're taking advantage of your illness again!
We've got tons of pictures
of potential suitors!
Throw them away!
ROGUE TOWN, EAST BLUE
Congratulations on your enthronement, sir.
Our hotel was built exclusively for royal families
who go to the Reverie every four years.
We hope you like it.
It isn't not-not-so-bad.
SALLY ISNTOINETTE - THE QUEEN OF GOA KINGDOM
Right, honey?
Well, it's nothing special.
He means it isn't not-not-so-special.
All it offers is a view of the scaffold
where Gold Roger was executed.
H-Have a nice rest
after the fatigue of your journey.
King Stelly.
Yeah, you guys are eyesores to me.
Go away, trash.
Y-Y-Yes, sir!
The reason that countries
are buzzing a little...
...is because of the Reverie
that takes place in the
Holyland of Mariejois, the center
of the world, every four years.
At this paramount meeting,
leaders of 50 nations gather together...
...to discuss matters of concern
from around the world,
and establish future guidelines.
However, since they are all judicious
and sly leaders of nations,
things never go smoothly.
The leader of the Happosui
Army - Don Chin Jao...
KANO KINGDOM, WEST BLUE
I mean, the new leader Sai
is not back yet, is he?
Since Straw Hat and the others took down
the Donquixote Family,
our enemy can't buy weapons from them.
Thanks to that, the war is over.
Looks like we can make it to the Reverie.
There are tons of things that we want to say!
THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE SEA FLOOR UNDER THE RED LINE
Again, I can't do it.
I'm scared.
Luffy-sama promised me.
When I see him again someday,
he'll take me to a real forest above ground!
PRINCESS SHIRAHOSHI
THE PRINCESS OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
Of course, Luffy-kun will take you farther.
But on this occasion,
you only have to go straight up to Mariejois.
Your brothers and the Neptune Army
will come with you, Princess Shirahoshi!
But...
Oh, boy...
Shirahoshi...
Father, could we go without
her this time-mi-re-do?
RYUBOSHI - THE PRINCE OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
Yeah! We got tons of signatures
on the petition...
MANBOSHI - THE PRINCE OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
...that asks to relocate the Fish-Man Island!
Ooh mambo!
That is like saying that we
don't trust humans-jamon.
NEPTUNE - THE KING OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
What should we do?
Shirahoshi, what did you
learn from the Straw Hats?
FUKABOSHI - THE PRINCE OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
If I can see you again someday,
I promise I won't be a crybaby!
Take me out for a fun stroll again!
A stroll?
Do you wanna go to your mother's grave again?
No.
I want to go somewhere farther next time!
I want to go to a real forest above ground!
Okay, fine!
Will you promise?
We promise!
This meeting is what our mother Otohime
was looking forward to.
Come with us!
Meanwhile, Luffy and the
others who left Zou...
Hey, starboard...
Okay...
How's that?
Oh, a little more...
Hey, hey, hey!
Pull yourselves together! Or we'll sink!
Shut up! Because you jumped off
the elephant all of a sudden,
we're all worn out! Idiot!
Thank you.
I'm savoring the joy of living now.
But... I'll make you pay for it!
It made my blood freeze in my veins...
Oh, all I have is bones though.
Damn! What did I do to deserve this?
No... We swerved from the course again.
Port...
Okay! Leave it to me!
Look! She's full of energy...
Wow! I'm really right on the sea!
This ship looks so heavy but it's
floating and moving forward!
CARROT - A MEMBER OF THE MINK MUSKETEERS
Wh-Why are you here?!
Whaaat?!
Chopper's foster mother Dr. Kureha
and Rebecca who helped Luffy
take down Warlord Doflamingo
start to move for the Reverie!
Meanwhile, Luffy's team,
welcoming a new member Carrot,
gets news about another incident
that shakes up the world!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To the Reverie! Rebecca and the Sakura Kingdom!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!