kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji, Luffy
and the others set out
for the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom waits,
while people in different countries
started preparing for the Reverie...
...that takes place in the Holyland of Mariejois
every four years.
Wow! I'm really right on the sea!
This ship looks so heavy
but it's floating and moving forward!
Wh-Why are you here?!
"To the Reverie!
Rebecca and the Sakura Kingdom!"
Carrot?!
Carrot, why are you here?!
I came along with you!
Garchu!
Nami!
MUNCH!
Munch!
Chopper!
CHOMP!
Chomp!
Baron Corpse!
CRUNCH!
Crunch!
Too hard!
I'm sorry but can we go back?
What?!
Don't do that! Wanda will be mad at me!
Are you trying to cause trouble to
those who saved us, Carrot?!
I just wanted to go on an adventure
at sea along with Luffy and
the others even if only once!
We're going to sneak into the Emperor's headquarters!
We're not playing!
Please! I'll do anything - take me with you!
I didn't wanna cause you trouble so I brought...
Look!
Lunch!
Juice!
A snack!
An extra shirt!
Unlike everything else,
the shirt is not a carrot, is it?
No, no. But there's one on it!
That's nice!
How long will they last?
Like a half day! The sea is vast, isn't it?!
What?!
It'll take several days to get to Big Mom's island?!
Even if we go straight?!
I can't believe it's so big and wide!
The sea is like a wonderland!
This will be my first sleepover!
A wonderland? It's not even an island.
Oh, well.
You're here now and it can't be helped.
Can you protect yourself?
Yes! Thank you! I'll be alright...
Why are you eating my carrot?!
Pat her head, Luffy!
That was close! You almost killed me!
You're strong!
Okay, you can have the carrot.
Luffy was almost defeated!
Well, she is quite a fighter.
Pedro-san, when did you get up there?
You really like heights.
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
Somebody, make something!
All right!
I'll do it so watch the sea, okay?
--Yes, sir!
--Yay!
Each of you must pay me 5,000 berries.
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
All of our allowance will be gone!
What should we do then?
Brook, either you or I should make something.
You're right.
If we leave it to Luffy-san,
we don't know what he'll make for us!
I'll make something!
What?!
Count on me!
I'll cook you a lot of delicious dishes!
Oh, no...
Oh, please don't... Hey, wait!
Food! Food! Food!
Wait! Don't do it!
Luffy! Can you even cook?!
Meanwhile, another country starts preparing
for the Reverie...
What?!
THE SAKURA KINGDOM, GRAND LINE
What did you say, Dr.
Kureha? Are you serious?
DALTON - THE KING OF THE SAKURA KINGDOM
Why are you looking so displeased?!
Dalton, you will attend
the Reverie as the first king
of the Sakura Kingdom, right?
DR. KUREHA
Y-Yes.
In that case, I'll be your
ship's doctor, I said!
Are you happy?
Well, I'm amazed how you
reconstructed this Winter Island
and built a kingdom that is good
enough to attend the Reverie.
Thanks to them.
You mean those pirates
who took away my stupid son?
Yes, the Straw Hats.
And... Dr. Hiriluk.
That quack...
My name is Dr. Hiriluk!
I'm a doctor!
Skull...
This is a symbol of the belief that
nothing is impossible!
I will save this country as a doctor!
By raising this,
I'll fight just like pirates do!
Are you happy, young man?
The doctor hunt has come to the final stage.
I hear that you and I are
the only doctors left in this country.
Wapol is trying desperately to catch us.
Even if that wasn't the case,
you're already an outcast in this country...
...since you're the worst of the quacks.
I won't get caught by some doctor hunt.
I'll save this country
using medical science one day.
I'm gonna... die...
Yeah, you will...
What... happened to you?
Mushroom...
Medicine...
That's an Amiudake mushroom!
Doctor also said he got better!
There's no way he'll die!
You're a liar!
He was happy about your thoughts.
The skull in the book indicates poison.
That's a lie!
That's not a lie! Remember it!
There's no medicine
that can work for all diseases in this world.
That's why doctors exist!
That's not true...!
Listen.
You can't save people just by being kind!
If you want to save them,
then learn medical knowledge and skills!
Without skill, you can't save anyone!
You guys can't kill me.
Huh?
Hey...
When do you think a person dies?
When a bullet from a
pistol pierces his heart?
No...
When he's attacked by an incurable disease?
No...!
When he eats a deadly poisonous mushroom soup?
No!
A man dies when people forget him...
Even if I disappear,
my dream will come true.
The citizens' sickness of the heart
will be cured as well...
Why're you crying... Dalton?
I wonder... if it's the same for a country...
Yeah, if there's someone to pass it on to...
I had... such a good life!
Goodbye, quack...
Thank you, Chopper!
Please... teach me to be a doctor!
I'll become the all-purpose medicine!
I'll become a doctor who can cure anything!
I'll cure even a country!
Because... Because...
there's no disease in this world that can't be cured!
--Are you guys pirates?
--Yes...
R-Real ones?
Real ones.
You have a flag with a skull?
It's attached to our ship.
Are you interested in pirates?
No! You idiot! No!
You idiot!
Okay, okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
But... Then... wanna come, too?
To the sea!
Why don't you come with us...?
Dodge it! Watch out!
You can't break this flag!
He must've been blown away! Such an idiot!
See? It didn't break...
You'd better be prepared if you're gonna
meddle with someone else's skull flag!
Gum-Gum...
Hold on a sec!
I'll give you status and a medal!
Doctor...
The kingdom is...
The Drum Kingdom is...
Then... I'll make you vice-king...!
...about to fall!
...Bazooka!!
Thank you. Drum will definitely...
...be reborn...
I'm sorry, Doctor!
But I wanna see the world!
What do you think someone like you
can do at sea?!
Are you gonna live in a fantasy
just like that quack did?!
You're wrong! It wasn't a fantasy!
Doctor's research had
actually been completed!
Was it okay to bid farewell like that?
A pet I was taking care of is being taken in
by someone else. That's all.
I don't like... tears...
Are you ready, young men?!
I will make cherry blossoms bloom.
Once my invention is completed,
this country will be saved!
Doctor...! Dr. Kureha...!
Now, have a safe trip, my stupid son...
I wonder where he is and what he's doing now...
My stupid son...
I'm sure he's having a good time
sailing some sea with the Straw Hats.
THE EVIL BLACK DRUM KINGDOM
The Evil Black Drum Kingdom!
The first king Wapol-sama
is leaving for the Reverie!
WAPOL - THE KING OF THE
EVIL BLACK DRUM KINGDOM
I remember how I came back...
...as a king who'd even be
allowed to attend the Reverie
after getting kicked out of the Drum Kingdom.
My life has been full of ups and downs!
I got blown away by Straw Hat
and woke up in an unknown place.
I ate trees and rocks.
I was okay with being all by myself.
I ate lamps. I ate benches.
The whole town was a snack to me.
Of course, it was because I was a king.
But the Navy arrested me.
I shook them off and fled in tears!
I got clear but that made me realize
that I was no longer a king.
Would you like to buy a box of matches?
I was selling matches
and living under a bridge.
Using the Munch-Munch Factory,
I was playing with refuse.
But those toys that I created
won the hearts of children!
WAPOL'S TOY STORE
I earned some money by selling those toys,
and opened Wapol's Toy Store!
The business thrived instantly!
A local scientist uncovered
the secret of my toys:
a new alloy, Wapometal!
The number of customers, increased!
The store, expanded!
Toyshop Wapol was booming!
Business was prosperous! Profits were rising!
The Munch-Munch Factory was flourishing!
I rose from the quagmire
and became the CEO of the Wapol Konzern!
I married Miss Universe and
my life has been filled with happiness!
Wapol's insignia has
spread all over the world
and I came back into power as an evil ruler!
No matter how many times I talk about it,
it still feels good!
Oh, yeah! Let's publish it as
"Wapol-sama's Great Memoir"!
Wapol-sama! I have a report!
The Drum Kingdom that you once ruled
became a new country - the Sakura Kingdom,
and Dalton will attend the Reverie as a king,
they say!
What?! The Sakura Kingdom?!
Damn Dalton...
How can I drag him down at the Reverie?!
DRESSROSA - A KINGDOM OF PASSION
Luffyland! This way!
Lucy...
You always try to strangle everything
within your hands
and try to manipulate everybody!
It makes me feel like I'm suffocating!
What?! Can I come too?!
Of course, you can!
Would you like to come as my lady-in-waiting?
I'd love to! Thank you, Viola-san!
You must be excited, Rebecca!
I am!
But what am I supposed
to wear to the Reverie?
You can wear one of my gowns.
--What do you think?
--They're all nice!
Very beautiful!
You can take whatever you like.
Oh, but...
...maybe I'll take my mother's dress!
Yes! That sounds good!
THE PRODENCE KINGDOM
King Riku! I turned down the Navy escort!
ELIZABELLO II - THE KING
OF THE PRODENCE KINGDOM
Would you like to go to the Holyland with me?
Why does everyone think of it
as a vacation or something?
RIKU DOLDO III - THE KING OF DRESSROSA
What's wrong with that?
The Reverie is like a festival!
Meanwhile, Luffy's group...
Now, what should I make?!
Oh! There is tons of food!
It's a nice kitchen!
Yes, Sanji-san usually cooks
and we all eat here, talking and laughing.
Oh, yeah.
Let me give you the tour of our ship.
What?
Garchu! Baron Corpse!
CRUNCH!
Crunch!
Again, you're too hard!
This is the aquarium bar.
There are so many beautiful fish!
Well, it's just a place to store fish we caught
to keep them fresh to eat later.
Are you listening?
This is a room where Nami-san figures out
where we are using the sea
chart or keeps the ship's log.
There are a lot of books!
Help me...
This is a big bathtub!
It hasn't been filled with warm water yet.
You can take a hot shower too.
Let's see.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ow! Ow! Ow!
I didn't know you could feel heat too!
Of course, I do!
These are Nami-san's tangerine trees,
Robin-san's flower garden
and the Usopp Garden.
Oh! I can grow carrots here!
Let's plant some now!
Okay, I won't say anything.
Oh, I can't believe I get to travel on such a lovely ship...
It's so wonderful!
This is quite a large headline.
"The island, for decades
veiled in mystery..."
"...was finally revealed."
"The Revolutionary Army's
general headquarters - Baltigo..."
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S HQ FOUND
"...has already been laid to waste?!"
Luffy's arch-nemesis Blackbeard
seems to be behind
the destruction of the Revolutionary Army!
Meanwhile, Kaido, the strongest
man in the world, is burning with
rage against Luffy and Law!
As the Four Emperors start making a move
in an eerie way, the Straw
Hats face another crisis!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Kaido Returns! An Imminent
Threat to the Worst Generation!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!