I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji, Luffy
and the others set out for
the Whole Cake Island where
Emperor Big Mom waits.
Don't get caught by Big Mom!
She's the emperor of the sea!
Yeah! See you!
Ya-hoo!
Meanwhile, people in different countries
started preparing for the Reverie,
the World Conference
that takes place every four years.
All right!
I'll do it so watch the sea, okay?
--Yes, sir!
--Yay!
Each of you must pay me 5,000 berries.
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
All of our allowance will be gone!
What should we do then?
I'll make something!
What?!
This is quite a large headline.
"The island, for decades
veiled in mystery..."
"...was finally revealed."
"The Revolutionary Army's
general headquarters - Baltigo..."
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S HQ FOUND
"...has already been laid to waste?!"
"Kaido Returns!
An Imminent Threat to the Worst Generation!"
Good, good!
Everything is nice and fresh!
Alright then, let's do it!
Oh, how exactly do you cook?
I have no idea!
Who cares!
Let's just chop everything up!
Oops!
Pekoms, are you okay?
Thank you.
I'm fatally injured but it's nothing. Grr.
Luffy does nothing but crazy things.
He's the worst.
I've never seen anybody jump off Zou. Grr.
Pedro?
Where's Luffy?
What? Oh, I think he's in the kitchen.
Is anything wrong?
Go get him. It's serious.
What?
What?!
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S HQ FOUND
The Revolutionary Army got defeated?!
I thought you-gara were
the son of the revolutionary - Dragon...
Sabo!
That's my brother!
Sabo-san?! The other brother that
you said you met at Dressrosa?
Is he the Chief of Staff?!
That makes him No.2 of the Revolutionary Army!
What an unusual group of
three brothers you guys are!
Wow! I can't believe it!
So this Dragon guy beside him is...
Yes, that's him!
Your grandpa told you two years ago.
Come to think of it, Luffy...
I heard that you saw your old man.
What?! My dad?
What do you mean by my dad?
I have a dad?
Oh... Then he didn't tell you who he was?
I heard that he saw you off at Rogue Town.
Luffy's old man was in that town?!
Wh-What's my dad like?
I'm curious... about Luffy's father!
Your father's name is...
...Monkey D. Dragon.
He's a revolutionary!
The leader of the Revolutionary Army - Dragon.
That's your father!
What?! Is this my dad?!
--After all these years?!
--I've never seen him before!
What?! Luffy's father is
the boss of the Revolutionary Army?!
Oh my! Oh my! Garchu!
Didn't you look into it at all
over the last couple of years?!
Normally people would care
if their father is such a famous figure!
And he took care of Robin for quite a while.
I see! I've never seen him before!
He doesn't really look like me.
Anyway, I'm worried about Sabo!
Jeez...
Well, you can't really
empathize with a picture.
"The location of their general headquarters was found
by an anonymous tip."
"However, when the Navy and
Cipher Pol arrived there,"
"the Blackbeard Pirates had already
destroyed the headquarters."
Blackbeard?! Those bastards!
But why did Emperor Blackbeard want to
attack the Revolutionary Army?
Isn't it strange?
Back in Dressrosa, Sabo fought...
--...against the champion. Is that why?
--Hey, Luffy!
Emperor Blackbeard fled
after butting heads with Cipher Pol, it seems.
Hey, Luffy!
There is no report on casualties.
Hey!
If your-gara father or brother
had been caught or killed,
that would've made headlines.
Hey, Luffy!
So I guess they're okay for now.
Yeah! You're right!
Hey, Luffy!
What do you want?!
Thank you for cooking for us
but is that normal?!
What?
Fire?!
What?!
Why?! Why is it on fire?!
No!
Oh, no! I left the stove on!
What?!
Oh! There's an explosion!
Put out the fire!
Wait a minute! A storm is coming!
What?!
What is that?! Electro?!
Furl the sail now! The
wind is gonna rip it up!
What about the fire?!
There'll be heavy rain! It'll put it out!
--So lucky!
--Cut it out!
Yeah! It's raining!
It's putting out the fire! Phew!
Yeah! Pour more!
Ya-hoo!
Oh, he's quick!
Chopper, are you okay?!
I need a hand! There!
Okay!
Here I go!
Brook! Get cola ready to fill
up at a moment's notice!
I got it!
You do something, too!
I'm fatally injured!
ZOU
Then Carrot is out at sea now?!
Why didn't you tell me sooner, Bariete?
I'm sorry-saru, Wanda!
I told Carrot that she had to tell everyone
that she was going-saru.
But she said...
No way! If I tell anybody,
they'll try to stop me!
Keep it to yourself just for a while!
N-No! I can't keep it to myself-saru...
You really can't-saru?
I see! She bribed you-teia, didn't she?
Shock!
N-N-No! Wh-Wh-What are
you talking about-saru?!
These bananas are...
I-I mean, they sure look delicious but...
Who said anything about bananas?
You caught me-saru...
But Carrot didn't wanna
go behind your back...
That's okay.
I'm glad to know where she is.
I was just worried that she was missing.
If she's with Luffy and the others,
she'll be fine.
Duke-sama, please get some rest.
I'll post extra guards if you want.
The enemy was probably using a Vivre Card.
I wonder how they got it.
I hope the card was lost
along with the fleet that Zunesha sank...
Do you think they'll return?
We'd better be on the lookout.
Okay.
Come on!
Pull me up already!
A CERTAIN COUNTRY
Kaido-sama!
I was able to confirm!
We were right!
As we thought,
Jack-sama failed to rescue Joker!
That means the man-made Devil Fruit
SMILE trade is practically at an end...
He's a weepy drunk today.
That means we can't have more Gifters!
Joker! Oh, Joker!
How come you got beaten?!
You said we'd form the strongest pirate group
made of all Devil Fruit eaters!
And yet...
You've been taken down by... those upstart brats
before we fulfilled that dream?
Poor Joker! Even though it's primarily
your own fault for being weak!
But everyone's talking about Straw Hat these days.
If you underestimate him...
If I underestimate him...
Then what?!
Who do you think I am?!
He became a quarrelsome drunk!
K-Kaido-sama... Please calm down!
Straw Hat Luffy! Trafalgar Law!
I know!
They're from the generation, right?!
Those brats think they're something
just because they brought down a Warlord!
They must realize they messed up my business!
Screw them!
Hey, you!
Tell those idiots from your generation!
"You'd better run! What we were doing
was just playing at being pirates!"
Eustass "Captain" Kid!
Oh, it's cold!
--We covered up the roof!
--Okay, thank you.
All right! The storm passed!
And we covered up the roof that was blown off!
I saved the food I made so eat up!
Yeah! We get to eat! We're hungry!
Oh, do you like it?!
My original curry!
Luffy, we can't eat uncooked rice!
--What's that bitter purplish thing?
--It's full of fish bones.
--So much jam!
--Something's slimy and light blue...
What did we do to deserve this?
How could you guys be so rude
after I've taken the trouble to cook this!
Yuck!
--See?!
--How can I eat this?!
Don't knock it over!
How dare you waste food!
Sanji-san would be mad if he heard about this!
We had tons of food and it's all gone!
Yeah, I messed up several times
so I used it all!
What?! That was a week's
worth of food for all of us!
I thought you were hungry!
It's not funny!
What are we gonna do now?!
Luffy...
Hey, I'm starving...
Sanji-san! Help us!
Thus, Luffy's group faces a lack of provisions
on the very first day of their voyage.
Luffy's hungry group launches a
high-stakes mission to acquire food!
They head for a Navy frontline base
where many tough soldiers are stationed!
Young officers who are
responsible for the Navy's
next generation and the Straw Hats
get caught in a fierce battle!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Hungry Front! Luffy and the Navy Rookies!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!