I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji from Big Mom,
Luffy and the others...
...parted from Zoro and the rest who have started
preparing for a battle with Emperor Kaido.
They headed for the Whole Cake Island
but now face a serious food shortage...
Hey! Cut it out!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Luffy-san, you can't eat him!
--Luffy! It's me! It's me!
--Let go of him! No! He's gonna eat you!
That's enough!
--I can't do this anymore...
--Nami-san!
We're in dire straits without any food...
Will we be able to see Sanji-kun?
Hey! You-gara guys!
There's an island!
An island?
Oh, could it be...
...the island on the chart?!
Yes!
The gods saved me!
It must be a reward for being so good all the time!
Food!
Okay! Guys!
Let's go to the food island!
Yeah!
Wait!
Don't go to that island.
Why?!
Do you know something?
Pirates shouldn't go there.
That island is...
...a Navy base!
A Navy base?
"A Hungry Front!
Luffy and the Navy Rookies!"
Please look out for the Sunny!
--Yeah, leave it to us!
--You really going?
Don't worry! We'll steal their food
and be back soon!
Even though you're with Straw Hat,
don't lower your guard!
They have notorious hotheads from
various Navy units on that island.
That's an annoying frontline base
where they observe the Whole Cake Island.
If you underestimate them, you'll get hurt.
Okay, guys!
Let's execute our plan right away!
Yeah!
Vice Admiral Prodi.
The reserves will arrive soon.
Mm-hm.
What's going on?!
JUSTICE
They're all useless.
Cowardly weaklings!
I'll beat you all up!
Get him, everyone!
That's enough, new boy!
You're Vice Admiral Prodi.
Just who I was looking for.
Send these dumb-asses
back to their old units.
You twit!
Thank you for
your better-than-expected reaction!
Okay, everyone!
Come out and get changed!
I'm so excited to sneak into the base
disguised as a Navy soldier!
--I don't wanna wear this.
--Wear it if you wanna get food!
Okay.
Luffy! I smell something good!
I think it stopped.
If we'd arrived here a little later,
we would've run into that Navy ship.
That was close.
Nami-san,
I'm going back to the Submerge.
Thanks! Please keep guard!
Nami! Look at the tower!
The soldiers are carrying food in there!
That must be their food storage!
But their headquarters is close to it
so we'd better watch out!
Yeah, let's grab the food carefully
without causing any trouble!
Uh-huh!
Okay, Luffy, let's go...
He's gone!
Carrot too!
Food...
Not that way!
Did you plan it, Garp?!
He destroyed one whole ship!
That's not good.
You think it's not your problem?!
Aren't you his instructor?!
Grount requested the transfer!
Take good care of him!
Clank.
Vice Admiral Garp.
--Grount was transferred to Vice Admiral Prodi?
--Yeah.
Why did he want to go to such an remote place?
What is he thinking?
Damn, that old bastard!
Hey, why did you want
to be transferred here?!
Big Mom is somewhere near here, right?
I'll bring her down!
You're so naive!
All-Hunt Grount. You're just 17 years
old but you're a naval captain?!
What are the people at the HQ thinking?!
Plus, you used to be in Kuzan's unit.
We have two soldiers with the same
background here. Do you know them?
Maybe.
How could Kuzan leave
such a good-for-nothing brat behind?!
Well, he's worthless too since he left the Navy
after losing in the power struggle!
We only hear bad rumors about him these days!
Don't talk bad about Aokiji-san!
You'd better be careful
not to become like him.
Hey! I'll assign him to duty soon!
Let him rest a while!
Yes, sir!
Aren't we there yet?
We're getting closer!
It's from that building!
Oh, Luffy and Carrot!
Of all places,
they're going into the headquarters!
We gotta catch them first! Let's go!
--Okay!
--Honestly!
Oh, this is great!
--Rest here until you get assigned to a task.
--Be nice to your "friends"!
Hey.
Hey, newbie!
Why did you wreak havoc earlier?
If you don't care about
your colleagues, go away!
Yeah, go away!
Hey, we're talking to you!
What an insolent twit!
Don't push your luck, newbie!
--Ouch!
--You okay?!
That bastard!
Do you still wanna fight?
Bring it on!
Okay.
But before that...!
Oh, I missed you, Grount!
Shut up!
That's annoying!
Let go of me, Bonham!
Calm down or I'll break your bones!
Hey! Zappa's here too, right?
Where is he?
He's... there!
As soon as he got here,
he started proposing to every single woman but...
...he finally got turned down
by the very last one.
Hey, it's been a while since we last met!
We have a lot of catching-up to do!
We three will have a good
time together again!
As long as you stay out of my way...
I mean, let go of me!
Here you go!
Eat it up!
Yum-yum!
Put a lot of carrots on mine!
Hey, are you okay?!
What's wrong?!
Report this to the headquarters A.S.A.P.!
FINE-
TUNED
JUSTICE
FINE-TUNED JUSTICE
A ghost?!
Yes, they're saying that it appeared in front of them
out of the blue and attacked them.
Yeah?
I see. So you're saying a ghost
tied them up and took their uniforms?
Yes... No... I mean...
Don't be ridiculous!
Listen! Enforce the search inside the facilities
and along the shoreline!
Go find their invasion route!
--Now, go!
--Y-Yes, sir!
Hey! What's going on with the
Video Transponder Snails?
All of them are running, sir.
--Let's go to the monitoring room!
--Yes, sir!
It's hot!
This spicy flavor is addicting!
You're still a kid, huh?
Screw you!
What's so funny?!
He's getting as hot as curry.
So good!
Look, Luffy!
A seagull-shaped carrot! How cute!
Can I have yours?
Yes, you can.
Thanks!
I can't believe it.
They're totally exposed and no one's noticing.
I'm hungry...
Nami!
You don't look familiar.
That's unacceptable!
A new soldier like you has to eat a lot
and gain weight or you can't keep up!
Eat up and hang in there!
Huge man right there,
you can have some too!
Great! Thank you!
Don't mention it. Just eat it!
Okay!
This is so good!
What's the situation?
We still haven't found out who invaded
or their route in.
Where are they hiding?
I won't let them get away at any cost!
Nami and Chopper!
Nami! Chopper! We're here!
--Hey!
--Come here, guys!
Nami!
I heard someone said "Nami"!
Where is she?!
Let's eat together! Come on!
A-Am I seeing her in a vision?!
Why is she here?
This is the chance of a lifetime!
I won't blow it!
What's the matter, Zappa?
Wh-What?!
You're Ms. Nami of the Straw Hats,
aren't you?
No, I'm new here. My name is Mina...
You can't fool me.
Oh, no! He knows who I am!
I've been gazing at...
...your wanted poster night and day!
Urgh! What's wrong with him?!
And now, you're in front of me!
Oh, my beautiful amore!
Forget that we're a Navy soldier and a pirate,
and marry me, amore?!
Marry?!
No, no, no!
I've never thought about marrying!
Let me loosen up your closed heart
with my lonely heart!
Accept my love! Baciami!
Stay away! You make me sick!
Oh, it's spicy!
Are you in your right mind?
Ms. Nami...
She ran away.
What's wrong with that creepy soldier?!
Are you okay?
Oh, it's heavy!
They serve delicious curry here, huh?
One, two!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Where the hell are they?!
Oh? Is that a fight?
What's going on here?!
Is this...?
Hey! Zoom in to this guy!
Yes, sir!
D-Don't tell me he's...
Garp's grandson?!
To all soldiers across the island!
We found the invader!
He's devouring curry in the cafeteria!
He is none other than Straw Hat Luffy!
Straw Hat Luffy?!
Is that him?!
--Chopper, let's run!
--To where?!
To the food storage outside, of course!
I'm not gonna leave empty-handed!
They must have hid their ship somewhere!
Look everywhere along the coast!
Yeah!
I wonder if
Luffy-san and the others are okay...
For the pride of the Navy,
catch them at any price!
Don't let them escape from this island!
Oh, no!
Luffy! We're in trouble!
What's going on?
He's the man of 500 million?!
Ms. Nami's captain?!
He looks dumb. Straw Hat Luffy...
I will...
...kick your ass!
It's a no-where-to-run solitary
island far off in the sea!
Luffy and the others are
besieged by the Navy!
Grount, Bonham and Zappa raise
their fighting spirit against
the man worth 500 million - Luffy,
and their ultimate fighting techniques
blast leads them to a battle
royal against the Straw Hats!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Implacable Three! A Big
Chase After the Straw Hats!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!