kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji from Emperor Big Mom,
Luffy and the others were heading
for the Whole Cake Island.
But now they're facing a
serious food shortage...
Luffy snuck into a Navy base which they stumbled upon
to steal food,
but he was surrounded by soldiers.
Among them are three Navy rookies
who are looking to subdue pirates.
Where the hell are they?!
Oh? Is that a fight?
What's going on here?!
Is this...?
Hey! Zoom in to this guy!
Yes, sir!
D-Don't tell me he's...
Garp's grandson?!
Oh, no!
Luffy! We're in trouble!
What's going on?
He's the man of 500 million?!
Ms. Nami's captain?!
He looks dumb. Straw Hat Luffy...
I will...
...kick your ass!
"The Implacable Three!
A Big Chase After the Straw Hats!"
Straw Hat Luffy... I will kick your ass!
No, let me take care of him.
The captain of the Straw Hats...
Huh? What did you say?
If I can kill him,
Ms. Nami will be mine!
Luffy, what should we do?!
They know who we are
and we're surrounded!
"What should we do"?
We have no choice!
We're gonna run!
That's right! We're gonna eat more!
What?!
Carrot! Let's eat more!
I'll have some too!
Hey! That's enough!
--Let's take the whole pot!
--Good idea! We got food!
Nothing'll be left for us to eat!
I love pretty girls who know what they want!
That fool is worth 500 million?
He's a big nothing.
I'll take him down!
I'm eating here! Don't bother me!
We don't have curry here
for you damn pirates to eat!
Everyone knows they're there now.
Are they gonna be okay?
Don't worry.
He's not gonna get caught by the likes of them.
More importantly, what we gotta do now is
steal food!
No good. I can't open it.
It's locked.
Leave it to me.
This is my chance to show my skill as a cat burglar!
Damn!
How pathetic, Grount. Let me fight!
Breath Qigong - the first step!
Reinforcing!
Adios!
Finger Pistol!
You can move quickly!
Finger Pistol Yellow Lotus!
Flying Finger Pistol Sting!
I'm a master of the Six Powers!
Tempest Kick!
All this moving is making me hungry.
Are you okay, Luffy?
Where are Nami and Chopper?
Running is all you can do?!
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body!
...Jet Pistol!
--Let's look for more food!
--Okay!
What?
Oh, carrots!
A present for you.
What? Are you gonna give me those carrots?
You pretty and cute young lady...
Wh-Wh-What's your name?
I'm Carrot!
Ms. Carrot!
What a lovely name!
Here!
Yay!
I'm so happy! Thank you! Garchu!
Munch!
G-G-G-Garchu!
Carrot, let's go see Nami and Chopper!
Okay!
He took my Ms. Carrot!
If I can chop his head off,
both Ms. Nami and Ms. Carrot will be mine!
Ms. Nami! Ms. Carrot!
You're such a pain in the neck!
I just wanna eat more!
I'm sorry for doing this
after you gave me carrots.
Ms. Carrot...
Thank you, Carrot!
Luffy-san!
Oh, did I surprise you?
I'm sorry.
By the way, can I see your panties?
Brook, where are Nami and Chopper?
Oh, um,
they're at a food storage facility outside.
Food?! Okay, let's go, Carrot!
Uh-huh!
This way!
Food! Food!
Carrots! Carrots!
--That bastard!
--Outta my way, Grount! I'll beat him!
Ms. Carrot!
I'll do it! Stay out of it, Bonham!
--What did you just say?!
--Ms. Carrot! Electrify me more!
Please! Please!
There they are!
Gum-Gum Jet Gatling!
Hurry up!
We'll stop you!
Get out of my way!
This is fun!
It's down this way!
Ow, ow, ow... It's a dead end.
Oh, I'm sorry!
I forgot you can't run through a wall
if you're flesh and blood.
I'm just bones - rather boneheaded actually!
Stop!
What a fool!
You're literally a cornered rat!
Even if you're feared as one
of the Worst Generation,
you act dumb when it counts.
Grount, he's just like you!
What?!
Are you saying that I'm a dumb-ass?!
I didn't say that!
But I won't deny it either.
Oh, my dear Ms. Carrot!
Give me the "garchu" once more!
Luffy, what should we do?
--It's down this way, right?
--Yes.
Ms. Carrot!
Oh, wait!
Damn!
--I smell food from that way!
--Luffy, you have a good nose!
Let's chase them!
--Luffy-san, I'll leave the rest to you!
--Yeah!
I'm gonna go back to the ship then!
You're finally here, Luffy.
--Yummy!
--This is nice, isn't it, Luffy?
Why are you guys so relaxed and eating?!
She's right. Hurry up, Luffy.
You can't eat too much here!
You too?!
Come on!
Let's take food and get out of here!
Why? I haven't had enough!
Straw Hat Luffy!
I recognize your large appetite
and how fast you can run away!
Fight me!
Straw Hat Luffy.
We don't have food for pirates here!
Kung Fu Point!
I'll fight you!
Iron Body!
So you can transform yourself too.
What?
Breath Qigong - the second step.
Reducing.
Gracias!
Nobody can stop me!
So quick!
Huh! You can't see me, can you?!
I don't need to see.
Guard Point!
Those crappy attacks won't work
against Guard Point!
If so, I'll just break it by force!
Ten Finger Pistol!
The Six Powers will take you down!
Heavy Point!
I'm a monster!
Heavy Gong!
Iron Body Strength!
I'm second to none in transformation!
Love Slashing!
Straw Hat, I can't let you go that easily.
Nor Ms. Nami's heart either!
No! This guy again!
Carrot! Thanks!
I love both the beautiful Ms. Nami
and the brave Ms. Carrot!
Ms. Nami! Ms. Carrot!
Will you be my wives?
Even if you say no, I know you love me!
You're fickle.
I don't think you understand what girls want.
Cool down and think about it!
Weather Egg!
Come on and hatch, thunderclouds!
What? Th-Thunder?!
Thunderbreed Tempo!
An awakening of love!
It's like heaven!
--That was cool, Nami!
--Now, let's go!
Wait, Straw Hat!
Wow! He's tough.
I wanna go on an adventure
along with beautiful ladies!
That's such an impure reason
to go on an adventure!
By taking down Straw Hat,
I'll be the captain of
Ms. Nami and Ms. Carrot!
Burning Blow!
Armament Hardening!
Oh, no!
Oh, I'm hungry again!
Straw Hat!
Huh? You're so persistent!
My name is All-Hunt Grount!
You'd better remember it!
But your journey ends here.
Because I've never lost to anyone!
Damn!
H-His punch is heavier than before.
That's because I hadn't eaten anything.
Damn!
Grount!
Pirates...
And the Four Emperors...
I'll bring them all down!
No, I'm the one who brings
the Four Emperors down!
--Are you okay?!
--Grount!
Okay, let's run!
--Where is the Submerge?
--That way!
You pests!
I can't let you pass through here.
Have you ever imagined
how many people are living in fear and tears...
...from your barbarous acts?!
All for your selfish dreams,
despite the misery you cause,
you guys call it an adventure!
And as Navy soldiers, we can't let you off!
Otherwise...
I'll be demoted!
So you're doing it for your own benefit?!
That's how fine-tuned justice works!
And now, I'll take your lives!
Grount recalls former Navy Admiral Aokiji!
Luffy struggles against the
Navy's desperate resistance
and when Grount stands in his way again,
a decisive battle between a
pirate and a Navy soldier,
each with their pride at stake, begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Devil's Fist! A Show
Down! Luffy vs. Grount!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!