I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Sanji, the cook of the Straw Hats,
suddenly left his friends behind.
He was being pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Split up temporarily from
Zoro and the others,
Luffy's team is heading for the
Whole Cake Island where Big
Mom waits to take back Sanji!
They came across Germa 66's ship
and met Sanji's siblings, Yonji and Reiju.
The rash on Luffy's body is all gone!
It was delicious!
Sanji's sister!
Thank you for saving my life.
But...
I still want Sanji back! He's my friend!
Look at that!
Bricks and houses and everything...
They're all...
...made of chocolate!
A chocolate town!
"Totto Land!
Emperor Big Mom Appears!"
Wow! There are so many kinds
of people and animals!
What the...! What the...!
What's with this town?!
There are tons of chocolate and candies!
What should I try first?!
What should I do?!
Chopper!
Look! Chocolate is pouring out!
Oh, I knew you wanted to start
with the fountain of chocolate!
The chocolate spout!
So sweet!
What's with this chocolate?
It's unbelievably good!
I can't stop!
CHOCOLATE BATHHOUSE
"Chocolate Bathhouse"?!
A chocolate bath?!
Can you really get cleaned
up? But I wanna try!
--Chocolate clothes?!
--Can you eat them?!
He's eating it!
Chocolate instruments?!
Chocolate clocks?!
Chocolate fireworks?!
You set off chocolate?!
--So interesting!
--It's a paradise!
What is it, Chopper?
I smell something really delicious!
What?! Let's go!
I managed to cover for us
but we should not stay long. Grr!
We gotta do what we have to do and just go...
Are you done?
Wow! This is cute!
Oh, Nami, you look great!
Thanks!
Hey, look! My costume looks
quite nice too, right?
Yeah, that's really gorgeous!
How's this?
Do I look like a pirate, Broo...
What?
Do you want more?
It's gonna take one more day to
get to the Whole Cake Island where Sanji is.
Go food shopping.
Okay! Yay!
I can't wait!
I wonder what kind of place it is!
Pedro, do you have binoculars?!
Thanks! Let's see...
Wow! It's so diverse here, Pekoms!
I see Minks, too!
It's like a wonderland!
Yes, that's exactly what
Mama's dream is about.
Humans, Minks, Fish-men,
Longarms, Longlegs, Dwarves...
A country where all races in the world
can live together without discrimination.
No, I mean everything in the world!
Everything in the world?
Yes, that's Mama's ideal world, Totto Land!
TOTTO LAND
Realize you're already deep
into a great territory!
This island is Cacao Island
run by the Minister of Chocolate.
The name of the town is Chocolat Town!
Chocolat Town?! What a wonderful name!
Everything in this town is made of chocolate.
What?! I love chocolate!
Am I allowed to eat it?!
Grr! In this town,
you can eat chocolate all you like!
Yes!
But be careful!
It's against the law to eat
the roof-tile chocolates.
Because they won't be able
to keep off rain or snow.
Window glass is the Minister
of Candy's jurisdiction
and construction posts are
the Minister of Biscuit's.
And everything else other than chocolate is
private or public property.
Looks delicious...
Hey! Were you listening?!
I couldn't understand at all.
Say, are their panties
also made of chocolate?
Of course, they are.
I can't wait to see chocolate panties!
We're not here to take a break.
Come back as soon as you
finish food shopping. Grr!
Okay!
Brook, you gotta get changed already.
Okay...
I'll stay in the ship since they know my face
but I love chocolate.
Get me some!
Okay!
Hey, Straw Hat!
If you're gonna go,
stop wasting your time and put on your disguise...
Luffy and Chopper have
already gone to the town.
What?!
Hey, what do you think will
happen if they find out
I brought you guys here?!
Act cautiously!
Don't worry!
We'll know where they are soon.
Somebody ate a cafe!
There they are!
Screw you!
If it were just the chocolate
walls they could be put back later
but the whole cafe is gone!
You guys messed with candies,
marshmallows, almonds and jelly beans!
That's a crime of Snackalism!
I need to question you!
Come to the station with me!
But, old man,
there is a good reason for this.
Yeah? Out with it!
It was too delicious!
Okay, well said, idiots!
Come with me!
Oh, no! They're gonna get arrested!
Don't make a scene, Pedro-san!
Wait, Chocopolice-san!
Nami! This way!
Wait!
They're in trouble! What should we do?!
What was that?
Is that...
A carpet?
Carpet! Carpet!
The carpet is flying...
Oh, you're the... owner!
Oh, more trouble!
The owner of the cafe came!
Look what they've done to your cafe!
Oh, no!
I can't believe this!
THE OWNER OF CAFE "CARAMEL"
NITRO THE JELLY
RABIAN THE CARPET
How could you leave this much?
This isn't what we agreed to! Gee!
You have to finish it properly!
Hey, do you know her?
No, I don't. Who is it?
And what's that thing on her shoulder?
I thought the combination of jam and biscuits
and chocolate here was delicious!
Oh, flying carpet! Wait!
Oh, no. I can't get up.
What are you doing?
Here! Try this!
How is it?
It's good!
Chocopolice-san, I'm sorry.
The cafe will be expired soon
so I asked them to eat the whole building!
Oh, pardon me! I didn't know
they were a demolition crew!
Come on, guys!
You should've had a sign out
when you were working.
There were still some customers, too.
Well then, if you'll excuse me.
Yes, thank you!
And I'm sorry to disturb you, everyone!
So it was nothing serious.
Oh, we were so worried.
Oh, yeah!
Congratulations on getting married,
Pudding-sama!
Your wedding day is approaching
and you're checking in on your cafe?
Don't work too much.
We all wish for your happiness!
Thank you!
She saved Luffy and Chopper.
She's so kind. I wonder who it is.
They're so lucky!
This is how fortune favors
the Pirate King to-be.
Oh?
Captain Pedro?!
You're Captain Pedro, aren't you?!
I thought so! It's been a while!
Why are you here?
I'm here for sightseeing. Don't tell anyone.
O-Okay. It's a pleasure to see you.
You know people in this town, Pedro?
I'll tell you later.
Pedro?
The wall chocolate is good!
I want it! I want it!
Hey, guys, how much can you eat?
I'm in a candy house. This is like a dream!
I'm so happy.
Where did the food in your stomach
from earlier go?
Luffy! This wall is delicious too!
When did you get there?!
Okay!
It's so good!
Every part of it is good!
Brook, you gotta try this too! It's good!
You too, Nami!
Is it really okay to eat this much?
Yes!
Um... Can I see your panties...
Don't push your luck!
Okay, I'll just have this then.
Jeez.
It's delicious!
So your name is Pudding.
Thank you for helping us!
No, no! I'm the one who
should be thanking you!
Why?
Because you said...
"It was too delicious"!
That chocolate at the cafe is a
new blend that I came up with!
Did you like how it melted in your mouth?
I added milk to cocoa butter
and highly-pure beet sugar
and kneaded it for three days
straight at 29 degrees Celsius!
I don't know what you're talking about
but it was so good!
It was!
You said it was delicious
and it really makes me want to cry!
Thank you! I'm so happy to hear it!
Wh... What a nice girl!
Do you like making chocolate?
I love sweets!
This town smells like chocolate
and it's like heaven!
Even the table is chocolate!
It's nice to know that!
We really want to stay
and thank you, Pudding,
but we need to go...
Yeah? That's too bad.
Before you go, would you like a cup of tea?
I guess you have a sweet taste in your mouth.
Tea sounds good!
Okay. I'll be right back.
Oh, what a nice girl!
She's really a nice girl!
I haven't asked your name, have I?
I'm Luffy.
The future Pirate King...
Hey!
What?
Luffy?
SOME ISLAND WHERE YOU CAN GET EGGS
The Emperor is on the move!
There'll be a tea party!
A tea party sounds like fun!
Don't be silly!
What are they gonna make this time?!
No idea! But so many people will die again!
Just one person?
Tighten security at the entrance!
AN ISLAND WHERE YOU CAN GET FLOUR
Dammit! Big Mom!
AN ISLAND WHERE YOU CAN GET FRUIT
How dare she do this?!
How could she do this for a
stupid thing like a tea party?!
THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
How long do we have until the tea party?
Three days, Mama
Flower! Flower!
I see
What about Germa's son?
He's here, Mama
Furniture! Furniture! Furniture! Furniture!
There will be a wedding
How is the cake?
The wedding cake
--The design?
--Okay!
--The budget?
--Don't be stingy!
Ingredients must be carefully selected
Kill the people and rob them
Eggs!
I got them.
Flour!
I got it!
Fruit!
I got it.
We'll make it taste good!
Let's eat a delicious cake!
Sweet dealings!
The tea party from hell!
--Is this strawberry jam?
--Or somebody's blood?
I don't care either way
If you're invited, be there at any cost!
A sweet moment
Sacrifices to the Devil
This is a dream land for everyone
All kinds of races come together
Totto Land!
Mmm, I can't wait!
I heard he is here
Yes, he is here
Straw Hat!
The lovely girl Pudding
who saved Luffy reveals
the surprising truth of the Big Mom Pirates
and her budding love for Sanji.
Is she an enemy or an ally?
As the gang takes precautions against her,
she makes an unexpected move!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Emperor's Daughter!
Sanji's fiancée - Pudding!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!