kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Sanji, the cook of the Straw Hats,
suddenly left his friends behind.
He was being pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Split up temporarily from
Zoro and the others,
Luffy's team is heading for the
Whole Cake Island where Big
Mom waits to take back Sanji.
On the way there, they secretly
stopped by at Chocolat Town,
none of the outermost towns of
Totto Land, for food supplies
but they got in trouble by eating a
whole cafe and were saved by
the owner of the cafe, Pudding.
So your name is Pudding.
Thank you for helping us!
No, no! I'm the one who
should be thanking you!
Why?
Because you said...
"It was too delicious"!
I haven't asked your name, have I?
I'm Luffy.
The future Pirate King...
Hey!
What?
Luffy?
"The Emperor's Daughter!
Sanji's fiancée - Pudding!"
CHOCOLAT TOWN, CACAO ISLAND
Luffy is...
Oh, no!
Now that I look closer, you look familiar!
Straw Hat Luffy!
That's right! I'm gonna be
the King of the Pirates!
We're totally screwed.
Are you people really
the Straw Hats, the pirates?!
Yes, we are!
Sanji-san's comrades?! You're kidding!
I'm not kidding! Sanji is our buddy!
What? Do you know Sanji?
Wait a minute.
I can't stop thinking that I've heard
the name Pudding somewhere before...
Yes, me too.
Uh-huh, you're right. Where was it?
Pudding... Pudding... Pudding...
Pudding?! Ah!
The highlight of the party
will be a wedding ceremony.
The groom is the third son
of the Vinsmoke Family,
GROOM - THIRD SON OF THE
VINSMOKE FAMILY - SANJI
Sanji!
What?!
What?!!
The bride is the 35th daughter
of the Charlotte Family,
BRIDE - 35TH DAUGHTER OF THE
CHARLOTTE FAMILY - PUDDING
Pudding.
Marriage?!
Pudding-san, would you by
any chance happen to be
a member of the Charlotte Family?
I am.
I-It's no mistake.
You should know this, Luffy!
What?!
Are you the Big Mom's daughter
who's gonna get married to Sanji, Pudding?!
Mm-hm.
Sanji's fiancée...
I'm jealous! She'll be such a beautiful wife!
W-Wife?!
Oh! But why?!
You people aren't even Mama's allies!
How did you pass the TARTE security?
Why did you come?!
Y-You're gonna be killed!
You're already in Mama's territory
and she's a very scary pirate!
But I know you people are scary pirates too!
No!
Wait! Calm down!
We won't get rough with you!
Luffy, what should we do with her-gara?
Don't get rough, Pedro!
Let her go, Pedro.
We came to take back Sanji.
What?
So you came for Sanji-san...
To take him back.
I knew he didn't consent
since Mama is so self-centered.
She even uses her children's marriage
to strengthen her pirate group.
We're giving up on marrying someone
freely out of love.
We only have two choices; give up or run.
One of my older sisters that I loved very dearly
went out to the sea looking for love.
To seek a match.
Just out of curiosity,
it said you're the 35th daughter
of the Charlotte Family.
Does Big Mom have 35 daughters?
Well, she has 39 daughters and 46 sons.
We're 85 brothers and sisters.
Oh, my!
Wow! That's so many brothers and sisters!
We have different fathers.
Mama has 43 husbands so we're a family of 129.
What... 129?!
Some of my older brothers and sisters
already have children
so if you count them in, there are more.
The Big Mom Pirates consist
mainly of her blood relatives.
She's true to her name - Big Mom!
Have you met Sanji?
Y-Y-Yes... just once.
Although his eyebrows are twirly,
he is very kind and gentlemanly!
Flower! Flower!
Even though he's got heart eyes,
he knows so much about making
sweets and taught me a lot!
Flower! Flower!
We like the same stuff and he's so manly!
I heard his feet are black
but he's tough and dependable!
He is, isn't he?!
That's not what "Black-Foot" means.
You really got him! He's a great guy!
D-Don't tell me you're in love with...
Are you in love with Sanji-kun?!
L-L-Love?! Well, I mean...
Mama's decision can't be overturned.
And if I marry someone, I prefer, um...
I like Sanji very much too!
We're the same!
No, I can't say such a thing!
SHOCK!!
Shock!
This is totally unexpected!
I can't believe such a lovely girl is the bride!
No wonder Sanji-san's got heart eyes!
We should tie her up!
She'll tell them that we're here.
If they find us while we're on
one of the outermost islands,
we'll never be able to get to Sanji!
How could you say that, Pedro?
How else can we silence her?
Don't forget she's Big Mom's daughter.
Yeah but she's scared of her mother too!
That's why she'll tell her!
How would you know?!
You stay out of this!
Excuse me.
I won't tell Mama about
Straw Hat-san and the rest of you!
I'm Big Mom's daughter
so I know it's hard to believe me but...
Don't say that.
I am scared of Mama but I've made up my mind!
If you all came to take back Sanji-san,
I'll help you!
How commendable of her...
You sure?
Yes because Mama and I
are two different people.
Let me garchu one more time!
How can you help us?
I think I can still let go of my feelings...
...towards Sanji-san!
What's that?
A map?
People in Totto Land...
give their blessings to my marriage.
So do the members of the Vinsmoke Family.
Mama looks forward to the wedding cake.
None of us can disobey Mama's order
so I knew I couldn't marry for love,
but I've been dreaming
ever since I was a child.
Wondering what my husband would be like.
And then, Sanji-san came along.
I was surprised
because he was such a wonderful man.
But he actually said to me in the end,
"I want to marry you but I can't do it."
"I want to go back to my friends."
What?! Sanji rejected a girl?!
But... it's good to know...
I knew he wanted to continue the adventure!
It wasn't just him who wanted to be back
because you all actually came here
to take him back at the risk of your lives.
Even if this is Mama's decision,
it'd be hard for me to stay with someone
who didn't want to get married.
And most of all, I know you all
care about Sanji-san so much
and I can't take him away from you.
He said he wanted to go
back to his friends too.
Then all I can do for him
is help him with that.
Right?
Pudding-san!
Take this route.
This is the only way you can get there
without Mama's seeing, which
only we children know of.
Is that where Sanji is?
If you go along this route,
you can get to the Whole Cake Island.
But Mama won't let go of Sanji-san.
So let's meet up at the southwest coast of
the Whole Cake Island tomorrow.
I'll bring Sanji-san there at any price.
I'll cooperate with you!
Is it okay?
Won't you get punished by Big Mom?
I'm her biological daughter.
Don't worry.
You're in enemy territory.
Worry about yourself.
Pudding...
But is it really okay?
Sanji-san and you all care about each other.
Pudding-san, you're so...
It's a bit of a shame
but my next husband to-be...
...could be someone nicer!
H-How wonderful this girl is!
Is she really the Emperor's daughter?!
Thank you, Pudding!
You're welcome!
Pudding-sama, we're here to pick you up.
One moment!
I'm working now so wait a second.
Get out through here.
And go in the direction of the cafe.
Got it!
Say, Pudding-san, before I leave,
may I see your panties...
Hurry up!
Pudding-sama!
Yes!
You need to stop working until the wedding,
Pudding-sama.
But I have customers...
You have to prepare for the wedding too.
My heroes, the evil army - Germa 66!
It gives me a thrill-rero.
BROCK COLLIE ISLAND, NEW WORLD
Charge!
This country is doomed!
It's Germa!
It's Germa 66's ship!
Thank you for coming, Germa-sama!
Cut it out.
Let me explain the situation.
Don't need that either.
What?!
--Do you have the money ready?
--O-Of course.
--Then, we have no business with you.
--Just stay here and watch.
Oh, it's you! The groceries
that you ordered are ready.
They're there so just take them.
Oh, there they are!
Can you carry them?
Thanks. We'll be fine!
Chocolate burger?!
Don't look at other stuff!
Let's go! Pekoms is waiting for us!
I want the chocolate burger, Nami!
--Chocolate pasta.
--Chocolate fried chicken.
We have enough food! Come on!
Oh? Pekoms?
Pekoms?
Pekoms-san?
Aren't you here?
Pekoms!
Did you find him?
No!
This is strange.
Doing number two, maybe?
What about the bathroom?
Hey!
There is a message in the bathroom!
"Turn back"?
--Did Pekoms write this?
--Who else would do that?
Did somebody invaded?
Has Pekoms been abducted?
Maybe they've found out about us.
In any event, this is serious.
TURN BACK
"Turn back" means if we don't do so,
something's gonna happen.
Yeah.
Okay, everyone, keep that in mind!
Let's go on!
It's getting exciting!
Consulting the map that Pudding drew,
Luffy and the others head
for the Whole Cake Island!
However, on that island,
Emperor Big Mom is running amok!
Trees and buildings have been destroyed
and no one can stop her insane rampage!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Massive Attack! Mom's Hunger Pangs!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!