I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Sanji, the cook of the Straw Hats,
suddenly left his friends behind.
He was being pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Split up temporarily from
Zoro and the others,
Luffy's team is heading for the
Whole Cake Island where Big
Mom waits to take back Sanji.
The girl who they met at
Chocolat Town on Cacao Island was...
Are you the Big Mom's daughter
who's gonna get married to Sanji, Pudding?!
Mm-hm.
I won't tell Mama about
Straw Hat-san and the rest of you!
I am scared of Mama but I've made up my mind!
If you all came to take back Sanji-san,
I'll help you!
Take this route.
This is the only way you can get there
without Mama's seeing,
which only we children know of.
Is that where Sanji is?
If you go along this route,
you can get to the Whole Cake Island.
But Mama won't let go of Sanji-san.
So let's meet up at the southwest coast of
the Whole Cake Island tomorrow.
I'll bring Sanji-san there at any price.
I'll cooperate with you!
There is a message in the bathroom!
TURN BACK
"Turn back"?
--Did Pekoms write this?
--Who else would do that?
Did somebody invade?
Has Pekoms been abducted?
Maybe they've found out about us.
In any event, this is serious.
"Turn back" means if we don't do so,
something's gonna happen.
Yeah.
Okay, everyone,
keep that in mind!
Let's go on!
It's getting exciting!
"A Massive Attack!
Mom's Hunger Pangs!"
BROCK COLLIE ISLAND, NEW WORLD
Damn!
--All done?
--Yes, sir.
Okay, let's go.
How dare you kill my wife?
How dare you kill my children?
How dare you destroy my country?
You're Germa, aren't you?!
You guys are not human!
Wall.
I can't believe it took four hours.
I have to attend my brother's wedding.
I have no interest in your family.
Nor your war for that matter.
It's finished.
How could a war between such
weak countries last two years?
--The commission?
--I got it.
--Thank you!
Our country has been saved.
Did we ask demons for help?
No, we didn't! They're angels!
Drop your weapons!
The war is over! It's over!
Thank you, Germa!
Germa 66! Hurray!
Germa! Germa! Germa! Germa!
The wedding is in three days.
Two days is enough
to get to the Whole Cake Island.
What about Sanji?
He's already here.
Oh, great. I can't wait to see him.
Yeah, right!
See you in two days.
Clank.
After their guide Pekoms disappeared,
Luffy's team left Cacao Island
and is following Pudding's directions
to the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
I'm worried about Pekoms.
We gotta look for him!
Thank you but that won't be easy.
He's a tough man so he'll be okay.
Yeah but...
I'm getting nervous.
Because we are going deeper into
the Emperor's territory.
We should just trust this map and go on.
At any rate, we need to get
to the whole Cake Island
without being seen by the enemy.
Hey, where are we now?
We haven't gone far from Cacao Island yet.
It's still a long way to go
to the Whole Cake Island.
Okay.
There's no need to rush, Luffy-san.
Pudding-san promised us...
...that she'll bring Sanji-san
to the southwest coast of the
Whole Cake Island at any cost.
I smell something good!
Yeah, it's not the smell of the sea!
It's sweet!
What kind of snack will
the next town be made of?
Oh, it's fun out here on the sea!
Hey, I see an island!
Yay! What kind of snack will be there?!
I can tell from the smell!
It must be something sweet!
The next one is probably a town made of jam.
Jam?!
We're not gonna stop there though.
What?!
Here, look.
When we see Jam Island,
we turn in the direction of the
Log Pose 2 instead of approach.
But it's sweet! Nami!
We're not gonna go there
even though it's sweet?!
Let's see...
That way.
Okay!
Luffy, starboard! In the direction
of sanji (three o'clock)!
That's right! Chopper! Carrot!
We're going in the direction of Sanji!
But it's sweet!
We're gonna go pick up Sanji!
Hard a starboard!
That's too much!
You're bad at this, Luffy-san!
You too, Brook!
But it's sweet...
By turning towards the next island
before getting too close to another one,
we can avoid their surveillance network,
she said.
Oh, so that's how you read the map.
--Can you do it?
--Count on me.
Luffy-san, I'll take it from here.
Okay.
Alright, guys, I'll cook something for you!
What?!
I gotta cook!
Please!
Luffy, wait a sec!
What do you want, Nami? I'll cook.
No!
I'm not gonna mess up this time!
I'll do it! Don't you ever set
foot in the kitchen again!
I'm not paying you one dime!
--I don't need your money!
--What?!
Can I look, Pedro?
I wanna help!
Okay.
Let's see...
Hey! The water is grape-colored!
Grape?
--She's right!
--Yeah, it is!
There is an island that
spills juice around here.
It's no harm to us.
What?! Is that juice?!
This place is such a paradise!
Pedro, how do you know
so much about this area?
Remember? You also saw someone
you know in Chocolat Town.
Yeah, I've been here once before.
What?
Hey, Brook! What are you doing?!
It's not me!
What was that?!
I see something in the water!
What?!
What is that?!
Oh, no! It's kind of snake-like!
It's gone.
Carrot-san, do you see anything?!
Let's see... Oh, look! It's coming again!
There it is!
It's gigantic!
Wow! It's big!
It's a Giant Sea Centipede.
They reside in this area.
They are monsters that eat anything -
people, ships, etc.
No! Giant Sea Centipede, go away!
We'll be eaten!
Luffy, this is your job!
All right!
I'll do what little I can too!
Here it comes!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Oh, is that it?
Who wants more?!
What?! I wanted to fight too!
Sorry, sorry!
What?! What?! What?!
What is it this time?!
Wow, look at that!
This one is bigger than the last one!
It's twice as big as the last one!
It's almost as big as the Neptunians!
The sea of the New World is unbelievable!
Why are you so happy?!
This one is enormous.
This one may give us some trouble!
I won't let you eat my ship!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Its shell is too hard so
it doesn't feel anything!
Plus, it's massive!
Okay, aim at its belly!
Let's attack all at once!
Gear Two!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp!
That's impressive.
I'm exhausted from being scared...
The worst is yet to come.
Are there more of those?!
He said we'll attack all at once!
But again I didn't get a chance to show off!
Do you think it was edible?
No! Don't eat it!
Meanwhile, on the Whole Cake Island...
THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Croquembouche!
Mama! Stop! Mama!
Mama... Mama, please stop!
Move!
Croquembouche!
Oh no! It's Mama's illness!
Hurry up-bon!
What does she want this time-soir?!
She wants...
...croquembouche!
Croquembouche?!
Is that the decorated dessert that
is composed of cream puffs piled up?
This will be a challenge.
Oh! No, wait!
I think there is a tourist group of
cream puffs staying at a
hotel in the city-je-t'aime!
They already checked out this morning.
Should we just make one?
What does the chef say?
I want to make the dough special.
Could you get me almonds?
I'll tell the Minister of Nuts!
Croquembouche! Croquembouche!
Mama is heading towards Sweet City now!
She's coming this way?!
This is the capital! Mama's castle is here!
We can't talk her out of it!
She's losing her mind from the attack!
The death toll is still rising!
Issue an evacuation order in Sweet City!
Only a croquembouche can stop Mama now!
This way! Hurry up and evacuate!
Hurry up!
Hey! Isn't the croquembouche ready yet?!
Croquembouche!
Mama! I hope she's not
gonna eat the capital up!
Mama, please stop!
Mama, let's not do this!
Bring me croquembouche!
Mama entered Sweet City!
She entered Sweet City!
Oh, she's finally here...
Mama's Hunger Pangs are
very troublesome-bon!
You don't know when the attack will strike.
It's worse than any kind of disaster.
Is the chef still making it?!
The kitchen is busy as hell!
All we can do is wait-main.
The destruction continues
until she gets a bite of what she craves.
Anyway, evacuate all the residents!
Run! Hurry up!
Big Mom's having a tantrum!
--Stop!
--Not in this city!
Mama! Mama! Not in this city!
--She'll destroy her own castle!
--It's no good. She can't hear us.
Croquembouche!
Losing herself, Big Mom eats up everything
in town and terrorizes Sweet City!
When even the Big Mom
Pirates run out of options,
that man who used to be one of the
Seven Warlords cuts through the rough
sea and shows up to end the crisis!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Capital City Falls?! Big Mom and Jimbei!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!