I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Sanji, the cook of the Straw Hats,
suddenly left his friends behind.
He was being pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Split up temporarily from
Zoro and the others,
Luffy's team is heading for the
Whole Cake Island where Big
Mom waits to take back Sanji.
I guess you're leaving, Jimbei.
But,
having a pledge of loyalty reneged
brings shame to a lord.
Jimbei, you know this means
I'm going to lose a powerful asset - you.
Yes but...
No "but"!
You should lose something too!
You have to pay a price!
Now, spin it.
I can't wait to see what you're gonna lose!
What are you gonna do after you defeat Kaido?
That's too far ahead!
I haven't thought about it...
Next, you'll need the Road Ponegliff
that Big Mom has!
If so, this would be our biggest chance!
Since we came this deep into her territory,
we'd better steal Big Mom's Road Ponegliff
in addition to taking back Sanji!
When we reach the island,
could I have a little time?
This time, I'll get it!
And Luffy and the others arrived at their
destination by following Pudding's map.
Hey, somebody's there!
Sanji?
Is that Sanji?! Hey!
Sanji!
"A Mysterious Forest Full of Candies!
Luffy vs. Luffy?!"
--Did you see him?
--Are you sure, Luffy?!
Where? Where?
Where is he?
Oh?
Where did he go? Sanji!
Sanji!
THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
We are go!
--I never get tired of looking at it!
--Me neither!
Channel 3!
Here it comes!
Shark Submerge 3!
I'll take Pedro-san then.
I'm sorry, Luffy!
I said I'll go on my own
but I'm relying on Brook.
Don't mention it!
I think I can help you, Pedro-san!
Infiltration is my specialty!
I'll get a copy of the Ponegliff at any cost!
Yeah, I'll be counting on you!
Brook! Pedro!
Stop it!
I'm sorry that I always scare you!
After we meet up with Sanji and Pudding,
we'll be waiting for you around here.
We all have to be really careful!
Don't forget Pekoms' message!
TURN BACK
Yeah, we decided to go on!
We just gotta do it!
--We're counting on you!
--See you!
Good luck!
See you later!
Okay, let's go!
Shark Submerge 3.
Commence dive.
Depth: 15 meters. Visibility: good.
Oxygen: good enough. Cola: full.
All quiet.
It's going well!
Let's go up the river,
straight to Big Mom's castle!
I hope the river is deep.
Thank you for this!
SOUTHWEST COAST
Ya-hoo!
Okay, I landed!
We've arrived at Big Mom's island!
That's huge!
The whole island is made of cakes!
--I smell an adventure!
--I don't want one!
As soon as we find Sanji-kun,
we'll go back!
Hey! Sanji! Pudding!
We're here as promised!
Don't shout! The enemy will notice!
Hey, did you really see them, Luffy?
I did! I'm sure!
But when we looked,
they were already gone!
Yummy! Nami, try and eat the soil!
It's hard whipped cream!
Yummy!
You're right! It's meringue.
Is this island full of candies like the others?
What?! I wanna live here!
Around here!
I'm sure I saw Sanji and Pudding here
but when I looked away, they were gone!
This is certainly the southwest coast.
And I know you don't lie,
but I don't know why they left.
I wanna see Sanji already.
Oh?
Hey!
There he is!
--Sanji!
--What?
Sanji!
--What happened?
--Hey!
What's going on?
Sanji was there just now!
Why is he hiding?
Really?
Oh?
Sanji?
What? Where did he go?
We lost him!
But this place looks delicious!
It's a forest of candies!
Smells sweet!
If all three of them saw him,
it can't be wrong.
But why did he have to disappear?
Sanji-kun...
Believe this if nothing else.
I didn't mean to hide
anything from my friends.
Maybe he feels embarrassed...
Hey! Sanji! Come on out!
We're here to pick you up!
Sanji!
Okay, let's split up and search!
I'm going this way!
Where you see a bunch of cakes!
I'm going straight!
Where the sweet caramel-like
smell comes from!
Then, I'll go this way!
Look at those jelly beans! They're cute!
Wait! I don't want a secondary disaster!
What?! We just lost him
so all we can do is chase a hunch!
That's how people who get lost would think.
Plus, aren't you guys driven by
some other cravings?!
Some other?
Cravings?
No, we aren't.
Don't lie!
All right! I'll search with you guys!
All three of you, stay with me! Okay?
Mm-hm. Got it!
We got permission! Let's eat!
--Yay!
--I love sweet things!
Are we gonna be okay like this?
Look! There are lollipops!
Oh yeah! Let's go!
Damn Sanji! How dare he hide
in such a delicious place!
That bastard!
I said "Stay with me"! Hey!
Strawberry-flavored!
Strawberry?! I want that too!
--This flower is a candy!
--Really?!
This is where the caramel smell comes from!
It's so sweet! It sticks my teeth!
I'm so happy!
Hey, guys! Do you remember?
We're here to pick up Sanji-kun!
You guys are too distracted by the candy!
I thought we were gonna look for Sanji-kun!
I know!
But there are sweets everywhere!
Don't you think that's strange?!
We're in the enemy's territory!
We'll search to some extent
and if we can't find him, we'll go back.
What?!
Why?!
This green river! It's melon juice!
Really?! Let me try!
--So sweet!
--Isn't it?!
If you take a close look at this bridge,
it's a doughnut!
Hey! That's enough!
Cross the bridge!
Nami!
It's a crocodile!
Do you wanna take it down, Luffy?!
No.
Oh, just humans...
What did you think we were?!
That's not important!
The crocodile is wearing clothes and a hat
and he talked!
Just as I thought,
this forest is dangerous and strange!
If that surprises you, take a look at us.
Well, I know what you mean but...
I think we'd better trust Pudding
and wait by the sea!
I'm sure she'll bring Sanji-kun!
And look!
Our road back is already problematic!
We'll be fine. If we jump over
the river, we can always go back.
You're right but I don't think we should stay in this forest
any longer...
What?! I wanna stay here
and eat more candies!
Why don't you have a lollipop too?
What?
What?!
There's another Luffy?!
Who are you?!
"Who are you"?! I'm Luffy!
Stop mocking me!
What do you want?!
How did you do this?!
How about this?!
I said "Stop mocking me"!
Or I'll beat you up!
What?! What's going on?!
Which one is the real Luffy?!
They move and talk exactly the same!
No, they're a bit different!
Like a mirror-image, his scar and accessories
and everything are inverted.
It really looks like there's a mirror!
Who is that?!
Who are you?!
She's asking who you are!
Answer her, you idiot!
There he is! I found Sanji!
There! Up in the tree!
Hey! Sanji!
Get out of my way, you fool!
Sanji!
Sanji-kun, what are you doing up there?!
Oh, he's running again! Sanji!
You bastard! Outta my way!
Damn! You guys, go ahead!
Chase him!
O-Okay!
I'm coming too!
Don't get separated!
Chopper! Carrot!
This forest is strange!
Something's gonna happen again!
I know! But if we lose Sanji again...
Sanji!
Nami, go with them!
I'll catch up with you after I beat him up!
Yeah, okay!
Why are you doing this, Sanji-kun?
Sanji!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Sanji! Please stop!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Who the hell are you?!
Luffy continues fighting a fierce battle
against the other Luffy!
Meanwhile, in front of Nami and the others
who are headed deeper into the forest,
a mysterious big man
and a rabbit knight suddenly appear!
In the forest where everything
starts moving and going
out of control, the Straw Hats
get caught in a deadly trap!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Mom's Assassin! Luffy
and the Seducing Woods!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!