I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji
who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Then, in a mysterious forest,
they finally found Sanji. However...
Hey!
There he is!
Sanji!
He disappeared for some reason.
In addition, a Luffy double who moves and talks
exactly the same as him appeared.
And then, they found Sanji again.
However...
Sanji-kun, what are you doing up there?!
Oh, he's running again! Sanji!
You bastard! Outta my way!
Damn! You guys, go ahead!
Chase him!
O-Okay!
I'm coming too!
Don't get separated!
Chopper! Carrot!
This forest is strange!
Something's gonna happen again!
I know! But if we lose Sanji again...
Sanji!
Sanji! Please stop!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Who the hell are you?!
"Mom's Assassin!
Luffy and the Seducing Woods!"
What?!
Yikes!
Th-There's a gigantic half-buried man!
It's a Giant!
--You scared me!
--We should be saying that!
Are you okay?!
Who did this to you?!
What?
Your body is half-buried!
My body?
I'm just asking you "Did someone bury you?"
What's the matter?
I'm half-buried because I wanted to be.
What?! Is he stupid?!
I shouldn't have been worried!
The thing is...
I wanna have some juice.
I don't care!
Chopper, don't take him seriously!
He'll drive you crazy!
Wait, wait, you guys.
He's saying something.
Ignore him!
I like apple juice very much.
--So what?!
--Don't listen to him.
If you go left,
there are waterfalls of apple juice.
I like them very much.
Remember what Luffy told us?
We should be looking for Sanji-kun.
Am I dreaming?
You're looking for someone, aren't you?
He came this way.
What?! Did he?!
I said "Don't take him seriously"!
If you get me some apple juice,
I'll tell you.
Okay, okay.
Watch out! Nami! Chopper!
A rabbit?!
No! Let's run!
There are talking trees and crocodiles,
and the rabbit was trying to kill us!
This place is weird.
Let's go back to see Luffy!
We still know the way!
But what about Sanji?!
We don't know
if he was real or not anymore!
We finally saw each other
but he didn't even get up!
He didn't say anything!
Yeah...
And if that's the real Sanji-kun,
do you think he'd just stand by
and watch us going through this?!
N-No, maybe not...
Yeah, he said nothing and disappeared
when we first found him.
All right. Let's go back.
The needles are...
Look! The clock is like that too!
Everything about this forest is strange!
Did you hear that?
Yes, I did
Move over
Tree, tree, tree, tree
Close up their way out
Flower! Flower! Flower!
Let's play
Let's play a murder game!
--Chopper, can't you go faster?!
--This is the fastest I can go!
Is he coming?
Yeah, he's coming after us!
We gotta get out of this
forest as soon as possible!
Yeah!
That rabbit is formidable!
But he's not a Mink!
You sure?!
Is he a Devil Fruit eater?
They've noticed
The Straw Hats have noticed
About us
--No, they haven't.
--There's something wrong
They've noticed
--Brulee-sama is...
--...Playing with them
Who will make prey of them?
It will be delicious if we
make smoothies out of them
See! He can't use Electro!
Take this!
--Carrot! Stay with us!
--Okay!
I'm sorry, Bird-san!
C...
Crane!
RANDOLPH - THE CRANE RIDER
THE BIG MOM PIRATES
--The weapon is...
--...Coming towards us!
Does it bring back memories?
It's good to finally see you!
I was surprised to know
that weak old Sanji is still alive
and is a pirate now.
Say something.
Go away.
I cut ties with my family.
I have nothing to say to you guys.
Well, we have something to say!
I heard you're refusing to
marry the daughter of the Charlotte Family.
You're a good-for-nothing fool.
You have no choice.
Didn't you hear me?
I said "Go away."
Yeah? Then, why don't you
make me go away yourself?!
Diable Jambe!
Flambage Shot!
Chopper! Carrot! Dodge!
Okay!
What's going on back there...
No!
What?!
He can serve as a landmark!
Oh, you guys from earlier!
The field of lollipops!
A little more to go until we reach Luffy!
You bastard! Outta my way!
Gear Three!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant...
...Pistol!
--He's still fighting!
--Luffy!
Let's go back to the coast!
Oh? Why're you guys here?!
Hurry up! I'll tell you later!
This forest has a bunch of creepy traps!
Let's go back to the Sunny!
Okay!
Somebody's after us!
Let's get out of the
forest as fast as we can!
That's the river where
we saw the talking crocodile!
If I remember right, as soon as we
cross the river, we can get out!
Let's jump over it like this!
Here we go!
Wait, guys! That's not the real me...
Did you say something, Luffy?!
No, I didn't.
Guys! Let's keep running
without slowing down!
Okay!
What happened to Sanji?!
He ran away from us
and didn't come back!
Something's wrong with him,
even though he sure looks like Sanji!
Let's talk after we get out, Nami!
Yeah! I'm glad that we still know the way!
We'll reach the coast soon!
Yeah!
--Oh?!
--What?!
What?! Why?!
Oh, it's you guys again!
Hey, could you pull out the thing
that's stuck to my...
We just went straight back the way we came!
Why are you here?!
Don't yell. It scares me.
Did you ask why I am here?
I was here the whole time!
You were here the whole time?
It's you guys that left and came back.
--Chopper, let's try again!
--Uh-huh!
Hey! Pull out the thing
that's stuck in my head!
Running through the field of lollipops...
Jumping over the crocodile's river...
Let's get to the coast this time!
You scared me!
Why do you guys keep coming back here?
Again?! Even without the Log Pose working,
we don't need to know the directions
because it's one simple path!
Going straight back this way...
Slowly... Slowly...
Oops.
Flower?!
What?! The trees and flowers are moving!
One, two! One, two!
The soil is moving and talking!
What's going on?
What are those things?
What's with this forest?!
--They found out!
--They did!
Cake!
Flower! Flower!
There was no path from the beginning!
You finally became aware...
...of the terror of this forest!
Hey, Luffy, what are you doing?!
This is the Seducing Woods!
Nami! That's not Luffy!
Who are you?!
Who am I?
We were together the whole time!
No matter how many times you try,
you'll never get out of this forest!
Never...
Not until you die!
Let go of me!
Calm down, young girl.
Look at the scar on my face.
CHARLOTTE BRULEE
THE 8TH DAUGHTER OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
Isn't it terrible?
Who are you-teia?! A tree?
I'm not a damn tree! I'm Brulee!
Brulee?
A cute rabbit and a pretty girl...
How nice...
When I see those beautiful faces...
it makes me want to scratch them up!
The Kingdom of Germa once ruled
over the North Blue with their
massive military forces!
Its king is Sanji's father,
namely Vinsmoke Judge!
When Sanji sees him again,
it brings back memories
from his rough and painful childhood!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Seafaring Kingdom! Germa's King Judge!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!