I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Separated from Nami and the others in
the Seducing Woods, Luffy caught...
How did you guys multiply?!
Leave or Life?
Life.
"The Land of Souls!
Mom's Fatal Ability!"
What's going on?!
They have multiplied and
are barking like animals!
What happened to you guys?!
Aren't any of you real?!
Hey, Sanji!
Pudding! Chopper!
Carrot!
Nami!
Untie me!
She talks like a human!
I'm the real Nami!
Listen! I was looking for you!
How dare you tie me up all of a sudden!
I... I'm really sorry...
But it sure is surprising.
What's going on?
She certainly looks like me.
If all the real ones are among them,
that'd make it easy.
I thought you guys multiplied.
No, we didn't!
I mean, we kinda did but...
Cut it out! Hey, you!
What?!
You know something, don't you?
You were here the whole time even
when we were attacked by that woman!
I didn't see anything!
Don't lie!
Hey, what happened?
I was attacked by you, Luffy!
By me?!
To be exact, that was a fake you who I
thought was you and tried to escape with!
What do you mean?
That "Luffy" suddenly turned into
a giant woman and attacked us...
Let go of me!
Who are you-teia?!
I'm Brulee!
Brulee?
A cute rabbit and a pretty girl...
How nice...
When I see those beautiful faces...
it makes me want to scratch them up!
Nami!
No!
Stop resisting, young lady.
Wh-Where's Luffy?!
Well, I don't know.
I guess he's wandering in the forest.
Climate Baton!
Nami, are you okay?!
Yeah! That was close!
Thank you, Usopp!
How insolent!
Carrot!
Leave it to me!
You have a pretty face
but a lot of nerve as well!
Eleclaw!
It's my turn!
Reflection!
Carrot!
Are you okay?!
Carrot's punch came out of the mirror!
What did you do?!
I'm a mirror!
I ate the Mirror-Mirror Fruit
and became a mirror human!
Just like a mirror reflects light,
if you throw a punch at my mirror,
it'll reflect it back too!
Be careful, Carrot!
I'll destroy your stupid mirror!
What a silly rabbit.
Mirro-world!
Now, come on in!
Carrot!
She disappeared...
What did you do to her?!
One down!
I can't get out! Let me out!
What did you do?! Give her back to us!
Stay away, Nami!
I can't do that.
Nami!
Chopper!
Help me!
Mama already knew that you guys were here!
What?!
Did you think that no one noticed?
How idiotic!
We are all coming after you guys
by Mama's order!
That one...
These ones...
Those fools...
And him!
All of us have been commanded by Mama!
"Leave the Straw Hats at large for now."
"But don't let them see Sanji."
"Make them regret standing against me!"
Mama knows everything!
Alright, Homies! Don't let them escape!
Oh, no! We'll be surrounded!
You can't get away!
No!
Chopper!
Nami, run!
There are too many enemies!
If all three of us get caught, we'll be dead!
They are members of the Emperor's clan!
We should've been more careful!
Go look for Luffy!
I'll do the best I can here!
Okay! I'll be back!
Rumble!
Monster Point!
That's amazing! He's already a funny animal
but he also has such a special skill!
Mama will be happy!
All the races of the world aren't enough
because she's an unrivalled exotic animal collector!
Now, catch them!
Stop, you brat!
Go away!
She can't get away!
Luffy! Where are you?!
Then, I kept running around
and was looking for you until it got dark!
I see! I'm glad that you found me!
All right!
Let's go save Chopper and Carrot now!
Where are they?
Here.
It all happened right here.
But now, they're all gone.
That's why I'm asking him!
You were watching the whole time!
Where's Chopper? And Carrot?!
THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
How are the Straw Hats doing?
They're being tormented
in the Seducing Woods!
By Brulee-sama!
And by the Homies!
You'll never get out of the forest!
How much more can they stand?!
I see. That's good.
There you are, Cracker.
What do you want, Mama?
Go teach Straw Hat and his clan a lesson.
Straw Hat?
They're in the Seducing Woods.
Give them a taste...
...of pain and terror
which will make them welcome death!
Okay.
Mama.
Say something already!
That woman, Brulee, and the forest monsters
didn't even touch you!
That means you're one of them!
One of them?
Well, I'm certainly not their enemy.
Where are those two?!
Oh! If you want me to tell you,
bring me some apple juice from over on my left...
We have no time for that!
If you really tell us something good,
sure, I'll bring it to you!
You mean it?!
Yeah, since you insist on it,
I wanna drink it too!
Uh-huh!
By the way,
you look quite strong but...
...are you strong too?
Y-Yes, I am strong! So what?
I see. You don't look strong.
That reindeer guy was surprisingly strong,
but the trees of the forest attacked him
without hesitation.
Once they're ordered,
they're not gonna stop...
...until they fulfill their mission!
Yeah? Then, why did they stop attacking me?
When I beat tons of them,
they quieted down too!
Hey, how can they even move?
Every six months,
the citizens of Totto Land...
...must pay one-month worth of their "souls"
to the country in exchange for their safety.
"Soul"?
Yes, in other words, their lifespans.
So the people lose two months
of their lifespans in a year
and one year of their lifespans out of every six.
What do you mean?
Linlin, I mean Big Mom
ate the Soul-Soul Fruit.
What's that?
She can manipulate people's souls.
With that power,
she's claiming part of the citizens' lifespans.
At that moment, they have to choose to stay
in Totto Land or leave.
Leave or Life?
Life.
And by spreading the collected souls
all over the country,
all kinds of things come to life
and are anthropomorphized.
We call those who came to life the Homies.
Collecting and scattering the souls...
...are done by incarnations made of
Linlin, I mean Big Mom's own soul.
That's the truth of Totto Land.
In the town of chocolate where we stopped by first,
a variety of things were alive too!
Is that why the crocodile talked
and the rabbit acted like a human?!
That's correct.
Animals can be anthropomorphized too.
What a power!
What about them?
They're different.
They're merely animals who have been turned into
human forms by Brulee's power.
Oh, by the way, souls can't be infused into
other people and corpses.
Why didn't you say something?!
You've been watching the whole time!
I don't wanna get involved in anything!
Why are you buried here
if you don't wanna get involved?!
Why?! Who are you?!
Say it! I'll give you the juice!
O-Okay! I'll say it so get off of me!
Stop!
Say it already!
Years and years ago, I was Big Mom's...
I mean, the pirate Charlotte Linlin's...
Linlin's...
Linlin's husband!
What?!
Wh-Why is the one of the
Sweet 3 Generals here?!
CHARLOTTE CRACKER - THE 10TH SON
ONE OF THE SWEET 3 GENERALS, THE MINISTER OF BISCUIT
THE BIG MOM PIRATES
Straw Hat!
I'm going to...
...put an end...
...to your lives!
The Sweet 3 Generals are the Big
Mom Pirates' greatest warriors!
One of them, Cracker comes to attack!
When a tremendous wave of his anger turns
the Seducing Woods into hell,
a fierce deadly battle
between Cracker and Luffy begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Top Officer! The Sweet 3 General Cracker Appears!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!