I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the
Whole Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
They entered the Seducing Woods
and started to fight against Cracker,
one of the Sweet 3 Generals.
Pretzel Roll!
Meanwhile, Pound who was watching Nami
being attacked and cornered...
Let go of her, Brulee!
Nami finally drove Brulee off.
Thunderbolt...
...Tempo!
In addition, Nami became
confirmed that the Vivre Card
that Lola gave her was Big Mom's.
I see. It's no mistake!
Lola's mother is Big Mom.
The fact that those trees in the forest
are afraid of this Vivre Card is the proof.
I'll make the most of it, Lola!
"An All-out Duel!
Gear Four vs. the Bis-Bis Ability!"
Can't you sleep?
What do you want?
You're as cold as ever.
Don't you think it's natural for a big sister
to worry about her sweet little brother?
Stop it. That creeps me out.
Ichiji and Niji will be here by tomorrow.
For the first time in 13 years,
the whole family will gather together.
Tomorrow's gonna be very busy.
We'll meet Big Mom at the Whole Cake Chateau.
And we'll have an engagement ceremony
for you and Pudding.
You'd better get some rest.
THE SEDUCING WOODS
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Axe!
...Grizzly Magnum!
Double Pretzel...
...Roll!
Oh, no! We'll get involved!
Hey! Don't spread out too much
and neglect our duty as the Seducing Woods!
We shouldn't let anyone out of here!
O-Okay!
Block his way!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Gatling!
Hard Biscuit!
Damn! It's hard!
This guy's Color of Arms!
If you think of Vinsmoke Sanji as your friend,
why don't you leave him alone?
He's a prince of a mighty kingdom.
He's in a totally different class from you.
By taking a noble wife, he can live here...
...in great comfort.
You can't even wish your friend happiness
and you're just being selfish
saying you're gonna take him back.
Seeing such an annoying captain,
the virtuous prince would be disgusted
and probably say:
"Get packing, you pathetic low-class pirate!"
He surely is pathetic!
You low-class pirate! Get packing!
Muscle Balloon!
Gear Four!
Bounce-Man!
Muscle Balloon is a good name.
But what can a balloon do?
Let me say it one more time!
Get packing, you pathetic low-class pirate!
Gum-Gum Kong...
Hard Biscuit!
...Gun!
Cracker-sama!
Don't underestimate Sanji!
Even if he's happy
and doesn't want to come back,
he'd never talk to us like that!
SWEET CITY
So that's the Whole Cake Chateau
where Emperor Big Mom is.
--Yeah.
--How's security?
The chateau is heavily guarded
by Biscuit Warriors.
Biscuit Warriors?
Pedro-san, how can we get through
such tight security?
Don't worry. I have an idea.
Let's use that one-gara.
What?
What is this place?
I think it's a world in Brulee's mirror.
I wonder how far it goes.
I see no end.
But I see mirrors everywhere.
--Let's look into one.
--Yeah.
My ankles hurt!
Hang on, Carrot!
This isn't that hard so stop whining!
All right!
What do you mean by making
the most of Linlin's...
I mean, Big Mom's Vivre Card?
Didn't you hear what that
arrogant tree said earlier?
You mean Kingbaum?
He said "We Homies can't
fight against her-ju!"
Stop!
Are you guys trying to escape?
I'm sorry. It was his idea.
Don't lie! It was yours!
Listen. You guys are gonna be my loyal servants
from now on.
Stop talking nonsense, you brat!
Yeah! Who do you think you are?!
What? Are you gonna resist?
Am I talking nonsense?
N-No, you aren't-ju...
Rabbit-kun, what do you think?
--I'm sorry. It was his fault.
--Hey!
Listen, you guys must back Luffy up now!
A-Are you telling us
to fight against Cracker-sama?!
That's impossible-ju!
Oh, yeah?
Come on, go help Luffy now!
Take Cracker down!
We can't fight Mama's Life Paper -
Vivre Card-ju!
You little...
I'm gonna go see Sanji!
Gum-Gum...
Don't push your luck!
Pretzel...
...Kong Gun!
...Roll!
Cracker-sama!
What?!
You did a good job breaking...
...my armor!
Who are you?!
Who am I?
I think I already told you
that I'm Sweet General Cracker.
THOUSAND ARMED CRACKER
That was my favorite armor...
Armor?
No way! He coughed up blood!
--That was jam!
--Jam?!
Since I'm a true artisan,
I even make sure that it tastes good too.
I ate the Bis-Bis Fruit
and became a biscuit human.
I can generate an infinite amount of biscuits
and manipulate them!
To shape them into anything...
Crushed Biscuit!
And if I craft it carefully...
There you go! The face of a tough warrior!
Throughout history, biscuits changed
their shapes with the times
and on their bakers' whims.
Not that many people have ever found out
what I truly look like.
In fact, the picture on my wanted poster
that's issued by the Government...
...is not me. It's my armor.
I hate pain. I hate shots too!
That's why I wear armor or manipulate it
to fight.
It multiplies as I clap my hands!
That's how my dreamlike biscuit works.
So I have a limitless force at my disposal!
The one that you broke with your life
was just one of my Biscuit Warriors...
...that I can generate endlessly.
Do you understand why you'll never see
Vinsmoke Sanji again?
I'll be back.
I'm gonna see Sanji!
The Biscuit Warriors keep
multiplying without end!
The back and forth battle between them
and Luffy's Gear Four attacks intensifies!
Meanwhile, Sanji meets
his two older brothers!
Their outrageous behaviors enflame
Sanji's chivalrous spirit!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The First and the Second
Join! The Vinsmoke Family!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!