kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the
Whole Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy is fighting a fierce battle against
Cracker who revealed
himself in the Seducing Woods.
Meanwhile, Sanji faced his
older brothers Ichiji and Niji
for the first time in
years at Germa's castle.
You bastard...
How much of an asshole can you be?
Are you trying
to leave a scar on a woman's face?!
"The Benefactor's Life!
Sanji and Owner Zeff!"
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Gun!
Damn! I see no end!
That's right. There is no end.
My biscuits are endless!
I'll destroy them faster
than you can make them!
Finding out which of us is faster?
Sounds like fun!
Gum-Gum...
...Double Culverin!
Don't underestimate my ability!
Damn. This is no good!
I don't have time!
Are you giving up?
Or are you running out of energy?
I'm gonna destroy them all at once!
Here we go!
Gum-Gum...
Defense!
...King Kong Gun!
What the?!
Oh, no!
Is he deflating?
Damn...
I've already reached the limit.
I need 10 minutes.
I gotta hide somewhere.
What did you say? A woman?
Why are you defending a mere cooking wench?!
So gentlemanly.
The food fell on the floor.
This is called Aligot.
It's made from cheese blended into potatoes.
Sanji-sama, I'll clean it!
Potatoes increase your immunity
and stabilize your blood pressure.
They're very nutritious.
And maybe because you guys are so special,
the cut of meat in the confit
has been carefully selected too.
It's a very elaborate dish to make
for breakfast.
Oh, please don't, Sanji-sama!
A person of royal blood mustn't
eat food off the floor!
Hey, are you out of your mind?!
That's disgusting!
It's perfectly flavored too.
The spirit of the poor has taken root in you!
Stop doing such a disgraceful thing!
Don't, Niji! The wedding is coming up!
Thank you, sir.
You only bring shame to the Vinsmokes.
What's shameful to me is
being part of the family!
What?!
An idiot who has no respect for food.
A man who beats a woman.
The arrogance of royalty that compels you
to see your servants as less than human!
Everything about you guys goes against
what I stand for!
What you're saying is the kind of
nonsense all those losers spout, Sanji.
I couldn't understand what you were saying
since we were young.
Royalty has its own reckoning of the world!
You're the unreasonable one!
He's right.
You're more wrong than ever.
Is it because of the bad
influence from this man, Sanji?
Big Mom's ability to collect information
is greater than people think.
So you were working at his
restaurant until two years ago.
We've already zeroed in on its location too.
Seems like this picture was taken recently.
The sea restaurant, Baratie!
What's wrong? You're turning pale.
Where did your spirit from earlier go, Sanji?
Say something. Huh? Hey!
What are those?
These are bracelets to prevent
him from escaping-bon.
Seems like both the Straw
Hats and Sanji himself are
going to oppose this marriage-bon.
I'll lend you these bracelets
and tell you his weak point just in case-soir.
His weak point?
Well, only in the worst-case scenario
where you become uncontrollable,
I'll use it as a threat like,
"We'll chop this guy's head off."
Don't do anything stupid.
You know what we're capable of.
Don't ever resist.
Give up on your friends and
accept this marriage to Pudding.
Then, everything's going to be alright.
Sanji!
I will find the All Blue some day!
Captain!!
That damn brat!
So you've come to, little brat?
You're very lucky.
Pirate...! Ow, ow, ow...
There's no way you can move!
Whose kicks do you think you took?
What about the ships?
Who knows... The sea was very rough.
I wouldn't be surprised if they
were completely destroyed.
We're the only ones who washed up here.
There's no fruits or animals
on this rocky mountain.
We have no choice but
to wait for help anyway.
That bag over there is your share.
What?
That's the food that luckily washed up here.
It's five days' worth of food
at most if you eat normally.
Use your head and eat.
Good thing that we're both cooks.
Wait a second! Is that your share?!
It's huge!
Of course! I'm an adult.
My stomach is larger than yours.
You should be grateful
that I'm even sharing food with you.
Don't expect any pity from me.
You damn geezer!
You watch the other side of the sea.
As soon as you see a ship, let me know.
Until then, we won't be in contact at all.
It'll be fine. I have
five days' worth of food.
If I have five days,
a ship or two'll definitely pass by.
But just in case,
I'll divide them up for 20 days for now.
If I have 20 days,
a ship'll pass by for sure.
It'll be all right.
I'll definitely survive. It's easy!
DAY 5
DAY 10
This is the last piece of
bread... It's gotten moldy...
DAY 25
Ahh... How wasteful...
leaving this much food...
You guys stop eating the
customers' leftovers.
I ditched food that looked rotten earlier.
We have plenty of food.
--Why don't you have some, too, huh?
--I don't want it!
My last piece of bread...
DAY 70
I wonder... if that damn
geezer already died...
He's still alive...
And there's still that much food, too...
What did you come here for, little brat?
I came to steal your food.
If you think you can kill me, go ahead.
I'll die if I don't eat anyway.
To think you to have this
much food all to yourself...
What?
Didn't I tell you that
we wouldn't be in contact until we saw a ship?
Why...?
This is all treasure...
It's odd that
we can't eat when we have money.
What is this?!
What's the meaning of this?!
Where's your food?
You haven't eaten anything this whole time?
Hey! Say something!
What happened to your leg?
That time...
So it wasn't a dream...
In order to save me, you...
What about the food?
Did you give me all the food you had?
That's right.
Without that leg,
you won't be able to be a pirate anymore!
I guess...
Why...? I didn't ask for your help!
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
Why...? Why did you?!
Because you...
you had the same dream as me.
The All Blue...
Whoa!! Damn geezer, is
this the sea restaurant?
We're gonna be busy!
We'll be fine 'cause I'm here!
Hey, little brat!
You're too slow, little brat!
I'm not, you damn geezer!
Fooling around with a woman again,
little brat?!
Little brat!
Little brat!!
Sanji!
Don't catch cold.
Owner Zeff!!
Thank you for all the damn things you've done for me
over all these years!!
I'll never forget your kindness...
for the rest of my life!!
Let's have a peaceful wedding tomorrow.
We'll have lunch with Big
Mom and Pudding today.
Get yourself ready to visit their castle.
Okay, Sanji?
Damn Straw Hat... Where did he go?
Search for him.
10 minutes is long...
I can't even use Haki.
Oh, damn...
I gotta go see Sanji!
Using up all of his Haki,
Luffy is paralyzed and
Cracker's numerous blades come for him!
Meanwhile, deep under the Germa Kingdom,
Sanji sees a forbidden experiment -
the source of their immense military strength!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Angry Sanji! The Secret of Germa 66!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!