kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Sanji was having a meal with
his father and the others
at the castle in the Germa
Kingdom, his home country,
but he got into an argument
with his arrogant brothers.
However, he was forced to back down
because his foster parent Zeff was taken hostage.
Well, only in the worst-case scenario
where you become uncontrollable,
I'll use it as a threat like
"We'll chop this guy's head off."
Let's have a peaceful wedding tomorrow.
Meanwhile, Luffy was fighting a
fierce battle against Sweet General
Cracker in the Seducing Woods.
What the?!
Oh, no!
But as time ran out for Gear Four Bounce-man,
he collapsed in the woods.
I gotta go see Sanji!
"An Angry Sanji!
The Secret of Germa 66!"
Cracker-sama,
I didn't wanna do such a thing-ju!
She ordered me and I had no choice...
Good job, Kingbaum!
Nami!
Luffy! Are you okay?
Damn you! Don't think you can survive
after challenging Cracker-sama!
Oh? How could you say that?
You really think you're in
a position to mouth off?
Stop it-ju! Damn...
Nami...
Bounce-man's time is up.
What?
I can't use Haki for 10 minutes...
I need to rest.
Okay. Let me take care of you.
Alright, guys!
Carry Luffy into Kingbaum's mouth!
What?!
You tell them to do it, too!
I thought you were the master of this forest!
Y-You...
What?
I've got no choice-ju!
Homies, do as she says!
What?!
Be careful with him!
You saved me, Nami...
Get some rest.
He's coming!
Let's run! Now!
This is so humiliating-ju!
That way, huh?
Don't get caught, guys!
Dammit!
BRULEE'S MIRRO-WORLD
That little brat...
I'll make her pay!
Once my wound is healed, I'll cut her up!
Before that, let's take care of
the raccoon and the rabbit first.
Oh, there he is, Chobro!
What? Really?!
Isn't that Sanji?
Which one?
It definitely is Sanji!
Hey, Sanji!
Sanji!
No, that's not Sanji!
Run! If they find us, we're in trouble!
Damn...
Where is Sanji?
We have to find him
before it's too late...
CHOBRO, SOMETHING BIZARRE CAME!!
Mama's in a good mood-nasu.
No wonder.
Tomorrow is the tea party and today,
the whole Vinsmoke Family will come visit.
You're right-nasu.
I hope Pudding-sama will be happy-nasu.
Yeah, I'm jealous of the groom!
Sanji-sama is probably getting ready
at the Germa Kingdom's castle by now.
I bet so-nasu.
--Hear that?
--Uh-huh.
--Sanji's in Germa's castle now!
--Uh-huh!
Let's hurry!
We must find a mirror to the castle!
I got it, Chobro!
There we go.
What am I thinking?!
What are you doing over there?
You cooking wench.
Um...
Is somebody there?
Somebody, help! Call a doctor!
Hey, stay with me!
Damn! They did this behind my back!
What did she do to deserve this?!
They knocked a woman unconscious...
I've never met such scum!
It's your fault, Sanji.
Yonji!
You gave a woman of low birth
a taste of self-confidence.
What do you mean by that, you asshole?!
Do you want to see Niji?
Of course, he's the one who did it.
Follow me. I'll take you to him.
You're gonna be fine. Don't worry.
What's wrong? Are you coming?
Yeah, I'm more than happy to!
Where is he?!
Well, you'll see.
This is...
You were curious, weren't you?
Because we weren't allowed to
go in here when we were kids.
54 Type-MBs. 30 Type-MSTs.
And 21 Type-MHs need to be restocked.
Got it.
What are they?!
Are you curious what they are?
Germa 66 is feared around the world.
And these are its soldiers!
Go faster! He's gonna catch up to us!
I'm going the fastest I can-ju!
I can't go any faster-ju!
It hasn't been 10 minutes yet...
You guys right there!
--Y-Yes?
--Can we help you?
Bring him down!
That's impossible!
Impossible or not, buy some time!
For Luffy's recovery!
Now, go!
She's the worst!!
Cracker-sama, forgive us!
It's impossible as I thought!
Even if you use us, we're no match for him-ju!
Just give up already-ju!
No!
It's my turn to help Luffy.
Keep running!
If we get caught,
you guys will get punished too!
You're terrible-ju!
When it comes to the crunch, I'll...
What's the matter?
Who is that?
Cracker-sama!!
Cracker?! Is that him?!
What's wrong, Kingbaum?
Why are you taking Straw Hat's side?
There is a good reason for it...
No excuse.
I'm gonna kill you all!
What's with him?
Woman, I'm Sweet General Cracker.
The soldiers of Germa 66?!
Why are they in water?
That's culture fluid.
They all have the same face...
Are they alive?
Sanji, humans are...
...replicable!
Germa has been a kingdom of science
for generations.
He might not look it but our father was
once renowned as a skilled scientist.
Before we were born,
he was part of a lawless
foreign research team
and together with the famous Dr. Vegapunk,
he was working on weaponry.
Him with Vegapunk?!
Yes, in their younger days.
What Vegapunk accomplished at that time was
the discovery of the Bloodline
Elements within living things!
It was just one step away from
usurping God's place
because it was akin
to discovering the blueprints of life.
The World Government saw it as dangerous
and arrested Vegapunk.
The research team was disbanded...
By which I mean it was bought up by the Government.
However, our father escaped
the Government's reach
and continued his research here in Germa.
His research on duplicating
and modifying life.
And then,
this underground facility has been built!
They're all duplicates of
just a few talented soldiers!
They're Clone Soldiers!
Clone?!
Of course, they're not aware of that.
You see, Sanji?
Many countries are afraid of our army
but at the same time, they wish to have it.
It can't be helped
because they're strong and obedient.
They're programmed not to fear death
and not to turn on their masters.
When they die, we can just restock.
It takes five years to make
a 20-year old soldier.
This is the depot where we
keep a stock of the soldiers.
Look. It only takes five
years to create them,
but they look like they've been around
for two decades.
Stop it! That's enough!
This makes me sick!
Sanji.
When I heard that you became a pirate,
I thought "That failure might've
grown up to be a better man."
But you haven't changed and I'm disappointed.
Niji!
You asshole...
How could you do that to...
...Cosette-chan!!
Sanji carried the hope of his
father Judge and was expected
to rule Germa when he was a little prince!
He was created by an immoral and
mad scientific experiment and the
hellish life he lived as
a child is now revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Past that He Let Go of! Vinsmoke Sanji!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!