I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
In the Seducing Woods,
Luffy and Nami have been
fighting a deadly battle
against Sweet General Cracker.
Meanwhile, Sanji recalls
his painful past at home,
the Germa Kingdom, which has been
concealed deep in his heart.
You are... a failure.
Wait! I don't wanna stay here!
Let me out!
"To the East Blue!
Sanji's Resolute Departure!"
What a pain! Bring it on all at once!
They're developing very fast!
Your children are real superhumans!
Easy win!
Kids!
Well done!
--Father!
--Father-sama!
I'm proud of you all!
My dearest children!
SIXTH MONTHS INTO SANJI'S IMPRISONMENT
Where do they take that luxurious food
every mealtime?
I don't know. We don't have any guests.
Don't be nosy! It's King-sama's order!
We'll just cook it as we're told!
Sanji!
Royalty mustn't serve anyone!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Your mother is dead!
Stop following the legacy of the deceased!
Ouch!
Oh, boy!
--Ow, ow, ow!
--Are you alright, Sanji-sama?!
King-sama told us not to
allow you into the kitchen.
Please!
Let me... stay!
It's done!
--Where are you going by yourself?
--To see my mother.
The medical ward is at the far end
and the weather is...
--I can make it.
--But...
Stop following me.
Don't tell my father.
Get in your houses!
What?! This is not your food!
S-Stop!
S-Sanji-sama!
Are you here by yourself?!
I appreciate what you did...
But we can't
let Queen-sama have stomach trouble...
But maybe it tastes good...
What?!
Sanji!
Did you come to see me in this rain?
Your father will be mad if he finds out.
--Uh-huh.
--Your Majesty.
This is from Sanji-sama.
Did you make this for me?
Mm... Mm-hm.
Epony!
Y-Yes, Your Majesty!
Don't be presumptuous!
Bring what Sanji really made for me!
Well, yes.
But it was damaged on his way here
so I threw it into a trash can.
--Bring it to me!
--Yes, ma'am!
Wow, nice!
Omelet rolls and fish and a banana?
Sorry, Mom! I messed it up!
I tripped over and dropped it on my way here.
It's been crushed and it
got wet in the rain...
Let's try.
It's good!
What?!
--Really?!
--Yes!
Mom!
Sanji, will you cook for me again?
Uh-huh!
Mom!!
Sanji, will you cook for me again?
You want cookbooks and utensils?
"The All... Blue"?
"Where fish from all four seas live..."
"A legendary sea"!
Look! I told you that it was Sanji!
You're right! That is him!
So he's alive.
Why did Father tell such a lie?
Because he wants him to be dead.
In that case, if he really dies,
will it make Father happy?
Stop it!
You're a failure who deserves
to die, right, Sanji?!
Ow...
Don't think I'm on your side.
I don't wanna get involved.
Those three are Father's ideal fighters.
They don't have emotions
so they don't feel sorry or sad.
My body was successfully modified
but that's the difference between me and them.
Bye.
Th-Thank you, Reiju...
Oh, yeah. We'll climb up the Red Line soon.
Seems like we'll fight some wars
in the East Blue.
War?
Get underway towards the East Blue!
The estimated travel time is
three weeks.
We crossed the Red Line
and entered the East Blue.
We're on course towards Kojia,
our target country.
Hey!
We're going to go destroy some country soon!
I wish they'd let us fight too.
You never learn...
Reiju, I...
I want to be a cook!
Fire!
--It's Germa 66.
--What?! Do they truly exist?!
What's going on?!
Judge-sama, our target country
Kojia has noticed us!
Subdue them!
What did I say? Don't tell me that!
If I can... run away...
...here in the East Blue...
I'll never...
...have to see...
...Dad's face again, right?
Step back!
You have only one chance!
Don't ruin it!
Go ashore!
It's just begun!
The key to your iron mask is in Father-sama's room!
Go get it!
What?!
I'm gonna go see what it's like outside!
Okay?!
Uh-huh!
When you get into his room,
look for a skull symbol on the wall!
You'll find a secret door there!
I got it!
What are you doing over there?
Sanji... Why are you here?!
Father-sama!
I'm gonna get out of this kingdom!
Don't get in my way!
You got quite a sharp tongue
while you were imprisoned.
There is no easy sea where a normal kid like you
can survive on your own!
You'll die!
So what?! You can't stop me!
That's a relief!
I guess I'm human after all.
Even though you're useless,
I couldn't kill my own son.
But you'll go away voluntarily?
I'm not gonna stop you.
You can take the key to the iron mask.
But can I ask just one last
favor as your father, Sanji?
Don't ever admit that I'm your father...
...in front of other people!
It's a shame that I don't
want anyone to know!
You realize that, don't you?
What about the cruise ship at the port?!
It has nothing to do with us!
It's just an unlucky ship! Leave it alone!
Get onboard that ship!
Sanji! You're a boy! Stop crying already!
Listen! Don't ever come back here!
Uh-huh!
The sea is broad! You'll...
You'll definitely meet kind people someday!!
Run!!
Don't look back!!
Run! Sanji!!
Cornered by the Biscuit Warriors
multiplying around him without limit,
Luffy doggedly pursues a slim chance to win!
It's eat or die!
Luffy eats and eats like never before
and challenges the limits of his stomach!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Battle of Limits! Luffy and the Infinite Biscuits!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!