kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated
the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Nami fought Sweet General Cracker
to protect the exhausted Luffy,
but got cornered by Cracker's fierce attack.
However, that's when...
Don't touch...
...my friend!
Meanwhile, Sanji was beaten by
Ichiji and the rest of his brothers
and was branded a failure.
"A Battle of Limits!
Luffy and the Infinite Biscuits!"
Sanji-sama!
Oh, no. Is he conscious?
Get out of my way.
Oh, Reiju-sama, we'll treat him right away.
I said "Get out of my way"!
I'm sorry!
Boy...
Are you going to see your fiancée
with that face?
If you'd given up on the owner of the restaurant
that you were working at,
you could've avoided this.
Why did you come back?
I thought this was the place
that you didn't even want to remember.
Sanji.
THE SEDUCING WOODS
You damn brat.
But I guess you didn't pick a fight
with Mama for nothing.
Luffy...
Nami!
Get in there!
Yeah, okay!
Dammit...
I'm hungry...
Go, Biscuit Warriors!
Straw Hat... I'm gonna take my time to torture you
and then kill you.
You too, traitor, and your friends!
Is it...
It's hard!
You can't eat my biscuits!
They're quite hard
so that they can block your attack!
They're not common biscuits!
Oh yeah! They're biscuits!
Weather Egg!
Rain Spark!
Biscuit Warriors, kill him!
Its sword crumbled?!
Luffy!
They're no longer the warriors that they were!
They got softened by the rain!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
They sure are softened!
It's not over!
Yummy! Nice and crunchy!
Yes!
He ate Cracker-sama's Biscuit Warriors-ju!
What?!
How could you eat them?!
Biscuits are food!
That's right, Luffy!
Once you eat them, they can't turn back!
Eat as much as you can!
What a crafty woman-ju!
How dare he...
What's with that kid?!
Luffy, pull back for a while!
No! I'm gonna eat them all!
There's a way to make them more delicious!
What?!
Let's go, guys!
Okay!
What?! Don't let them get away!
I'll eat as many as I need to!
Wait for me, Sanji!
BRULEE'S MIRRO-WORLD
Meanwhile, in Brulee's Mirro-world...
It's strange...
I put two shackles on each of them
but why aren't they here?
This isn't it, either.
We still can't find Sanji, Chobro.
Well, we'll find him!
We gotta find a mirror in Germa's castle
at any cost!
Okay!
I found you!
She's back!
You can't escape!
I can't run anymore, Chobro!
Stop running around in the mirror!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Gavel!
...Rocket!
And...
...Munch-Munch!
You little...!
You still gonna eat?!
He ate them all.
The apple-juice-flavored
biscuits from before were good
but the melon-flavored ones were good too.
The change of flavor worked!
You can eat forever like this, right?
How much more can his stomach take?
But I guess I ate too much.
That's obvious!
People can't eat that much!
I bet your stomach can't take it anymore!
All right, I'm gonna make
more of them for you!
You're tired too.
Go, Biscuit Warriors!
Rain Spark!
This time, it's the original flavor!
Alright, Luffy! Eat as much as you want!
Oh, okay!
She's doing it again!
I'll eat and eat and eat!
Then, we'll take Sanji back!
GERMA 66
Judge-sama, it's time.
The preparations are complete.
Okay, tell my children!
We're going to leave for
the Whole Cake Chateau!
Ready? It's gonna hurt.
Just do it.
It tingles a little...
Don't touch it.
How is it?
The swelling has gone down.
Ouch!
It's a facial mask that
only works for swelling.
It suppresses the normal physical reaction
so it only makes bruises worse.
But it's better than your fiancée
seeing your swollen face.
The members of the Charlotte Family won't take
their spouse's last name.
So if they accept you as a part of their family
you can live a happy life.
Damn you...
You came back voluntarily.
Don't expect me to do anything.
There's no second chance.
Anyway,
where did you get your chivalry from?
Woman! Woman! Woman! Woman!
Woman!!
Shut up! We don't need a female chef!
Cut it out!
I teach people things through kicking.
I can't do that with a woman!
Why?! If she doesn't learn,
you can kick her!
You idiot!
Ouch!
Men mustn't kick women!
That's common sense from back when
dinosaurs were still around!
Listen, little brat!
You can make as many mistakes
as you need as a human!
But if you betray the honor of manhood,
I'll cut off your manhood at its root
and chop off my own head as well!
What?! Why do you have
to do that to yourself?!
That's how a parent pays the price.
You fool...
Don't become someone that I hate.
Now, get back to work.
That's a tradition from the dinosaur age.
I-I'm stuffed now.
Screw you!
I'm sick and tired of fighting you!
You fight, run away,
come back and eat!
Is he really human?!
Cracker-sama is something
but so is Straw Hat's appetite!
Cracker-sama...
Hey, can he really make
an infinite number of biscuits?
Yes, he can-ju.
But he'll run out of energy.
No, you will!
Eat until you burst!
Then you'll finally give up on your friend.
I'm not gonna give up!
I'll eat and eat and go see Sanji!
I'll bring out more Biscuit
Warriors for you then.
Eat them and pop, Straw Hat!
And...
...I'll tell Mama that you guys helped them,
Kingbaum!
What?! But you've already
cut off the top of my head!
That's not fair-ju, Cracker-sama!
We are just in awe of
Mama's Vivre Card that this girl has-ju!
So we are just obeying Mama!
Yes, yes! That's right!
Save your excuse until you see Mama!
You got in my way for sure!
If it weren't for that woman's rain and strategy,
my hard Biscuit Warriors...
...wouldn't have turned into
delicious crunchy snacks!
Shut up! This is a pirate battle!
Just because your weakness has been revealed,
don't take it out on our soldiers!
O-Our?!
Are we her soldiers now?
Got a problem?
I'm sorry!
Let's put an end to this, Biscuit Warriors!
This is it!
All I can do is eat them.
They'll turn back even if I break them.
But... Urp...
to be honest, I can't eat anymore.
Make sure to protect me, Homies!
G-Got it!
Hey, Nami, can we try something
other than eating them first?
While I go break them and come back...
Weather Egg!
I don't know who you are to the Emperor!
But Luffy will become
the King of the Pirates!
So there's no limit to his appetite!
What?! Nami, I've been
eating all this time so...
I don't know why, but is
your stomach boundless?!
No...
Rain Spark!
The warriors will get softened again!
Oh, no!
No... I can't...
Wait for me, Sanji!
Dammit!
Look at how he eats!
Luffy eats and the biscuits multiply!
Luffy is on the brink of blowing
up and he can't even move
but when Cracker's fatal blade closes in on him,
Gear Four's new power kicks in!
The deadly battle for taking back Sanji finally
comes to an end!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Power of Satiety! A New
Gear Four Form - Tank Man!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!