What's the matter?
I thought I taught you how to use a sword.
I refuse!
My hands...
...are for cooking only.
Hey, what are these?
You said your hands are important to you.
That's great.
Do you know the shackle collars
that the slaves to the Celestial Dragons wear?
If they try to escape from their masters,
they'll explode along with their heads.
Those work the same way.
So you were working at his restaurant
until two years ago.
Well, only in the worst-case scenario
where you become uncontrollable,
I'll use it as a threat like,
"We'll chop this guy's head off."
Why?!
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
Why...? Why did you?!
Because you...
you had the same dream as me.
Whoa!! Damn geezer, is
this the sea restaurant?
We're gonna be busy!
We'll be fine 'cause I'm here!
Hey, little brat!
You're too slow, little brat!
Fooling around with a woman again,
little brat?!
Little brat!
Little brat!!
Hey, Sanji!
Don't catch cold.
Owner Zeff!!
Thank you for all the damn things you've
done for me over all these years!!
A HEARTBREAKING DUEL!
LUFFY VS SANJI! - PART 2
This is how it should be. This is good.
Hey, Sanji!
Your Majesty, something
is charging towards us.
It's been a while!
What?! That idiot reached this far
into Big Mom's territory?!
What is the big tree behind him?!
It's running!
Hey!
Sanji-kun!
I'm glad that we made it in time!
I thought I'd never see you again!
Why are they... here?
Is that Straw Hat Luffy?
Hey! We're here to pick you up!
Sanji!
Stop it, you fool!
The Calicoach will turn over!
Let's go, Sanji!
You said you'd be back in the note
but I didn't wanna wait.
Banquet!
I was gonna come by myself but...
You said your hands are important to you.
If you try to get off of this island,
your hands will be blown off!
If someone declines Mama's invitation...
...So Zoro and the others must've gotten
to the Land of Wano...
We'll chop this guy's head off.
...That's why Nami, Chopper, Brook and I came
to pick you up. And...
You are a sacrifice, Sanji.
I haven't changed...
But if you betray the honor of manhood,
I'll chop off my own head as well!
Sanji, I'm hungry!
I don't think of you as my son even one bit!
That's how a parent pays the price.
--It's a shame that I don't want anyone to know!
--Sanji!
Hey, Sanji!
Don't catch cold.
...And I had no choice so...
Hey! What are you doing, Sanji-kun?!
Get packing, you low-class pirates!
My name is Vinsmoke Sanji.
I'm a prince
of the Germa Kingdom!
I'm sorry for keeping it a secret.
I thought that it'd make you miserable.
The difference between our standings
couldn't be clearer.
If I stay here, I can spend money
and use soldiers and servants as I like.
Going back to that crappy ship
with you and your friends...
...or staying here,
marrying Big Mom's beautiful daughter.
It's pretty obvious which is a happier life.
Don't take the note seriously.
I won't go back with you!
I can't believe you've come all the way here.
Thanks for your trouble.
Get out of here... I forgot your name.
Screw it! What are you talking about?!
I'm not convinced!
Okay, I'll help you drive them off.
Sit back!
I'll...
...send them away!
What do you mean by sending us away, Sanji?
Get packing.
There is no other meaning.
I don't know what made you come,
but I appreciate
that you took the trouble.
Having said that, if you really think about me,
you should've done the opposite.
Rather than being with you guys
who are poor and weak,
it'd be better to be part of
the rich and powerful Big Mom Pirates.
I'll be happier.
I'm not so sure about you becoming the King of the Pirates
to be honest.
It's only human nature
to jump on the bandwagon.
Stop joking, Sanji-kun!
What are you talking about?!
Then, all this time,
you've been fooling me.
Yeah, that's right.
I've actually been looking down on you.
What is that glow? A flame?!
This ought to be fun to watch.
I bet you didn't see it coming
so it's hard to accept.
I'll prove it to you. Get ready.
Diable Jambe...
No, Sanji-kun!
Joue Shot!
Luffy! You're bleeding!
Sanji-kun, did you really...
Get ready to fight.
Use your Haki or you're gonna die.
I just wanna talk to you.
Why do I need Haki?
I'm not gonna...
...fight you!
Then...
...go away!
I'm not gonna do that either!
You've always...
...been selfish!
Hey you, cook!
Join my group!
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
Please stop, Sanji-kun!
We just came to pick you up!
Luffy has...
...fought against their top officer all night
to get this far!
So his body is...
Cut it out, Nami!
Stay out of this!
This is...
...a duel!
You call this a duel?!
Sanji-kun!
Get out of my sight now!
Luffy!
Go away!
Get the hell out of my sight!!
Stop... Please stop, Sanji-kun!
Get out of my face...
...now!!
I refuse!
Get out of my sight now!
Luffy!
No matter what I do, you're not gonna leave,
are you, you low-class pirate?
If you're not gonna go
away, I have no option.
I'm not gonna go easy on you anymore.
Don't regret this after you die.
Sanji-kun!
Here we go!
Sanji-kun... Please stop...
That's enough! Stop, Sanji-kun!
We'll leave!!
I won't!
You're a good cook,
so let's be pirates together!
Concasser!
Luffy! Luffy!
How strong...
After all, he's a Vinsmoke.
Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy! Hey! Stay with me!
Luffy! Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy!!
Hey, Sanji!
Goodbye!
Sorry -
we should never have done this!
Oh! A bitchy girl! How hot!
The superfluous ties have
finally been severed.
Thanks for waiting.
--Let's go.
--Yes, sir.
Luffy!
Wait!
Sanji!!
"Low-class pirate"?!
I know you were just saying
things that you didn't want to!
Stop lying!
Did you think
that you could send me away that easily?!
Screw that!
No matter how many times you kick me,
you're the one...
...that gets hurt!!
Luffy! Why?!
Whatever the reason is, he can't do this...
Shut up!
Should we stop, Sanji?
Keep going.
Say...
do you know the All Blue?
It's a miracle sea!
In that sea...
Our journey...
...isn't over yet!
I'll be here waiting!
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
...starving to death!
You're the cook of my ship!
He was making food for rats again!
I won't eat anything
other than what you cook!
Even if I get hungry or
spears rain down on me,
I'll stay right here and wait for you!
Be sure to come back, Sanji!
Without you, I...
I can't become the King of the Pirates!!
Hey you, cook! Join my group!
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
I'm hoping to go someday...
to the Grand Line.
Then let's go now.
It's not the right time yet.
Say... do you know the All Blue?
--No...
--Oh, you don't?!
It's a miracle sea!
In that sea...
Luffy stands where he told Sanji
he'd wait without moving an inch
while black shadows that seem to cover the
whole land are coming for him with a storm!
Big Mom's vengeful battalion rumbles
the earth rushing at Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Storm of Revenge! An Enraged
Army Comes to Attack!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!