My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy finally found Sanji
headed for the Whole Cake Chateau.
But Sanji rejected his
friends' offer to regroup.
They got into a duel but Luffy
refused to fight against Sanji...
...taking the full onslaught of his attacks.
Wait!
Sanji!!
I'll be here waiting!
I won't eat anything
other than what you cook!
Be sure to come back, Sanji!
Without you, I...
I can't become the King of the Pirates!!
"A Storm of Revenge!
An Enraged Army Comes to Attack!"
What did you say?!
Cracker...
...has been beaten?!
Straw Hat...
Luffy.
Are you really gonna wait here?!
We're right in the middle of enemy territory.
I'll wait!
Pound said the people
who took down a Sweet General...
...ended up being annihilated
in the blink of an eye
by Big Mom's vengeful army
that came along with a storm.
So the enemy will come...
But Sanji-kun...
Sanji will come!
So I'll wait here!
Crap! My head has been completely trimmed...
What's going on?!
It was clear but suddenly,
dark clouds are gathering...
What's wrong, Kingbaum?!
That mountain is the Whole Cake Chateau
where Mama lives!
Mama is angry-ju!
Big Mom is?!
But...
No...
No way...
You've got to be kidding!
Is this the power of one person?!
Linlin is always accompanied
by weather elements.
Nothing can stop her when she gets mad.
Prometheus-sama and Zeus-sama
are running wild!
Mama is... outraged!
What the...
The weather's suddenly getting worse.
Clear the way!
The enraged army will pass by!
An army to avenge Cracker-sama
has been organized!
Move! Get out of the way!
Enraged army?
Look how many there are!
Seems like they're gonna go
after Straw Hat to kill him.
If I remember right,
he said he'd be there waiting for you.
This is it for him!
I can't believe it!
That's Bobbin the Disposer!
Amande the Mad Moiselle!
Oh! That's Montd'Or the Scribe!
I wonder how much
the total of their bounties is?!
I'll be here waiting!
Well, I guess that captain
won't be stupid enough
to not run away after seeing that battalion.
It started raining.
No... this is... syrup.
Luffy?
I'm not gonna let even syrup in my mouth!
I won't eat anything other than
what Sanji cooks!
Welcome to the Whole Cake Chateau!
Please come in.
Mama is expecting you-bon.
Rain! Rain! Rain! Rain!
Those soldiers look weird.
They have the shapes of chess pieces.
Is it Big Mom's power?
It doesn't matter.
They're all gonna become our allies anyway.
What's appealing isn't just their number.
You saw the army that went
after Straw Hat, right?
There were so many chimerical beasts.
This'll work out better for us
than merely reinforcing our troops.
At last!
Our dream will finally come true.
Our dream!
Oh, there's Mama! Mama!
--Mama!
Are you all being good?
Mama, mama!
What is it, Anana?
The head chef won't let me use a knife.
I wanna cut my stuffed animal.
Oh, no!
Dolce, Dragee,
go and borrow one for her.
No, Mama! Once Anana has a knife,
she'll pop our balloons!
Yeah! She's bad!
I'm gonna kill her someday!
We shouldn't say those things, right, Mama?
Everyone has 100 to 200 people
who they want to kill.
Be nice to each other, my children.
We'll have Big Sis Pudding's
wedding tomorrow!
Are you excited?
You get to eat a delicious wedding cake.
Yay! Yay!
Now let's meet!
The groom's family!
Door!
It's good to have you here, Germa 66.
Sorry to be late.
Emperor Big Mom!
We've had a little problem
but it should be okay now.
So you're Black-Leg Sanji.
You'll become my daughter Pudding's husband.
Don't be shy!
Oh, Pudding! There you are.
Sorry for being late.
Anyway, I've heard a lot about him.
Your son's a cook, huh?
He's perfect for Pudding.
Well, it doesn't matter even if he's not.
It's a political marriage.
As long as you and I share mutual interests,
that's all it matters, Judge!
Yeah but it'd be nice
if our children are happy.
Let's have a nice wedding tomorrow!
Yes, let's.
--Tea
--Green tea
What would you like to have?
I'll have tea.
Tea! Tea! Tea! Tea!
Tea!
--Eat us! Eat us!
--Start with me!
--You can have me too!
You need lots of honey, young man!
It's very...
Sweet!
La la lunch! La la lunch!
--Sausage!
--Cabbage!
--Ham!
--Pancake!
Delicious!
Could you be quiet?
What?!
Don't say such a thing!
Let's have a delicious lunch!
La la lunch! La la lunch!
It's so noisy!
How do I taste? Am I good?
La la lunch! La la lunch!
S... Sanji-san...
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU IN PRIVATE LATER
It's getting rough.
Nami!
What's the matter?
Go hide somewhere!
What?
They're coming!
Oh, no-ju...
Oh, no-ju!!
How many... are there?!
Luffy, you gotta get away too!
I'm not gonna go anywhere!
Luffy...
Luffy! Please! Hide yourself at least!
It's okay to get away from
here just for a while!
No!
Sanji might come while I'm gone!
You guys, back up a little!
Don't do it, Luffy! It's impossible!
Don't you know whose territory we're in?!
That's a big army... You can't beat it!
We found Straw Hat Luffy!
I promised him...
...that I'd be here waiting!
No matter how many enemies Luffy beats,
he sees no end to the deadly
struggle against the enraged army.
Sanji will be back!
Contrary to Luffy's expectation, however,
Sanji is beyond the point
of no return and pressed
to make the biggest decision of his life!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The End of the Adventure!
Sanji's Resolute Proposal!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!