kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Big Mom became furious after learning
Cracker, one of the Sweet 3 Generals,
got taken down by Luffy.
To avenge him,
She deployed an enraged army on Luffy.
Luffy didn't retreat from the spot
where he decided to wait for Sanji
and he faced the enraged army
gathering all his strength.
Bring it on!
Meanwhile, Sanji was with Pudding...
You're my... salvation.
Sanji-san...
If I'm good enough for you...
Let's get married tomorrow.
Luffy keeps fighting
without knowing Sanji's decision.
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Whip!
...Giant Axe!
"I'll Wait Here!
Luffy vs. the Enraged Army!"
IN THE OUTSKIRTS OF SWEET CITY
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Gatling!
Hawk Rifle!
You bastard!
I'm not gonna go anywhere!!
He's already reached his limit! Attack!
Luffy!
Thunderbolt...
...Tempo!
I can't create big thunderclouds like those.
But I can use Big Mom's thunderclouds!
There's more to come!
Thanks for all the damage.
What is this?!
Get down here!
I wasn't paying attention.
I didn't expect that a girl like you could
make such a big lightning strike.
Famous Sword...
...Shirauo.
It's not what you think-ju!
We didn't mean to change sides!
Amande-sama!
Slow Ballad.
Ouch...!
I-If you're going to kill
me, d-do it quickly!
It's pointless killing someone quickly.
I cut at the most painful
and tormenting speed.
I can't believe it, Straw Hat.
He doesn't seem like
he was fighting Big Bro Cracker all night!
The Chess Peacekeepers aren't that weak!
How could he tear them to pieces like trash!
Now, bring it on!
Luffy!
I'm gonna take care of you!
Cream Monster!
Ouch!
MIRRO-WORLD
How interesting, reindeer!
You became muscular.
But...
--Let's do it, Carrot!
--Uh-huh!
Th-This reindeer's strong!
I'm gonna run over and kill you!
What?!
The rabbit can fight too! Be careful!
Watch out, Carrot!
Huh?! Chobro!
What? What?!
What's going on?!
Now, what should I do with them?
Gum-Gum...
Oh no.
That's not gonna happen, Straw Hat!
Elephant Gun!
What?
What is this place?
You're in...
...the World of Books!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
Luffy, what is he doing?
Ow, ow, ow...
What are these?!
Get off of me!
Luffy!
I-It's cold!
What's going on?
Cream Monster!
Luffy!
Stop it!
Stop!
Luffy! Get down!
Nami!
Watch out!
Cream...
...Punch!
Luffy!
No...
I'll give you one more-fa!
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
You want some?
No.
I'm here to ask you a favor.
What is it? I'm listening.
I'm going to marry Pudding-chan.
In return,
I want you to let my friends go!
I'm begging you.
Okay.
What? R-Really?!
Yes, really.
When it comes to reasonable deals,
I can be reasonable myself!
I'll let all members of the Straw Hats
who are your friends for now
leave this island alive!
I promise.
If you drop the idea of running away
and marry without resistance,
I'll turn a blind eye to everything!
I appreciate it!
I'll make Pudding-chan happy at any cost!
Oh, you're so in love with my daughter!
I'm glad!
Listen.
The things that the Straw Hats have done to me
are normally inexcusable.
They destroyed the maze-like forest
and took down one of our Sweet Generals.
On top of that, at the Fish-Man Island,
not only did they eat my candies...
...but they also picked a fight with me.
But now, the top priority is
you and Pudding's marriage.
If things go well,
about this time tomorrow,
I'll gain Germa's military strength
and we'll all have a delicious wedding cake!
If you don't run away,
everything will turn out for the best, Sanji.
Yeah!
Luffy...
We finally got him.
He gave us a lot of trouble.
We avenged our big brother!
Kingbaum...
Is that...!
A Vivre Card.
I was wondering why the Chess Peacekeepers,
who are Homies, couldn't fight like usual
and how you guys could
make it out of the forest.
Now I understand.
Why did you have Mama's Vivre Card?
It says "Lola."
What?!
Lola?! Did you steal it from her?!
Oh, man! That runaway girl got killed?!
--Lola!
--What were her last words?!
It's not like that!
She's my friend! She gave it to me!
I doubt it.
Tell Mama that yourself.
Unfortunately,
we were ordered to catch you guys alive. Let's go.
Oh, look at that.
Most of the Chess Peacekeepers
have been beaten.
I'll...
Luffy!
You bastard...
Wait...
Please stop!
I'll... wait... here...
For Sanji...
Luffy!!
Luffy and Nami have been
captured in an inescapable cell
in a book kept deep inside
the Emperor's chateau!
Meanwhile, Brook and Pedro are trying
to sneak past
Sweet General Smoothie and heavy security
in order to perform an
unprecedented safecracking!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Invading the Chateau!
Reach the Road Ponegliff!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!