kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
To take back Sanji who
was being pressed into a
marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated
the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy eliminated Sweet General Cracker
in the Seducing Woods
and finally saw Sanji again,
but Sanji rejected his
friends' offer to regroup.
Be sure to come back, Sanji!
Without you, I...
I can't become the King of the Pirates!!
Luffy stayed behind to wait for Sanji
and clashed with the enraged army
that was organized to avenge Cracker.
Meanwhile, in a secret meeting with Pudding,
Sanji revealed what was on his mind.
I just wanna go away without hurting anyone.
My adventure ends here.
I won't let your marriage with me be hell!
He learned Pudding's feelings
and made a decision.
If I'm good enough for you...
Let's get married tomorrow.
Then Luffy finally got knocked out
in the battle against the enraged army.
"Invading the Chateau!
Reach the Road Ponegliff!"
A GUEST ROOM WHERE SANJI STAYS
Goodbye!
Sorry - we should never have done this!
I'll be here waiting!
Everyone...
Stay safe.
Luffy.
Nami!
I'm glad that you came to.
I was worried
because you've been passed out all this time.
What?
Oh yeah, I remember! Nami!
I'm gonna free you now!
How is this possible?!
This won't come off no matter how much I pull!
That's useless, Straw Hat.
Did you do this?!
Of course! Who else could
do something like this?!
PRISON LIBRARY IN THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
Let us out!
Huh? Why would I wanna do that?!
You bastard! I shouldn't be here!
I gotta get back to that spot
before Sanji comes!
Luffy...
Well, good luck with that.
But you'll never be able to get out of here. Ever!
I'll catch you alive soon.
Let's eat them! Let's eat them!
What should we do, Chobro?
Carrot, lend me your ear.
My ear?
Listen, we're going to...
Okay, okay, got it! That's my Chobro!
What are you whispering about?!
Guys! Attack them already!
Go!
Wh-What the...
What are you guys doing?!
Those are just reflections!
TREASURE REPOSITORY
Security is very tight as I thought!
Oh, Pedro-san, there they are!
The two Ponegliffs and...
...the Road Ponegliff!
It is said that...
...there are about 30 Ponegliffs,
inscribed stone blocks...
TREASURE REPOSITORY IN THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
...that have never broken for
over hundreds of years...
...which exist in the whole world-bon!
And only nine of those 30 Ponegliffs
have specific kinds of information.
If you take those to the
last island - Raftel,
the stones will reveal the
truth of this world-soir.
Please don't do it, Sweet
General Smoothie-sama!
Please! Please!
Have mercy on me, Smoothie-sama!
Smoothie-sama...
But, in order to go to the last
island Raftel, you need...
...four Road Ponegliffs, the red stones!
Including the one delivered by Jimbei
the other day...
A present for you. I got it on my way here.
It's from me too!
...we Big Mom Pirates have two Ponegliffs
and one Road Ponegliff.
That means three stones in total-vous plaît.
I know how important those three stones are.
But...
ONE OF THE SWEET 3 GENERALS OF
THE BIG MOM PIRATES MINISTER OF JUICE
...why did you suddenly
tighten security now, Tamago?
I got nothing to do until the tea party.
C. SMOOTHIE - 14TH DAUGHTER OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
BOUNTY: 932 MILLION BERRIES
So I don't mind guarding them.
Yes, thank you-renaissance.
There is a former pirate captain
who came to this island about five years ago.
He is a Mink Ponegliff thief
and it seems that...
he has snuck onto this island again-souffle.
Oh, no!
His life was spared because his
compatriot Pekoms begged for his life.
Why did he return?
Pedro!
If you get all four red Road Ponegliffs,
you can reach Raftel.
In other words, that's the road
to become the King of the Pirates!
That's a quest worthy of
the Four Emperors-bon.
For the sake of Mama, we put our lives on
the line to protect these stones-chocolat!
OUTSIDE OF THE TREASURE REPOSITORY
IN THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
Brook.
SPIRITS CELLAR
What? They increased security?
Yes, they were calling her
Sweet General Smoothie.
She is a beautiful woman with long legs.
Sweet General... That
means she's a top officer!
I thought so.
No wonder she looked strong.
It's hopeless.
They now have perfect security.
There's no chance even at night.
Our last hope may vanished
when Tamago noticed I was here.
Luffy and the others are having difficulty.
It'd be nice if we could
complete our mission smoothly.
I was touched by what you said the other day.
In order for Luffy-san to become the
King of the Pirates, he'll need
the Road Ponegliff someday.
But it won't be so easy to come back here.
Rather, we have to clash with them head-on
if we really want to come back.
I don't think we all could
make it this far again.
That's right.
Given this, maybe now is the rare chance.
But if we invade, both of us will get killed!
Who is Baron Tamago's target?
It's me.
Pedro-san, would you be
willing to serve as bait?
That's exactly what I was thinking.
"MIRRO-WORLD" - BRULEE'S HOUSE
Boil, boil, boil! Boil, boil, boil!
Boil, boil! Boil, boil!
Chobro, help! It's hot!
Stop whining, you brat!
I don't eat humans.
But the Minks could be edible so I gotta try.
Don't eat me! I'm not delicious!
Let Carrot go, Brulee!
She's not a real rabbit!
Of course, she's not delicious!
What? You think so? Then,
maybe I shouldn't try.
He's right! I'm too tough
and stinky and disgusting!
I'm not gonna let her go.
Keep your mouth shut, you odd reindeer.
You'll join Mama's collection
of strange beasts!
C-Collection of strange beasts?
That's right. So just sit there quietly.
Okay! We managed to get to this point.
I made sure to get tied up in Heavy Point
so I could escape from these
chains instantly by transforming.
I'm giving Chopper trouble!
Pedro will be mad at me!
It's been six hours since I used Monster
Point yesterday so I can use it already!
When the delicious soup is ready,
dump her in!
Boil, boil, boil! Boil, boil, boil!
She's gonna be delicious! Let's try!
Boil, boil, boil! Boil,
boil, boil! Puff, puff!
Chobro!
Now's the chance!
Boil, boil, boil! Boil, boil, boil!
Boil, boil! Boil, boil!
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU LIBRARY
Here it is.
There is always an infinite
universe in a book.
Look. This is a super-rare, man-eating lion
which has a human face.
"Manticore."
It's a strange beast escaped
that from Impel Down
during the attack of
Blackbeard two years ago.
Loincloth, loincloth!
It moved!
And this one is my pride and joy!
Isn't it beautiful?
What a shame. But it's living in the book.
Those animals in books will never age.
That's how it's supposed to be because
what's in a book should never change.
Help!
The books in this library contain
rare creatures from across the world.
Cool!
That's what my son Montd'Or is capable of.
Recently, we got a Centaur from Punk Hazard
and a Griffon that we
found in the South Blue.
I even got something like this!
A Long-Limbs human!
Help!
Let me out!
Even a human?
Big Mom.
Since I stepped into this country,
I've seen a wide variety of races.
Of course! Because that's the kind of country
that Totto Land aspires to becoming...
But there is one race that I don't see
and I couldn't stop thinking about it.
If they're here, we would know.
It's the Giant Tribe!
They say that all races are living in this country
but I haven't seen even one of them.
All I've seen is people who
are bigger than the others.
Oh, yeah?
I guess you haven't happened to run into one.
Oh, I just didn't get a chance.
Mama!
What do you want?
Ma... Mama... Ma, we... we... we have
brought those... those two here!
Okay.
Will you excuse me? I'm very busy today.
The weather isn't so nice
but have a good afternoon.
What's the matter?
W-Well, I got nervous.
They're the real Germa 66.
Especially Ichiji-sama and Reiju-sama
were just as cool as I thought they'd be.
Shut up! How foolish you are
to be influenced by a comic strip!
The important thing isn't how they look.
Those two?
Yeah, I've already closed it.
Let's see, what page was it?
Page 55-fa.
51.
53.
55.
There they are.
These two? I like the look on their faces.
Lick!
How long are you gonna keep us like this?!
Let me take a shower!
My body is covered in sticky syrup!
Sounds like it's so sweet, Candy-chan. Lick!
PEROSPERO - ELDEST SON
OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
Here comes Mama.
What?
Huh?
A Transponder Snail?!
It's been a while, Straw Hat Luffy!
You finally made it this far.
Is this Big Mom?
Let me out! I gotta go back!
I'm gonna get out of here
even if I have to destroy everything!
Whoa-whoa, you've still
got that kind of spirit.
Since you didn't bring the whole crew,
I thought you'd forgotten what you said to me
on the Fish-Man Island.
I'll kick your ass all over the New World
and make the Fish-Man Island my territory!
Yeah, I'll kick your ass someday!
But we just came to take
Sanji back this time!
Enough with bluffing!
You're just gonna rot
away helplessly in there.
Straw Hat, you're already doomed!
Shut up!
If you wanna fight, show yourself, Big Mom!
I'm gonna fight you right here right now!
Brook and Pedro finally start creating a ruckus
in the Emperor's headquarters!
Meanwhile, Luffy comes
under hard questioning by
Big Mom but he challenges her head-on!
Big Mom erupts into volcanic rage and
things are in a tense touch-and-go situation!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Fateful Confrontation! Luffy and Big Mom!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!