My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy got knocked out by the enraged army
that was organized to avenge Sweet General Cracker,
and he and Nami were held captive
in the Whole Cake Chateau.
Big Mom talked to them
through a Transponder Snail
and got furious when she learned
Nami was her runaway daughter Lola's friend.
If you know where she is, tell me.
Children don't know how indebted they are
to their parents as they say!
She's a dumb daughter who ran away
rejecting the biggest-ever political marriage!
If only she had gotten married submissively at that time,
I could've got tremendous power!
I'd already have beaten
Kaido, Red-Haired and even Whitebeard,
and become...
...the King of the Pirates by now!
What a boring story, Big Mom.
Lola didn't marry.
You haven't become the King of the Pirates.
That's all.
Just because you're the Emperor,
don't be cocky!
I'll win Sanji back!
We're the ones who'll have the last laugh!
At the same time, Brook and Pedro
who snuck into the Whole Cake Chateau,
were attempting to infiltrate the Treasure Repository
where the Road Ponegliff is kept.
What's going on-soir?
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Baron Tamago, it's the intruder!
Hustle up!
Don't let him do whatever he wants!
The intruder's in the other area!
Now, in the pirate Emperor Big Mom's castle...
Let's start...
...a special live show!
"Shout of the Soul!
Brook and Pedro's Lightning Operation!"
We're currently searching for the intruder!
A lot of guards have been injured
by the attack on the Treasure Repository!
The attacker has explosives!
Don't let your guard down!
I can't believe they let this happen
the day before the tea party!
There he is!
So quick!
This is it, intruder!
Shoot!
Shoot him down!
Run!
Where is he now?!
He went downstairs to the third floor of Red-Bean Baum Cake,
near the Courtyard!
It won't be easy to take him down!
Corner him in the garden-soir!
--Roger!
--Clank.
Didn't he come for the Ponegliff?
What's wrong?!
There is a member of the Straw Hats
who can't be located-soir.
Pedro is bait-bon!
--Let's close this door!
--Yeah!
Oh, no!
Now he can't get inside...
Oh, boy! That was really close.
What?
What?!
I can't handle any more soldiers!
There you are, intruder.
Well, there are a lot less than before.
Only Pedro-san could've done that!
What kind of creature are you?
You're very strange, even for this country.
I agree.
Mama would be happy.
Get him!
--Clank.
--Hey, Baron Tamago!
Smoothie-sama!
You were right. There's another one.
That one is bait like you said.
Damn Pedro! He created a big mess!
We let him get into the Treasure Repository
and lock the door.
Sorry. It's my fault.
But there is only one entrance
to the Treasure Repository.
Even if he can steal the treasure,
it's impossible for him to run from Smoothie-sama.
As long as you guard the door closely,
there won't be a problem-dezvous.
You're right. Count on me.
If he beats the guards inside and comes out,
I'll kill him. Is that okay?
No, the man inside is probably a skeleton-bon.
Mama would love to have that strange beast.
Beat him but don't kill!
Got it.
Pedro-san told me.
BISHOP　　　　　　　 PAWN
Through Big Mom's ability, you are all infused with human souls.
KNIGHT　　　　　　　　 　ROOK
KING　　　QUEEN
That means you Chess Peacekeepers are...
...driven by soul!
Oh, no!
How powerful!
Wait a sec!
It's not tuned yet!
Tear him apart!
This is it, you damn skeleton!
Oh, please!
W-W-W-W-Wait, wait!
Please wait!!
What happened?!
You don't know my other name, do you, baby?
It's Soul King!
The Chess Peacekeepers!
The soldiers infused with souls...
...will not be able to stay on their feet...
...when they face my serious shout of the soul!
Baby.
You'd better check the Courtyard of the castle-nasu.
They have good soil
so they grow beautiful flowers there-nasu.
I'll show you-nasu.
No, I know where it is.
What do you need flowers for, Sanji-sama?
Pudding-chan!
"MIRRO-WORLD" - BRULEE'S HOUSE
Please! Don't do it!
I don't wanna be eaten!
You guys are hungry, aren't you?
We're starving!
Let us eat already, Brulee-sama!
That looks crocodelicious...
This will be the finest game dish ever.
Don't eat me!
--Let me down!
--Just give up already.
Brulee dug her own grave.
What? What?!
The Carrot that got caught with me at that time
was a fake one.
It's a frog that has been transformed into
a mirror image of Carrot by Brulee's ability.
The real Carrot...
...is in the attic.
Stop! Don't eat me!
Please! Help! Chobro!
Help me!
But I feel bad for the frog.
There are 16 enemies in this house.
The most troubling ones are
Randolph, Aristocroc,
the mysterious chimney man Diesel,
and... Brulee.
My only chance to get them off-guard...
...is the moment they drop the fake Carrot.
Randolph, cut the rope.
Okay.
Your pretty face will get scalded!
She'll go crazy once she gets dropped.
I gotta put the lid on right away.
Here we go, Brulee-sama!
Now! Carrot!
Uh-huh!
Winding up and...
What are you doing, Randolph?
Brulee-sama,
someone came down from the attic!
What?!
There are two rabbit girls!
Good!
Calm down! Hey!
Hurry up, Carrot!
Count on me, Chobro!
What is she gonna do?
Randolph! Just cut the rope!
O-Okay!
Carrot!
Take this!
What?!
Oh, no! You can't do that! No!
Nooo!
--Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
-Brulee-sama!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
Ouch! Ouch!!
All right!
Rumble!
--Brulee-sama!
--This is bad news!
Time to start our countercharge!
PRISON LIBRARY
You bastard! Let me out!
Hey! Are you listening?!
Warty-head!
Just let me out already!
Shut up-fa! Keep your mouth shut!
Damn! I'm gonna destroy this thing!
It's no use! Just sit quietly-fa!
Enough with that-fa!
Oh, this is unusual.
What do you need, Pudding?
Pudding?
--Hey! Pudding! Get us outta here! We got caught!
--No, Luffy!
The other guys are listening too!
What brought you to a place like this-fa?
Brother Opera, can I talk to Luffy-kun and Nami-chan
in there for a minute?
Luffy-kun? Yeah, go ahead-fa.
Hey, open it for her-fa!
Yes, sir.
Let me put a bookmark here.
Pudding...
You two...
Hey, Pudding!
We went to the coast!
Stop it! Pudding will be in trouble!
You got beaten up.
Luffy-kun.
Nami-chan.
I'm sure my brothers and sisters
did horrible things to you.
I'm sorry!
No, don't...
I couldn't go to the coast where we promised to meet either...
I'm really sorry!
That's okay. Raise your head, please.
Why is she talking in whispers?
Listen, there is something
that I have to tell you two.
What is it, Pudding?
I actually...
...was proposed to by Sanji-san.
What?!
The Straw Hats start a counterattack!
The captured Chopper and Carrot launch a coordinated attack
to pull them out of the fire!
Meanwhile, Pudding whose heart is wavering over her marriage
with Sanji tells Luffy and Nami her firm determination!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Goodbye! Pudding's Tearful Determination!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!