kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into
a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Brook and Pedro who snuck into the Whole Cake Chateau
from a different route,
started their operation
to get a copy of the Road Ponegliff.
You don't know my other name, do you, baby?
It's Soul King!
The soldiers infused with souls...
...will not be able to stay on their feet...
...when they face my
serious shout of the soul!
Meanwhile, in front of Luffy and Nami
who were held captive in
the Whole Cake Chateau,
Pudding showed up.
Listen, there is something
that I have to tell you two.
What is it, Pudding?
I actually...
...was proposed to by Sanji-san.
What?!
"Goodbye!
Pudding's Tearful Determination!"
It made me happy.
But...
...I know Sanji-san is just being nice to me.
I'm causing everyone trouble.
That's not true...
So don't worry.
I'm not going to marry him.
Listen.
Hey, wait, Pudding!
Goodbye.
Where's Reiju?
I don't know. She left for somewhere earlier.
A GUEST ROOM - THE VINSMOKE FAMILY
--Tea
--Green tea
Which'd you like to have?
I'd rather have booze.
What?!
Wh-What if you had to choose?
Tea.
Yes!
Anyway, Father, where will Sanji and
his wife live after they get married?
Of course, in Germa.
Then, I can take my time and
pay him back for kicking me.
The daughter is the key.
If we don't hold her as a hostage,
we don't know what they'll demand hereafter.
We're dealing with pirates.
I see. A hostage, huh?
Maybe they want to hold Sanji hostage too
in case something happens, huh?
Don't be silly, Niji.
Even if they do, would killing
Sanji upset us that much?
You're right.
Never!
I can't wait...
...to live close to Sanji again.
SANJI'S ROOM
May I come in-nasu?
Yeah.
Thank you for going shopping.
It's nothing-nasu.
Um, I got some news-nasu.
We're currently holding
Straw Hat and Cat Burglar-nasu.
They got Luffy and Nami-san?
It's okay.
After me and Pudding-chan's wedding tomorrow,
they'll be free.
I made a deal with Big Mom...
About this time tomorrow,
I'll gain Germa's military strength
and we'll all have a delicious wedding cake!
If you don't run away,
everything will turn out for the best, Sanji.
And a Mink Man and Soul
King are still rampaging.
Brook!
Sweet General Smoothie and Baron Tamago
went to subdue them,
but they're still struggling to...
That's enough.
Can I have my groceries?
Yeah, here they are-nasu.
If you're hungry, I can bring you something
like nasu (eggplant).
No thanks.
--Can I use this kitchen?
--What?
Pudding-chan didn't show up at the dinner table
so I'll cook something for her.
I see-nasu.
I'm worried about her.
Yes, I heard that she
still doesn't feel well...
Ouch!
"MIRRO-WORLD" - BRULEE'S HOUSE
Oh, ow, ow, ow...
Yes!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Oh, no!
Brulee-sama!
Electrical Luna!
This is bad! I gotta tell Mama!
Leave it to me, Chobro!
Choo-choo! Choo-choo!
Choo-choo and choo-choo and choo!
Idiots! No one can catch up with me
once I start running...
Ouch!
Garchu!
What?!
Guess who?
No, no, no... Let go of me!
Not yet!
I said "Let go of me"!
Okay.
What?
I-I'm gonna crash!
I can't stop!
There!
Yes! We beat Brulee's group!
Chobro!
All right!
Now we can use Brulee's ability
to jump in and out of the mirrors!
Let's travel in this dimension
across the island to look for everyone!
Soul King's shout of the soul...
...is still far from over!
Baby!
Here's the finale!
Now, all that's left is those who can't
be destroyed by the shout of the soul!
Go!
H-He disappeared!
Song of Scratches...
Blizzard Slice!
I've already cut you.
What?
The keys!
Damn you!
How dare you do that!
I've got to do it!
Swallow Banderole!
I asked my partner to risk his life
before I came here!
I have to get what I need...
...or I'll lose face!
Who said that I don't have a face to lose!
...A face to lose! ...A face to lose!
...A face to lose!
Guards, can you hear me?
Answer!
I need to hurry up.
These are the keys.
Pedro-san! I'll do it!
I guess all the guards inside got beaten...
Probably.
This is the only entrance.
Prepare to attack.
Yes, ma'am!
Is the intruder in there?!
Mama! You didn't have to come!
I can handle it!
Get out of my way, Smoothie!
Who are you?
Don't you know whose treasure...
...you're messing with?!
Don't tell me it's...
Big Mom!
Oh? What a strange creature!
That's odd.
You are...
The intruder is passing through
the hallway near the Courtyard!
Corner him from both sides!
All hands, shields up!
Charge!
Almost there!
Alright! We cornered him in the Courtyard!
Damn! What are they up to?
It's been a while-bon!
THE COURTYARD IN THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
Baron Tamago!
Captain Pedro of the Nox Pirates!
Although you're my enemy,
I've already given you due respect.
Every time we face each other,
this scar on the left eye that we both have
itches-toi-et-moi.
Five years ago, you really held on to life.
Why are you doing the same again?
You don't have much time
left to live-soufflé.
That day, Mama took...
...50 years of your life-bon!
Yes, I know that.
I'm not...
...expecting to go home alive!
--Hey, Luffy!
--I...
...gotta go!
I can't stay in a place like this forever!
Damn!
Oh, yeah! Okay!
Hey, Luffy!
I got an idea to get us out of here!
What?
Let's go!
Sanji!
Pedro engages in a duel
against his fated rival Baron Tamago!
And his horrific past involving
Big Mom is revealed!
When it's all revealed,
Pedro's lightning sword attack,
along with his determination, strikes the Baron!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The History of the Left Eye!
Pedro vs. Baron Tamago!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!