My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Pudding whispered a few words to Luffy and Nami
who were held captive by the Big Mom Pirates.
Meanwhile, in order to obtain the Road Ponegliff,
Pedro invaded the Whole Cake Chateau,
but Baron Tamago stood in his way.
They saw each other
for the first time in five years.
I'm not...
...expecting to go home alive!
In the world of mirrors, Chopper and Carrot
started their operation to find Sanji.
"The History of the Left Eye!
Pedro vs. Baron Tamago!"
SWEET CITY
Sanji!
Not here!
Oh, there's a ghost!
Not here either.
Oh, my!
Is it farther away?
Wake up, Brulee!
Where is the mirror to the Whole Cake Chateau?
We saw it once before.
Where was it?
Diesel! Don't you know?!
How do I know? Dammit!
I wonder if Luffy and Nami found Sanji.
I hope so.
They said they'd go to Mom's castle, right?
Uh-huh.
As long as we're touching Brulee,
we can jump in and out of the mirrors!
This dimension is connected to
the mirrors across the Whole Cake Island.
We should've reached the castle already.
Brulee! Wake up!
Gee!
Anyway, we gotta try to find it ourselves
until she wakes up!
Let's keep going until we find it!
You guys will pay for this!
Stop it, Luffy! What are you thinking?!
It's no use.
If you don't stop,
your hands are gonna tear apart!
That's what I'm trying to do!
What?!
No! Don't do it!
I have no choice!
Is there any other way to get us out of here?!
Isn't it better to have your arms being torn apart...
...than die?!
A little more to go!
No, no, no!
They're really gonna break apart!
I told you it's no use-fa.
Are you okay?
Dammit!
Are you still trying? Stop!
I'm not gonna stop!
I should tell...
Big Sister-sama!
That's terrible!
What are you doing up there?
As you can see,
I'm trying to get a copy of the Road Ponegliff.
You're very honest.
But you have nowhere to run.
Give up and come down here!
You look so relaxed.
When you face the Emperor, you have no choice
but to turn defiant instead of being nervous.
Oh, do you want to fight me?
Yes, because I haven't fulfilled my mission yet.
Your mission?
I'm gonna take you down
and get a copy of the stone!
You think I can be beaten so easily?
No way. I'm putting my life on the line!
I see. Do whatever you want.
Zeus!
Yes, Mama!
ZEUS, A THUNDERCLOUD
Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
PROMETHEUS, A SUN
Napoleon!
Yes, Mama!
NAPOLEON, A BICORNE
You'll be mine!
COURTYARD ON THE THIRD FLOOR
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
PEDRO
FORMER CAPTAIN OF THE NOX PIRATES
BOUNTY: 382 MILLION BERRIES
BARON TAMAGO
KNIGHT OF THE BIG MOM PIRATES
BOUNTY: 429 MILLION BERRIES
Straw Hat and Cat Burglar are
already ours-bon.
Give up-bon.
So what?
Then, let's have it out-bon!
Your Electro won't work against me
anymore-s'il vous plaît!
I'm not going to be scared of the Minks-bon!
I guess you're prepared.
That's right. I'm wearing special tights
that protect me from Electro-feuille.
I'm gonna sort things out with you here!
For the sake of my dead friend.
That must be the Whole Cake Chateau.
The sweet smell drives me crazy.
It's literally a candy country.
What are we gonna do now, Pedro?
We're talking about Big Mom.
It's not gonna be easy, Zepo.
Big Brothers?
Big Brothers! I thought so!
--You-gara...
--Pekoms.
Big Brother Pedro! Big Brother Zepo!
Garchu!
Garchu...
Why are you here?
Grr! I'm a member of the Big Mom Pirates now.
The Big Mom Pirates?!
What are you two doing here?
It's better you don't know.
We cornered them!
We've been ambushed?
You can't go any farther-bon,
Ponegliff thieves!
I'm not going to let anyone
enter the Treasure Repository-bon!
You'll never pass through here-feuille!
We're gonna get in there
or our trip to this island will be wasted!
Baron Tamago-sama!
Are you okay, Pedro?
I am but not him.
Damn you!
Big Mom...
You're an exception!
I have to bring you down myself-s'il vous plaît!
You'll lose more than an eye this time!
You...
That was close-bon!
My left eye still itches sometimes-feuille.
I remember the pain of
getting stabbed by you-toilette!
I remember too, of course.
What happened that day
remains etched into my left eye!
Look what you've done, you thieves.
Big Brothers, why?! Grr!
You tried to steal something on my island
and you stabbed Tamago's eyeball.
You have to pay.
Bring the roulette!
You spin it first.
What the...
Big Bro!
I'm taking 100 years of your life!
Stay with me, Zepo!
Zepo...
Zepo!!
Big Brother Zepo!
There wasn't enough for 100 years.
He only had 30 years to live.
Since you're his partner,
I need you to pay the rest.
Now, give me the remaining 70 years.
Sunny-side Legs!
This is it-bon!
You're getting tired-bon!
Now, give me 70-years' worth of your soul!
Please, Mama!
He was like a big brother to me!
If you take 70 years,
Big Bro Pedro will die too!
Stop, Pekoms. That's pathetic-bon.
I'm begging you, Mama!
Pekoms...
Stop crying, Pekoms! All right.
10 years. I'll take off 10 years.
What?!
But you took away an eye from Tamago
and that's serious.
I'll take 60 years of your life!
Aren't you satisfied, Pekoms?
W-Well...
Hey, Big Mom!
How many years will you spare for this?
Big Bro!
It's pointless to die here!
The dawn of the new world is coming!
I have to go back!
You're so handsome.
I'll reduce it to 50 years.
Go on with your life.
Legs Benedict!
Say it-bon, Pedro!
Why did you come back?!
To this nightmarish island where your partner got killed
and 50 years of your life was taken away!
The Straw Hats saved my home country
and I'm indebted to them!
On top of that,
I believe they'll lead the world to the dawn one day!
Pedro!
The dawn of the world will come before long!
In time, the Straw Hats will surpass you-gara people
and change the world!
They can't do anything!
Where do you think you are-bon?!
It's the Whole Cake Island-bon!
So what?
I believe in the Straw Hats.
That's why I'm happy to spend
the short remainder of my life...
...for them!
But don't get me wrong.
I'm not gonna die here!
They haven't met their goal on this island yet!
I'm not gonna die now.
Cutting ties with his friends,
Sanji looks forward to marrying Pudding, his only hope.
However, when a dark plot behind the wedding
and a stunning secret are revealed,
he stands in a daze all alone
as the cold rain pours down his back.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Moist Cigarlette! The Night Before Sanji's Wedding!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!