My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
To obtain a copy of the Road Ponegliff,
Brook snuck into the Treasure Repository
and got in a deadly fight against Big Mom.
Sanji not returning is
the worst thing that could happen?
I don't think so.
Do you think no one's gonna die?
What kind of fool regards his own death
as part of a plan, young lady?
Meanwhile, Sanji was learning about
the secret behind his birth from his sister Reiju.
There's no way that you're a failure.
Our mother protected her child
at the risk of her own life
and he was born with the spark of humanity.
That child is you, Sanji.
That's why you're kinder than everyone else!
Things can't get any worse!
We were all fooled! Sanji, too!
I gotta let him know!
Look after Nami, Jimbei!
"To Reach Sanji!
Luffy's Vengeful Hell-bent Dash!"
Look for Straw Hat!
Which way did he go?!
He got out of the underground Prison Library
and ran through the first floor already!
--All hands, go to the second floor!
--Yes, sir!
Sanji!
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU - SECOND FLOOR
There he is!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Where are you?!
Answer if you're there!
Take him down!
Don't get in my way!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
...Whip!
Guys, get back!
--Cadenza-sama!
--I'll take care of him!
I can't let him cause any more trouble!
He seems like he knows something about Sanji.
Brat, don't push your luck!
Do you forget that you fell
at my brother's feet?!
You're the guy from that time!
Gear Two!
Get out of my way!
Why are you still thinking?
You've already got your answer.
Abandon Germa and run away, Sanji.
Germa clings to their past glory
and stands for nothing but destruction.
The world doesn't need us.
All Big Mom wants is our
scientific technology.
I don't think she's interested in
taking your mentor's life.
Your father and brothers who treat
the seafaring restaurant as hostage...
...will all be dead tomorrow.
We deserve that
because we're a group of assassins.
I only have a grudge against them
but why do you have to die, too?!
There is a bit of humanity left in me
but I'm our father's accomplice
who was modified not to disobey him.
My hands are dirty too.
I deserve death.
Baron Tamago!
Cheep!
Cheep, cheep, cheep.
That call is...
Is he gonna evolve?
Into Viscount Hiyoko?!
Viscount Hiyoko?
Cheep! Cheep!
You ate the Devil Fruit.
BARON TAMAGO WAS REBORN AND
EVOLVES MORE...
Indeed.
VISCOUNT HIYOKO
Viscount Hiyoko's sword technique
which surpasses Baron Tamago's.
Prepare for a taste of it!
Bring it on!
TREASURE REPOSITORY
You're quite a man with backbone.
Yes, my backbone's all I got.
Like I said,
I'm gonna take you down
and get a copy of the stone!
I like you even more!
I'll definitely add you to my collection.
All right!
--Zeus!
--Yes, Mama!
--Prometheus!
Surrender already!
Not so fast!
I'm sorry that I don't know when to give up!
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
That call is...
Is he gonna evolve into the third form?!
Into Count Niwatori?!
How silly.
I must take him out now.
Stop!
Baron Tamago to Viscount Hiyoko
and now, to Count Niwatori!
As he transforms, he gets stronger!
He ate the Egg-Egg Fruit!
Count Niwatori is the true knight!
You should be terrified!
When he's transformed,
he'll get strength that you're no match for!
Stop him!
I'm not gonna wait.
Stop!!
Okay, I'll stop.
This is it.
Nice to have so many soldiers around.
You bastard! What are you doing?!
Get back!
Run!
It's nice to be bait.
Don't do it!
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Gatling!
Humph! Is that all you got?!
Get knocked down again!
Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
...Eagle Bazooka!
Spit it out!
Where's Sanji?!
No way!
How hard her skin is!
Now...
How annoying.
Don't give us trouble.
--He's not pretending, is he?
--I don't know.
Seems like he's had enough.
Jeez.
Au... Aubade Coup Droit!
You son of a...!
IN FRONT OF THE DOOR TO
THE TREASURE REPOSITORY
What?! Another problem?
Yes, ma'am.
Boss Jimbei is in the castle and...
Don't tell me he rose in revolt!
Yes, seems like he did.
We have one mess after another.
What shall we do?
Alright, tell all soldiers this.
Okay.
Tomorrow's mission is
Mama's long-awaited dream.
Y-Yes.
--What will happen if we fail?
--What?
In the worst case, what'll happen?
I-I don't even wanna think about it!
Me neither.
If we bring any more problems
to the moody Mama,
it'll affect tomorrow's mission.
You're right!
Then what shall we do?
A-Are you telling me to lie...
If you lie to Mama, you'll be put to death.
F-Forgive me!
If there is no problem,
we don't need to tell her anything.
Don't you think so?
Y-Yes, I think so!
We're on the fourth floor.
Block up all the paths to this floor!
Handle everything in the lower levels.
Solve all the problems immediately!
Yes, ma'am. Understood!
If so, it's safer to kill them
than capture them!
--That's fine. I give you permission!
--Yes, ma'am!
What a cute creature.
You're a skeleton from tip to toe
but you're alive - it's a miracle.
How you fought was impressive too, Soul King.
The Chess Peacekeepers are
totally afraid of you.
You're not known as Soul King for nothing!
Their arch-enemy.
But...
NAPOLEON, A BICORNE
...you can't beat these three.
ZEUS, A THUNDERCLOUD
PROMETHEUS, A SUN
I'm giving them my soul directly.
So their souls are in a different class.
We finished the inspection, Mama!
There is nothing in his clothes!
There is nothing in this tube either!
--In his cane sword...
--And in his cloak...
There is nothing!
He didn't steal anything!
That's good then, Soul King.
I'm sorry to suspect you. Pet, pet.
How frustrating. What a humiliation.
The Tamate Box goes without saying,
but I can't let you steal
a copy of the Ponegliff or other stuff either.
It'd be foolish if I allowed you to take it
and let someone reach Raftel again.
I'm not gonna mess up like I did with Roger!
He read the stone with his strange ability
that allowed him to hear the voice of all things,
but we have someone who will eventually
have a similar ability.
The ones who will reach Raftel next
will be none other than us.
Mama!
Oh, my dear Pudding!
We were just talking about you.
What's wrong?
Has your third eye opened to its true power?
Come on, Mama!
You say that every time you see me!
I'm not pure blood of the tribe!
There's no guarantee
that such power will awaken in me.
I'm sorry.
But you certainly have the rare Three-Eyed
People's blood in your veins.
If you don't have an awakening
as a Three-Eyed People member,
you're just a creepy-looking girl.
P-Pudding-san?
Three-Eyed?
No! The fact that we know each other...
...must be kept secret!
That skeleton man.
I didn't expect him to be here.
Well, he got caught so that's good.
Listen, Mama. It's too embarrassing for me to
talk to you right here so let's go to your room!
Okay, of course. No problem.
Where's Sanji?!
I'm asking where he is!
Cadenza-sama!
That bastard! Attack him!
Sanji, you have to run away.
I forgot to mention it but those bracelets...
If you try to get off of this island,
your hands will be blown off!
They won't blow up because I swapped them.
Is there any other reason
that you can't escape?
Get it together, Sanji!
Outta my way!
Consider what's important to you!
What's important to me?
Stop Straw Hat!
Join my group!
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
Where are you?!
You're a good cook,
so let's be pirates together!
You'll never meet...
...such great friends...
...like them twice!
Outta my way!
Sanji!!
Retrieving Sanji is within sight!
Jimbei and Nami run around inside the castle!
And, anxious to share the secret plot behind
the wedding, Luffy rushes to find Sanji!
Luffy fights hard battles against enemy
officers that stand in his way one after another,
then Reiju who once saved his life shows up!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Chateau in Turmoil! Luffy, to the Rendezvous!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!