My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
With Jimbei's help,
Luffy successfully broke out of the Prison Library,
and went on a rampage by himself
searching for Sanji.
Spit it out!
Where's Sanji?!
Meanwhile, Brook who had snuck into the castle
to obtain a copy of the Road Ponegliff,
fought a deadly battle against Big Mom
but was defeated.
What a cute creature.
You're a skeleton from tip to toe
but you're alive - it's a miracle.
How you fought was impressive too, Soul King.
And Pedro who was causing a distraction
for Brook,
lit dynamite after a fierce fight
against Baron Tamago.
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
"The Chateau in Turmoil!
Luffy, to the Rendezvous!"
VISCOUNT HIYOKO WAS REBORN AND
EVOLVES MORE...
COUNT NIWATORI
Count Niwatori, glad you're okay!
Damn Pedro,
I can't believe he detonated himself.
Count, there are so many wounded!
Put out the fires-bon!
Take the injured to the medical center-soir!
Yes, sir!
Oh, that was close!
You could be dead now, Pedro!
How reckless you are!
Pedro, I was so surprised!
I was even more surprised.
Hey, Pedro!
Imagine if you were called to from inside a mirror
all of a sudden.
But you came up with a plan like this instantly!
That's our Pedro!
Nice to have so many soldiers around.
It's nice to be bait.
Anyway, is this a mirror dimension?
It's hard to believe.
No one can come in or get out of here
without Brulee. So it's safe!
We can get away through this dimension
with Sanji!
Tell us what you know!
What?! Luffy and Nami have been caught?!
Yeah, that's what I heard.
I'm worried about Brook too.
I hope he got a copy of the Ponegliff without trouble.
They're all in danger! Let's hurry up!
Carrot! Is everyone's portrait ready?
Yes, they're ready, Chobro!
You sure?! Well done!
Then, let's search for everyone
by showing them to the mirrors!
Okay!
Mirror, mirror!
Tell us where these people are!
They look nothing like them!
That girl with long hair ran by here earlier.
The mirror talked!
What? That means Nami has broken out?
Is she with Luffy?
She was with Boss Jimbei!
J... Jimbei?
Wh-What?!
Sanji! Where are you?!
Outta my way!
It's me, Sanji!
Listen to me! Sanji!
Stop him!
Sanji!
Where are you?!
Back down, guys!
Cabaletta-sama!
Straw Hat!
Oh? Didn't I take you down before?
That was my big brother, Cadenza!
I'm gonna smash you up!
I'm not like my brother! Physical strength isn't all I got!
C. CABALETTA - 8TH SON OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
I don't care.
I'll just beat up whoever gets in my way!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Bullet!
What's the matter, Straw Hat?
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Gatling!
I'll make you suffer just as my brother did!
I-I gotta tell S-Sanji...
Sanji?
Oh, the groom from Germa.
That scum betrayed you guys!
Just leave that shit-bag alone already!
Don't speak bad about Sanji!
What?!
You can't get away from me anymore!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Rifle!
I can't believe it!
Cabaletta-sama has been defeated!
Sanji!
C-Chase him!
Stop!
Sanji!
Sanji! Where are you?!
Sanji! I'm hungry!
Oh, oops!
Where are you, Sanji?!
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU - THIRD FLOOR
Abandon Germa and run away, Sanji.
You'll never meet...
...such great friends like them twice!
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU - FIRST FLOOR
There they are!
--They're coming, Jimbei!
--Hold on tight!
Five Thousand Brick Fist!
Do you think Luffy met Sanji-kun safely?
It's already hard enough to look for him
in this giant castle!
But he is running in bad shape fighting enemies...
I hope he'll be alright.
Stop!
We must keep up too
and get out of this castle already!
Oh! There he is!
Chase him!
Boss Jimb... I mean, Jimbei's risen in revolt!
Stop!
This way!
Block their way!
Oh, no! I think we will be surrounded.
What? Isn't there a way out?
Can you take the back, Nami?!
Count on me! I'm fed up with this!
There they are!
Stop!!
Nami!
You guys are annoying!
Storm Cloud Rod!
What?! Chopper!
What?
Chopper! Why are you here?!
Oh! Chobro!
Carrot!
Nami! We're here to save you!
I see! I'm sorry!
Oh, no!
More enemies are coming from the front!
Nami! Get in the mirror now!
What?
Sanji!
Answer if you're there!
Stop, Straw Hat!
Sanji!
Hey!
There's something you need to know!
Where are you?!
Listen to what I have to say!
Ow, ow, ow...
Where did he go?
He's so quick! Which way did he go?
In here?
I can't open it!
--Let's go that way!
--Yeah!
You're Sanji's sister!
That's right.
Why did you do that? I'm in a hurry!
You're looking for Sanji, right?
He was just here.
What? Really?!
Where did he go?!
Pudding was fooling us!
Sanji's bride Pudding said she'd kill him!
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
Thank you. I'm okay.
He knows about Pudding.
What?! Has he known all this time?!
He just found out.
I convinced him to get away from this island
but he was worried about
the hostages in the East Blue
and the harm that it'd cause to you guys.
By "hostages," you mean Baratie?
I know them well too so if they're really in danger,
I'll even go there and fight for them!
Do you want something to eat?
N-No thanks!
I'll be here waiting!
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
...starving to death!
You're the cook of my ship!
I won't eat anything other than what you cook!
But that's good. Sanji...
Sanji knows about Pudding.
If he's not being fooled, that's good.
Aside from that, I've done everything I can.
Okay, thank you, Sanji's sister!
What? Why are you going that way?!
This isn't the rendezvous point!
Sanji!
We'll chop this guy's head off.
You are a sacrifice, Sanji.
If you don't run away,
everything will turn out for the best, Sanji.
At the wedding tomorrow,
you Vinsmokes...
...will all be eliminated!
We're here to pick you up! Sanji!
Get packing, you low-class pirates!
It's too late for me to turn back, Luffy.
Oh! Something hit the house!
--My house!
--What's going on? It's so late.
A person?
H-Hey! Are you okay?
There you are.
I gotta get there as soon as possible.
I'll be here waiting!
I've got to be there waiting!
At that spot!
Death or escape.
Sanji, who has lost everything, is torn by the ultimate conflict.
Meanwhile, Luffy, nearly fainting from hunger, fights deadly
battles against his pursuers in order to see Sanji again!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Deciding to Say Goodbye! Sanji and his Straw-Hat Bento!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!