kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Chopper and Carrot in the Mirro-world
got back together with
Pedro, Nami and Jimbei who
had their own troubles.
Luffy was on a rampage in the Whole
Cake Chateau looking for Sanji
and came across Sanji's sister Reiju.
If he's not being fooled, that's good.
Aside from that, I've done everything I can.
What? Why are you going that way?!
This isn't the rendezvous point!
I've got to be there waiting!
At that spot!
"Deciding to Say Goodbye!
Sanji and his Straw-Hat Bento!"
You're Straw Hat Luffy, right?
We'll take care of you right here.
Get out of my way!
Which direction was it?
It's that way!
Okay, let's get out of this city...
Don't get in my way!
Are you okay, Chobro?
I'm okay because I'm Chobro.
I can't believe this!
We're inside the mirror?!
That girl...
Jimbei! Why are you with these rats?!
Brulee.
This is obviously treason.
I heard you just sought to leave our crew
but got scared by the roulette.
I owed Mama for protecting the Fish-Man Island
after Whitebeard died.
Since I was leaving,
I wanted to fulfill my duty to her.
But I only smell death and evil intent
from that roulette.
Roulette?
It's a good thing that you didn't do it,
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei.
Five years ago, my partner spun the roulette
asking mercy of Big Mom
and lost his life.
That thing is made to kill whoever spins it.
So it's rigged?!
Of course it is, you idiots!
Mama won't let anyone leave alive!
Whether it's a minor intruder...
...or an affiliated pirate
who was once loyal!
She'll welcome those who come to her
and kill those who leave!
That's her...
We don't have time!
Let's get going!
We gotta get Brook, Luffy and Sanji!
I'm not going!
You're over the weight limit!
Let's go!
Garchu!
Oh, ow, ow!
What's wrong, Prometheus?
The cut Soul King gave me
was deeper than I thought
and it's opening again!
How pathetic!
I mean, we gotta give this one credit.
Because no one's ever hurt you guys before.
Mama, are you gonna keep
that skeleton here forever?
What? "That skeleton"?
Pudding-san, how could you call me that?
--Yeah, of course!
--Too close!
There's no other creature like this!
It's a work of soul art!
I'm gonna carry it around for a while
rather than put it in a book.
No...
You did a fine job with Straw Hat.
I didn't expect them to pass through
the Seducing Woods.
But we've successfully confined them
in a book at the Prison Library.
Yeah, I went to see them too.
That serves them right.
"That serves them right"?
--Are you gonna kill them?
--Yeah, after the wedding.
I sent bargirls to everyone in Germa.
I think they're drunk by now
and totally unsuspecting.
Okay. But Reiju was snooping around me.
She's very intuitive.
But it's already been resolved.
What? You didn't kill her, did you?!
What, Mama?! Don't you trust me?!
I only shot her leg!
I shot her once and erased her memory.
I can't believe what I'm hearing.
Pudding-san? I thought that
you were a very nice girl.
Be careful. You're our precious bride.
If she tries to get revenge,
it'd be a big deal.
Thank you for your concern, Mama.
But...
...thanks to her, I got to try my gun.
With this, I definitely can riddle Germa's
modified human bodies with bullets.
That's great. You're such a smart girl.
Tomorrow,
your gunfire will be the cue for everything.
I can't wait.
A decorated hall.
Unending applause and laughing!
Appearing there is the groom Sanji
and our sweet bride!
The wedding kiss
will draw everyone's attention.
Sanji, with his goofy face, will try to lift your veil
and kiss you.
That's when...
...he sees your third eye for the first time!
The moment he sees his beautiful bride's
creepy real face,
he'll fall back a little!
That's the moment! Okay?
Kill him with one shot.
Aim at the spot between his eyebrows.
It's here.
Pudding-san will kill Sanji-san?!
Everyone there will be stunned and frozen!
The people of Germa will become upset
and as they turn around and run,
it'll already be too late!
Countless guns will be pointing at
the unarmed Vinsmokes!
There'll be no time for them to be scared
before their blood spatters!
Like fireworks,
the sound of gunshots won't stop!
A rain of bullets that'll keep piercing through
their bodies even after they die!
A pool of blood expands on the floor!
The lifeless forms of the six Vinsmokes!
Gunshots will become shots of joy!
And the real party begins there!
Let's celebrate with a cake!
Let's celebrate with tea!
When they lose their useless leader,
the whole of Germa will become mine!
SANJI'S ROOM
Yes, the groom - Sanji-sama surely is
sleeping in his room.
Don't let him out or let anyone in until morning.
Keep close watch.
Yes, ma'am!
Oh, no! I fell asleep-nasu!
In Sanji-sama's bed!
Is he not back yet-nasu?
I guess he won't come
back any time soon-nasu.
Well, then let's sleep
a little bit more-nasu.
MEETING ROOM
So, Pekoms was with them until Chocolat Town.
Their objective is to take Sanji back.
There were six of them when Pudding
lured them to this main island.
Soul King is in Mama's hands now.
Don't touch!
Pedro detonated himself in the Courtyard
on the third floor, right?
Indeed-cock-a-doo.
Two down.
And of the four who entered the Seducing
Woods, a rabbit and a raccoon...
...got caught by Big Sis Brulee -
she reported so at noon today.
That means four out of the six of them are out.
The problem is...
...these two who took down Big Bro Cracker
and got out of the Seducing Woods.
We surely locked them up
in the underground Prison Library.
Why is there a rumor that they broke out?
Only one of us was
there in the Prison Library.
What happened, Big Brother Opera?
They say Jimbei appeared.
That's groundless!
Don't make me repeat myself-fa!
In fact, where is he now?
There's no information-fa!
No one has come to the basement!
As I promised to Mama, I was torturing
Lola's whereabouts out of them!
They didn't know anything
so I burned them to death!
I know I went a little too far.
D-Don't you trust your brother, Montd'Or?!
Of course I trust you.
I can't say that I failed
to guard them! Never!
Mama will take all of my lifespan away-fa!
How are Sanji and the Vinsmokes?
They are all in their rooms.
Okay, it's all good!
All the intruders have been caught!
Right now, in the giant kitchen,
they're preparing for tomorrow!
Let's make it a great wedding tomorrow
for our precious sister Pudding!
Yeah!
Expand the coverage and patrol until morning.
Yes, sir!
I don't trust Opera.
Get off of the island with
the Straw Hats, Sanji.
Huh?! I can't do that!
Even if I could, what about Baratie?!
Think about that after you escape.
If you stay here, we're all gonna die.
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
There you are.
It was a good thing that
we widened our search to the city.
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Damn! I can't hit them!
Dammit!
Boy... Did I make this for Pudding-chan?
What was I thinking?
These are all their favorites.
Forget them! Forget them!
You...
Did we finally beat him?
Don't get in my way!
I...
...gotta get back... to that spot!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
...Rocket!
I don't have to worry about Luffy and the others.
They can flee on their own.
All members of the evil army
Vinsmoke will die. I'll die too.
Just as Big Mom planned.
That's for the best.
That way our enemies get what they want.
It feels short but it was a fulfilling life.
Oh, food!
Are you Vinsmoke Sanji?
Montd'Or said you were sleeping in your room.
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
...starving to death!
Don't touch it!
That meat is...
...not for you!
I heard a loud noise from that way!
You son of a...
Hey, stop, you bastard!
What am I doing?!
Tiptoe silently, stealthy.
Save Brook, sleeping alongside the Emperor!
In an extremely tense situation,
the Straw Hats try to invade Big Mom's
incredibly destructive bedroom,
but they can't wake her up no matter what!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Emperor Rolls Over! Rescue Brook Mission!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!