kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
In the Mirro-world, Nami and Jimbei
finally reunited with Chopper and Carrot.
Let's get going!
We gotta get Brook, Luffy and Sanji!
Brook who was caught by Big Mom
saw Pudding's real face.
Thanks to her, I got to try my gun.
With this, I definitely can
riddle Germa's modified human bodies with bullets.
Luffy kept fighting
in order to wait for Sanji at the rendezvous point.
That meat is...
...not for you!
And Sanji was thinking of Luffy.
Will they be able to meet again?
"The Emperor Rolls Over!
Rescue Brook Mission!"
What's going on?!
--I just heard a loud noise from this way!
--Who was it?!
Is that it?
What happened?
B-Bobbin-sama!
BOBBIN THE DISPOSER
A FIGHTER (BISHOP), BIG MOM PIRATES
BOUNTY: 105 MILLION 500 THOUSAND BERRIES
What happened to the wall?
--What happened here?
--Who did this?
--It's nothing.
--B-But...
You guys can sit back.
Bobbin-sa...
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it myself.
He'll never ever get away with this!
Even the devil himself...
...comes from hell...
...to attend Mama's tea party!
MIRRO-WORLD
Mirror, mirror!
Here's the other three!
This skeleton and the straw hat
and the spiral eyebrows!
Have you seen them?
Tell us if you know!
--Two boys and a skeleton?
--Has anyone seen them?
--Have you seen them?
--No, I haven't.
--Have you?
--No, I haven't seen them.
I haven't either.
Here!
The skeleton is here!
--It's from that way!
--Let's go see.
Hey. Go faster. You're too slow!
I can't go any faster than this!
You guys are too heavy!
Stop grumbling. Just run.
A-All right! Gee, what jerks!
The mirror down there might be that mirror.
That mirror?
Well, you'll see.
Just hurry up!
Dammit!
I can't stand getting pushed around!
We've arrived. We've arrived.
So Brook is here.
This mirror is...
This mirror is so big.
Hey, look!
There's Brook!
Brook!
Mirror, mirror! Thank you!
You're welcome!
Hey...
Something big is enveloping Brook...
No way...
I can't believe this...
That place is...
What are you gonna do?
That room is...
...our Mama's bedroom!
The one of the Emperors - Big Mom?!
Wh-Wh-What should we do?
It's a good thing that he's alive but...
--Brook...
--I didn't expect him to be in such a place.
But why is she sleeping with him?
--He's in a deep sleep too.
--How could he even sleep?
Wake up, Brook!
No good. He's not hearing you at all.
He's a strange bony creature.
Mama won't let go of such a thing!
But don't worry.
I can make her loosen up her hand.
Mama! It's Brulee!
Choo!
--Help...
--Choo!
--Cut it out!
--Cover their mouths!
Electro!
Did it wake Big Mom up?
Oh, good. She's still sleepin...
She...
She sees us!
Oh, it's just a fly.
I guess she hasn't noticed us.
No! What, what? What's wrong?!
He woke up!
Brook! Over here, over here!
Come to us now!
Brook!
Oh, it's just a fly.
Don't go back to sleep!
What is it, Mama? An enemy attack?!
I'm sleeping!
Damn you!
There you are!
How powerful they are!
How can we...
...save...
Brook...
From those monsters?!
Hmmm...
More hair, maybe?
Hm, then how about this?
Yeah, looks good to me!
Where did you find this?
I found it in a death chamber in the castle.
Seaweed from the kitchen
is a substitute for his afro.
Okay, it's done.
--Oh! It looks exactly like Brook!
--Totally!
If we can replace Brook with this,
I don't think she'll notice
that we took him away.
Now, if we place Brulee
at the midpoint of the mirror,
we can go in and out of the mirror
as we want.
Damn! I'll make them pay for this!
I think it's all set now. Let's begin.
The Rescue Brook Mission!
Challenge 1!
Okay, I'm gonna go!
Don't make any noise!
Big Mom is cautious
even when she's sleeping.
If you think it's dangerous,
come back.
Be careful, Chobro!
I know! You can just count on me!
Watch your step, Chobro!
Relax! You're almost there!
Now, if I can just climb this bed...
What's wrong?
What is it, Chobro?!
D-Don't tell me he's about to...
--...sneeze!
--What?! Chobro, no!
--Fight it off!
--Please, Chobro!
Hold it! Hold it!
That's our Chobro!
Okay, just go!
Alright, wait for me, Brook.
I'll save you now!
You dummy!
I'm so scared! Really scared!
--Are you okay, Chobro?
--Somebody else has to go.
Okay, let me go next!
Challenge 2!
Okay, I made it this far...
I-It's really expanding!
--Look for the right time!
--Go when it's deflated!
Deflating...
Inflating...
Now!
That's it!
Brook, Brook, wake up.
Hey, Brook, wake up now.
Oh, no! The snot bubble's coming!
Run!
Did she notice...
Staaare...
It's staring right at me...
Is that...
A stuffed bunny!
That's not gonna work!
Oh, it's just a stuffed bunny.
What? That worked?
Now's your chance, Carrot!
I'll do it this time...
There's still a fly?
What an annoying fly!
--I'm so scared! Really scared!
--I know, I know.
We need to switch again.
How disappointing.
When it comes to this...
I must do it!
Challenge 3!
Brook!
Hey, wake up!
Oh, no! Did I wake her up?
No, she just turned over.
This is my chance.
While her hands are off of Brook...
--Now, Pedro!
--Switch them quickly!
I must do it in an instant.
Switch them as quick as I can
so she won't notice.
Escape spectacularly!
And go back to my friends!
That's our Pedro!
Let me call you Brother Pedro!
Pebro!
Oh, thank you so much, Pedro-san!
Don't mention it.
Okay, I'm imagining it perfectly.
She's rolling over!
Are you okay?
I can't believe I let my guard down!
Did he wake up?!
No.
But that's good for us.
He's out of Big Mom's hands!
Okay, I'll go!
Challenge 4!
Brook, wake up!
Brook!
It's me, Brook!
Ghost!
What is it?
Are you still here?
Oh, no!
You annoying fly!
Heavenly...
...Fire!
Yes!
That... That was close.
Thank you, Jimbei!
The mission succeeded!
Woo-hoo!
This is great! I'm so relieved!
Sanji, I'm almost there.
There you are, Straw Hat Luffy.
Didn't I beat you up right here before?
Dammit! Don't get in my way!
It's not working.
What's wrong with him?
Hey! Stop!
This isn't for you!
I'm sorry. There's somebody
that I really wanna give it to.
Gum-Gum...r
...Gatling!
He hasn't been hurt at all.
Is that all you've got?
You're not that strong.
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
It's my turn now!
You're so persistent.
I have to... wait for Sanji.
I'm not gonna let you go.
Nice try.
But this is it, Straw Hat!
Suffering from never-before-experienced
hunger,
Luffy continues fighting beyond his limit.
Though Sanji hasn't yet figured out
his course of action, he digs through
a heap of rubble searching for Luffy.
The two men never supposed to see each
other again try to reach the fateful spot!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Rendezvous! Luffy, a
One-on-One at His Limit!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!