I don't have to worry about Luffy and the others.
They can flee on their own.
All members of the evil army Vinsmoke will die.
I'll die too.
Just as Big Mom planned.
That's for the best.
That way our enemies get what they want.
It feels short but it was a fulfilling life.
Oh, food!
Are you Vinsmoke Sanji?
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
...starving to death!
It's not for you!
I'll be here waiting!
Straw Hat!
What's wrong with you?
I gotta be there waiting...
I have to stay awake...
Otherwise, I won't even know if Sanji comes.
Where are you, Luffy?!
Luffy!!
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
"A Liar!
Luffy and Sanji!"
Get packing, you low-class pirates!
Sanji...
I've been waiting for you.
You're late.
What's the matter, Sanji?
Get out of my face...
...now!!
I didn't ask you to wait.
I refuse!
You just made a promise
saying whatever you felt like.
You're always like that.
Don't be selfish and force things on others.
But you came.
Eat what you can.
Food...
I dropped it on my way here.
It's been crushed and it got wet in the rain.
It's just another failure, isn't it?
It's good!
Sandwiches and hamburgers!
They're Robin and Franky's favorites!
The best food ever!
Yum!
You put all of our favorites in here!
I want them to have this!
So good!
Yum! Yum!
Don't lie!
Oh, that was so good!
I had almost faded to nothing!
Have you had enough?
Yeah! The food you cook really is the best!
If you're finished, leave.
I'll stay.
What are you saying?!
Come with us!
Don't make me repeat myself!
I'm not going back!
Why?!
First.
I insulted my captain who
came all the way for me,
and did my best to hurt you
even while you didn't fight back.
That's why I can't go back to your ship now.
Second.
That damn geezer who I'm deeply indebted to
and the sea restaurant Baratie
where I grew up...
...have been taken as hostages
in case anything goes wrong.
That's why I can't escape from the wedding.
Third.
My evil biological family has been
trapped by Big Mom.
In a few hours from now,
they'll all be killed.
As long as you don't run away,
everything will turn out for the best, Sanji.
To my biological father,
older brothers and young brother...
I have no obligation.
I have nothing but resent for those scumbags!
You're a failure who deserves to die!
Don't ever admit that I'm your father...
...in front of other people!
It's a shame that I don't
want anyone to know!
But I...
...can't...
...turn my back on them!
For those three reasons,
I can't go back with you guys!
If you understand, get lost.
Say what you really want!
Sanji! I'm hungry!
Just cook something, you fool!
Sanji-kun, what are you gonna make today?
Sanji! I'm gonna catch something big!
You can count on us!
Oh! Thank you.
Who snatched the food?!
I knew it was you guys!
As your punishment, no dinner!
They're so cheerful every day.
I never thought
that I would look forward to mealtimes one day.
Super great food, please, Sanji!
Feed us more, Sanji!
Luffy... I...
I...
I wanna go back to the Sunny!
But I can't get the courage to run away!
Once the wedding begins, I know...
...I can't stop anything by myself!
I don't even consider...
...those scum as my family!
But I...
I wanna save their lives!
Well, that's how you are.
You got us! Let's crash the wedding!
No one's here?!
I'll go tell them to open the gate.
No need.
It'll open soon.
CHARLOTTE KATAKURI
ONE OF THE SWEET 3 GENERALS
(SECOND SON OF CHARLOTTE)
BIG MOM PIRATES
Five hours thirty minutes left
before Big Mom's tea party starts.
Sanji is coming back to the Straw Hats!
Their next objective is to execute a daring
mission to save Sanji's family
from the deadly wedding!
The key to the plan is one
of the most dangerous men
from the Worst Generation, Gang Bege!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sanji Comes Back! Crash!
The Tea Party from Hell!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!