Luffy and Sanji who had parted ways
finally reunited at the rendezvous.
Listen, guys.
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party
and the wedding
and save Sanji's family!
Then, Sanji'll be back with us!
B... Big...
Luffy... She's the Emperor of the Sea!
And then, Jimbei suggested a plan to Luffy.
You know Capone "Gang" Bege, right?
Yeah, he's the one who took Sanji away.
The main event of the tea party is
the wedding.
As you already know, Big Mom intends to
kill all the members of the Vinsmokes at the wedding
and acquire all of Germa.
Bege is going to kill Big Mom!
What?!
What the hell?
Seems like everyone has their own plot!
I feel bad for Pekoms
but under the circumstances,
do you really want to
make an enemy of Bege?
Luffy! Sanji!
Let's join Bege!
What?!
"A Secret Meeting!
Luffy vs. the Fire Tank Pirates!"
But you're right!
What?!
Hey, are you crazy, Luffy?!
You actually like it, Luffy?!
See, I told you!
Luffy, four out of six of us are against it!
Didn't you hear about Bege-san's ill deeds?!
Well, that way, everything'll
work out, right?
You can't make a decision like that...
Actually, I've already made an arrangement.
Do you want to meet him?
Okay, let's see him now!
What?!
Don't worry.
You can say no if it feels off.
Our goal is slightly different from theirs.
Luffy, Sanji. Bege and his clan's base is
in the northwest of the island.
The eight of us will head there first
from this dimension. See you there!
Stop counting us in!
Okay, got it!
FIRE TANK PIRATES' BASE
NORTHWEST WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Did you kill Bobbin?
Yes, he was going after Black-Leg.
FIRE TANK PIRATES
After all, Germa are my heroes.
"PHANTOM GUN" VITO
Are they really coming here?
Father?
"HIT MAN" GOTTI
Jimbei isn't the type of man to joke.
Since we're both standing against Big Mom,
we shouldn't make extra enemies -
he's right about that.
Now it depends on what Straw Hat will say.
If we don't like it...
We'll just kill him!
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
--Soft and fluffy...
--Moist and fluffy...
...life
There's no such thing
A life of torment, the taste of tears
STREUSEN - GOURMET KNIGHT
HEAD CHEF, BIG MOM PIRATES
A pinch of salt
Tears of mortification
A tablespoonful
If that's how it is
at least for your dessert
Don't you want some sweet cake?
Head chef! Head chef!
--Soft and fluffy...
--Moist and fluffy...
EASTERN INLET
No, Pekoms! You still have to rest!
Grr! Has Jimbei really told Mama
about that damn rat Bege?!
Of course!
By now, I'm guessing that the traitor Bege
has been beaten relentlessly by Mama!
Grr! You guess?! Your guess isn't enough!
I gotta make sure to tell her...
Whoa-whoa.
You need to keep resting, Pekoms.
But, Praline,
in case they stop him from telling her... Grr!
If that's your concern,
it's even better for you to leave it to Jimbei!
You'll be beaten again in your condition now.
Just keep quiet!
He's right, Pekoms!
As a ship's doctor, I won't allow you to go!
Don't ever get up!
He's right! He's right!
--Yeah.
--Rest! Rest!
You guys are acting weird.
Gulp!
There was something going on
all through the night in the inlet.
I saw some people carrying things around!
Gulp!
We can't let Pekoms know that
Jimbei is trying to be part of...
...the Big Mom assassination plot.
I appreciate that you saved me
but I gotta go!
No, no, we can't allow that!
What do you mean by that? Grr!
What are you guys hiding?!
GULP!!
Gulp!!
This is it!
FIRE TANK PIRATES' BASE
This is Bege's base!
So, what kind of guy is he?
You heard what Jimbei said.
You coward!
Think of him as a scheming
and brutal mafia boss.
My hero! Vinsmoke Sanji of Germa!
I'm happy to see you again-rero!
It's you...
Hey, where's everyone else?
Are you Bege?
Don't be in such a rush.
They are here or rero.
What do you mean by "rero"?!
Oh, Luffy! Sanji!
Sanji!
You made me worried, you bastard!
I'm sorry for that... Hm?
That aside,
why do you look like that?
Why don't you guys go take a bath too?
Why are you relaxing?! We don't have time!
And you don't even like to bathe!
No, you two must take one too-rero.
And then, we'll talk-rero.
A bath under these circumstances?!
Father doesn't see anyone who is dirty.
Who's dirty?!
What?!
Lola was turned into a warthog zombie?!
And she was chasing around
the guy who she fell in love with!
That sounds like her!
At that time and again
in the forest of monsters,
I don't know what would've happened to me
if it weren't for Lola.
I see! But you guys saved my sister too!
Thank you!
Oh, I'm crying tears of joy.
We have been very close since we were kids.
Because we're twins!
A zombie! I can't imagine a dead person moving.
The sea is like a wonderland!
And so, Lola has turned back to a human.
Yeah. I'm sure she's still
doing well as a pirate.
I wonder if she found someone to marry...
Big Mom sounded so mad when she talked about
Lola running away from a marriage.
Yeah... that was a big deal.
What?
Mama is reviled by all Giants
in the world for a reason.
All Giants in the world?
That's why even though
Totto Land has a diverse population,
there are no Giants.
Giants really exist!
One day,
a man showed up saying he
had fallen in love with Lola
at first sight and wanted to marry her.
And, believe it or not, he was
Loki the prince of Elbaph, the Giants' country!
A prince?! Wow!
Mama became so happy and teary-eyed.
She thought if Lola became
the princess of Elbaph,
her long-standing feud with
the Giants would be resolved
and she'd even get access to their army
which is said to be the world's strongest.
I see...
But she ran away.
After that, everything went wrong.
She tried to use me as a substitute,
but he noticed that I wasn't Lola.
And her relationship with the Giants
got even worse.
Then, she gave up the idea of
becoming friendly with actual Giants
and started investing in research
to turn people into giants.
Her anger towards Lola only amplified
and she was branded a criminal in this country!
If she comes back, she'll get killed!
Furthermore, she couldn't stand looking at me
because I look exactly like Lola...
Get that damn face out of my sight!
Every time I saw her, she hit me without mercy.
So, for years, I always had fresh wounds.
I thought I'd be killed by my own mother!
I can't see that monster
as my mother anymore!
But since Lola is a happy-go-lucky girl,
I guess she'd never imagine
that her mother wants to kill her.
I see... Everything makes sense now.
So when Bege said he was going to kill Mama,
I felt nothing at all.
You might think I'm terrible
but that's the truth.
Well, well, the bath felt so good!
Ah, just like heaven!
No, I refuse to move on to the next life!
Feels like we finished fighting.
I can't get loose. We still have to fight!
Luffy-san, Luffy-san.
I found milk in here!
Hey, don't go into our fridge without asking!
That's exactly what I needed.
My tooth has cracked.
I got my face broken.
Thank you for the milk!
Oh, all healed!
How is that possible?!
Hey, guys.
Have you really washed yourselves-rero?
Yeah, totally!
Let us see Bege already!
Not yet-rero.
Oh, how cute!
Can we wear these?!
How do I look?
You're looking great, Brook!
You look nice too!
Hey, look what I found!
Oh! That's so cool!
Right?
That's the robot from Germa's comic strip.
Why do they have that here?
Maybe, there's a big fan.
I'm gonna go on ahead.
Nami-san!
This is your last chance.
What?
Once you come back with us,
I'll drive you like a horse.
Be prepared!
Nami-san!
Does that mean you'll never let me go?!
You're extremely sexy after a bath too!
I won't forgive you, Chiffon?!
I can't believe you!
How can you help someone
who wants to kill Mama!
Chiffon-sama, please think twice!
You know no one can ever kill Mama!
Big Sis Brulee!
You know what she has done to me, don't you?!
Lola is in danger
and Bege and Pez are my only family!
I don't need anyone else!
Oh, it's okay, it's okay.
Alright! Let's go!
Yeah!
Are you Bege?
No, I'm not!
You?
Do you really think so?!
Then, which one of you is Bege?
Well, wait. He'll be here soon-rero.
Okay, everyone's here, right?
Are you a bit cleaner now?
It's said "Clothes make the man."
I won't do business with anyone
who doesn't care about their appearance.
Now, we have three and a half hours to go.
Let's decide.
First, whether or not we join forces...
The Minister is here! Open the gate!
There's no need.
CHARLOTTE OVEN
MINISTER OF BAKING (FOURTH SON OF CHARLOTTE)
BIG MOM PIRATES
BIG MOM'S TEA PARTY STARTS
IN THREE AND A HALF HOURS
Big Mom's tea party starts
in three and a half hours.
Luffy vs. Bege!
The chaotic meeting finally starts!
There's only one weak point for them
to take down the invincible Big Mom.
What is the secret weapon that holds the key
to fulfill the mission?
An unprecedented pirate alliance is formed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Deadly Pact! Luffy & Bege's Allied Forces!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!