My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Luffy and Sanji who had parted ways
finally reunited at the rendezvous.
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party
and the wedding
and save Sanji's family!
Then, Sanji'll be back with us!
As Luffy announced his plan,
Jimbei suggested he ally with Bege
who is in charge of the tea party's security.
Okay, let's see him now!
Thus, Luffy and his group went down to
the base of Bege's clan - the Fire Tank Pirates.
So, what kind of guy is he?
You heard what Jimbei said.
Think of him as a scheming
and brutal mafia boss.
Alright! Let's go!
Yeah!
"The Deadly Pact!
Luffy & Bege's Allied Forces!"
It's good, isn't it, Luffy?
Why don't you guys restrain yourselves?!
What? These are for us to eat, right?
You guys are nothing but nuisances to us.
Killing all of you right here is
the easiest solution...
You sure about that?
If I die, you'll lose your chance
to kill Big Mom.
Because there'll be no wedding.
If I'm not back there at least two hours
before the wedding, they'll be suspicious.
Yeah, unfortunately, you're right.
So we can kill everyone else except you.
I won't let you kill my friends either.
Don't take us so lightly.
We're not going to make a misstep
like we did in Zou.
We don't have time to intimidate each other.
Luffy, does your gut tell you
that you can team up with them?
What do you think?
You're Caesar, aren't you?!
What?! Caesar?! Where?!
He was there the whole time...
How could you not notice...?
Damn!
I can't make the impossible possible!
No matter how much I try,
I can't make a drug to turn people into giants!
This research is so pointless!
I'm not gonna work anymore!
Go ahead and do as you like with me,
Big Mom!
Caesar Clown!
I-I-I'm working my butt off!
Tell Big Mom so!
There's no need.
What?
When I asked them to let me watch over you,
they agreed without question.
I'm now a trusted Rook!
That's my heart?!
I'll get you out of here
if you help me with your power.
You fool!
Who do you think you're talking to?!
I'm a genius scientist
who can even destroy the world!
I know who you are.
That's why I came.
Damn!
I served Big Mom and now Bege!
I gotta work anyway!
Are you doing your job-rero?
I am! Who do you think I am?!
This is more my cup of tea
than the other one!
The greatest piece of art
will be completed soon!
That's good to know.
The Straw Hats will be here shortly-rero.
What?! Straw Hat?!
Oh, come on!
I don't ever wanna see them again!
When they're around,
everything goes wrong!
Father wants you to attend the meeting too-rero.
Don't be late.
I can't believe it!
I've got no choice!
C-Caesar?
No, I am Bege's sworn brother...
"Gangster" Gastino!
"GANGSTER" GASTINO
--He's not trying hard enough to hide...
--"Gastino"?
Because he's a gas human?
The way he laughs is the same!
Oh, you're not him. Sorry.
No, you are right!
He's obviously Caesar!
What?!
Oh, so it is you!
Why are you here?!
You think I'm here because I wanted to be?!
You idiot!
Because of you fools,
I was handed over to Big Mom
and when I was in a desperate situation,
he threatened me with my heart again!
I've been pushed around!
Tell Trafalgar Law
that I'll kill him when I see him again!
If I get a chance, I'll kill you too!
Cut it out! That's so dull!
That's just a waste of time.
Straw Hat.
Do you wanna join hands or not?
First, let me punch you for shooting Pekoms!
Here I go!
Stop it!
What?!
Pull back your fist, Luffy!
We can't come to an agreement like this!
But he shot my friend!
Someone talks bad about Father,
I can't take!
No, Gotti! Calm down-rero!
Cut it out!
I don't care. Let him do it.
Kick these bastards out!
You back off!
Why?!
I knew this would happen...
Well, it can't be helped...
Do you like Big Mom?
--No way!
That means you're on the same side.
Even if you don't share the same lifestyle or goal,
you have the same enemy to beat!
You can kill each other later,
but if you join hands now
it'll be in everyone's favor!
What's your plan?!
I have the perfect plan.
Let's just do it!
Then, I'll be through with you guys!
The guests have arrived!
They're rulers of the underworld.
Bege.
I have no interest in
the assassination of Big Mom
but is she the kind of person
who can be killed by guns and cannons to begin with?
My impression of her is like an iron balloon.
It feels like it's impossible to kill her.
Yeah, if you call it an assassination,
you have to kill her in one blow.
Otherwise you'll be in a siege and killed.
Is the Emperor of the Sea
as strong as they say?
Of course! She's a monster!
She wasn't even awake when we tried to get Brook back
but I thought we were gonna die!
She is someone who even killed her own son
for sweets.
Despite that, why did you choose
the tea party with all of her Top Officers in attendance,
as the stage of the assassination, Bege-san?
Well, it's no wonder you'd ask that.
First, let me answer...
Under certain conditions,
all we need is five seconds to be able to kill Big Mom!
Only five seconds?!
It's not only five seconds-rero!
It's not that easy to steal five seconds
in the site-rero.
The Big Mom Pirates is made up of
a bunch of skilled fighters and they'll be there.
Within a split second,
people like the Sweet Generals will block us-rero!
Then, it'll become a head-on fight
and we have no chance of winning!
This assassination plot was begun with
the capture of Caesar.
It's Gastino!
Don't ever call me that in front of Big Mom!
Listen!
When we accomplish this mission,
you'll give me back my heart and free me!
That's the agreement!
Don't forget.
If you break your promise,
I'll kill your son at any price!
Stop worrying about that, Gas-hiko!
Bege will keep his word!
Gas-hiko?! No, it's Gastino!
Gas-hiko!
You little...!
Doesn't matter...
Whatever your name is now, you're still a loser.
You see, he has an important job,
which is...
That's right!
Let me show you what I made!
Deadly poison gas - KX Launchers!
One is enough but I made two extras!
Each of them can inject five grams of
deadly organophosphate...
...d-directly into your body!
It's the most audaciously sinful murder weapon
in history!
The gas will destroy average people
by just touching their skin.
So if it's injected directly into your body...
I'm 100 percent sure...
No, 200 percent sure that you'll...
...die!
You're definitely gonna die!
I want everyone to die!
Okay, I get the picture.
So you have a weapon
that will kill her if it hits?
No, unfortunately,
even if this shell hits her
when she's at full strength,
it won't pierce through her hard skin.
There aren't that many weapons
that'll work against Big Mom in this world!
That's right.
My sword...
...was bounced off her body too.
Then it's pointless to have that thing!
You gotta pay attention.
I said it wouldn't work when she's at full strength.
There are two conditions we need
to make the KX Launcher work at its best.
First, we need a setting where
no one can attack us for five seconds.
Second, Mama should be weakening.
What kind of convenient situation is that?
What are you doing?!
There is one place where all those conditions
will be met...
That's the tea party!
Oh, Pez!
I'm sorry! Your daddy-waddy was too loud!
It's okay, it's okay!
It's been more than a year
since we allied with Mummzie-wumzies...
You're still speaking baby talk.
But we've never seen her get hurt.
Even when she destroyed the city...
Even when bullets...
...or bombshells hit her...
Even when she sank a ship...
She didn't get even a single scratch
on her tough body.
She is like an iron balloon
as you said.
But...
...there was one time
I saw Mummzie-wumzie getting a scratch.
You're talking about the incident of
Mother Carmel's picture-rero!
That's right.
At tea parties, they always put a picture
in the seat directly across the table from Mama
and no one will sit there.
It seems like
it's the most important treasure for her.
A picture?
Yes.
It's a portrait of Mother Carmel!
You could say that's Mama's only weak point!
Who is that person?
Seems like Mama is indebted to her
but we don't know the details.
She's a figure of mystery.
Is she dead?
I heard she disappeared.
So she is a missing person.
Even we family members don't know the specifics.
Once at a tea party, a servant accidentally
knocked it off the table...
Mother...
I was stunned by Mama's reaction to it.
She turned pale and
let out a loud shriek that I'd never heard before!
It was different from her Hunger Pangs!
All we could do was just cover our ears
to protect our eardrums...
People were passing out
and collapsing one after another!
On top of the shriek, she exercised
her Haki of the Color of the Supreme King!
Just because of a jostled picture.
The point is what happened next.
Mama knelt down from shock
and, believe it or not,
she scraped her knee
and it was bleeding!
I was surprised because I'd never thought
she had red blood like normal human beings.
When she breaks down like that,
her body becomes fragile.
So, at the tea party today,
if we break that picture in half,
what do you think will happen?!
Mama would be devastated!
And no one there would be able to move
for more than five seconds!
Then the KX Launcher will show
its real strength...
and the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom -
will die!
The news of the assassination of Big Mom
will spread across the world!
But isn't that shriek gonna
make us paralyzed too?!
Don't worry. We have these.
"Invisible Symphonia System"!
Oh, earplugs!
If just breaking a picture would create
such a big mess,
we gotta save Sanji's family
at that moment too!
Hey, don't think it's someone else's problem!
It'll take about three seconds
before Mama'll have the attack after breaking the picture.
If you're surrounded by the angry Big Mom Pirates
before it gets messy,
it'll be miraculous for you
to stay alive for three seconds!
I need you to take that role, Straw Hat!
Wait a minute!
That means Luffy is going to be bait!
Bege! Nami and her friends saved Lola!
How could you ask him to take a deadly role?!
Okay!
I'll do it!
What?!
Big Mom's tea party starts in three hours.
Big Mom, Germa, the bride Pudding!
They each have their own agendas and schemes!
As the clock ticks down to the hellish tea party,
the most important role in the assassination mission of
Big Mom is entrusted to Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy Engages in a Secret Maneuver!
The Wedding Full of Conspiracies Starts Soon!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!