My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Luffy and Sanji who had parted ways
finally reunited at the rendezvous.
We're gonna crash Big Mom's
tea party and the wedding
and save Sanji's family!
Then, Sanji'll be back with us!
And the meeting on the assassination of
the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom, has begun.
It seems like it's the most
important treasure for her.
If we break that picture in half,
what do you think will happen?!
I need you to take that role, Straw Hat!
Okay!
I'll do it!
"Luffy Engages in a Secret Maneuver!
The Wedding Full of Conspiracies Starts Soon!"
Wait a minute!
Do you know how dangerous it is
to break Mama's precious portrait of Mother Carmel?
You need to think twice...
Well, I just came up with an awesome way
to show up at the scene!
A way to show up?
What?! What is it?
Sounds like fun! I wanna hear it!
Me too!
No way. If I tell you now,
it'll ruin the fun.
What?!
--What was I worried for?
Sounds good.
Then, I'll be counting on you.
Yeah!
Now, do you know when to break the picture?
When Sanji kisses Pudding, right?
Idiot, I won't do it! I can't!
What?! You won't kiss her?! Why?!
Didn't you hear what Brook said?
The wedding kiss
will draw everyone's attention.
That's exactly the moment...
...Pudding-san will shoot Sanji-san!
I'll dodge the shot.
So the gunshot is the cue.
Okay! That's easy!
Alright, let's go over the plan.
When Pudding shoots the gun,
Straw Hat breaks the picture!
Big Mom will shriek.
And we'll put the Invisible
Symphonia System on.
Say "earplugs."
Then, it's all downhill from there.
While the people are in a panic,
you guys will rescue Germa.
And with the KX Launcher
and the deadly poison gas shell,
we'll assassinate Big Mom.
Finish everything in 10 seconds tops.
10 seconds?
After that, the longer we stay there,
the more likely are we to die.
So it's a race against time.
Hmph!
That's the first rule of assassinations.
It all depends on Straw Hat.
After he breaks the picture,
there'll be three seconds before Mama starts crying.
Whether or not he can stop the Ministers
who'll come attacking is the key.
Yeah! Count on me!
How do we escape?
As soon as we kill Big Mom,
this dumbass will come in!
Yes, I'll come in!
"Dumbass"?!
--He's such a piece of crap.
--Is this jerk part of the plan?
Shut up!
Listen, since I can fly,
I'll plunge into the site with a mirror to escape!
Along with that woman!
Don't count me in! Mama will kill me!
You guys did a great job
bringing Brulee here.
We couldn't have hoped for a more useful power
to help us escape.
Your compliment doesn't
make me happy, you fool!
You fool!
Once you finish,
dive into Caesar's mirror quickly!
Big Mom will still be shrieking.
And then, we can just run away
in the mirror dimension in comfort.
Think of a mirror that is big enough
for you to come out on your ship.
A big mirror...
Oh, the dresser!
Uh-huh!
The mirror will provide you the quickest way
to escape from the island.
Through the Mirroworld,
we can get to the Sunny in no time.
That's quite a plan.
Yeah, I think it's gonna work well!
No, you have to be careful.
Pedro is right.
If you make even one small mistake,
you'll face death...
That's how dangerous it is.
These bastards...!
Once each of us gets to our own ships,
our alliance is over.
We should just get out of this territory
as fast as we can.
Good luck in battle!
Okay!
I guess we're set.
The party starts at 10, right?
Two and a half hours to go...
I gotta go back to my room
since I'm the groom.
We have to go back too.
Let's get ready for fake security duty.
Hey, Bege. Could you do me a favor?
What is it?
When I show up in a funny way...
Don't try to be funny!
You're gonna die!
Who did this?
--Well...
--Our Bobbin the Disposer...
Who killed him?!
W-We haven't found the killer yet.
We're investigating!
When did he get shot?
Probably, late at night.
The Straw Hats did it?
Straw Hat? No way...
Brother Opera said he burned Straw Hat
and Cat Burglar to death after torturing them.
I don't know about that.
I can't trust him until I see their dead bodies.
I have a report.
Someone saw Sanji-sama heading to
the outskirts of the city late last night.
What? Sanji?!
Straw Hat and Sanji...
If either of them killed Bobbin...
The wedding is out of the question.
IN FRONT OF SANJI'S ROOM
Where's Sanji?
He's in here.
Any visitors?
After we saw him sleeping in his bed last night,
no one entered or left.
Are you sure?
Yes, sir! I am sure!
Hey, Sanji! You there?!
Hey! Are you there?!
Oh? Sanji-san?
Sanji-san?! Where are you?!
O... O... Oh no-nasu...
On top of Sanji-san's disappearance,
if they find out that I was sleeping...
M-Mama will kill me-nasu!
What's wrong?! Aren't you there?!
What should I do-nasu?! What should I do-nasu?!
What should I do-nasu?!
I'm coming in.
How annoying...
What do you want from me this early?
Were you in the room this whole time?
Of course.
Is there anyone who can prove
that you were here?
You ordered a soldier to watch me.
Hey! Eggplant Soldier!
Y-Yes-nasu.
Was Sanji here the whole time?
Are you sure?
Y-Yes-nasu.
Hey, isn't that enough?
I gotta get ready for the wedding.
Not yet.
What?
Straw Hat died.
I see.
But I don't believe it.
Straw Hat is still alive and plotting something
secretly with you, isn't he?
I'm a prince of Germa Kingdom
who will marry Big Mom's daughter today.
I don't care if a low-class pirate plots something
or dies a dog's death.
If my preparation runs late because of you,
Big Mom'll get mad, don't you think?
Let's go.
Good job.
You surprised me-nasu!
Hey, Sanji!
What should I do-nasu?!
Sanji, what are you doing?!
S-Sanji-san?
Shh! Be quiet and do as I say.
It's for your own good too.
Sanji-san,
where have you been until now-nasu?
I told you.
I went out to deliver Pudding-chan food.
Oh, that's right-nasu.
Don't ask what happened after that.
It's not cool.
O-Okay-nasu...
CHEESE TOWN, MILK ISLAND
Today is a holiday because of the Tea Party!
Let's celebrate with Supreme cheese and beer!
So Pudding-sama's old enough to marry now.
The groom is Germa 66's third son.
We'll have a strong ally!
PEANUT TOWN, NUTS ISLAND
The family of the Du Feld
Conglomerate has arrived.
A bunch of celebrities will attend as guests!
Congratulations!
It's a little too early!
CHOCOLAT TOWN, CACAO ISLAND
That's okay! I'm so happy!
Today's Sanji-sama's wedding.
The escort soldiers couldn't
even enter the castle.
Obviously, we can't attend either.
Of course not.
No one needs a guard for a wedding.
Yeah, it should be a peaceful day.
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
Everyone from the Vinsmoke Family,
good morning!
Yonji!
Wake up and change!
SIXTH FLOOR - A GUEST ROOM IN THE BAUM CAKE
What happened to Reiju?
She's not in her room.
Oh yeah,
I haven't seen her since yesterday.
Oh, Reiju-sama finished with her preparations
in another room.
I see.
There is still an hour before the Tea Party
so take your time.
Wh-What happened?!
NINTH FLOOR - BIG MOM'S BEDROOM
Call the Ministers!
I-It's not moving! It's dead!
My lovely skeleton!
That's too bad but, Mama...!
Today, you have the Tea Party
that you've been waiting for...
And what else?
The wedding cake!
Mr. Morgans and all the other VIPs
have already arrived.
EASTERN INLET, WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
You can't do this to me!
Untie me, Grr!
ALADDIN
THE FIRST MATE OF THE SUN PIRATES
We'll leave some water and food.
I'm sorry but I'm sure
someone'll find you soon.
Screw you!
Where are you guys going?! Grr!
--We'll leave this country.
--What?!
That's why you guys were
carrying out your stuff all night long...
Goodbye.
You guys are the Big Mom Pirates' affiliate
and you're leaving the country...
That means you're betraying Mama.
Does she know about this?!
We can't let her know.
She'll kill those who leave.
That's who she is, right?
Jimbei expresses his gratitude to you.
He does?!
We're very lucky to hear Pekoms' story.
I don't think Bege can pull off his plan
to kill Big Mom that easily
but I can't believe Mama is plotting
an assassination of Germa too.
If Luffy and his clan find out about it,
they'll push themselves to save Sanji.
They'll be in danger and I can't just sit back!
I've got to help them!
That means I will raise...
...a full-fledged rebellion.
CHARLOTTE PRALINE
21TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE, MARRIED TO ALADDIN
I will betray Big Mom.
To fufill my duty to her,
I once told her directly that I was leaving.
But I took it back,
because of the numbers
written on the roulette.
Those numbers represent the number of my friends
who would be victimized along with me!
That's why I need you all
to get away from here.
The price that Big Mom wanted me to pay...
...was an unreasonable sanction
that was more than taking my life!
On the day of the Tea Party,
the Hors-d'oeuvre Ships,
interceptors from each island,
will escort the guests
and security will be lax.
And if something happens at the Tea Party,
it'll draw everyone's attention.
So that's your chance to escape!
Alright. We'll take the chance
and break out of Totto Land.
But it's still a deadly venture.
I'm prepared for that.
That's not a problem - but Jimbei,
we just want to help you to become free.
Yes, I know.
No, you don't!
In order to save Straw Hat,
you'll even sacrifice yourself!
Say I join the Straw Hats one day...
I will fight for the captain Straw Hat Luffy
at the price of my life!
Aladdin, it's just a matter of...
...doing it now or later.
I see. Do as you like.
But do your best to save your own life too.
Okay?
We'll set sail for the Fish-Man Island.
If Big Mom finds out that we left her crew,
she may turn her rage on the Fish-Man Island.
You're worried about the Ryugu Kingdom too,
right?
Yes.
We'll save it at any cost!
I'm sorry!
Don't mention it!
We've known each other for decades.
We'll live to see each other again,
Jimbei!
Why would Jimbei feel grateful to me?
By the way, did he tell Mama...
Hurry up and get ready to leave!
Yeah!
Hey, wait! You bastards!
Where've you been, Reiju?
It's none of your business.
I know you guys were partying until late.
Of course, I asked them to change my room.
Don't interfere with adult stuff, idiot.
Let's go.
The Tea Party will take place on the rooftop.
At last,
we proud Germa 66 will have
Big Mom's power on our side
and rule the North Blue again!
You're in a good mood.
But most importantly...
Sanji hasn't run away, has he?
Both the groom and the bride are
fully prepared.
What are you thinking, Sanji?
Why didn't you escape?
You know what's going to happen.
It'll be nice if we can make it out alive
but this is the Emperor of the Sea.
It'll turn into a scene of carnage for sure.
I'm depressed.
What's wrong?
Pre-wedding jitters?
I don't think so!
After I kill that stupid-ass Sanji,
I don't want his blood on me...
...and in order to go back to being a good girl,
I gotta erase everyone's memories.
When I think about all that...
What a pain in the ass!
At the Tea Party, the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom
is plotting to kill
every one of Germa including Sanji.
And at the same Tea Party, Capone "Gang" Bege
is scheming to assassinate Big Mom.
During that commotion,
Sanji is planning to rescue his family.
And the one that holds
the key to everything...
...is Straw Hat Luffy!
Everyone has their own objectives...
...and the hellish Tea Party starts soon!
Leaders of the underground and
a whole new set of Big Mom's
strongest and most terrible children
gather at a gorgeous venue!
When the man with a billion berries bounty?
Sweet General Katakuri's
horrific ability is revealed,
the hellish Tea Party finally starts!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Family Gets Together! The
Hellish Tea Party Starts!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!