My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
Luffy and Sanji who had parted ways
finally reunited at the rendezvous.
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party
and the wedding
and save Sanji's family!
Then, Sanji'll be back with us!
Luffy and his clan allied with Bege
who is plotting to kill the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom.
Everyone has their own objectives
as the Tea Party is finally about to start.
"The Family Gets Together!
The Hellish Tea Party Starts!"
Will I marry that lowlife?!
No way!
At the wedding tomorrow,
you Vinsmokes...
...will all be eliminated!
Sanji-san...
S... S... So...
So cute!!
IN FRONT OF THE TEA PARTY VENUE
Everyone, please line up here!
Let us do a security check before entering.
Oh, here they come!
Congratulations!
You're in our way. Move.
We have to do a search.
Huh?! Who do you think you're talking to?!
I have full authority over
security of today's Tea Party.
This is Big Mom's order.
We'll keep all kinds of weapons here.
He's the real one-rero!
I don't have anything else!
We'll keep your Raid Suits too.
No one's allowed to bring any weapon in.
Raid Suits are no exception.
What happens...
...if we refuse?
Stop!
If that's what Big Mom wants,
we'll go along.
Welcome to Big Mom's Tea Party.
--Start repairing the cake!
--Yes, sir!
This is the venue layout that Bege got.
Big Mom will sit here.
I'm getting nervous.
I wonder if this plan's gonna work out.
Okay! I'm all ready!
Luffy?
Don't worry! Everything's gonna be alright!
I'm going out for a bit.
Going out?! To where?!
Oh, I don't have enough time!
--It's gonna start!
It's time for Mama's Tea Party!
--It's time!
A Porkswagon comes rushing
I wonder if he can make it
--He's late
--He has to hurry
The big guests...
...will come out!
LOAN SHARK KING
"GOD OF FORTUNE" DU FELD
QUEEN OF THE PLEASURE DISTRICT
STUSSY
MAJOR UNDERTAKER
DRUG PECLO
PRESIDENT OF THE WORLD ECONOMIC JOURNAL
"BIG NEWS" MORGANS
WAREHOUSE KINGPIN
GIBERSON "THE HIDER"
SHIPPING KING
"DEEP-SEA CURRENTS" UMIT
Why did you get invited-nen, undertaker?
You're so small-minded
Stop it
Stussy-sama!
Can't an undertaker celebrate
people's weddings?
I won't have anyone who smells so much like blood
talking shit about me, Du Feld!
Hey, I'm so happy to be invited
Morgans-sama!
This marriage will make a headline!
Germa and our company are strongly tied
But it's a story that has already been
spread across the underworld
--So it's too old!
--That's right, that's right
It doesn't need to be transported
Hi there, how are you?
Welcome
Perospero-kun
Leaders of the underworld
If you walk through the castle
you're going to be a little late
Would you like me to... Lick...
...take you there?
Wow!
By the Candy Escalator!
--This is amazing!
--His candy sculptures are always...
...very artistic!
I'm humbled.
Mama hates late arrivals.
So shall we?
Oh, the staircase is moving!
How beautiful!
This is great. Very easy.
See you later.
You can have these.
Wait for three minutes
and you can lick the Candy Escalator too.
Now, I got to go too.
To the hellish...
...Tea Party.
Smells good.
Please come in.
This place always looks delicious-nen.
Welcome, guests.
Hi, Smoothie.
Would you like a welcome drink?
Today, we have a piece of Mt. Mauri Lava,
a beautiful woman who stabbed a thousand men,
and a giraffe that makes funny sounds.
--I'll have a cup of the giraffe.
--Me too.
Okay. I'll squeeze it now.
That's very funny!
Here you go.
Tastes great and it's smooth going down.
Open it!
I refuse your body search!
No, you can't do that, Mr. Jigra.
Let go of me!
I said "Let go of me"!
ORGAN DEALER JIGRA
Is Big Mom already inside?
I got an invitation for
the last Tea Party too.
But for the life of me, I couldn't go.
Because I had my mother's funeral!
I wrote a letter explaining it
but what do you think
Big Mom sent me afterwards?!
It was my hospitalized father's...
Hey! Who shot?! He's a guest!
You are...
ONE OF THE SWEET 3 GENERALS
BIG MOM PIRATES
SECOND SON OF CHARLOTTE
BOUNTY: 1 BILLION 57 MILLION BERRIES
Sweet General Katakuri!
CHARLOTTE KATAKURI
Why did you shoot him?!
This is what he was going to say.
"What do you think
Big Mom sent me afterwards?"
"It was my hospitalized father's head."
"I'm here today to get revenge."
"Open the gate."
Bang.
Bang, he shot.
Two of your men would've been shot.
Is it wrong for me to throw a jelly
bean at him before that happens?
Luke Bege.
Tell Mama that it was my call.
This is what you're gonna say.
"I see."
"Alright then."
He'll be the biggest pain
in the ass at the party.
He has trained his Haki of
the Color of Observation
so much and now he can see
slightly ahead into future.
His bounty is over a billion.
He's a monster!
I see... Alright then.
50...
No, 100 raiders...
...are coming.
What?!
ORGAN DEALING ASSASSIN GROUP
Riddle them with bullets!
That's useless.
That's not working!
I guess Jigra couldn't wait for us.
The organs of the Tea Party guests
and the members of the Big Mom Pirates!
We can sell them high
and make a fortune!
Can I have your liver?
Give us your hearts.
Damn!
Your job is done, guys.
CHARLOTTE OVEN
FOURTH SON OF CHARLOTTE (MINISTER OF BAKING)
CHARLOTTE DAIFUKU
THIRD SON OF CHARLOTTE (MINISTER OF BEANS)
Are you Big Mom's sons?!
Your organs will fetch high prices!
Rip all of their organs out!
You think you caught me like this?!
--The knife melted!
--Run!
They're too strong!
You can't escape.
Wh-What the?!
Know your place, losers.
Th-They're monsters...
Know your place!
Loser!
Meanwhile, Luffy is...
THE SEDUCING WOODS
Wait!
Where did they go?!
And finally, at the Whole Cake Chateau...
It's about time.
It's time for the Tea Party.
Everyone! Thank you for coming all this way!
Wherever you look, all you see is sweets!
Eat!
Drink!
And enjoy the party to your heart's content!
Enjoy everything...
...that'll take place here!
Luffy and Bege finally sneak
into the hellish Tea Party!
The dignified groom Sanji and
the lovely bride Pudding!
Dark plots and strategies
behind their smiles!
While a tense mutual deception gears up,
a bloody wedding begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Broken Couple! Sanji and Pudding Enter!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!