kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Luffy and Sanji who had parted ways
finally reunited at the rendezvous.
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party
and the wedding
and save Sanji's family!
Then, Sanji'll be back with us!
In order to accomplish that,
Luffy allied with Capone "Gang" Bege
who is plotting to kill the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom.
With the Tea Party close at hand,
the guests showed up one after another.
Everyone has their own objectives...
...as the Tea Party finally starts.
Eat!
Drink!
And enjoy the party to your heart's content!
Enjoy everything...
...that'll take place here!
"The Broken Couple!
Sanji and Pudding Enter!"
NINTH FLOOR
A WAITING ROOM FOR THE BRIDE AND GROOM
This is the Tea Party venue.
Everything just started.
The bride and groom
finished their preparations
and they're going through the ceremony
which'll start at 12, one last time.
Everything is going well.
After the exchange of vows,
the groom lifts the bride's veil
and kisses her.
The wedding kiss
will draw everyone's attention.
That's exactly the moment...
Pudding-san will shoot Sanji-san!
Sanji-san?
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing...
I'm just getting nervous...
Me too...
S-So cute!!
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU - ROOFTOP
Hey!
Straw Hat?
We're almost ready.
Okay.
How interesting!
Hey, stay in there!
You can't mess around now!
Go back in!
What is he thinking?!
Oh, I can get out from here too!
What's going on with your body?!
It's so cool!
Don't play with my body!
Don't be so serious!
What are you doing?!
Maybe, I should've killed them...
What now?
Oh my...
Vito, what are you doing?
Father, it's amazing!
The president of the WEJ
and Germa's boss are talking-rero!
Of course, they talk.
They both have ears and a mouth.
Well but it's an extraordinary party-rero!
The eldest son and the Minister
of Candy - Perospero.
The eldest daughter and the Minister of Fruit -
Compote.
The second son - Sweet General Katakuri.
The 14th daughter - Sweet General Smoothie.
The third son - Daifuku
and the fourth son - Oven.
Countless monsters all around.
It was so encouraging to have them
on the same side,
but it freaks me out to think
that we'll make enemies of them all-rero.
Huh? "Enemies"?
If you have time to do that,
go check downstairs.
Okay, Father. Let's go, Gotti.
I heard that the wedding
cake will be very fancy.
I can't wait to see Pudding-sama
in a wedding dress.
Mama.
Here's Mother Carmel.
Yes... Our beloved...
...Mother!
Oh, it's nice to see Mother
smiling brightly as always.
She's like the sun.
That's right.
Mother is the light of this world!
I don't know who she is, though...
This is my first Tea Party
so about this lady...
How are you related to her, Big Mom?
Don't stick your nose...
...into my memory!
Cheers!
How's everything going down there?
The cooks finished preparing for the Tea Party
so they're enjoying a banquet.
We blocked all passages while they're at it.
Good. With those being blocked,
no one can come up for a while.
Now we'll set the Horned Transponder Snails
to jam radio signals
and isolate the venue.
--Don't forget to set up for you-know-what too.
--Yes, sir.
All there is left to do is set up for it.
What we need is in that room.
Hey!
What are you guys doing there?
Well, we're out of booze
so we came to get some...
Oh, you guys ran dry too?!
It's this way.
But you guys don't look familiar.
What's wrong-rero?
Oh, sirs!
Thank you for making the rounds!
Is there something wrong-rero?
Well, there are two unfamiliar guys.
Maybe, they're invaders.
Just to be safe, this needs to be taken care of,
right, Gotti?
Yeah.
You were unlucky-rero.
We brought you a present, a combined gift for you
and your daughter-nen, Charlotte.
Oh, that's a treasure box!
My favorite!
I wonder what's in it.
I brought you a present too, Linlin.
Take one from me too!
Mine's something rare from the south.
Uh-huh! I went to the farthest north.
I'm so grateful!
For always getting so many presents like this!
Thank you!
I'm so happy!
Speaking of treasure box, Mamigo,
I heard you've landed a
great undersea treasure.
Oh?
You have quick ears.
That's my Morgans.
And it's true.
The treasure box that'd been passed down
for generations among the undersea royalty!
For some reason, Neptune let go of
his hold on it and it's here now.
This is the legendary...
...Tamate Box!
Oh! Look how stately it is!
What's in it?
Have you opened it, Mamigo?!
At the huge feast after Pudding's wedding,
I'll open this along with everyone's presents,
and show it to you all!
I can't wait!
I'm thrilled to see such a precious moment!
I've been waiting for this day too!
Father!
Oh, are you finished?
All the preparations are done-rero.
Okay. Good job.
Guys, go get changed.
Yes, sir.
Caesar, bring out the mirror.
You jerk! You called me that again!
So this is the entrance to the Tea Party.
Enjoy it as much as you can,
losers of the world!
Caesar Clown?
You're a loser too.
Just hide that mirror somewhere around here.
Shut up! I know!
When Big Mom starts shrieking,
bring that mirror and burst into the hall.
That's your job.
That's our only escape route.
Be sure not to get any ideas.
It's too late for me to betray you!
Oh, no!
Bege and his people are up to something!
I pared it off.
Information leaks will
bring unexpected crisis.
It's 30 minutes to the wedding.
Are Straw Hat and the others ready?
I hope he's not playing around like a fool again...
Check for yourself!
They're in your body!
Hey, you fools! Why're you sleeping?!
You should be getting ready!
Let them sleep.
It seems like they haven't slept much
since they arrived.
I'll wake them up 10 minutes before.
I can't believe this.
I'll ditch them
as soon as they get in my way.
No problem.
I'm watching out
and getting ready for them.
Those idiots... How ridiculous.
I know!
You need to go back inside.
I'm gonna get into the hall.
Everyone, prepare yourselves!
Once we enter,
there's no turning back!
I hope you're ready too...
Vinsmoke Sanji!
No! No!
She is very cute but don't be fooled!
I...
I wasn't planning on getting married
when I came here so...
It's really strange to me to sit side-by-side
with you like this now...
I feel like I'm dreaming...
Stay cool, stay cool.
I'm not gonna get fooled again.
Is it...
...a good dream or a bad dream?
Oh man, she's so cute!
Of... o-o-of course, it's a good dream!
Really?! That's good!
Hey, calm down!
She's just acting!
She's planning to kill me!
Oh?
Maybe, I was really just dreaming...
No, no, no! Don't get screwed!
Believe what you saw!
Sanji-san, is there something wrong?
What? N-No, no, no, no! It's just...
Oh, yeah!
A-About the wedding kiss... Um...
In case you have a problem...
doing it for the first time in front of the people...
I-I-I don't mind kissing
you on the forehead or...
Kiss me on the mouth.
We're gonna become husband and wife.
What was that?!
Sanji-sama crashed into the ceiling?!
How did he end up like that?
He's bleeding so much!
Oh, no!
Sanji-san!
What's wrong with this damn dirty water imp?!
I wanna blow him away already!
You don't look happy.
No, I am happy...
Let's have fun.
It's a big day for our dear brother and sister.
Yes...
Everything is okay, right?
Yeah... There is nothing wrong.
That's good.
Today is more special than any other day.
Don't drop your guard. Lick.
I know.
I'm glad that you seem like you're
having a good time, Judge.
Of course, I am!
This is the best day of my life!
It is for me too!
Because we're gonna become family soon!
To the North Blue's... No...
To the soon-to-be world's strongest family...
Cheers!
Bang.
Yes?
It's almost time.
Please proceed to the venue.
Sanji-san, are you ready?
Yeah.
Shall we?
The time has finally come...
I'm nervous but excited too!
Me too.
I'm really...
...really excited.
It's twelve o'clock! It's twelve o'clock!
Okay, ladies and gentlemen!
It's today's main event!
The 35th daughter of Charlotte -
Charlotte Pudding-sama and...
...the third son of Vinsmoke -
Vinsmoke Sanji-sama's...
...royal wedding...
...starts now!
Marriage!
--Marriage!
How awesome!
Without further ado,
here are the bride and groom!
Wow!
The Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom Pirates!
And the evil army - Germa 66!
The young couple will connect
their notorious families' paths to their dreams!
Mariage de Raison!
With the two tying the knot, another flower
of evil will bloom out madly in this world!
Give it up for them!
Look at that!
For this extremely beautiful day!
Give it up!
That fool!
What a great actor he is!
The bloody wedding now begins!
At an altar on a stately wedding cake,
a vow of love has been made!
Puddingfs heart wavers and
tears fall down her cheek!
When their romantic wedding kiss triggers
all the plots to be carried out,
Luffy finally makes an appearance
at the stormy Tea Party!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Deadly Kiss!
The Mission to Assassinate the Emperor Kicks Off!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!