kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
Luffy and Sanji who had parted ways
finally reunited at the rendezvous.
I...
I wanna go back to the Sunny!
Listen, guys.
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party
and the wedding
and save Sanji's family!
Then, Sanji'll be back with us!
To accomplish that, Luffy
allied with Capone "Gang" Bege
who is plotting to kill the
Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom.
Everyone has their own objectives
and the Tea Party has finally started.
Mama.
Here's Mother Carmel.
Yes... Our beloved...
...Mother!
And then...
Okay, ladies and gentlemen!
It's today's main event!
The 35th daughter of Charlotte -
Charlotte Pudding-sama and...
...the third son of Vinsmoke -
Vinsmoke Sanji-sama's...
...royal wedding...
...starts now!
Give it up!
That fool!
What a great actor he is!
The bloody wedding now begins!
"A Deadly Kiss!
The Mission to Assassinate the Emperor Kicks Off!"
Wake up!
Luffy!
The ceremony has begun! Luffy!
I can eat more...
Wake up!
Do you wanna let Sanji down?!
Hey! Is there any way to wake him up?!
He was running around the forest
right before he fell asleep so...
Food is the only thing that'll wake him up.
Hey, do you have any meat?!
We don't have time!
--Meat?
--He's gonna have breakfast now?
--Hurry up!
--Okay!
This is your requiem!
Just listen to it with that
stupid look on your face, Sanji!
Sanji-san, thank you!
Sanji-san, I'm...
...so happy!
P... P-P-P-P-Pudding-chan...
Me... Me too!
No! No! Stay rational!
If you don't pay attention, you...
You... you... you'll...
You'll get killed!
Marriage
Marriage!
Tough love...
I've been in...
Bitter love...
Fell in love, fell in deep, got hurt...
And I've reached the aisle
Even if rain falls down on me
Even if spears rain down on me
Don't ever let that hand go
--Head chef!
Here comes the congratulatory...
Wedding cake!
Bravo!
Beautiful! Brilliant!
How gigantic! And stately!
Looks delicious!
It's a magnificent wedding cake!
You did a wonderful job, Streusen!
I have to give you praise!
It's more than I deserve!
I can't wait to eat it!
It's amazing! The sweet cake will be the altar
where we make our vows!
No, you're amazing!
Oh, stop! Come on, Sanji-san!
Just drop dead already!
Pudding-chan looks beautiful...
Feels like watching my old self.
How many decades ago was it-nen?
I guess someone wants to die.
Ouch-nen!
Have fun, my guests.
The climax will come soon...
It'll be over before you know...
Please. Enjoy the wedding
from these VIP seats.
It's about to start!
The bloodbath!
In a few minutes...
At the moment of the wedding kiss...
The bloody banquet will begin...
I'm sorry! But I need you to go away,
Vinsmokes!
Sanji's lucky!
If I'd known she was that pretty,
I wouldn't have minded marrying her.
With Big Mom's daughter? No way.
He's a sacrifice. Don't forget.
Once you're married,
you'll be under Big Mom's control for all your life.
You're right.
That's the last thing I want.
I see... We're surrounded by
the siblings of Charlotte,
and quite easy targets.
And we're unarmed
so we're basically sitting ducks.
That's how it should be...
Germa is an irrelevant kingdom now.
But...
Sanji...
I want you to get away.
You have a plan, right?
Can I trust you?
Luffy-kun!
It's time.
Meat...
Meat!
How easy.
Luffy, the gunshot cue to start the mission
will be any minute!
Yeah, let me finish this first!
I can't wait anymore!
Whoa, hey! Not yet!
In sickness and in health,
for richer for poorer,
to have and to hold,
till death do us part...
Hurry up, guys! We don't have time!
You can't tell us that!
Do you plight yourself to love
and to be loyal to each other?
My wish is finally gonna come true!
What's wrong, Pudding?
Why are you collapsing?!
Now you may lift her veil and kiss her.
Something wrong, brother?
You saw the future, Katakuri!
I'll lift your veil.
Okay.
Take a good look, Sanji...
At...
At my creepy...
...third eye!
Good boy.
Stay like that...
What a beautiful eye!
What?
I'm sorry! When I saw it up close,
I couldn't take my eyes off...
What is she doing?!
Don't hesitate, Pudding!
Pudding... chan?
What is he saying?
Appearing there is the groom Sanji and...
...he sees your third eye for the first time!
The moment he sees his beautiful bride's
creepy real face,
he'll fall back a little!
Screw him!
What is he thinking?!
Since I was born, I've never been told...!
Not a single person has ever told me
that this eye's beautiful!
What's wrong, Pudding?!
Just shoot him!
No one's ever...
You're my daughter but that creeps me out...
Grow out your bangs, Pudding.
Yes... I understand, ma'am...
She's a monster!
So creepy!
What's wrong with this kid?!
Look! She's a freak!
Don't do it!
How's that, freak?!
Freak! Freak!
Freak!
Go away, freak!
--You're sick! Stay away from me!
--No... I'm not...
--Freak!
--I'm not a... freak!
I'm not... I'm not...
I'm not... I'm not... I'm not...
I'm not... I'm not!
I'm not!!
I'm not!
I'm not...
I'm not gonna shut up as you make fun of me!
You stupid sons of bitches...
I'll wipe you all out!
Run!
Pudding-chan...
Screw you...
Screw you!
I'm gonna kill you!
I'm an ugly freak!
Hey, did you forget the plan, Pudding?!
Pudding-chan, are you okay?
You do it! Priest!
That's no use! He'll dodge!
He dodged!
Straw Hat! Go now!
That's the gunshot, Luffy!
Great! I can make it!
What was that gunshot?!
The priest fired!
No, he got shot!
Why?!
What's going on?!
Is this--?!
What the hell is going on?!
Katakuri, what happened to Pudding?!
We have a bigger problem!
It's an unanticipated situation, Mama!
Not even I can do anything!
What should we do?!
Sanji hasn't been shot!
Is the plan still on?
Let's go!
I'm sorry, Mama!
I had no choice but to do what they told me to!
We'll take Sanji back!
What the--?!
I can't stop them!
They'll come out of there!
What?!
Big Mom!!
Whaaat?!
The hellish Tea Party is in chaos!
The dutiful boss "First Son of the
Sea" Jimbei finally takes action!
To fulfill his duty, he brings out a sake cup
which represents the bond
between mother and son!
In order to join Luffy's crew,
he engages in a fierce clash
against the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Returning the Sake Cup! The
Manly Jimbei Pays His Debt!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!