My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Sanji and Pudding's bloodbath wedding
finally began.
To assassinate Big Mom, a plan was hatched
in which Luffy shatters the
portrait Big Mom holds dear
after which Bege delivers a final blow.
What a beautiful eye!
Being moved by Sanji's unexpected kindness,
Pudding couldn't shoot him...
And with the gunshot cue,
Luffy and the others' plan has been put into action.
We'll take Sanji back!
I can't stop them!
They'll come out of there!
Big Mom!!
Whaaat?!
"Returning the Sake Cup!
The Manly Jimbei Pays His Debt!"
It's on now...
ABOUT THREE AND A HALF HOURS AGO
BEGE'S BASE
A mirror inside the wedding cake?
Yeah!
If you can put a mirror inside of it for me,
I can jump out of the mirror
dimension like "Wham"!
Then it's gonna be sweet and fun!
It doesn't need to be sweet or fun!
Don't make me repeat myself!
Your job is...
I know!
You want me to break the picture, right?
But I wanna get out there
in a funny way when I do it!
Don't be silly!
Are you thinking of
breaking the wedding cake?
You guys don't know how much
Mama is looking forward to it...
You made copies of Nami and
the others in the woods.
Yeah!
She can make copies of someone by reflecting
them in a mirror and projecting
them on other animals!
So what?!
I caught them...
Turn them all into me.
What?!
AT PRESENT - THE WEDDING PARTY VENUE
P-People are coming out of the cake!
Oh my! I can't believe it!
It's another flashy bit-nen...
No, that's not it, Du Feld.
This is big news!
He's a pirate from the Worst Generation!
Straw Hat Luffy!
The unimaginable is happening!
Why is he here?
Are they all Straw Hats?
Why are there so many of them?
Run! The cake is collapsing!
What are they?!
Straw Hat Luffy?!
That bastard!
D-Don't tell me he came
to take back the groom!
Pudding-chan, pull yourself together!
It finally started...
The crucial moment is coming.
The photo frame is...
There!
Go get it, Luffy!
What's going on, Montd'Or?!
I thought that Straw Hat Luffy and the other one
died in the Prison Library!
Dammit!
Opera, that dumbass...
I knew he was lying!
How dare he try to save his own skin!
My...
...precious...
...cake is...
The cake is...
What the...?!
She's acting weird...
Oh... I was looking forward to it...
Mama, please keep your composure!
I know how you're feeling.
Cake!
Head chef! Please get away from here!
Mama is acting strange!
Bring me a new cake...
Th-That's impossible...
Life...
...or...
...wedding cake?!
G-Guys...
It's the Soul Pocus!
Their lifespans will be taken!
This is quite a scoop!
Big Mom can tap into
everyone's obsession with staying alive!
If you fear death even a little bit...
Look! There it is!
H... H-Help!
No!
Everyone who ruins my pleasure...
I'll take your lifespan!
MIRROWORLD
Go! Go!
Okay, that way!
The voice we just heard...
I guess Big Mom is throwing a fit outside!
We're kind of desperate too.
The venue is getting messier than we thought.
Mama! I'm really sorry!
Whoa...
Stay at the mirror.
I'll make you pay for this!
Have you released them all?
This Luffy is the last!
All right! Let's go, Pedro!
Yeah! To back Luffy up!
We gotta go too! To back Sanji-kun up!
Are you ready?
Yes, I have my earplugs!
We'll rescue Sanji's family!
Okay, we'll leave the rest to you, loser.
Is he that bad?
He's the worst!
Once I get my heart back,
I'll teach them a lesson...
That bastard, Straw Hat...
He can't mess with me!
You asshole!
Which one is the real Straw Hat?!
Monkey D. Luffy...
I know your name now.
Come! To the New World!
What a boring story...
You haven't become...
the King of the Pirates.
I'm gonna pick a fight with you again!
Just because you're the Emperor,
don't be cocky!
I'll win Sanji back!
We're the ones... who'll have the last laugh!
The cake has... collapsed...
Dammit...
How dare he ruin the wedding cake!
Which one is the real Straw Hat Luffy?!
Where is he?!
Is she dumb?
It's just a diversion strategy.
Show yourself! Straw Hat!
Does she think that he'll respond?
I mean, if he responds...
I'm here!
He... He responded!
There you are, Straw Hat...
I'll destroy you!
That's the photo frame!
Vito... Gotti...
Is the Launcher ready?
Yes, we can jump out anytime,
Father.
Straw Hat... Do your best.
No, let go of me!
They're coming in hoards!
Come on!
That must be the real Luffy.
Once Luffy breaks the picture,
we'll burst in after three seconds...
Uh-huh...
Are you listening? Be serious!
Zeus!
Hey, Mama!
Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
I'll beat them all at once!
Alright!
It's easy!
Take this!
He can do it!
Gum-Gum...
What?!
This is the real one!
The other Straw Hats are...
...the animals of the island,
that were transformed by Brulee's ability.
Don't pay them any mind!
I see! So they used Brulee's ability!
Damn...
What the hell is this?!
My limbs are buried and I can't pull them out!
What kind of ability is this?!
Katakuri! Are you trying to help me?
You're my son - you can't do...
No, Mama!
He was going after...
...Mother Carmel's portrait.
How do you know its importance to us?
I thought only people close to us knew.
Spit it out! Who told you?
Shut up!
Let go of me, you fool!
Damn... The mission is suspended.
Somebody! Just break the picture!
Luffy!
Damn.
Leave it to me, Pedro!
Ocean Current...
...Shoulder Throw!
Run!
You don't need to explain about me...
That was close...
Katakuri ate a special kind of
the Paramethia-type...
...Mochi-Mochi Fruit.
Jimbei!
You can get away from it with liquid
but you better not touch it in the first place.
Jimbei?
I'm the one who told Luffy
about Mother Carmel.
Since I'm your ally,
I hear those talks.
Those idiots!
How dare they interfere...
They came this far to take back Sanji!
The wedding has been ruined...
I thought that silly Straw Hat was dead...
Don't worry, members of Vinsmoke.
We Charlotte will handle this...
Lick!
You...
I thought you gave up leaving my crew...
But you defended the guy
who broke the cake...
I take it as complete mutiny,
is that okay with you?
Jimbei?
Yes, I'm absolutely okay with that.
You have some nerve...
I want to leave your crew and...
...join the Straw Hats!
What?!
This'll make a headline!
The former Warlord Jimbei joins
the Straw Hats!
Well, okay...
Do as you like after leaving.
But I need you to pay the price
for leaving.
You don't wanna live your life in shame,
do you?
Right...
If you promise that
you won't hurt anyone else,
I'm happy to give you my lifespan -
as much as you can take!
Hey, what are you talking about, Jimbei?!
You can't join my crew if you die!
I love to take people's lifespans!
I see...
That's how much you don't like me.
You'd rather die than
stay where you don't want to be...
I won't feel sorry for you!
Oh... Here we go again!
The Soul Pocus!
All right! You got yourself a deal...
You fool...
Stay...
...or...
...life?
Life!
Mama...
It... can't be stopped now...
Is Jimbei gonna die here...?
Go to hell...
Stay or...
...life!
H-His soul isn't coming out of his body!
This can't be true...
He's not even a bit afraid of Mama!
Of course not...
I'm a man who wants to be
part of the future Pirate King's crew...
I can't be intimidated by
a mere Emperor of the Sea!
Mama... can't take his lifespan?
If you won't take my lifespan...
I'm returning the sake cup.
Now, I'm leaving the Big Mom Pirates!
Thank you for all your troubles!
I can't believe he's doing it now...
How cool... Jimbei...
Yay!
Congratulations, Jimbei...
That means you're my enemy now, right?
Jimbei!
Go to hell!
The portrait of Mother Carmel has been broken!
But after the moment of joy,
the Big Mom Pirates' supernatural powers are
brought down on Luffy and the others
and when a fierce battle breaks out,
an unexpected crisis falls on Sanji and Judge!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Mission Failed?! The Big Mom Pirates Strike Back!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!