My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
Sanji and Pudding's bloodbath wedding
finally began.
Luffy and the others successfully broke
the portrait of Mother Carmel,
but their objective - Big Mom's shriek -
hasn't come yet.
However, the assassination plot of the Vinsmokes
has already been put into action.
Oh, boy.
I've never seen such a pathetic assassination as this!
This is more like just
violence instead. Lick.
Don't you think so, Judge?
I have... devoted my whole life...
My everything...!
Towards getting revenge on the countries
in the North Blue!
To restore the Germa Empire!
Big Mom!
Say something, Big Mom!!
Look at yourself!
Tell me...
it's not true!
It's no use. Look at her.
--Mother... Cake...
--She's confused by a series of shocking events.
It made me a little nervous when the portrait of
Mother Carmel was broken,
but the intensity of her anger pushed her
over the edge of sanity so we were okay.
Alright! If I show this to Big Mom again,
things are gonna go as we planned, right?
S... traw... Ha... t...
You can only see slightly ahead into future.
But even if we can't see it,
we all have the right...
...to change the future!
"Run, Sanji!
SOS! Germa 66!"
Get out of my way!
Don't get in my way!
They're coming one after the other...
Get out of my way!
I don't want them to see my face!
If they do, they'll kill me!
Shut up!
They already know it's you.
Those guys are wreaking
havoc using your ability!
Okay! This mirror is the linchpin
for the allied forces to get out.
Once I fulfill this task,
I'll get my heart back.
And when I get there,
I'll teach all of them a lesson!
How's everything going inside?
I'm not hearing her shriek yet...
How's Big Mom?
Just as we planned...
The cake has been destroyed
and the herd of Straw Hats is going crazy...
The portrait of Mother Carmel
has been broken too...
So then, why isn't Big Mom shrieking?!
What's going on?!
Luffy-san, listen to me!
Big Mom's had too many shocks
in quick succession,
so she doesn't know
how to focus her anger.
Okay! I'll do it if you say so!
Leave it to me!
Stop Straw Hat!
Don't let him get close to Mama!
Why are you getting in my way?!
Bege!
Bege, you bastard...
Go to hell, Katakuri!
Bege?!
What are you doing, Gang Bege?!
I knew you'd betray us, Bege...
I don't have time to fight them all!
It's not working!
I won't let you do it!
Ouch!
What the...?!
You can't have it!
I won't let you take it!
Soul...
What?!
...Solid!
I got it back.
Brook!
Cold air...
Let me handle this man, Luffy-san!
Yeah! Thank you!
You can't get away...
How annoying...
Come and fight me!
I'll burn you up!
That's awful.
But I don't have any flesh to burn!
Along with that chattering mouth,
I'll burn you to the marrow of your bones!
You have a good sense of humor.
How useless...
Brother Peros!
Shoot them up already!
I know.
Boy... The man who sees the future
wants everything fast.
But for this occasion,
I can see the future too.
Being bound in my candy,
you guys will die with pitiful faces!
That's the only future I see!
If we'd at least had the Raid Suits,
we wouldn't have let you do as you like!
Raid?
What is it? Is it some kind of weapon?
Lick.
Whoa-whoa, why would you want to bring
such a thing for your son's wedding?!
Run, Reiju!
It's you again!
Don't get in my way!
Sanji...
What is he doing?
He's making a fuss...
Sanji...
I underestimated your kindness.
We're good-for-nothings
but you still won't abandon us.
I've always hated being a Vinsmoke
and been ashamed of it.
But...
...when I saw you as a grown man...
Run!
I felt relieved!
Because I noticed there was still conscience
in our family's blood...
Thank you, Sanji!
What a touching camaraderie. Lick.
But it's over now.
Now, it's fun time!
Run!
Oh, no! Sanji's family is...
Where's Luffy?
Hurry up, Luffy...
You bastard!
Pedro!
Don't touch it, Luffy! Go!
Thanks!
Five Thousand Brick...
...Fist!
Bege!
Go to hell, Katakuri!
Oh no, you don't!
Mama...
Mama... No!
M...
Mother...
Mother!
Mama!
All right!
Now, take care of the rest by yourselves.
Well, I guess they can't hear me.
Mama got injured?!
She's become weak!
Hey! Somebody, stop Bege and the others!
Bege!
How dare you betray us!
Goodbye, Big Mom!
Mother...
Please... listen to me, Mother...
No one...
...listens to what I say.
Hey, Mother...
Where did you go?
Why did you disappear all of a sudden?
The secret of the Emperor
of the Sea, Big Mom's birth
and the fateful encounter with
her only weakness, Mother Carmel.
Taking place on the legendary
island of the Giants,
the world's strongest girl Charlotte
Linlin's sweet and grim,
old and secret story is revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Mom's Secret! The Giant's Island
Elbaph and a Little Monster!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!