My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
At the hellish Tea Party,
Big Mom finally shrieked.
And her past has been revealed.
Semla!!
How dare you...
Linlin!
Linlin destroyed the village of Elbaph!!
Mother Carmel saved Linlin who was on a rampage...
Please forgive her!
But Carmel had a different, secret side.
I've been trafficking kids for 50 years.
She's the greatest product we've ever had!
And on Linlin's birthday, it happened.
Happy Birthday, Linlin!
Thank you, everyone!
We piled up your favorite sweet, Semla,
and made this Croquembouche!
I hope it's good!
Eat as much as you want!
Uh-huh! Thank you!
It's so delicious!
What?
Everyone?
Mother?
Where did you go?
Hmm? Huh?
"The Launcher Blasts!
The Moment of Big Mom's Assassination!"
Mama!
63 years ago, Mother Carmel and the other children
went missing.
There were two people who witnessed the whole thing
which even Big Mom herself didn't know.
Where did you go?
One of them was a warrior from Elbaph,
who came down to see if the House of Lambs was okay.
M-Monster!
He turned pale and started running,
and never came back to this island again.
Eventually, all the Giants in Elbaph
and the other places got to know the story
and Charlotte Linlin has been even more hated
by the Giants...
...to the extent that
no one wants to utter her name.
Where did you go?! Mother! Everyone!
And the other witness...
...was a cook who used to be a pirate
and was living on the island she was left on, named Streusen.
He was amused by it.
He had an ability...
...to turn any object into food,
which was the Cook-Cook Fruit power.
I've never seen a monster like that.
Don't leave me alone...
If I let her be alone, she'd die.
That's a waste.
Where did you go, Mother?
Hey, what's the matter, little girl?
If you just keep crying,
you'll only get hungrier.
Say, little girl,
do you wanna talk about your dreams or something?
Who are you, old man?
Hey, don't come too close.
Hey, old man, have you seen Mother?
Don't you know where everyone's gone?
I don't know...
But I bet they'll come back soon.
You think so?
Yeah, I'll stay with you until then.
I'm good at cooking.
If it's just you, I can provide enough food.
I'm hungry...
Count on me!
See?
These two who met at the time
will be the co-founders of the Big Mom Pirates.
Linlin!
Come to your senses! They'll shoot you!
So, at the tea party today,
if we break that picture in half,
what do you think will happen?!
Mama would be devastated!
And no one there would be able to move
for more than five seconds!
Then the KX Launcher will show
its real strength...
and the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom -
will die!
You're doomed, Big Mom!
Mama!
Mother.
Everyone gets in my way.
True happiness for people is to be equal.
But to find a country like that in the world today
is nearly impossible.
So let's make this place our country!
A country where everyone will look at things
in the same way!
Country?!
Yes, a country without racism or
anything of that sort
and everyone will look at things
in the same way!
In the same way! That's nice!
Everyone should get bigger!
Wow! How cool!
That's a beautiful dream, Mother!
Linlin!
Everyone, let's work hard together!
I'll do it!
--Me too!
Yeah!
Let's make this place a dreamland!
I'll do my best too, Mother!
You're a good girl, Linlin.
I am!
If there are a lot of countries like that,
the world will be more peaceful.
Everyone can become happy.
Mother's dream was my dream!
Peace? Is that your dream, Linlin?
It is! I'll build a country
that Mother would like!
Why don't you stop crying already?
Hey, hey, hey! I wanna see Mother's magic!
Magic?
Yeah, she was good at doing magic tricks.
I think she put out her hands like this...
Then...
Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
What?! The magic trick that Mother used to do!
Why?!
I could do it too!
Flower, flower! Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
Earth!
--Earth!
--Flower, flower!
What the...
Is that a Devil Fruit power?
--Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
--Tree! Tree!
Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
Flower! Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
Wow! I could do it too, Mother!
When she returns,
I'm gonna show it to her!
--Tree!
--Flower! Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
What an amazing power!
She's the real deal.
Thank you, Linlin!
Let's sing together
How interesting! Alright, I decided!
I'm gonna set out to sea with her!
--Nice! Nice!
--A country where...
...everyone grows big
and looks at things in the same way and is equal.
Alright, Linlin. Let's build the dreamland!
Count me in!
Uh-huh!
The appointed time is long past.
I hope she didn't run away with the kids!
That damn Carmel!
If she did such a thing,
she'll be in trouble with Cipher Pol.
Stop, you guys!
What's wrong?
I just heard a voice from somewhere...
What?
I see nobody.
But I'm sure I heard...
--Flower, flower!
--What?
Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
Flower, flower!
What... What is that?
Flower, flower! Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
What?!
The flowers are singing?!
Tree, tree, tree!
Let's play, let's play!
Let's play!
Wh-What's going on with this forest?!
Let's play, let's play!
Stay away!
Stop!
How could you do that?!
What?
Y-Y-You're Charlotte Linlin, aren't you?
We're here to pick you up.
Pick me up?
That's right. Now, come over here.
--No!
--What?
You're all bad people!
Wh-What... What?!
It hurts! So sad! It really hurts!
See? The flowers say, "It hurts"!
Say sorry!
Be careful!
Don't think she's just a kid!
Eventually, the two took to sea
and showed what they were capable of,
and became infamous.
Hey, look at this wanted poster!
A 50 million berry bounty for a kid?!
How is that possible?
A castle fell at the hands of a girl?!
The mastermind is Charlotte Linlin!
Cipher Pol reported that she's a security risk!
She'll become a powerful villain one day!
Catch her at any cost!
Yeah!
Tarte tropezienne!
Kouglof au chocolat!
Madeleine! Brioche!
And the colorful tower of macarons!
So delicious!
There she is!
Watch out, Linlin.
I'm eating sweets!
Don't interrupt!
Charlotte Linlin continued wreaking havoc
and became a threat to the world overnight.
She's a pirate!
Run!
Nice, Linlin.
Why don't you become
the king of the sea like this?
That'll be more fun!
Bring me sweets!
Your Majesty!
Oh, no!
If you do, I'll guarantee you a peaceful dreamland!
If you all just listen to me,
I know you'll be happy!
Those who don't listen are selfish
so I've got to kill them!
Mother, I miss you...
I miss you!
Mother!
I'll make everyone big one day!
Then, let's sit around the table together again!
But there are still people
who don't listen to me!
I'm so sad and I can't stop crying!
Because the one-and-only portrait of Mother...
You're a good girl.
The one-and-only portrait of Mother
that was precious to me...
...got broken by them!
I won't forgive...
The Straw Hats!
I won't forgive them!!
The mission failed!
What?!
They failed!
Listen, since I can fly,
I'll plunge into the site with a mirror to escape!
Once you finish,
dive into Caesar's mirror quickly!
Unfortunately, it's time to do my job!
Dammit!
I can't believe the launchers that I made were destroyed!
That monster old bag! After all, she's the Emperor of the Sea!
Retreat, everyone!
Dive into the mirror!
What unbelievable wind pressure!
Oh, no! We're on the rooftop!
We have nowhere else to go!
We have no chance of winning, either!!
Luffy and the others get caught by
the formidable Big Mom Pirates.
That's when those five finally
unite their strength and stand up!
Germa 66, the group of modified humans that terrorized the world,
shows their true power!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Evil Army! Transform! Germa 66!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!