My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
At the hellish Tea Party,
Big Mom finally started shrieking.
During that confusion,
Sanji saved the members of the Vinsmoke Family
and Bege fired the deadly poison KX Launcher
at Big Mom. However...
The mission failed!
Oh, no! We're on the rooftop!
We have nowhere else to go!
We have no chance of winning, either!!
"The Evil Army!
Transform! Germa 66!"
Full-Scale Rook!
What?!
The Big Father!
Oh, cool!
What the hell is that?!
Open the gate!
Allies!
Let's take shelter in the castle for now!
All right, hurry up!
Yeah, I wanna go in!
Firetank Pirates! Cover them!
--Rero!
--Yes, sir!
Damn!
Bege! I saw it with my own eyes!
I can't believe you were
plotting to kill Mama!
Is that what he's been
up to from the beginning?
Get inside the castle-rero!
Rook! Cannon preparation!
Cannon firing!
So cool!
It's a robot! A castle robot!
How can you be excited at a time like this?!
How long can we hold out?
My eardrums are gonna be busted-nen!
Mochi?
I no longer hear the shriek-nen!
I'm okay now-nen!
Is that...
The Tamate Box!
The treasure that's been passed down
for generations on the Fish-Man Island!
That famous Tamate Box!
Move, move, move!
Let me escape first!
What?!
All right!
Wh-What the hell is this?
Who's messing with Gastino-sama?!
Big Brother!
He's gonna kill me!
All those badasses came together!
Run! They're definitely gonna kill me!
Big Brother! Thank you!
Let's go!
They're gonna come attacking!
Shut the gate now!
No! Nami and the others aren't here yet!
--Hey! Get up here!
--Hurry up!
Guys!
I won't let you go!
Cover them-rero! Hurry-rero!
Nami!
I'll squeeze you to death!
Nami-san!
Nami!
We're gonna fight you!
Achoo-uch.
--Ouch, ouch! It's hot!
--You can't get away now!
Chobro!
Geniiie!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Chopper!
Carrot!
Nami-san!
Let's go! Germa 66!
Shoot! Shoot!
ELECTRIC BLUE
You annoying bastards!
All of you, burn to death!
I-Is that...?!
Germa 66! They're the best-rero!
The Germa that I saw on the comic strip!
The real ones are here now!
Germa's scientific technology.
Those are the shape-memory armors!
They're even resistant to fire!
I'll bind them with my candy again!
Candy Wave!
Kneel before Germa's scientific might!
You obnoxious fleas!
You've got a huge body
but you're not so formidable.
Nami-san!
Are you guys okay?!
I am!
Sanji-kun!
I'm glad that you're okay, Nami-san!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Whip!
Luffy!
--Hurry up!
--This way!
We should retreat too-rero!
Well, well, the legendary hidden treasure,
the Tamate Box!
I came far enough that they won't find me!
I like how it's chaotic-nen!
Let's take this opportunity to
replace what's inside...
She's still vulnerable!
We can still kill her!
This is our last chance!
Cannon firing!
Damn!
Candy Wall!
Perospero!
Oh, that hurts...
Germa's on your side too?
Get ready for this, you rats!
You won't be laughing for long!
Rook! Movement!
I'll shoot her in the back
until we run out of bullets!
Go to hell, Big Mom!
Cannon...
...firing!
What happened?!
Father, the cannons on the left
have been destroyed!
All the cannons in the castle are
stuffed with mochi,
and we can't fire them!
K-Katakuri!
In that case,
the Big Father will run her over to a pulp!
How did it go?!
I have an announcement for
everyone in the castle!
The assassination of Big Mom...
...ended in failure.
The Big Father's limbs are bound with candy.
We can't even move now!
We'll be surrounded by the
"Emperor of the Sea" Big Mom Pirates
and forced to fight a hopeless battle
under siege.
No...
Big Mom finally comes to her senses!
Like a raging beast, she attacks the Big
Father to bring down Luffy and the others!
Meanwhile, Sanji and his father, Judge, face each other.
What words will they exchange?
The long-standing conflict between
father and son comes to an end!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Cutting the Father-Son
Relationship! Sanji and Judge!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!