My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
After failing to assassinate Big Mom,
Luffy and the others were cornered.
But then,
Bege transformed himself into a huge castle.
Oh, cool!
Meanwhile, as the Big Mom Pirates
came attacking,
Germa 66 fought back
using their scientific technology.
We should retreat too-rero!
And the whole team took shelter in the castle.
However, their attacks were blocked
and on top of that, the castle is stuck.
"Cutting the Father-Son Relationship!
Sanji and Judge!"
We'll start killing anyone who steps out...
Just come out already!
How could you have been
used by them so much...
I-I'm a victim, Big Brother!
Just kick all of their asses already!
Poison?
That woman is troublesome...
There you are!
You're something, Bege!
You turned into such a big castle!
The Castle-Castle Fruit is cool!
This is no time for that!
Think about the situation we're in!
Dammit...
The assassination plot that we worked on for over a year
ended in failure!
This is the first time we've failed to kill someone.
In the end, the Emperor of the Sea proved
out of our league...
Now, what should we do?
We don't have that much time.
I'll tell you why.
She stopped crying?
Mama...
That fool, Bege, has betrayed us.
Betrayal?
Listen carefully, you guys!
This castle is me.
It's strong but not unbreakable.
If they destroy the castle, I'll die.
Then the castle will be gone...
And once you guys get thrown out,
the monsters will prey on you, too!
Prey?!
I won't forgive them...
Mama!
I can feel her anger...
You're damned if you stay and damned if you leave.
You're in dire straits!
Don't blame it on me, Bege!
That launcher was the world's most advanced...
--Wh-What was that?
--Father!
Hey, Bege! What's the matter?!
Honey, are you okay?!
Could it be...
It's from outside!
What?
Outside?
You bastards!
Come out!
Bege!
Straw Hat!
I'm scared!
She's looking at us!
Come out!
Bege!
Straw Hat!
Big Mom came to her senses!
Big Mom!
Honey!
That damn beast!
All of you, come out of the castle!
Show yourselves, you fools!
Honey!
Father!
So you betrayed me?
Bege!
Honey! Stay with me!
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
Come out, Bege! Straw Hat!
Bege!
Take Pez!
Come out!
Wait!
Mama! It's me!
Bege's my husband and we have a child!
Please forgive him! Let it go!
Chiffon!
You look exactly like Lola as always...
The attack is coming!
Watch out!
Get back, Chiffon!
Madame!
Mama! Please!
I told you not to show your face!
That was close...
Are you okay?
Madame!
Were you conspiring with them to kill me, too,
Chiffon?!
You're not gonna live to eat
tomorrow's sweets!
Mama!
When the castle is destroyed and Bege dies,
they'll all be thrown out of there.
Don't let anyone get away!
The Firetank Pirates. The Straw Hats...
Plus, Jimbei! Germa 66!
They messed up the wedding
and the Tea Party!
I can't believe we've been taken so lightly.
Let's hang them up
to set an example for others!
Come out!
Bege!
Honey!
Are you okay?
Damn, that old bag!
Even with a cannon,
the Big Father won't get a scratch,
but its defenses aren't a match for her!
I've got to get out and kick her ass!
No, Luffy!
Chopper, stop him!
Okay!
What the?! Hey! Let go of me!
Hey, Chopper! Let go of me!
Luffy! Don't get carried away!
We came to take back Sanji-kun,
didn't we?!
We got a copy of the Ponegliff
and achieved Sanji-kun's wish
to save his family!
We accomplished our goals!
If you have enough time to fight back,
think about how we can escape instead!
If we wanted to fight, we would've brought
Zoro and everyone else too, right?
Luffy-san, Nami-san is right.
We made it this far
because there are only a small number of us.
Let's all go to the Land of Wano safely
where Zoro-san's waiting!
Bege!
Father!
Look! Bege is...
What should we do then?!
Bege is getting attacked on our account!
Good boy, good boy. Don't cry!
Dammit...
Our results are catastrophic...
I'm not willing to sit by
and watch your relish in your success!
Wait a minute, Bege-san!
You can't drag us down with you!
I did what I had to do too!
Give me back my heart now!
Drag you down...
That's not a bad idea.
I didn't care about you guys at all
from the beginning.
But...
...my precious subordinates...
...and my beloved wife and child are here.
I can't let them die!
Honey!
Father!
Bege!
There's only one way...
...for everyone to survive!
Only one?!
What is it?!
Come out!
I'm gonna destroy it!
It's not gonna last long...
Get ready to attack anytime.
I can crush them with this!
Let's get rid of...
...every one of them!
Just come out already!
Then, I'll keep you all in the mirror dimension!
The only way to survive... That is...
This room in the Big Father...
is actually inside of my body...
Hey!
Don't panic!
No matter how strongly we're attacked...
Whether the Big Father leans or falls over...
I'm the only one who'll get hurt.
As long as you guys stay here,
you're not gonna get affected!
--Come to think of it...
--It's only Bege-san who is suffering.
We can hear Big Mom's voice...
But it remains calm inside.
That's right...
And it won't change
even if I turn back to my human form.
So you mean,
we'll be safe as long as we stay here...
Listen... I'll change back to my human form
keeping you guys inside.
Then, Caesar will carry me and fly away
to escape.
If it goes well, we can get out of trouble.
Hey! How could you put my life in danger
without even asking me, you fool!
That's like digging our own grave!
We'll get riddled with bullets in an instant!
There's no chance of success!
There are many users of the Color of Arms too!
I can turn into gas but it doesn't matter!
You don't know if there's any chance of success!
You can't tell unless you try.
You're only agile when you're escaping!
What did you say, you fools?!
Let me ask you a question.
Sanji...
Why did you save us?
We're hateful enemies to you
and we totally fell into the trap!
Because my father would be sad...
If I had stuck to my resentment
from my old days...
Please let me out!
Dad! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry to be born weak!
Help me, Dad!
Help me! Dad!
He'd be disappointed in me
for becoming such a small-minded rat...
...who'd laugh at your blood family's death.
Don't catch cold.
I don't wanna live a life in which I'm too ashamed...
...to face him!
Don't ever admit that I'm your father...
...in front of other people!
It's a shame that I don't want anyone to know!
You realize that, don't you?
13 years ago,
Vinsmoke Sanji who escaped from Germa
died once at sea...
And that's what you wished for.
So admit this!
You're not my father, Vinsmoke Judge!
Don't ever show yourself in front of us again!
Very well.
I promise...
...I won't approach you...
...or the East Blue!
I already did my part!
Doing more isn't part of our deal!
Come out!
Bege! Straw Hat!
--Honey!
--Father!
I don't wanna be here anymore!
If nothing is done, you'll die too, Caesar!
Open the gate!
Gang Bege!
Until you and Caesar Clown fly away into the sky,
we Germa will escort you!
W-Wait a minute!
Why do you decide what I'm gonna do?!
Your high-handed attitude hasn't changed, Judge!
Oh, yeah... You Germa people can fly too...
Then, we'll leave you behind, okay?
No problem.
Alright, if we need to buy time, I'll...
--That's okay, Luffy.
--But...
I don't wanna be indebted to this "failure"!
That's how they wanna settle it...
Wait, wait! Whoa-whoa!
I didn't say I was gonna do this, you fools!
Caesar!
Shut up and do it!
Ouch!
You'll regret this!
Come on out already!
Bege!
Straw Hat!
Are you ready?
Caesar Clown...
I wasn't ready at all from the beginning!
You guys should protect me!
Alright! Let's go crazy!
You have the wrong idea.
Our mission is to let Caesar and Bege escape
quickly and safely.
This is a battle for evacuation.
Defense is harder than offense.
I know.
I understand the mission.
Get ready to step out!
Getting ready to step out!
We're ready!
Bege!
All right!
I'm gonna deactivate the castle!
Let's go!
Germa! Start attacking!
Luffy and Germa 66 join forces
and a deadly escape plan begins!
Big Mom's furious attacks raise Luffy's fighting spirit!
To prove himself as the future King of the Pirates,
his special Gear Four techniques blast!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Escape From the Tea Party! Luffy vs. Big Mom!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!