My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
After failing to kill Big
Mom, Luffy and the others
executed a plan to escape from the
Tea Party at the risk of their lives.
Caesar is trying to get out of the site carrying Bege
who has the whole team inside of his body,
with Germa 66 escorting them.
To save Reiju who was cornered,
Luffy and Sanji went outside.
The one that becomes
the King of the Pirates in the end...
...is me!
Meanwhile, Stussy of Cipher Pol-"AIGIS" 0
who was undercover and
infiltrating the Tea Party,
let the Tamate Box she was trying to get ahold of
fall off a cliff.
--What?!
--No!
You can drop dead without worrying!
I'll use your scientific technology and...
...I'll make the world peaceful!
Thunder Bolt!
"The Execution Begins!
Luffy's Allied Forces Are Annihilated?!"
Father-sama!
Did he die?!
Father!
Hey, wait, guards!
Are you guys leaving us...
Katakuri!
You were so close.
Just a little more to go.
Sparking...
...Figure!
Don't worry. We'll do our part! Just go!
You don't have to tell me!
You think you caught me cold?
Seems like you don't value your life.
It's no use to threaten me.
Unfortunately... I don't feel fear.
You're still alive... I'll put you at ease.
Goodbye... Vinsmoke Judge!
We won't let you do it!
You came to save your father?!
What beautiful family love! I like it!
Don't mistake us. It's part of a Germa
member's duties to save our leader!
And that's all.
What cold-hearted children.
On behalf of your cowardly father,
I'll...
...rediscipline you if you want!
I see... Then, die.
If you think you can do it...
Go ahead!
Don't let them get away!
Shoot, shoot!
Don't turn back, Caesar!
You gotta give it your best, too!
It's impossible!
Shoot them down!
Is everything okay?!
--Come on, Caesar!
--What happened to Luffy and the others?!
Don't push your luck.
None of you can get away.
Be prepared!
You guys, go ahead and run!
It's not gonna be that easy.
Lie there for a while.
Extra...
...Hachis Hash!
How annoying!
You poison-woman...
It's no use...
You can't beat me if you can't hit me.
I don't have to beat you...
Our job is to let them escape.
You're a pain
so I just wanna stall you...
"And buy some time," huh?
Besides, even if I can't hit you,
I can blow you up with me!
Sparking Figure!
Double!
Big Bro Katakuri!
Take this!
Bring it on!
Niji!
Okay!
I'll burn you to a crisp!
Mama!
--Look at them!
--They look kind of cool!
Of course-rero! They're Germa-rero!
To fulfill their job,
they don't care about their own safety...
They're ruthless to others and themselves.
No wonder they're strong.
But the Big Mom Pirates are not
easy opponents to beat.
Not just Germa,
you do your best too, Caesar!
Don't say such an irresponsible thing!
Mama!
What's the matter?
Now, Caesar!
Go! You can make it-rero!
That's it! Go!
You can do it, Caesar!
You're still a loser, though!
Huh? What did you just...
Watch out, you...
What?
--Hey! Get out of my way!
--Huh? Who are you?!
--You're me!
--No, he can't be me!
It's me, Caesar Clown!
Brulee?!
I won't let you escape!
I have grudges against you guys
piled up like a mountain.
I finally get to settle
the score a little bit!
Boost the voltage!
I'm doing it!
Is this all you've got? It feels kinda nice.
A real electric shock....
...should work like this!
Is he dead?
Nice try.
Other people might have succumbed...
But I can neutralize your poison.
Reiju?!
You'd better focus.
Everyone!
We're in trouble, Caesar!
Everyone got defeated?
Oh, no...
We're finished...
No...
Germa!
If nothing is done,
we'll all get killed for sure!
I don't want that!
Then...
We have only one option.
Rather than sit and wait for death to come...
We'll fight, right?
--I'm going too!
--Me too!
We're going too, of course!
I have no choice...
All right, let's start...
...the executions.
Mama!
The Tamate Box!
What is it?
A little back in time...
RYUGU KINGDOM, FISH-MAN ISLAND
Luffy and the others saved the Ryugu Kingdom
from the New Fish-Man Pirates
and received the Tamate Box
from King Neptune as thanks.
But...
Your Majesty!
About giving all the stolen treasure
to Luffy-kun and the others if they can find it...
I need to ask them to return
just the Tamate Box.
What are you saying?
I'd never tell anyone to return
what I already gave them!
Even if what's in it is not treasure...
...but a bomb?
What?
There's going to be a huge
explosion if they open it?!
I must ask them to return it immediately.
You gave all the treasures to Big Mom?!
Maybe it won't explode,
Minister of the Right.
Your Majesty, you are so positive!
Now, back to the current action...
From the ceiling of the East
Baum Cake second floor,
a giant crack is running through
the Red-bean Baum Cake Meeting Room!
Not just a crack! It broke up!
This is the Red-bean Baum Cake third floor!
What's happening?!
The room is starting to slant!
It's not an earthquake!
I clearly heard a big explosion earlier!
--Is it an enemy attack?!
--It keeps leaning!
What's going on?
No way...
It's falling over-bon...
The Whole Cake Chateau!
It's falling over-bon!
Cock-a-doodle-do!
SWEET CITY, THE CAPITAL
Was it our enemy's cannon?!
This is the Emperor of the Sea's stronghold!
How can anyone invade this island?!
So it really was an explosion?!
What caused the blast?!
Stop falling!
Everyone's gonna die!
Does it have something to do with
the wedding on the rooftop?!
This has to be a joke!
But this is big news!
Was that what I think it was?
I think so!
The timing was dead-on!
What else could have caused it?
But... why the Tamate Box?!
Guys, hold onto something!
Where are Straw Hat and the others?
What is all this?
I don't know...
But it saved us anyway!
Otherwise, all of us would've been killed.
What's going on?! What's happening?!
Something saved us...
We don't know if we've been...
...saved or not, yet!
We're in big trouble, Mama!
The Whole Cake Chateau is crumbling now
due to an unknown explosion!
Something's going on outside!
We don't feel anything in Bege's body though!
What is happening?
I don't know. But...
...the place is in chaos now.
Could it be...
...that the Whole Cake Chateau is shaking?!
What kind of joke is this?!
Am I dreaming?
Look, Caesar!
It's a big mess....
How did it happen?!
Who did it and what did they do?!
Big Brothers...
Big Sisters...
Oh my brothers and sisters!
I can't stop!
Mama!
Mama!!
Terrific!
I don't know who did it
but I gotta thank them!
We didn't have to kill her!
Now,
the "Emperor of the Sea" Big
Mom Pirates have been...
...annihilated!
The giant chateau that is bigger
than a mountain crumbles!
The members of the Big Mom
Pirates fall one after another.
In that desperate situation,
Streusen exercises his true ability!
Luffy and his allies' deadly escape plan enters
another stage!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Chateau Collapses! The Straw
Hat's Great Escape Begins!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!