My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
After failing to kill Big Mom, Luffy and his allies
escaped from the Whole Cake Chateau
and saw Kingbaum again
on their way to the Sunny.
Being driven by her Hunger Pang attack,
Big Mom chases Luffy and the others.
Wedding cake!
And only a wedding cake will stop her attack.
The wedding cake was a chocolate chiffon cake!
I can make as good a chocolate flavor as the head chef,
if not better!
And Big Sis Chiffon is an expert of
chiffon cakes!
Together, we can make that cake!
Take the Spear of Elbaph!
Elbaph?!
Look out for her attack!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
"Pudding's Determination!
Ablaze! The Seducing Woods!"
Wedding...
...cake!!
That resembled the Giants' technique!
Hakoku Sovereignty!
Why is it?
Kingbaum!
Mama! Forgive me-ju!
I've been forced to do this-ju!
Oh, no! The next attack will come!
Let's get off and fight!
Kingbaum! Who was the girl you were with?
Your girlfriend?
No, stop, Kin-chan!
Are you okay, Kin-chan?
--Kin-chan!
--Lady Tree!
S-She's my fiancee-ju.
Wow! Fiancee?!
That's right-ju!
We promised to stay together forever-ju!
Then...
you must live on!
Survive for her sake!
To see her again!
You're right-ju!
I can't just drop dead now!
Run, Kingbaum!
What lies ahead is a new life with her!
A future filled with love is waiting for you!
Lady Tree!
Yes!
--She's like a devil...
--That's our Nami!
Give me the cake!
Okay, it's my turn!
Wait, Luffy! I have a plan!
Wedding...
What are you gonna do?!
...cake!
Black Ball!
Thunder likes thunder!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
That's it!
He ate them!
It's delicious! It's delicious! So delicious!!
Oh! Mama!
Oh, wait!
What are you doing, Zeus?!
Oh no, he's totally into it.
They're running towards the Seducing Woods!
Wedding cake!
Once we get in the forest,
we'll have the upper hand!
Because Kingbaum is...
...the master of the forest!
It's Kingbaum-sama!
Kingbaum-sama is coming!
Get out of my way!
Awesome!
--Oh, my...
--You're something, Big Tree.
Move! Move! Move!
Oh, look! There's the Sunny!
--What?
--It's a straight line to the coast.
Your plan is amazing!
That's my Nami-san!
GERMA KINGDOM
I'm impressed, Germa...
Did you think I'd say that?
Hidden darts?!
What's with him?!
I'm gonna show all I've got
for the first time in a long time.
People who say such a thing
are often weak.
What's the matter?
Show me what you've got already.
Okay.
You're too slow!
How thrilling!
Sparking!
How... fast... he can move...
I can go faster if you want.
Cut the crap!
As long as Big Mom doesn't ride on Zeus,
we can shake her off!
His name is Zeus?
Yes, that cloud was created by
part of Mama's soul...
Yeah, I'm Zeus.
Zeus-sama!
--Zeus!
--He's here!
Be careful! He's strong!
Hey, hey, those small thunderclouds!
I want more of them!
What?
Black Ball? Were they good?
I've never had such rich-tasting thunderclouds
that went down so smooth!
Hey, are there more?
Oh, those taste good?
It's fluffy!
Give me, give me, more, more!
Hey, Cloud!
Forget it and give us a lift!
No, I can't. Only Mama who gave me
part of her soul can ride on me.
Oh, so you're just an ordinary cloud.
So ordinary...
Zeus... In that case...
Will you become my servant?
Huh?
Gladly!
She's not asking you.
Then you can eat the Black Ball every day!
What? Really?!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
You have no loyalty to your boss?
I know you can become a huge thundercloud
that covers up the whole sky!
That was so cool!
Oh, really?
I've never been complimented like that!
M-Mama...
Here she comes!
Wedding cake...
Big Mom!
M-Mama...
Mama!
Seducing Woods!
Stop them!
Oh, no! Mama's angry!
It turned back to the annoying forest.
Can't we just kick them out of our way
and go straight?
We can't!
While you're rampaging like that,
you'll lose all sense of direction in this forest!
That's right.
This forest disorients people.
My command is
nothing compared to the queen's-ju!
But...!
Lady Tree!
Wait!
Run as hard as you can
for the sake of love and the future!
It's Mama's order! Stop them!
Get out of my way!
I'm not gonna die here-ju!
Why are you doing this, Kingbaum-sama?!
You can do it, Kingbaum!
--Hang on tight!
--Okay.
Tree! Don't stop!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Oh, that's convenient.
They keep coming.
All right!
Kingbaum! Go faster!
Ouch, it's hot. What is that?
It's...
Ugh.
That's Prometheus-sama!
He's angry!
Hey, Kingbaum.
You betrayed Mama...
P-Prometheus-sama!
It's hot!
Here he comes!
--Is he trying to crush us?
--Kingbaum, get away!
Kingbaum, run!
Your fiancee's waiting for you, isn't she?!
He can't move! Let's get off!
Run!
Nami! This way!
Nami-san!
You-gara will get hurt, too!
Nami!
Tree!
Kingbaum...
Nami-san!
Wedding cake!
Where's Bege?
We'll catch up to him soon!
There's a fire in the Seducing Woods...
SWEET CITY, THE CAPITAL
I think Mama is fighting.
This is the Mirroworld. Montd'Or!
We have 10,000 soldiers
who are waiting to be sent anytime anywhere!
Got it. We'll be in touch.
Candy. Biscuit. Nuts.
Battleships from those islands, keep an eye on
the southwest coast where the Straw Hats' ship is moored
and don't let them raise anchor!
Yes, sir!
Your encirclement will be
the first hurdle for them.
Tart ships from Flavor Island
and Liqueur Island will follow that.
Get ready and stand by at the port.
Wait for the Warning Signals
from the Territory Slugs.
Roger.
They can't get away from the security network of
the Territory Slugs.
SOUTHWEST COAST - THE SUNNY
It's noisy in the forest.
No wonder...
Mama is going after them herself
so there is zero chance for them to make it here.
I bet so.
Well, then, why are we setting up an ambush?
Just in case.
They're coming after us with the Tart Tanks!
Fire!
We'll get to the coast soon!
They can't catch us!
Brother Bege!
Wow! You scared me!
Pudding-sa... I mean, Pudding!
Even if you're a young girl, I'm not gonna show mercy!
I've got to talk to Big Sis Chiffon!
Let me see her now!
Big Sis Chiffon! Where are you?
Pudding! What brings you here?!
Big Sis!
I need your help!
Mama's having another Hunger Pang attack!
She's craving a wedding cake!
Hunger Pang attack?!
Yes, and the wedding cake she wants
is a chocolate chiffon cake!
I guess that's enough information for you.
So you need my chiffon cake.
If we combine my chocolate
and your chiffon cake,
we can make a wedding cake
that will satisfy Mama!
If we let her eat it,
we can stop her attack!
I'm sorry, Pudding...
I'm leaving this country just like Lola.
I no longer care what happens to Mama
or to this country!
Yeah! So just go away, Pudding!
It's not that...
My real purpose is...
...not to save Mama or this country, either!
Oh, good boy, good boy.
I need to stop Mama as soon as possible...
Otherwise, he...
...and his friends will get killed!
Luffy and the others are confused by
the shifting ways of the Seducing Woods!
However, in the midst of the scramble,
the untamed warrior Pedro's lightning speed,
and Nami's magic cast from her new weapon,
the Sorcerer's Climate Baton, will clear their way!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Lightning Counterattack! Nami and Zeus the Thundercloud!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!