My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
After failing to kill Big Mom,
Luffy and his allies escaped
from the Whole Cake Chateau
and continue heading towards the Sunny.
Big Mom chases after them
in the middle of her Hunger Pangs attack.
Bring...
...the cake!
Meanwhile, Brook and Chopper
arrived at the Sunny first,
but it was the Big Mom Pirates
who were waiting for them.
Do you want to fight?
Of course!
We'll save the Sunny!
Pudding asked Sanji to make a
wedding cake since it's the only
thing that can stop Big Mom.
That way, we can distract her attention from you!
So hang in there until that time!
Sanji was about to part ways with
Luffy and the others for the time being but...
What are you doing right there?!
Get away!
"Save the Sunny!
Fighting Bravely! Chopper and Brook!"
Ikoku Sovereignty!
Enough already...
That was close.
Everyone's okay, right?
Let's go! The Sunny is waiting for us
at the coast!
Wait! Their course is off.
Rabian, descend again!
Fly straight from the previous spot to the sea coast!
Roger!
Luffy-kun and everyone!
Wait! It's not that way!
There's a wall ahead of you!
What? Pudding? She's the nice Pudding!
I thought we were going straight.
Of course, we've been fooled.
Everyone! The sea coast is this way!
Okay, let's go!
We won't let you go!
Leave them to me!
Memory Filament!
Flashback!
Oh, I've got to go grocery shopping...
Big Brother hit me!
It's time to walk my dog.
My son is missing.
Has anyone seen him?
What's going on?
Anyway, let's go before it's too late!
Memories of the former owners
of those souls that've been
infused into the Homies...
...are flashing back temporarily.
While they're confused,
they're not under Mama's control!
So Luffy-kun and the others can
get out of the forest now!
I see. Thank you, Pudding-chan!
Why?! Since when were you there, Sanji...
...san!
Well, since a short while ago.
--What?!
--Didn't you notice?!
Now, Pudding-chan,
let's rush to Chocolat Town.
G-Get off and swim, idiot!
Your eye is beautiful even when you're mad...
Are you okay, Pudding?
I-I'm fine... D-D-Don't mess with me!
O-Or I'll kill you, Sanji...
...san!
Oh! It's the end of the forest!
All right! Let's go straight to Cacao Island!
Brook! Chopper!
Is that your ship?
Yeah, it's getting attacked.
I guess they were ambushed...
Oh, no! Our big brothers are there!
Our brothers are attacking
Sanji-san's friends...
Hmph! Your friends are dead!
That will teach ya!
They're no match for my brothers!
Your friends will be swallowed by the sea!
What are you saying, Pudding?!
Oh, no! That's not what I meant to say!
What do you wanna do?
Go back to the ship?
No, I'll come along with Pudding-chan.
What?
Are you sure?
We'll keep on going then!
Yeah, we don't need to worry about them.
Instead, let's get started...
...on the cake that can make Big Mom unconscious
as soon as possible!
You're quite tough...
How could you hold out this long
against these many people?
Lick.
Go to hell!
This is it!
Kung Fu Point!
Die!
How's that?!
What an interesting exotic animal...
Get off the ship!
Oh, yeah!
You have to keep your
eyes on the prize, baby.
Not that I have eyes myself.
You fight quite well against
the Chess Peacekeepers, skeleton...
Because I am...
...Soul King!
Enemies keep coming out of the mirror...
It's the mirror in Nami and Robin's room.
Will they get mad if we break it?
If we can break it, let's break it
and apologize later.
Who are you gonna apologize to? Lick.
You saw the lightning earlier, right?
That was pretty intense.
It shows how mad Mama is.
I bet there aren't even bones left of
Straw Hat and the others.
No one will return to this ship.
I'm saying I'm going to
show some mercy on you.
No matter how much you try,
our soldiers will emerge endlessly.
And you guys will use up all of your energy
eventually.
If you submit right here, right now,
I'll at least spare your life...
Just let it go already.
What a useless conversation.
We got sick and tired of answering to
that line of yours...
I just need you to get off of the ship.
The Sunny is ours!
Do you really wanna fight me?
I see...
Seems like you really
don't value your life...
All right.
I'll kill you with my own hands.
Lick.
Cake...
Where is it?
My...
...wedding cake!
I see the sea coast ahead!
Hurry up!
We made it!
But, is Pudding really on our side now?!
I don't know! We shouldn't lower our guard
until we get out of their territory!
I think we can make it!
We're almost there!
I won't let you get away!
Hey, Zeus!
How could you do that?!
Why did you get us involved?!
I'm sorry... It wasn't my intention!
I don't care about your intention!
Don't ever be inattentive again!
Yes, I know...
But those were so delicious...
Those thundercloud eggs.
Huh?!
Hey, do you really understand?!
Mama's orders are absolute!
I know...
Give it to me!
My wedding cake!
Oh, no!
Dodge!
Damn...
That was close!
Thank you, Jimbei!
Everyone, be careful!
Another one's coming!
Cake!
Duck!
Mama!
You can't get away from me...
Straw Hat!
Oh, please! We're almost to the Sunny!
Wedding cake!
Damn!
Run! If we get caught,
we're all going to die!
Give me the cake!
You can't get away, Straw Hat!
Come on, Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
Luffy!
Heavenly...
Run, guys!
...Fire!
Are you tired now, Soul King?
Gavotte...
...Bond en Avant!
It's not working...
Brook!
Are you okay, Brook?!
Don't worry... I can still fight...
You've cut down quite a lot of our troops...
We'll bring you guys down
and take back the Sunny!
You're so naive...
I'll make you face reality.
Huh? What the...
My leg...
Damn! I can't move!
Chopper-san!
Brook!
You fools...
Those candies will slowly
seep into your bodies.
It's no use.
You won't be able to move from there...
Chopper-san!
Don't panic, don't panic.
Man...
What kind of positive thinking did you have
to believe you could take the ship back?
In order to catch you guys,
we're mobilizing all of our soldiers
across the island
to set up surrounding nets at various places.
You have nowhere to run.
The difference in power is obvious!
Damn!
I... I can't even transform!
Free Chopper-san!
Idiot! It's too late!
It's punishment for standing against me!
I'll turn you into a Candyman and lick you!
Lick!
The candy will coat your whole body,
fill you up inside and stop your breathing.
And with that agony,
it only takes three minutes
to kill the target!
No way...
And then, it's complete!
A sweet corpse - Candyman!
Chopper-san!
Stop!
It's too late to cry over your choices!
I certainly gave you a chance!
I said I'd let just the two of you go.
You guys really don't know anything!
This island...
...isn't sweet at all!
Chopper-san!
Why don't you count the sound of
the second hand?
That's just what sweet fools
like you guys deserve...
Oh, stop! I don't wanna get sweetened!
Oh, stop!
I'll turn you into a Candyman and lick you!
Hey, Big Brother Peros!
That's Mama...
Wedding...
Her Hunger Pangs attack won't stop...
Cake!
We have to lead her to
Pudding on Cacao Island...
If she finds out there's no cake
on this ship, she'll kill me.
I don't think we have gotten that far yet...
Let me eat!
Cake!
It's the coast! Get to the Sunny!
He was alive? Straw Hat...
It must be our soldiers who got struck
by the lightning...
Who are they?!
The ship has been hijacked!
What? Brook?! Chopper?!
What's that?!
Get back to the Mirroworld.
All of you will end up...
...lying at his feet in a few seconds.
Jump into the mirror!
Perospero and Katakuri...
Those two of all others...
The disaster continues!
It's amazing that you got this far...
I'm impressed.
But your destination is a graveyard!
You must die here!
Candy Maiden!
A wall of candy!
It's obvious that it's not just a wall!
Fish-Man Karate...
Gum-Gum...
Shark Brick Fist!
Jet Bazooka!
Yes!
Not yet, not yet...
Don't underestimate me!
Huh? What is it?!
Candy Maiden...
...Decoration!
It's gigantic...
This is it!
No one can get through here!
Go around and get to the ship!
No, run straight!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
The man who once attained everything
this world has to offer...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates.
There is a Mink who carries
the King's last wishes on his shoulders
and fights at the risk of his life!
To clear the way for Luffy
and the others who are in
a desperate situation, Pedro, that
man, takes the bet of a lifetime!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Before the Dawn! Pedro, the
Captain of the Guardians!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!