kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
After failing to kill Big Mom,
Luffy and his allies
escaped from the Whole Cake Chateau
and continue heading towards the Sunny.
Big Mom chases after them
in the middle of her Hunger Pangs attack.
It's the coast! Get to the Sunny!
Meanwhile, in order to take back the Sunny
that has been captured
by the Big Mom Pirates,
Brook and Chopper continue a perilous fight.
However, due to Perospero's ability,
they have been coated with candy.
Finally, just as Luffy and the
others who got through the
Seducing Woods come close to the Sunny...
Candy Maiden...
...Decoration!
"Before the Dawn!
Pedro, the Captain of the Guardians!"
No one can get through here!
Go around and get to the ship!
No, run straight!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
Is it a flame?!
Pedro!
The dawn of the world will come before long!
His-teia ability is just like Luffy's!
Wedding...
...cake!
Here she comes!
What should we do, Luffy?!
We're surrounded!
Luffy! Kick Katakuri off of the ship!
We'll try to set sail somehow!
I got it!
--This way!
--Okay!
That bastard!
He must've come through the mirror dimension!
Listen! Everyone has their own turn.
Wedding cake!
I don't wanna get involved with
Mama's Hunger Pangs.
Lick.
Armament Hardening!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Gatling!
Why?! I'm using Haki but I can't hit him...
Chopper! Brook! Are you all right?!
Stay with us!
Where is it?
The cake!
Carrot.
Don't get shocked by the unexpected.
What?
I think...
...Luffy and his crew are...
...the ones who our tribe
and the Kozuki Family
have been awaiting for centuries....
The ones who'll lead the
world to the new dawn!
For centuries?!
Hey, Montd'Or, can you hear me?
Yes, I can hear you.
Surround the southwest coast of the
Whole Cake Island with battleships.
Roger, Big Bro Peros.
Clank.
Surround the coastline-soir?
I guess Straw Hat and the
others are still alive.
What?!
Mama was pursuing on land
and Katakuri-sama was waiting at the ship,
but are they still alive-bon?
Yeah, they're so persistent.
Tarte of Nuts Island, respond!
This is Amande on Nuts Island.
Surround the southwest coast.
Don't let Straw Hat and his clan get away
at any cost!
Roger.
Coup de...
What?
Coup de Burst!
This ship can leap 1 km ahead!
If we try to set sail normally,
the ship will be sunk by Big Mom!
I don't quite understand
but we can escape that way, right?
Yeah!
Okay! Let's bet on it!
Big Mom is coming!
There you are!
Carrot! You-gara go help them
get ready to sail!
--What?
--Hurry up!
Okay!
Is it there?
The wedding cake?!
Hey, Brook, Chopper!
Stay with me!
Even if we can make it out of here,
it's meaningless if you guys end up dead...
We spotted the Straw Hats
at the southwest coast!
This is Minister Amande from
the Tarte of Nuts Island...
We'll corner Straw Hat and the others.
It's terrible.
Battleships are coming from the sea,
and Big Mom from the land.
We're totally stuck in the middle!
Nami! We have to get going!
I know! But I have to load
two more barrels of cola!
I'll do the rest so you go prepare
for the Coup-de-something!
All right, I'll leave it to you then!
Candy Wave!
What was that?!
Candy?!
Oh, no! We can't use Coup de Burst like this!
What's wrong?!
This is serious!
The Sunny has been caught by candy!
What?!
Did you see the power of Candy Wave?!
I'm a perfectionist!
Oh, there he is!
What should we do?
Turn Brook and Chopper back,
as well as the ship, candy jerk!
If nothing is done...
Cake!
It's either being destroyed by Mama...
...or being sunk by the cannons!
Either way, you have no chance to survive!
Beast Sword - Karajishi!
Hey, do you know how much my bounty is?
It's 700 million.
I'm not someone who a weakling
like you can defeat!
Lick!
This will be the last time we talk...
You escaped death. Lick.
It's pointless to die here!
The dawn of the new world is coming!
I have to go back!
You're so handsome.
I'll reduce it to 50 years.
Go on with your life.
At that time,
if you hadn't sacrificed your left eye,
you would've been killed for sure...
Was that how bad you wanted to survive?
All right...
How old are you now?
I'm 27...
You've had 50 years of your lifespan drained
so it's like you've lived 77 years already.
Now, I wonder how many years
you can expect to live...
I at least wanna choose where to die myself.
By the way,
you were the captain of the Nox Pirates...
"Nox" means "night," doesn't it?
That sounds rather negative.
They say, "Every night comes to an end."
And...
..."nox" means the same as...
..."before the dawn"...
If I can serve as a foundation for the
new dawn of the world
that the Master and the others are hoping for,
that's what I want the most.
I think I have enough time for that...
You once said that "before the dawn"
and "nox" meant the same thing...
But the only thing that's waiting for you
is the eternal darkness called death.
No...
There it comes! Gather up!
So that's the Roger Pirates' ship...
The Oro Jackson!
Roger! Oden-sama! Take me along!
I'll do anything! Take me with you!
Kid, you still have to wait.
I'm not a kid, I'm Pedro!
My time is limited.
Listen! Everyone has their own turn.
Be patient and wait!
It'll come naturally. Your turn, I mean...
Goodbye, Pedro.
Okay, Roger!
Pedro!
Roger...
What about him?
They say he died!
You've got to be kidding!
He's not gonna die!
He's the King of the Pirates!
I'm not kidding!
He got caught by the Navy
and at an execution ground in the East Blue...
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
This is the beginning.
A new era has finally dawned.
Wishes will be carried over.
The tide of time, people's dreams...
Those things can't be stopped.
As long as people search for
the meaning of freedom,
those things will see no end.
Roger...
I decided.
I'll take... to sea, too!
Even if you deny it,
the dawn didn't come to you...
Lick.
You think... so?
Roger said, "Everyone has their own turn"!
What are you talking about?
This is my turn!
This will break all of your-gara
magic spells, right?
Bombs?!
Stop, you fool!
What are you thinking?!
Let go of me!
I...
...had a feeling that this
would be my last journey.
What do you mean, Pedro?
Pedro?!
Goodbye.
What do you mean, Pedro?
One day, you'll see how important it was...
...to save Luffy and the others here
and let them set sail!
Pedro!!
Listen!
You-gara guys must go forward!
Pedro cleared the path for
a slight chance of escape!
However, to crush that ray of hope,
Big Mom and Katakuri
mercilessly attack the Sunny!
There is only one way to survive!
With Pedro's wishes in mind,
Luffy takes a big bet with determination!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I'll Be Back! Luffy, Deadly Departure!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!