The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"An Outcast's Dream!
Hiriluk the Quack!"
Day 3. Prognosis, the
bacteria were reduced to 30%.
Whoa! You're amazing!
Just as you'd expect from a monster!
But what happens if I do this?
Poke, poke...
What?! What're you doing?!
So funny!
Shut up! Go away!
Won't you become my friend?
I really really like you!
Y... Your friend?
Become a pirate!
I'm not interested in pirates at all.
And I never wanted a friend!
If you become my friend,
my other friends will all be happy!
Wait!
Why would I wanna
become your friend?!
Don't insult me!
You're definitely funny!
I'll definitely make
you become my friend!
In order for you to get
a healthy smile back,
I prepared an exceptionally
nutritious dish...
Thank you, Sanji-kun.
though you're still painfully beautiful
even after what your body's been through...
Good lord! When did you use
my kitchen without asking?
Madam, the roast over there is for you.
It's high in protein and is
good for rejuvena-- Ahhh!
I'm not a "madam."
I'm a sparkling single...
and still youthful.
You're still 139 years old... right?
Doctorine! Help me!
Wait! Hey! Wait!
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
What're you doing?
This guy's gonna join us
and become our friend!
Oh, really?!
I didn't say that!
You did.
I didn't!
You did!
Be quiet, both of you!
Wait!
Friend, huh? How deep a
meaning that word has to him...
To ask without knowing that...
There was one man whom he opened
up to when he was alone...
The man's name was Dr. Hiriluk.
He was a quack who gave Chopper
a name and called him son.
Hold it!
Did you find him?!
No! We can't find him!
That darn quack, Hiriluk!
We'll catch him no matter what!
Those're Wapol-sama's orders!
--Yes sir!
Dammit!
You can't go on like this.
Let's call a doctor.
No. There aren't any doctors
in this country...
except for the Twenty MDs who
belong exclusively to Wapol...
We'll beg Wapol and call
the Twenty MDs. I'll go.
You don't have to.
I'll examine him.
Hiriluk! N-no thank you!
Please don't!
A bunch of people you treated
ended up getting worse!
Don't be modest. I just developed a
wonderful all-purpose drug yesterday.
You're lucky.
Hmm? It's not what you think.
This is a tranquilizer gun.
I use it when the
patient's pain is severe.
I... I'm gonna go get the guards!
Please leave!
If you want money, I'll pay!
I don't take money from sick people.
I just want to help you.
Don't! Stop it! I've got a family!
Croak! Croak, croak!
Croak, croak, croak!
Croak! Croak!
Croak, croak! Croak!
Hmm? This is strange.
Did I use a wrong ingredient?
I thought frog extract would work...
Guess it was a failure. Oh man...
S-Sorry... I didn't
mean for this to happen...
Hiriluk! Are you there?!
--Hold it!
Hmm?
Are you happy, young man?
The doctor hunt has come
to the final stage.
I hear that you and I are the
only doctors left in this country.
Wapol is trying desperately to catch us.
Even if that wasn't the case, you're
already an outcast in this country...
since you're the worst of the quacks.
I won't get caught by some doctor hunt.
I'll save this country using
medical science one day.
Oh? Didn't you mean to say
"destroy the country"?
There're people on the bridge!
I'll see you around, quack.
I don't wanna see you again,
you thieving doctor.
I'll never get caught!
I'll save as many sick people as possible!
Hmm?
You've been shot? We need to stop
the bleeding right away or you'll die!
Don't worry. I'll save you!
It's a yeti! Shoot him to death!
I just made an ointment that even
works on broken bones 3 days ago.
You're lucky.
Don't let him get away!
Kill him!
Shoot him!
What are you?
You don't look like a human.
Oh, yeah. You're that yeti that
people have been talking about...
Yeah! It hit him!
It wasn't enough! Finish him!
H... How dare you...
Who do you think... I am?!
Hey! Wait!
I will never shoot you!
My name is Dr. Hiriluk!
I'm a doctor!
That was Chopper and Hiriluk's
first encounter.
So what happened... to the
reindeer taken in by Hiriluk?
What?! You can talk?!
Why did you stay quiet for 3 days?
I thought you'd hate me if I talked...
When I talked to humans the
other day, they shot me...
because it's strange for
a reindeer to speak...
You speak, so what?!
I can speak, too...
a lot better than you can.
Get out of here! Chopper!
What?
Dammit! It failed again!
Hey, are you okay, Chopper?!
Hmm? Well, you aren't okay
to start with, I guess...
Why are you calling me Chopper?
You're Tony Tony Chopper.
After all, you're a reindeer and have
fine antlers that could chop down trees.
That's a cool name, isn't it?
That's what I'll call you.
Chopper...
Listen, Chopper. Always observe patients,
and give them proper treatment.
Doing so will save people's lives.
Let's go! Patients are waiting
for me today once again.
Get out of here, quack!
I thought lizard eyeballs would work...
Never come back!
Go away!
Run! It's the guards!
Chopper! We'll use the decoy plan!
What's that?!
Take care!
What?
You almost got me killed!
Oh yeah?! You failed to die once already!
You clumsy blue nose!
Don't call me blue nose!
Doctor...
Hmm?
This is... the first time
I've fought with someone...
Makes sense... To fight,
you have to have an opponent.
Then... is it your first time
for this as well?
Hmm?
I'll give it to you. It's a gift...
as a memento of our making up.
A gift? Making up?
We both go through hardships
as outcasts, don't we?
But don't hold a grudge against humans.
This country is sick right now.
Both the citizens and the king
suffer from a sickness of the heart.
People would probably say that
you can't treat a sick country,
but that's not true.
Once my invention is complete,
this country will be saved!
There used to be a master-thief
in a country in the far west.
He had a serious heart disease.
He went to see every possible skilled
doctor and got treated by them,
but no one was able to cure him.
After being told he'd die,
he passed by a mountain
while frustrated and unsettled.
There... he saw a sight that
he had never seen in his life.
Cherry blossoms! He saw vivid
cherry blossoms all over the mountain!
And then, he went to see another
doctor and was shocked...
because he was told...
"You're completely healthy."
What?
He was cured! It was indeed
a miracle! Don't you think?
But this was unmistakably medical science!
By being emotionally moved, some sort
of change happened in this man's body!
In other words, there's no disease
in this world that can't be cured.
No matter what anyone says about me,
I'll save this country as a doctor!
That's why I raised this skull
towards all the diseases!
Skull...
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible!
I will save this country as a doctor!
By raising this,
I'll fight just like pirates do!
Hey! Reindeer!
Join us and become our friend!
Hmm? Whoa! That looks delicious!
It's cool to be a pirate!
Doctor, what are pirates?
Pirates?
Pirates are incredible guys at sea.
They have large, well-trained
bodies and eyes like an eagle.
Their voices are like
a thunder splitting the sky!
Are you... really a pirate?!
Hmm?
Yeah, I am...
Like I've been saying, join us!
It's fun to be a pirate! Pirates sing, too.
What? Th-they sing?
Yeah. And they dance, too!
You call that being a pirate?!
That's right!
And they go on lots of adventures!
Adventures? So pirates
go on adventures then?
Of course! Pirates risk their
lives to go on adventures!
You can meet lots of amazing people!
It's cool to be a pirate!
There're tons of incredible guys at sea!
Chopper, go out to sea some day.
If you do, you'll understand very
well how small your problems are.
This island that you were born on
is like this compared to the world.
Really?
No, it's smaller! Like this! It's true!
Your future lies beyond that sea!
The good times passed in the
twinkling of an eye... And...
The time to bid farewell...
comes for everyone...
It took one year.
Now your treatment is complete.
Your injuries are
completely healed, Chopper.
Yes! Thank you, Doctor!
Well then... take care...
What?
Now, leave! Live as you please!
I'm busy with my research!
I no longer have any moral
obligation to take care of you!
Doctor! I'll never cause you
any trouble! Please let me in!
I'll massage your shoulders everyday!
I'll make you tea and clean the house!
Please! Let me stay!
I don't have any friends!
I have no place to go!
Doctor! Doctor!
Chopper!
Look at this, Doctor.
I'm injured. Hey, Doctor!
Look at this!
Why... Doctor?
Go... to the sea! Go anywhere!
Don't ever come back here!
Forgive me, Chopper!
I'm gonna... die...
Yeah, you will...
Tell me! How many more days do I have?
Oh? If you're asking me
to examine you, I refuse.
You don't have the money to pay my fee.
Tell me!
You can't kill a person
with a tranquilizer gun!
I'll tell you. You'll die at 5 pm
on the 10th day from today.
You won't have to suffer any more.
10 days... That'll be enough...
In 2 days... In 2 days, I'll complete the
research I've continued for 30 years...
I will... make cherry blossoms
bloom in this country!
Cherry blossoms? So the research
you've continued for 30 years
was about making cherry blossoms bloom?
The miracle cherry blossoms that
saved you, a master thief, long ago?
That's right!
What?
You're a fool. This is a winter island
where it's bitter cold year around.
Cherry blossoms won't bloom here.
They will! I was a hopeless
thug and dying,
but I lived on and was able to
have a profound change of heart.
Every human in this world can be saved!
I'd like to prove it here in Drum,
the land where I was born!
Listen. What you're trying to do
isn't medical science or any science.
Even if the cherry blossoms bloom,
it will do nothing to human bodies.
Hiriluk!
Chopper! We're alike. So I will
at least teach you before I die...
that there's nothing
impossible in this world...
and that you can do anything, too!
But the story of these two
doesn't have a happy ending...
I'll show you...
the miracle cherry blossoms!
Even this sleepless town
has dozed off for now
From today forth,
something's going to change
I'm sure I can start fresh,
since I'm not alone
Just by having you by my side,
I feel I can become strong
I wonder how far I can go,
towards the place that leads to the future
Off in the distance it shines,
encompassing the world
Before dawn
Hey, Luffy. Are you really
listening to-- Hey, where'd he go?!
Geez... I wonder if he's chasing
Tony-kun again... He's refusing!
That's not true! Are you stupid?!
I've decided to make him join us
and become our friend!
But that's just what you want, right?!
Seriously... I wonder if there's
any medicine that works on fools...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms
And The Will That Gets Carried On!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!