My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
In order to let the Sunny escape
from the Whole Cake Island,
Luffy stayed in the Mirroworld by himself
and held off Katakuri.
However, he got overwhelmed by Katakuri's strength.
Gum-Gum...
...Giant...
...Axe!
There will be no victory in your future.
It leads anyone to the peak of happiness...
I'll make you taste true sweetness!
T-True sweetness?!
Meanwhile, Sanji started making the wedding cake
in order to calm Big Mom down.
All right!
Let's start baking!
For those who saved Lola!
For Sanji-san!
I'll make my special extremely-fluffy
chiffon cake!
I must help Sanji-san and the others get away!
With my very sweet chocolate!
Keep hanging on, guys!
I'll show them!
My bold cooking!
Learning that the Sunny was still on the run,
Katakuri ordered it set on fire.
Leave them alone!
I thought you were in a one-on-one duel with me,
Straw Hat.
Now, burn down Straw Hat's ship!
Roger!
Stop!!
"The Green Room!
An Invincible Helmsman, Jimbei!"
Stop!
No, you stop.
Leave my little brother and sisters alone!
I won't let you do it!
That's our brother!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
What?
Damn you!
A mirror!
Hey, Nami!
Jimbei, can you hear me?!
Somebody! Respond!
ON THE SEA IN TOTTO LAND
Wedding...
...cake!
Incoming on the right!
Jimbei! Port to avoid!
Okay!
The second round, loaded!
Fire!
Oh, no! They keep firing!
Guard Point!
Swallow Banderole!
Hey! Can you hear me?! Somebody!
What? Luffy?!
Nami!
Luffy, it's me! You alright?!
There are still some mirrors on the ship,
aren't there?!
--What?!
--Maybe in the boys' room or the bathroom?!
It's burning up!
We're gonna shoot, Joscar.
Yes, we are, Marscar.
It's burning! It's burning!
Luffy?! What about mirrors?!
Break them all! To pieces!
Are you out of your mind?!
How would you come back, then?!
I don't know but it should be all right!
I'll figure something out!
Sniff, sniff...
I smell something!
I don't have a nose though!
What?
The room is on fire!
What's wrong?!
How is this happening?!
What?!
Flaming arrows from inside the mirror!
Cannon-shots from behind!
One thing after another!
My eyes are spinning!
Oh, I don't have eyes to spin though!
Never mind! Let's put it out, Brook!
Now, you guys, keep shooting!
We're gonna keep shooting, Joscar.
Yes, we are, Marscar.
Enough, you idiots!
Luffy!
D-Dammit!
It serves you right!
Now, shoot it up!
Stop...
Sir, the milk, bananas and yogurt
that you ordered have arrived!
Oh, thanks! Bring them here!
Yes, sir!
INSIDE CHOCOLAT TOWN'S SWEETS FACTORY
We have to rush! We can't waste any time!
Oh, Pudding-sama!
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
There's no time for you to collapse!
W-We have a problem!
We're 30 grams short of butter!
What?!
Oh, please! We can't make it in time
if we order it now!
Even if it's just 30 grams,
it'll change the taste.
We can't stop Mama then...
What should we do?
--Don't worry!
--What?
Do we have prunes?
Y-Yes, we do...
Good. Let's turn them into a puree
and use it as substitute.
What?
Add some baking powder
and reduce the amount of sugar.
That'll compensate for the lack of butter.
Uh-huh. You're right.
Everyone! Hurry up!
Yes, ma'am!
Sanji-san...
In addition, you can cut back on calories.
So it turns out to be better for ladies.
Pudding-sama!
I told you that there's no time to collapse!
H-How dependable!
That's what I'd expect from Pudding-sama's husband!
What?!
You two truly are a perfect match!
Per... fect... mat... ch...
You really are an ideal husband and wife!
hus... band... and... wife...
Pudding-sama!
I told you to stop! We're running out of time!
Luffy!
Luffy! Are you okay?!
Those of you who'll march into the ship!
Follow me!
Oh, no!
Nami! Hurry up and break the mirrors!
All of them!
But...
An army of enemies is on its way!
I can't stop them by myself!
Let me focus just on this guy!
Huh?
Nami! We have a problem!
We can't get away!
A high wave!
What?!
You there...?
I'm sorry, Luffy...
I won't let you get away!
Nami! What's wrong?!
This...
...might be it for us...
Candy, candy... sluggie-gie!
What do you mean by that?!
What's happening there?!
Hey! Guys!
Straw Hat!
If we get swallowed up by it, we're dead!
Oh, yeah! The Coup de Burst!
We can't use it!
We don't have enough cola!
Pedro, I'm sorry!
You sacrificed yourself to save us but...
Everyone, listen!
My cake!
Wait! Wait, wait!
Wait a minute, Mama!
If you do that,
the cake will sink into the sea, too!
Mama!
--Hurry up!
--Okay!
D-Does this look okay, Jimbei-san?!
Yes, that's good enough!
But it's impossible!
You're trying to trim all the sails on the ship single-handedly!
Nami! How is the wind?!
A strong wind is coming from the south!
All right!
What are you going to do, Jimbei?!
I'm gonna tack the ship quickly!
What?!
You must be kidding! Why do you wanna
turn the ship?!
We'll enter the Green Room!
Here we go! Here we go!
Give it to me!
Green Room?! What is that?!
Why are we heading towards the wave?!
Jimbei!
Wedding...
...cake!
I see! By "Green Room," you mean "heaven"!
Doctor! I'm finally coming to meet you!
It's over! This is impossible! It's not surfing!
Pedro!
Hold on to the ship tightly!
Splash!
What's wrong?! What happened?!
Hey, can you hear me?!
Somebody! Say something!
Huh?
Are we in heaven? It's beautiful...
This is a hell of a ship!
The Green Room is a brief "wave room"
that forms inside a collapsing wave.
To children of the Fish-Man Tribe,
it was a perfect place to play!
Then, this space is...
No way...
We're inside the wave?!
We're gonna sail through it! Hang on!
You got a nice ship and a good navigator!
If you can control it well, this ship is invincible!
I can't believe it! He's controlling the sloop
like it's his own limb!
I've never seen such a helmsman!
You're cool, Jimbei!
So we're not gonna die?!
Yay!
I thought we weren't gonna make it!
That's impressive, Jimbei-san!
Very impressive, Jimbei!
Hm? Nami?
Bubble, bubble... Sluggie-gie...
Wedding...
...cake!
Well, who cares...
That serves those little punks right!
My lie was swallowed by the sea along with their ship!
Lick!
This is Perospero. Hey, Katakuri.
We took care of all of them!
What?!
Hey, Nami! Brook! Carrot!
Chopper! Jimbei!
Oh, no!
We were gonna invade the ship now!
The plan's aborted, guys!
It seems like the ship has already
sank into the sea.
But it's strange, Big Sis.
The other side of the mirror
doesn't look like it's underwater.
Look!
No way!
But, just to make sure, shoot one more.
Wow! The mirror! Big Sis, it suddenly broke!
What? What? What's going on?!
Nami-san! Why did you break the mirror?!
Luffy-san can't come back to the ship without it!
Let me focus just on this guy!
Just break them all!
All the mirrors on the ship!
But...
Do you wanna get in Luffy's way?!
It's the Captain's orders! Hurry up!
The barrage of Katakuri's deadly attack,
Willow Mochi, corners Luffy!
There is only one piece of a mirror that allows Luffy and his crew
to promise to reunite.
For his deeply-worried crew,
Captain Luffy shows his chivalrous spirit!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Threat of the Mole! Luffy's Silent Fight!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!