Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting in their own places
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Katakuri cornered Luffy
with his awakened Mochi-Mochi Fruit ability.
Mirror Mochi!
What? Those are mochi, too?!
You're dead!
No one's ever gotten away from my mochi!
I'm sorry that I have to wrap it up this way...
I was getting a little irritated!
Since it took me a lot of time and trouble to beat you,
I'm 40 minutes late for today's merienda.
Goodbye, Straw Hat...
"The Forbidden Secret!
Katakuri's Merienda!"
Pâtissiers!
Yes, sir!
We're on our way!
Katakuri-sama! That was
an incredible victory!
Of course, your win was
inevitable from the beginning!
But we were concerned
whether you could eat today's snack!
We were all ready and
waiting at three o'clock!
We know that you're a
perfectionist who wants to
have your merienda at a fixed time
every day so we feel your regret!
I don't need your compliments or consolation...
Prepare my merienda.
Yes, sir!
E-Excuse me...
The thing is, your tea...
...became cold after 40 minutes...
Iced tea is fine.
How generous!
But we're proud of today's sweets!
Here are your merienda today!
For Katakuri-sama who is himself perfect!
We made them from the perfect ingredients!
By using lots of the finest Corioli cacao
that we bought on the black market
and rich cow's milk that's
been pastured at a Sky Island
managing to keep its
dortisol level under nine,
we made this sweet chocolate doughnut!
And for this one,
we whipped the highest grade cream
which we got from the Minister of Cream
- Opera-sama the other day,
and made an icing, then gorgeously decorated the doughnut,
topped with sweet strawberries!
It's a feast for your eyes as well!
What's more, we prepared a doughnut
kneaded through with the Celestial Dragons' favorite sugar,
in order to make the spicy taste of Meylon cinnamon
stand out and so on...
They all have the richest taste possible
and we're pretty sure you'll be satisfied!
Please enjoy the extra-special sweetness!
I used so much Haki in the
battle against Straw Hat...
To take care of his crew who are on the run,
I need to take in enough energy.
Sugar is a source of power!
I'm gonna consume it.
--I'm going to enter the shrine...
--Yes, sir!
Don't let anyone in.
Of course not! No one will bother you!
Take your time!
He's so vigilant...
No one has ever seen him eat something...
How sensitive he is.
When eating, people let their guard down.
But even teatime in which
we can relax with others,
he makes into a time to concentrate his mind
and get nutrition by himself stoically...
That's our warrior who is worth over a billion
and serves as the backbone of the Big Mom Pirates!
He's totally in a different class
from the captain of the weak little pirate group...
Uh?
What's wrong?
Wasn't it there?
What?
Straw Hat's hand...
--Was it?
--Didn't you imagine it?
--Wh-What the?!
--What's going on?!
--The mochi is moving!
--Like I can't see it?!
--Why is it moving?!
--How do I know?!
What?! Straw Hat!
--He wasn't dead?!
--How did he get out of that giant mochi?!
I ate the mochi!
What?!
What's with the pirate battles in this place?!
I have to eat something every time to win?!
Only you can eat that much!
Hey! Where did he go?!
You mean Katakuri-sama?
Don't let anyone in.
Too bad! He's not here now!
He left the Mirroworld earlier!
He has important business!
Now, shall we go, too?!
Goodbye!
I feel the "voice" of someone strong there!
Oh, no! The Color of Observation?!
He's eating doughnuts.
Sniff, sniff.
The Color of Observation?
No, he just has a good nose...
That jerk! He must be relaxing
thinking he won!
No way! A fool like you can't understand him!
He is talking to the god of war
and to himself in the shrine now!
It's a holy time.
No one can disturb... him...
Wh-What the...?
Hey, where are you going?!
After all, that idiot got intimidated!
That's what I expected from
the captain of a weak little pirate group!
He's only good at running away!
--Is he coming back?!
--Why?!
I've lost weight!
Huh?! Is that how a human body works?!
All right! I'm all ready now! Let's go!
Stop!
Go away, go away!
Stay away from the shrine!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Katakuri-sama! We're very sorry!
Oh, doughnuts!
--What?
--What?!
Whaaat?!
CHOCOLAT TOWN'S SWEETS FACTORY
I want you to move fast but don't rush!
Quickly but carefully!
It's pointless if we
can't make a superb cake!
Roger!
Ah, Sanji-san... How dependable he is...
Pudding-sama! Pudding-sama!
Pudding-sama!
I'm sorry!
No, no! I have to focus on cooking now!
Chiffon-sama! The test cake is done!
Oh, it looks good!
Do you wanna try?
Huh? What... What?!
How is it?
Mmm... That's what I expected
from you, Chiffon-chan!
I wanna eat this for the rest of my life!
You're so sweet!
Oh, it's on your cheek.
Pudding-sama...
I'm not jealous! I'm not jealous at all!
Are you doing alright, Pudding-chan?
He's worried about me!
Pudding-sama!
I'm counting on you!
It's going well.
If we can keep up like this...
We're arriving at Cacao Island.
Pudding-sama has already started making the cake
at the Sweets Factory.
I'll go see how it's going as soon as we arrive.
Tell them so!
Yes, sir!
Oh, doughnuts!
So delicious, doughnuts!
Delicious to the hole, doughnuts!
By myself, I eat doughnuts!
Lying on my back, I eat doughnuts!
A forbidden pleasure, a sense of guilt and...
Doughnuts!
This is a blissful time.
Doughnuts, doughnuts...
Oh, doughnuts!
So delicious, doughnuts!
Big Bro Katakuri is a superhuman!
He's never once been on his back
since he was born!
He's a man who looks down on the ground!
He's always noble!
Calm and strong!
He's perfect in every way!
That's who our Big Bro Katakuri is!
You saw me eating!
The fight is still on!
What?
H-Have mercy!
I didn't see it! I didn't see anything!
I won't tell anyone!
Even if someone slits my mouth!
What did you say about my mouth?
Edged Mochi!
Nooo!!
You're alive!
I'm sorry that I didn't wait until you died!
I couldn't take it anymore!
Ouch!
There is a Color of Arms
that's better than yours!
Don't think you can compete against me!
You're just a worm to me!
You think you can beat me.
Stop being so confident!
Those who have seen my true self...
...can't be left alive!
Damn!
He didn't dodge and got kicked!
Why?
So what if I got kicked?!
I could ward it off easily!
The second attack didn't come right away!
I'm starting to understand...
...your ability.
Huh? What do you think you understand?!
I told you so many times!
Your ability is no match for me!
Here I go!
This time, I'll watch you dying!
Gear Four!
Rainfall Mochi!
Bounce-Man!
You're strong but not unbeatable!
Screw you!!
Get crushed!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Gun!
Katakuri's ability against which
no attack stands a chance...
Luffy finally finds out
its surprising secret!
A furious series of his Gear Four attacks corners Katakuri
aiming
at destroying the legendary
undefeated opponent!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy Fights Back! The Invincible
Katakuri's Weak Point!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!