Yes! We've got Super Powers
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Your dream is like a monster
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
will become your one and only treasure
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing in a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
The future gently brings a morning
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting in their own places
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Having cut off his retreat, Luffy
continues the fierce one-on-one dual
he challenged Sweet General Katakuri to.
Goodbye, Straw Hat...
I ate the mochi!
What?!
What's with the pirate battles in this place?!
I have to eat something every time to win?!
Oh, doughnuts!
So delicious, doughnuts!
Delicious to the hole, doughnuts!
You saw me eating!
Those who have seen my true self...
...can't be left alive!
I'm starting to understand...
...your ability.
"Luffy Fights Back!
The Invincible Katakuri's Weak Point!"
Gear Four!
Rainfall Mochi!
Bounce-Man!
You're strong but not unbeatable!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Gun!
Watch very carefully!
There are two prominent types of Haki!
--Watch out!
--Don't worry.
He's trying to hit me with his trunk
from the right.
It's the power to feel other's
presence more strongly -
called Haki of the Color of Observation!
If you enhance this power, you can tell
where your invisible enemy is,
and how many there are,
and what their next move will be.
Next, the Haki of the Color of Arms.
This power is the same as
wearing invisible armor.
Old man!
If the armor is hard enough,
it can be used as the offensive power.
Ouch! I'm a rubber man
so I shouldn't feel pain!
This is an efficient part of this power.
Other than exploiting their weak point,
this Haki of the Color of Arms is...
...the only effective countermove
against Devil Fruit power-users.
Logia-type Devil Fruit power-users seem
almost invincible because of their fluid body
but you can hit them solidly.
I thought that you were invincible!
Because the Color of Arms should allow me
to hit someone solidly!
And it should work even for Logia-users, too!
But my attacks went through your body!
I was wrong!
You can get...
...hit, too!
Even your iron-tight Armament Defense...!
I can break it in Gear Four!
Gum-Gum...
...Leo Bazooka!
...Culverin!
What's so remarkable
isn't your mochi ability!
But your Color of Observation,
isn't that right?!
Gum-Gum...
...Rhino Schneider!
Big Bro Katakuri...
...is a superhuman who's
never once been on his back!
This is it!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Organ Gun!
You figured it out...
That's impressive.
You're right. I'm just changing my own shape
and evading efficiently...
I can do that by seeing
the future with my Haki.
I just lost my cool a little bit...
...so I gave you chances to attack.
The Color of Observation can't be utilized
if you're not calm.
How many years has it been
since I last got punched?
I can see why my little brother Cracker
got beaten...
...just a little bit now.
The biscuit guy, huh?
Unstoppable Donuts!
It's not mochi this time?! Screw you!
Rhino...
Power Mochi!
I won't give you one more inch...
We're going back to square one.
CACAO ISLAND
What's going on inside?
CHOCOLAT TOWN'S SWEETS FACTORY
Are they okay?
What the?
Th-That's...
Bring me roasted soy flour and yogurt!
Baking powder! Stat!
Pudding-sama, you got a call!
Not now. I'm busy.
But it's from Brulee-sama.
What would you like to do?
Put it there.
Pudding, are you there?
Big Sis Brulee, what's the matter?
How's it going with the wedding cake?
It's going fine.
It'll be ready by the time Mama gets here.
I see. That's good.
The thing is, I wanna let you know
something concerning the Straw Hats.
I eavesdropped on their secret conversation.
Please! Open the door!
We can't do that, Pound-san!
Please give up and step back.
Why can't you?
Pudding-sama told us strictly.
I just wanna see Chiffon even
if only for a little bit!
Chiffon-sama?
Who is that?
He's Mama's 25th ex-husband...
Ah!
I knew it was her immediately!
Chiffon looked exactly the
same as when she was born.
She's as cute as she ever was.
I want to see her and talk to her
even if only for a moment!
Hey! Hey!
Isn't it a little noisy out there?
Some guy is yelling, huh?
But no worries. No one can enter!
What's wrong, Pudding?
Nothing. Big Sis Brulee, I'm listening.
So at 1 AM tonight,
the Straw Hats' ship that we lost
will emerge at Cacao Island where you are now!
Here?! At 1 AM?
The plan was to meet up with
Nami-san and the others at sea
and hand over the wedding cake...
Why do they wanna come to Cacao Island?
Because that's where they're gonna rendezvous
with their stray captain Straw Hat Luffy!
I see... But it's no good.
Big Mom and everyone know the plan!
Although...
Straw Hat Luffy will never
make it to Cacao Island!
What do you mean?
He pushed his luck and challenged
Big Bro Katakuri to a one-on-one duel!
So he'll definitely be destroyed...
That serves him right!
One, two!
It's 4 PM now, right?
That means, in nine hours,
the Straw Hats will arrive at Cacao Island
and wait for their captain who'll never appear.
Mama in her Hunger Pangs, and Big Bro Peros
who are after them will be there, too.
Everyone will gather together!
We can't afford to fail in that situation!
You take care of Mama, Pudding!
You're our only hope!
Count on me, Big Sis Brulee!
I'll stop Mama with the
greatest wedding cake ever!
I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, by the way,
even if the Straw Hats arrive
there sooner, don't worry.
You can leave them to Big Bro Oven's troops
who just got there!
What?! Big Bro Oven's here?!
It's Oven-sama!
Oven-sama!
CHARLOTTE OVEN
4TH SON OF CHARLOTTE, MINISTER OF BAKING
What do you mean I can't enter the factory?!
That's Pudding-sama's order...
Even me?!
Yes, no one.
Well, if that's what my sister wants,
I'll accept.
Then why is it so noisy
in front of the factory?!
What? Oh, that's because...
Hey! Chiffon!
He's...
S-Stop hurting me!
Shut up, you prowler!
D-Don't you remember me, Oven-kun?!
I remember you, my ex-stepdad.
I-I'm happy that you remember me.
I used to be your stepfather.
That's why I must remove you.
What?
Mama will be here soon.
Oh, Linlin will?!
Stop calling her that!
If she hears about this,
she'll get madder.
So I gotta get you as far away as possible
before she comes!
Wh-What are you gonna do...?
I just wanna see Chiffon even
if only for a little bit...
I wonder who's making noise out there.
Does it bother you?
Sanji-san! Were you listening?
Yeah.
Luffy-kun is in trouble!
Right.
I can't believe he's challenging Big Bro Katakuri
to a one-on-one duel.
That's too reckless!
I bet so.
Big Bro Katakuri is a superhuman!
His bounty is over a billion!
He's never been defeated!
What should we do?!
Then today,
he'll lose for the first time.
It's my turn to say...
This is it.
I won't lose!
I'll win!
The cake-baking in order to take down
Big Mom finally comes to a climax!
What is Sanji's secret ingredient ?
the ultimate whipped cream's tremendous power?!
Meanwhile, Luffy receives
Katakuri's fierce attacks again
and as his Gear Four runs out
of time, he gets cornered!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Another Crisis! Gear Four vs. Unstoppable Donuts!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!