Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting in their own places
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Luffy challenged Sweet General Katakuri
to a one-on-one dual
but since his Gear Four ran out,
he tried to ride it out in safety someplace else.
--Help!
--You fool!
Big Brother!
Why were you there?!
Wait! Straw Hat!
However, that place was Nuts Island
where Big Mom was wreaking havoc.
Where are you?! Straw Hat!
Big Mom?
Meanwhile, Sanji and the others...
It's done!
The ultimate cream - Simsim Whip!
To save some time, we'll
finish the cake on the ship!
Let's get together with the Sunny
that's on its way here, A.S.A.P.!
Here we go!
Let's take down Big Mom
who's causing our friends pain!
"The Rebellious Daughter, Chiffon!
Sanji's Big Plan for Transporting the Cake!"
Where is it?!
Wedding cake!
Run!
Oh, no... If nothing is done,
Nuts Island will be destroyed!
Mama, listen to me!
Neither the cake nor the Straw Hats are here!
Where are we?
Hey, Branch!
It's Brulee!
What's happening?
Straw Hat is...
Straw Hat?!
What?!
Straw Hat?! Brulee?!
Big Sis Amande!
What?! Straw Hat Luffy the pirate?!
Why is he here?!
Mama, look! Straw Hat is right there!
Straw Hat!
Why's Big Mom here?!
I thought she was chasing
after the Sunny on the sea!
Help, Mama!
Mama!
Oh, no! She's coming this way!
Straw Hat! Where is the cake?!
I told you I don't know!
Mama, Big Bro Peros! Help me!
Let go of her!
Candy Wall!
Gear Three!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Pistol!
It's no good! I can't break it without Haki!
Lick.
It's surrounding us!
Slow Waltz!
Yikes!
Big Sis! Don't cut me!
My Famous Sword Shirauo is craving blood...
Suffer like hell before you die.
I can't fight you guys now!
Mirror! Mirror!
Big Bro Peros!
This candy is in my way!
Candy Slug!
Give it to me!
Cake!
I have to keep running
until I regain my Haki!
CACAO ISLAND
It's all set! We must leave, mister!
Okay.
Mister, why are you in disguise?
Because I'm shy.
Clear the way, everyone!
We're taking the cake to the port!
Oh, whoa!
They baked it in such a short time?!
It's already assembled!
And it smells really good!
When it's complete,
I'm sure Mama will love it!
The smell makes me happy!
Are we in heaven?!
That's what I expected from Pudding-sama
and Chiffon-sama!
And WCI: 31!
Alright! Mama's coming!
We gotta run!
Pudding-sama! Chiffon-sama!
Please take care!
You just wait, Big Mom.
I'll let you taste the ultimate cake!
Oh! That's surely my daughter!
Chiffon! It's no mistake!
Wait, Pudding!
He's...
Big Bro Oven! Keep out of our way!
Pudding, where are you gonna take that cake?
I heard you were gonna ambush the Straw Hats
and Mama in her Hunger Pangs
attack here on this island!
We'll finish the cake on the ship
and stop Mama at sea!
At sea?!
Do you wanna let the rampaging Mama
come ashore at Chocolat Town?!
If we can contact Big Bro Peros,
we can meet up at sea!
Yeah, you're right.
I understand. My dear
little sister, go ahead.
Great! Thank you, Big Bro Oven!
But Chiffon!
You can't go any farther!
Big Sis Chiffon!
Oh, that's terrible, Oven-sama!
How could you do that to your little sister?!
It's none of your business!
This is our family's problem!
Let them take the cake to the port!
Yes, sir!
Big Sis Chiffon!
Chiffon-chan...
Chiffon...
How could you appear in front of me?!
You know what your husband tried to do...
don't you?!
Even if you're family,
treason is an inexcusable crime!
Stop it, Big Bro Oven!
Wait, Pudding-chan!
If you go now, you'll be
seen as a traitor, too!
What?
Ah! He's worried about me!
But I can't reveal myself
and fight, either...
What should I do?!
Give it to me!
Cake!
Big Bro Peros, stop her! It's my town!
Mama, you're way out of line!
You're ruining the town!
I won't let you get away! Straw Hat!
Damn! The town is all messed up!
Hm? Where did Straw Hat go?!
Man, that was really close!
But if Big Mom is here, that means
Nami and the others got away
safely at that time, right?
In any case, I need to rest now
until I regain my Haki!
I dropped Branch!
Where did she go?! That fool!
Hey! Come out! Where are you?!
What kind of an idiot comes out like that
when being told to!
Come out, Branch!
It's Brulee!
Damn...
There you are!
What have I done?!
I'll never lose you again! Without you,
I can't travel through mirrors!
Damn! You're a demon! A devil! A brute!
Now, I gotta find a mirror!
There's one! Let's go, Branch!
It's Brulee!
CHARLOTTE EFFILER - FIFTH
DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat!
Big Sis Effiler!
Go to hell!
I'll return them all to you! Fire Salute!
Let's run!
Help me, Big Sis!
Wait!
Don't shoot me!
I can't fight them without Haki!
Damn!
Where can I find a mirror?!
CHARLOTTE MONDER - SECOND
DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
I found you-monder!
This is Amande's island-monder.
I won't let you do whatever you like-monder.
Help! Big Sis Monder!
Let go of Brulee-monder!
Gum-Gum...
...Branch!
It's Brulee!
Whew, that was close!
That's my line!
Don't use me as a shield!
You won't get away-monder!
Gum-Gum...
...Branch!
It's Brulee!
--Branch!
--It's Brulee!
Brulee!
It's Branch!
Oh! Oops...
What?!
Where is it?! Mirror... Mirror!
There he is!
Straw Hat!
Where is the... cake?!
Mama, watch out! Brulee's there, too!
Mama! It's Brulee!
Oh, no!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
What should I do? What should I do?
Chiffon-chan?
I'm... already determined...!
My repayment won't be over
until I see Nami and the others leaving safely!
I'll... help making the cake until it's finished,
Big Bro!
They saved Lola's life...
I can't fulfill my duty like this!
This is not a quarrel between siblings
or teenage rebellion, Chiffon!
You're a traitor who tried to kill our queen!
I'd never expected I'd kill my sister...
Stop, Big Bro!
We need to set an example
for the others in this country!
Big Sis Chiffon!
Oh, no... Maybe I shouldn't be worried about
the consequences now!
Get your hands off of Chiffon!
Oven-kun!
I'm gonna save you! My dear daughter!
Who is he?!
You fool!
I thought I tossed you into the sea!
Whoever that is...
I'd better just save her quickly...
...so no one can see!
Hm? What?
Let's jump, Chiffon-chan.
What?
What? Did he just knock Oven-sama down?!
Who is that old man?!
Am I stronger than I thought?
Oh? Chiffon?
It obviously wasn't you!
Who did that?!
Black-Leg...
You're safe now, Chiffon-chan.
Thank you!
Big Sis, you have to hide!
O-Okay.
Let's rush to the sea!
Clear the way!
Black-Leg saved me...
But...
Who was that big man?
There you are, Chiffon!
Don't, Big Bro Oven!
You little...
Wait! We need Big Sis Chiffon
to complete the cake!
Chiffon!
Stop! Get your hands off of Chiffon...
She's more than just an ungrateful child...
I'll burn you to the bone!
Prepare yourself, Chiffon!
Stop it! Big Bro Oven!
If you do that, we can't stop
Mama's Hunger Pangs attack!
I guess I gotta get out there!
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
What is it?!
Oven-sama, we found Bege's ship!
Bege's ship is heading there,
towards Cacao Island!
Our fleet is pursuing them!
We'll drive them to the port!
Bege! You've got to be kidding!
I thought he was heartless
but I guess he's coming to save you!
Bege?!
Surround the ship!
There's only one enemy ship!
Drive it to the port!
Ya-hoo!
Boy, how reckless Chiffon is...
But that's my sweet honey!
Oh, good boy, good boy! I'm sorry!
You must be scared!
Chiffon, here I come!
Luffy runs around waiting for his Haki to
be recharged but Katakuri closes in on him!
Meanwhile, Chiffon is captured by Oven,
and Bege is surrounded by a great army.
The cornered Bege now takes a
big bet at the risk of his life!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Man's Way of Life! Bege and
Luffy's Determination as Captains!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!