Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Sanji is transporting the wedding cake
so as to fend off Big Mom's Hunger Pangs attack.
However, Oven, barging into the carriage carrying the cake,
caught Chiffon,
and commanded Bege who was trying to meet up with
Sanji and the others, to surrender.
What fools.
Burn it into your memory, Pez.
This is the way Papa lives.
Meanwhile, Luffy moved out of the Mirroworld
waiting for his Haki to be replenished...
I wonder if I can see
slightly ahead into the future, too.
What are you talking about?!
Don't push your luck, you short-ass!
I wanna surpass him!
I wanna defeat him at full strength!
The man with...
...a bounty of a billion!
"The Cake Sank?!
Sanji and Bege's Getaway Battle!"
10 minutes has passed.
Did he run back to his crew?
That's okay.
He can't get away from Mama anyway...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Why?
Armament Hardening!
Th-The cake is...
...flying in the air...
Hurry up, Bege!
Back off, guys!
Make room on the deck!
Y-Yes! Father!
Black-Leg! Alright, come on!
Who the hell is that?!
With just one leg...
Is he a chef?!
Okay! Let's go!
Everyone! Prepare for the impact!
The cake made it!
That was amazing, Black-Leg!
What's this good smell?
O-Only Germa could do that!
I'm not Germa!
Thanks for your work.
Bege! Pez!
Are you alright, honey?
Yes...
You're always so reckless...
Thank you!
S-Sanji...
...sa...
Pudding-sama! Stay with us!
I'm not gonna let them get away!
Oh, no!
Oven-sama! Please get out of the way!
Don't you know who I am?!
I'll stop that!
Come on!
SQUISH!
He got run over!
Don't take my paddle ship lightly.
Oh, good boy, good boy, Pez.
I know it was a little too loud...
He's still there...
--Peek-a-boo!
--Who is that guy? A peeping Tom?
Huh? What's the matter, Pez?
It looks like she's happy.
We wanna set sail towards
the southeast, Bege.
Okay...
We should just run through the town like this
and get to the sea.
Pudding!
We'll have to run over some chocolate houses.
What?!
In order to sail out all together,
we have no choice!
What a waste.
I'll fix them later.
Houses can be rebuilt.
So can families.
Yeah. Of course it'd be best
if they didn't break down...
This is my house now.
And I have this many new family members.
Ma'am!
You bastards!
Don't use cannons!
You might blow up the cake!
They're gonna get to the sea!
Don't let them escape!
Fleet, head for the southeast of the island!
We're on our way!
Alright! We got off of Cacao Island!
Hooray!
The Tart ships are far behind of us-rero.
No one can catch up to this paddle ship now.
Thank you, Bege. You saved us.
I didn't do it for you guys, Black-Leg!
Isn't it peculiarly hot?
Yeah, it is.
Father, the sea doesn't look right-rero!
--Fish are floating to the surface!
--They're boiled by the heated water?!
With the right amount of salt,
they probably taste good...
We'll get boiled next, idiot!
There's only one guy capable of this...
Look!
Tsk! I knew that he wouldn't die
just by getting run over by a ship...
Tropical Torment!
With my Heat-Heat Fruit,
I will boil you all to death!
It's hot!
It's simmering-rero!
We have other issues!
Oh, no! The temperature of the chocolate
will change!
The whipped cream will melt, too!
That means...
If nothing is done,
the cake for Big Mom will be ruined!
That fool, what is he thinking?!
Boiled fish won't make Big Mom happy!
What happened?!
The paddles got broken by the heat!
Rero-rero! Does he wanna sink our ship?!
Did Oven-sama forget how
important this cake is?!
It's okay...
It's gonna be okay...
Sink...
Sink!
You're acting strange...
Why do you suddenly start laughing and stuff, Pez?!
Who the hell are you?
Oven-sama! Watch out!
Stop!
Oven-sama!
What's going on?
Who is that?
Oven-sama's old enemy?
Pound!
Y-You're quite tough...
You fool!
Are you trying to kill your stepson?!
Father! The water temperature is dropping!
Retract the paddles!
Let's sail through this heated area quickly!
Yes, sir!
Let's hurry up and get out of here!
Yes, ma'am!
My grandchild whose name I don't even know.
Are you happy?
Let your father and mother care for you...
I couldn't do that for my kids...
Not yet? Not yet?
Linlin, you gave birth!
Yeah... Lola and Chiffon...
They're twins.
Twins?! I wanna hold them.
What?!
You've already served your purpose.
Go away.
What?
Linlin?
What are you talking about?
I'm their father! We're...
"Family"?
Don't overestimate yourself.
Linlin!
They're my children!
Please!
I wanna hold them at least once!
Linlin!
They're... my children...
That was 26 years ago...
Chiffon...
I'm so happy to see you even just once.
It seems like you're being chased,
but I'm glad that you look happy...
What's the matter, Pez?
You'll be fine!
We're leaving the hot sea soon!
There's nothing to be afraid of!
Stop, Mama!
Shut up!
Why did I give birth to twins?!
You're probably a failure just like Lola!
Stop...!
Kids who don't serve a purpose for me
aren't my family!
Don't show your stupid face to me!
It's alright. Daddy and Mommy are right here.
I've always been worried.
Did you have hard days?
Did you have lonely days?
I'm sorry that I couldn't be there for you
on those days...
I know it's late,
but let me say this.
Congratulations...
...on your marriage!
Chiffon!!
What?!
--We got out of it-rero!
--Let's keep this up and lose them!
The cake just barely made it through.
Let's hurry up! We don't have time!
We'll start decorating!
--Okay!
--Yeah!
ON THE SEA - THE SUNNY
There you are!
Give me the cake!
B-B... B-B-Big Mom?!
No matter how you look at it,
she's too strong for us!
What should we do?!
Maybe we'd better run here...
If we stop, that'll be the end!
Let's just run!
--Here we go!
--I'll go first!
I'll get them!
Oh? Who's our enemy?
It's the Straw Hats!
Oh, yeah! But I don't see the straw hat!
Excuse me! Where did the Straw Hats go?!
They went that way!
What?!
--Let's go! It's that way!
--Thanks for your kindness!
Oh! I can't go any farther!
--What were they?
--I don't know.
Idiots!
Why are all of those shells so useless?!
What's going on?!
As you know, when Mama isn't in her right mind,
they become undisciplined!
Let me go!
No, me!
Bavarois-sama! I can do it!
CHARLOTTE BAVAROIS -
TWENTY-SIXTH SON OF CHARLOTTE
Damn...
Mama hasn't slowed down...
We're at full speed, too!
Why can't we catch up to them?!
Well, they have Jimbei
who knows sea inside and out...
Bavarois-sama! We just got a call!
Here they come!
Guys!
What's the matter, Carrot?!
There are a bunch of ships ahead!
What?!
Oh, no! We're sandwiched!
Wedding cake!
Gear Three!
We just got together again.
Don't get too wild.
Even if you just ran away,
since I'm your opponent,
no one would've jeered at you.
Why did you come back?
Surrounded by a grand fleet led by Daifuku and Smoothie,
the Sunny faces a dire predicament.
However, just then,
inheriting Pedro's spirit,
Carrot transforms into her alternate form
which looks ferocious but beautiful under the moonlight!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sulong! Carrot's Big Mystic Transformation!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!