Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
The future gently brings a morning
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
After moving the wedding cake to Bege's ship,
Sanji and the others tried to escape from Cacao Island
but Oven stood in their way.
I will boil you all to death!
They were saved by Chiffon's father Pound
who happened to be there.
Congratulations...
...on your marriage!
Chiffon!!
Meanwhile, Luffy regained his Haki and
went back to the Mirroworld where Katakuri was waiting.
Even if you just ran away,
since I'm your opponent,
no one would've jeered at you.
Why did you come back?
"Sulong!
Carrot's Big Mystic Transformation!"
You chose death over the shame of
others thinking you ran away?
Chose death?
Or you've noticed
that you're no match for me
and come to beg to be our ally?
Beg?
Cut the crap...
I...
...came to defeat you!
Came to defeat me?
You're not given...
...such an option!
I won't let you get away!
Straw Hat!
Damn...
Before we got Big Mom and the others off of our tail,
our path ahead has been blocked...
Carrot!
Who's fleet is it that's in our way?!
Hang on!
That writing...
It says "Daifuku"!
What?! So it's him...
If I remember right,
he was at the Tea Party...
You got nowhere left to run,
you damn Straw Hats...
This will be your graveyard...
Bavarois-sama!
A fleet led by Daifuku-sama has arrived
ahead of us!
And we have reinforcements from behind!
Behind?
That's...
A fleet of reinforcements led by Sweet
General Smoothie-sama has arrived!
SWEET GENERAL SMOOTHIE
14TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
In addition, the flag ship which
Smoothie-sama is commanding,
CINNAMON - 16TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
CITRON - 15TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
has Citron-sama and Cinnamon-sama
on board as well!
That many of them?!
But with them, we're invincible!
All right. Let's do it, guys!
Yeah!
Guys!
Smoothie's fleet is coming from behind!
On top of Daifuku,
even Sweet General Smoothie is here, too...
Tart ships.
Spread out and block their way!
Roger! 15 degrees to starboard!
15 degrees to starboard!
Hey, Big Bro Peros,
why are you taking so much time for a rat?
Can I just sink them?
Do as you like. Lick...
You guys are so ostentatious!
Mama is gonna go to Cacao Island
where Pudding is waiting anyway.
It seems like Mama's getting thinner.
Lick...
Wedding cake!
All ships, prepare to fire!
As soon as their ship
comes within your range,
shoot it up!
Oh, no...
Daifuku's ships are preparing
to fire their cannons!
I don't think we're in their range yet...
Even if we try to move aside,
they'd block us from all sides.
Jimbei, let's keep advancing
without slowing down!
But we're up against Daifuku's ship...
He controls a genie and is tough to beat!
To find a way out of this situation,
we must go straight!
Right. Let's prepare ourselves.
I'll liven it up taking a Rumble Ball!
Go closer so I can jump onto their ship!
Fighting at close range...
It's gonna be tough.
--Mm-hm.
--Let's go!
They'll come into our range soon.
Fire all our shells at them.
--Yeah!
--It's our chance!
Hey, use faceless shells.
While Mama is in that condition,
they're uncontrollable.
--Oh, please!
--Daifuku-sama!
Shut up!
From now on, you must be a strong fighter
and constantly prepared.
Everyone has their own turn.
Carrot...
You-gara'll have your turn, too.
Don't worry...
I know you-gara can do it...
I'm sure you-gara can...
Be careful! They'll start shooting!
Yeah, I know!
Chobro!
Everyone!
Let me handle Daifuku and the others!
I'm sure I can help you!
Carrot?!
Because it's...
...a full-moon tonight.
Don't tell me you'll become Sulong?!
Are you trained for it?!
Don't worry... Pedro trained me.
I know what he'd say now...
"Leave it to me."
If Carrot is going,
I'm going with her!
Leave it to me, Chobro!
I may not look it
but I'm a member of the Musketeers.
Everyone, man the cannons!
We'll shoot salvos and sink it quickly!
Wait for my cue!
What do you mean, Pedro?
One day, you'll see how important it was...
...to save Luffy and the others here
and let them set sail!
I'll fight...
...on your-teia behalf...
Pedro!
What is that?
Her eyes are red...
She looks like a different person...
Carrot... So beautiful...
How mystic...
Oh, she looks pretty amazing...
I'd like to see her panties...
Is that what Duke Dogstorm was talking about?
But when we actually fought,
it turned out like this against Jack's unit
which was just a part of Kaido's army!
But we won't let it happen again!
We won't repeat the same failure!
We have an ace up our sleeve too.
If we fight again,
we'll show them the true power of the Mink Tribe!
This must be the ace he was talking about
at that time...
The true power of...
...the Mink Tribe!
D-Don't tell me that's...
We have a problem, Daifuku-sama!
It's a full moon tonight!
The Mink girl in the enemy group...
...became Sulong!
Guys! Prepare for a close-quarters battle!
If I'm correct, Pedro was from Zou,
the Phantom Island...
I guess she's from the same place...
She's gonna fall into the sea!
Carrot!
Don't worry.
Huh?! What the...
She just flew up from the surface!
Cool!
That's not all...
Here she comes! Shoot her down!
Yes, sir!
--Don't lower your guard!
--She's a fighter of Zou! She must be exceptional!
I'll bring her down!
What?!
Don't hold back! Take her out!
Damn! Shoot!
I got you!
Hey!
What's going on? Chopper!
Is she capable of that?!
Damn little rat!
Are you gonna stop our ships
by beating all soldiers in the fleet?!
While you're at it, your ship will sink!
So it's no use fighting...
The wheel?!
S-She broke the wheel!
Oh, no! Where is this ship going?!
That little rat!
Screw that little rabbit...
Let's go, Genie!
What can I do for you, Master?!
That little rabbit... I'm gonna chop her up!
I'll teach you...
...a thing or two!
Daifuku-sama! You're putting us in danger!
Where are you aiming, Genie-san?
I won't let you get away!
Come this way!
How aggravating!
Genie-uine Rage Split!
Please stop! Daifuku-sama!
That little...
That rat! She got another wheel!
What a cunning little rabbit!
She's jumping from one ship to another
and making them attack each other!
That's really amazing...
Yeah! That's awesome, right?!
She's like a little sister to me!
When the moon cycle and the weather
are in their favor,
they become quite strong.
The moon cycle and the weather?
Mm-hm...
They say if the Minks look at the clear moon
on a full moon night,
their wilder nature that remains
deep in their memories wakes up.
People call their white, ferocious look...
...Sulong, the Moon Lion!
Sulong?!
Their actual transformation makes them lose themselves
and attack others at random
so it's rather troublesome.
For others and themselves...
For themselves? What do you mean by that?
If the Minks can't control it,
it'll wear them out after just a single night of fighting
and they'll die.
What?!
Die?!
It's a double-edged sword...
The fighting technique could cost them their life.
Carrot-san...
It's so smart of her to take away their wheels!
Now, I'll go and back her up
before it becomes a close quarters battle!
--Back her up?
--You're gonna fall into the sea!
Don't worry...
Oh, yeah! He can run on water!
Because he's light!
We'll leave securing the sea route ahead to them
and keep moving forward at full speed!
--Mm-hm!
--Yeah!
Stop!
Bavarois-sama!
We have their ship in our range!
All right! Guys, shoot it up!
The enemy behind us caught up?!
Okay! I'll fight, too!
Unstoppable Donuts.
Haki becomes even stronger...
...in the heat of actual battle.
The more you face tough enemies,
the stronger you'll be.
Power Mochi!
I don't get it...
The difference in power is obvious.
Why do you wanna get up?
You know you can't win
so why do you keep fighting?
Shut up!
Don't make me repeat myself!
I...
No, you stop making me repeat myself!
There is nothing you can do to defeat me.
I'll beat you at any cost!
Using her Sulong power,
Carrot fights off the approaching ships
of Daifuku's fleet one after another.
Brook joins her and just when they think
they have repelled all the enemies,
Big Mom at the apex of her hunger shows
a stunning evolution!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Break Through! The Straw Hat's Mighty Sea Battle!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!