Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Luffy returned to the Mirroworld
where Katakuri was waiting.
I...
...came to defeat you!
Came to defeat me?
You're not given...
...such an option!
Meanwhile, at the Sunny
which has been sandwiched by the big enemy fleet...
Carrot... So beautiful...
How mystic...
"Break Through!
The Straw Hat's Mighty Sea Battle!"
Power Mochi!
I don't get it...
The difference in power is obvious.
Why do you wanna get up?
You know you can't win
so why do you keep fighting?
Shut up!
Don't make me repeat myself!
I...
No, you stop making me repeat myself!
There is nothing you can do to defeat me.
I'll beat you at any cost!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant...
...Bazooka!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Rifle!
Unstoppable Donuts!
Power Mochi!
Dodge to the left!
To the right!
Sluggie-gie!
Prometheus...
Zeus...
Mama?
Brother Peros!
Mama's acting strange!
Lick. Yeah I know!
She's gotten thinner and is breathing weirdly!
Prometheus... Zeus...
Napoleon!
What happened to Zeus and Prometheus?!
I'm calling them over now!
It's been almost eight hours
since her Hunger Pangs attack started!
We've never been unable to stop it
for this long
and never seen her getting that hungry!
Even we have no idea
what's gonna happen to her...
She's truly an unknown monster now.
Lick.
Is she gonna make it to Cacao Island?
By the way, Brother Peros,
I got a call saying that Pudding is
transporting the cake this way now!
Oh, really?! She's literally our savior!
Well, there's a problem, Big Bro!
It certainly is Pudding
who is transporting the cake...
but the ship is... Bege's, they said...
Lick? Did you say Bege?!
Why is the cake that'll save our country
on the assassins' ship?!
I-I don't know!
What do you mean you don't know?!
What are we gonna do?! We can't trust that cake anymore!
IN THE TERRITORY - BEGE'S SHIP
Coat more evenly there!
Hey! What are you doing?!
That's poison. Just pour it in already!
What are you doing, Black-Leg?!
That's my line! Screw you!
I'll never ever allow you to poison the cake!
Big Mom will eat this cake for sure.
Knowing that, what kind of idiots would we be
not to put in poison or explosives!
We can get rid of one of the Four Emperors!
Can't you see how big this chance is?!
Shut up! This is a challenge
where we put our pride as cooks on the line!
Don't do anything shitty!
We'll defeat the enemy with flavor!
Huh?! Stop dreaming!
Big Mom's eaten all kinds of delicious sweets
from around the world up until today
and you have to make a cake
that'll surpass her expectations!
That's impossible!
That's right! If we can't make that,
we'll be dead!
I'm looking forward to it!
Even if you succeed,
she won't let us walk away alive!
Cut the crap!
I guess you don't know who she used to be!
Mark my words, you'll regret not killing her
when you had the chance...
Father!
What did you do to him?!
Black-Leg!
What did you shove into his mouth?!
Ask him!
Father!
I... I could die...
Black-Leg, you bastard, I knew it!
It's so delicious that I could die!
This cream!
What?! He almost died from deliciousness?!
Father, I'm relieved-rero!
Father!
Listen to me, Bege...
You're free to do the assassination...
But you have to wait until I satisfy my guest!
I feed anyone who wants to eat!
That's what cooks do!
--Pudding-sama!
--Why are you collapsing?!
Did you eat the cream, too?!
Just don't pay her any mind!
Oh, damn...
It feels like I got hypnotized or something!
Maybe this cake will work for Big Mom, too...
Bege! I'm using my cooking skills on this
for the first time in a long while!
Believe in the power of sweets!
Yeah... Okay...
Now, let's hurry up!
Have you finished coating the cake?!
A little more to go!
Chiffon-sama!
Two chefs fell victim to the sweet smell!
Guys! Keep your wits about you until it's done!
Yes, ma'am!
Stay safe... Nami-san, I'm on my way!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
ON THE SEA IN THE TERRITORY - PROMETHEUS AND ZEUS
--Which way?
--Straight!
I'm sensing Napoleon's signal!
This is your fault, Prometheus.
We went all the way back for you to eat the wildfire!
Who do you think hurt me that bad, Zeus?!
You were manipulated by the enemy woman!
We're special Homies who were
created from Mama's soul!
If you betray her on account of your appetite again,
I won't forgive you!
I'm sorry... But those thunderclouds were good!
Do you really understand?!
--We can't steer the ship!
--We're drifting away!
IN THE TERRITORY - THE SUNNY
The sea route is opening up!
We can break through the enemy line!
Carrot is amazing!
Chopper! We must protect this ship!
Yeah!
No, they're coming back!
Thunder Charge!
Swing Arm!
I'll handle them!
Let's punch through!
--Yeah!
--Okay!
Carrot-san, wonderful!
Hey! The skeleton's running on the sea!
Just stop him!
I must keep up with her, too!
Shoot! Shoot!
Lullaby Parry!
--Wh-What the?!
--They fell asleep?!
I'm passing out! I have to stop soon.
How many ships left?
Damn that little rabbit!
Genie-uine Rage Split!
He-teia saved me the work!
We'll get her this time!
Genie...!
Carrot-san!
Guillotine!
Go to hell, brat!
I'm sorry, Pedro...
I guess this is it for me...
I hope I helped Luffy and the others...
...even a little bit.
Baron Corpse!
I'm glad that you're okay!
To the best of my poor ability,
I put everyone on the other ship to sleep!
You've already done enough.
Let's go back!
You saved me! Thank you!
No, thank you!
How do you turn back?
I can change back by shading my eyes
from the moonlight.
Hats or shades...
Or simply by closing my eyes...
Full moonlight raises our spirits!
You were really beautiful!
Carrot... Are you alright?!
Yeah...
Thank you!
You helped us out of a tight spot!
We were surrounded by the enemies
and our ship was almost sunk!
Well done! That's my little sister, Carrot!
I'm happy that I could help.
Can I stay in a room where I can't see the moon?
Of course! Leave it to us
and get some rest!
Oh, before you go,
could I see your panties...
Quit it!
Big Bro Peros!
Big Bro Daifuku can't fight anymore!
His fleet is drifting away!
How useless Daifuku is!
Mama... Are you really alright?!
There they are...
They're coming, Mama!
Zeus! Prometheus!
We're on our way!
M-Mama?! She's like a different person...
She moved like a feather...
Is that because she got too hungry?!
Lick. How many years has it been
since the last time I saw Mama move so swiftly?!
Give me the wedding cake!
Big Mom is coming!
Napoleon!
Transform into a sword!
Yes, Mama!
What the hell is that?!
Mama...
Straw Hat!
No way!
Big Mom!
What did she turn into?!
Where's my wedding cake?
Stand back, guys!
Get ready to even abandon the ship!
But...
Oh... I'm so hungry.
But nothing else can satisfy me.
Where is it?!
Where is the wedding cake?!
--No! The Sunny...!
--Oh, no!
How can we kick out such a monster?!
Unstoppable Donuts!
Nine-headed Mochi!
Gum-Gum...
Haki becomes even stronger...
...in the heat of actual battle.
The more you face tough enemies,
the stronger you'll be.
What are you doing?
Mom catches up to the Straw Hats
who are trying desperately to get away!
She destroys everything she can!
The Sunny catches fire!
But that is when Jimbei's Fish-Man Karate technique blasts off!
The battle between the Straw Hats and Mom now begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Finally, They Clash! The Emperor of the Sea vs. the Straw Hats!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!