Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Returning to the Mirroworld
with the fiery goal of taking down Katakuri,
Luffy plunged himself into
another desperate battle.
Gum-Gum...
Meanwhile,
on the ship heading towards Cacao Island,
Sanji was infuriated by Bege
who tried to poison the cake.
Listen to me, Bege...
You're free to do the assassination...
But you have to wait
until I satisfy my guest!
I feed anyone who wants to eat!
That's what cooks do!
At the same time, while the Sunny was trying to
shake the enemy fleets,
Big Mom descended.
No way!
Big Mom!
Where's my wedding cake?
Stand back, guys!
Get ready to even abandon the ship!
But...
Oh... I'm so hungry.
But nothing else can satisfy me.
Where is it?!
Where is the wedding cake?!
--No! The Sunny...!
--Oh, no!
How can we kick out such a monster?!
"Finally, They Clash!
The Emperor of the Sea vs. the Straw Hats!"
What are you doing?
There's nothing you can do now!
Handclap Mochi!
It's not working!
I still can't see it!
How about this?
Unstoppable Handclap Mochi!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
I'll break you this time!
Focus... I need to focus more...
Mochi Blade Bullet!
Right!
Up!
Mochi Blade Bullet!
I can't get a spare minute to focus!
Right!
Up!
Wall!
Back!
Damn...
His Color of Observation is unbelievable!
He's surely... strong!
I can do that by seeing
the future with my Haki.
I just lost my cool a little bit...
...so I gave you chances to attack.
The Color of Observation can't be utilized
if you're not calm.
If I can calm down...
You still try to resist,
but I'll just get rid of you.
Calm down... Calm down!
Focus! Focus!
Unstoppable Mochi Blade Bullets!
ON THE SEA IN THE TERRITORY
Wedding cake!
Did you hide it in here?!
Wait, Big Mom!
I don't see it!
It's not here!
Stop! You won't find the cake on this ship!
What?!
No way... That can't be true!
My son told me that it's here!
If it's not, I have to
kill my eldest son myself!
Sh-She remembers!
If you're lying,
you'll pay with your lifespan!
Just how lucid is she right now?!
I thought I could cover it up!
It seems like Big Bro's plan has failed...
You were too optimistic, Big Bro Peros...
Are you saying my son's a liar?!
Hey, Napoleon!
Yes, Mama!
Let's do it!
Cognac!
I'll burn you and cut you in half!
A big flaming sword!
No chance! Get away, Jimbei!
Go to hell!
Kairagi Glaze!
Mama-mash!
What the?!
He's absorbing Cognac!
Jimbei!
Don't think...
...you can overpower me, you damn shark!
Jimbei-san!
--Oh, no!
--Jimbei!
Where is it?! Give me the cake!
I'm starving to death!
Carrot!
Stop, Big Mom!
Carrot is in that room!
If you want me to stop...
Nami!
Tell me where it is!
I'm fine!
Oh, no! The sail caught
fire from Big Mom's head!
Where did you hide...
Get away, Nami!
That massive cake?!
Guard Point!
Chopper!
Well, well...
Look what you've become!
You're rarer than ever.
I'll definitely add you to
my collection of strange beasts!
You little chubby raccoon!
I-I'm not a raccoon! I'm a reindeer!
Once I get the wedding cake,
I'll make both you and Soul King my own!
Let go of me! The cake is not here
and I'm not your plaything!
Chopper!
Oh! If the ship sinks,
maybe my lie will go down with it!
If the Straw Hats lose the ship,
they'll be virtually wiped out.
The ship...!
The ship is gonna burn up!
Now, where is the wedding cake?
Let go of me!
Chopper!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
We have to put out the fire!
Water! Water!
Ocean Current...
...Shoulder Throw!
What happened?!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
Damn! Suddenly, the water...!
Oh, good!
The fire has been extinguished...
Jimbei-san!
Mama!
Get off of this ship, Big Mom!
If that's what you want...
Give me the cake!
Fish-Man Karate Hidden Technique!
Vagabond Drill!
Mama!
What?!
Yay! He kicked her out!
Jimbei, you're amazing!
--Thank goodness!
--You did it!
Guys!
If we allow them to wreck the ship anymore,
how will we face Luffy and the others?!
Don't slow down!
Once Perospero and the others
catch up to us, that'll be it!
--Yeah!
--Okay!
Count on us!
I'm sorry but...
...Big Mom will stand up again in no time!
--How's Carrot?
--She's okay!
Let's lose them at full speed!
Mama, are you okay?
Yeah!
That wasn't so bad, Jimbei!
Here she comes!
Oh! I have an idea!
I'll slice it up!
That's a good idea, Mama!
Then, I'm sure I'll find it!
The wedding cake!
It extended this time!
If she swings it around...
The ship will be finished!
At least she's not on the ship anymore!
Alright, Zeus-chan...
You like them, right?
Those are...!
Black Ball!
It's delicious! It's
delicious! So delicious!!
Yum-yum!
That's right! Now, help yourself!
What should I do?!
Humph! The same trick doesn't work twice!
Don't try to fool me, you temptress!
Nami!
It's me.
Oh, please!
That's right... I don't have any flesh
so lightning doesn't affect me.
Oh?
Do you wanna fight me, Soul King?!
I'm sorry that I don't know when to give up!
No way!
How hard her skin is!
I remember that you couldn't even
make a scratch on me with your sword!
You're right... So could I at least...
...see your panties?!
Huh?!
What?!
Okay.
It's done!
Three-Pace Hum...
...Soul...
...Notch Slash!
Our only target was you, Zeus!
Ow, ow, ow! Damn!
I let my guard down!
Stay with us, Zeus!
Positive Charge Black Ball!
Discharge and feel better, Zeus-chan!
You...!
Th-This is...
What is it?!
Unstoppable Mochi Blade Bullets!
You're holding your own
against me for this long...
I admit you have quite a lot of prowess,
Straw Hat.
But no matter how hard you try,
you can't beat me.
Unstoppable Donuts!
Damn, it's the technique he used before!
I almost... I almost can see his next move...
I can see it, Straw Hat...
Your future is in darkness!
Nine-headed Mochi!
Shut up!
My future is...
...mine to decide!
Luffy still can't see the future and
keeps ending up on the wrong end
of Katakuri's fierce attacks!
There seems to be no chance
of his winning anymore.
However, when Luffy gives an enraged war cry
and the memory of Rayleigh returns,
a miraculous turnaround begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Dark King's Direct Precepts!
The Battle Against Katakuri Turns Around!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!