Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
In the battle raging in the Mirroworld,
Luffy suffered fierce attacks
from Katakuri who had recovered his composure...
...while trying to enhance
his Haki of the Color of Observation.
Focus... I need to focus more...
Mochi Blade Bullet!
Right!
Damn...
His Color of Observation is unbelievable!
He's surely... strong!
Meanwhile, his friends on the Sunny
were cornered by Big Mom.
However, Nami and Brook caused
Zeus to discharge a bolt
and gave a tremendous blow to Big Mom.
Unstoppable Donuts!
Damn, it's the technique he used before!
I almost... I almost can see his next move...
I can see it, Straw Hat...
Your future is in darkness!
Nine-headed Mochi!
Shut up!
My future is...
...mine to decide!
"Dark King's Direct Precepts!
The Battle Against Katakuri Turns Around!"
FLOUR TOWN, WHEAT ISLAND
That scared me!
Mirrors are...
FLOUR TOWN, WHEAT ISLAND
If this goes on, there'll be
no mirror left in this town!
I didn't expect him to fight this long
against Katakuri-sama in the Mirroworld...
Is Straw Hat Luffy that strong?!
Power Mochi!
We keep getting reports on mirror-breakings
from various islands.
It's already 9:30 PM-soir.
It's been almost 12 hours
since the attack on the Tea Party!
What's going on? Dammit!
They're quite irritated.
Of course, they are.
If by any chance they let the Straw Hats flee,
it'll be a disgrace to
the Emperor of the Sea.
Well, as a newspaper magnate,
it's better for me because it'll make a good cover story.
Guys...
Do you wanna know something interesting?
Hey, stop!
That'll reduce the Straw Hats' chances to survive!
What is it, Stussy-sama?
At the Tea Party, Linlin revealed...
...the Tamate Box from the Ryugu Palace.
She got it...
...from Straw Hat Luffy, didn't she?
So what?
That Tamate Box...
...contained explosives.
Are you sure-bon?
Yes, I saw it by accident
when the chateau was caught in the blast.
Those assholes...!!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Rifle!
Unstoppable Donuts!
How long will you continue
attacking recklessly?
Unstoppable...
...Handclap Mochi!
I won't stand for that!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Oh... he's perfect and cool as always.
Big Bro Katakuri!
And...
...haven't you gotten a
clear shot yet, sniper?
Well, I've been shooting at him
without being noticed...
But he's moving so fast!
Damn!
Gee! You're useless!
So crappy!
If we don't take out Straw Hat soon,
Big Bro Katakuri will bring him down.
Everyone!
Who's head is going to be patted by Big Bro?!
Of course, it's Flampe-sama's!
I thought so!
I have 41 older brothers.
And 40 of them vote for
the Best Little Sister Award.
BEST LITTLE SISTER AWARD
FLAMPE
I won!
Everyone loves me!
That means I'm a much-loved little sister!
C. FLAMPE (AGE 15) - 33RD DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
(PRESIDENT OF THE KATAKURI FAN CLUB
AND SUICIDE SQUAD CAPTAIN)
I have to be the king of the little sisters!
So cute!
Everyone wants to be Big
Bro Katakuri's favorite!
But he's an icon for all
his 38 younger sisters!
Even all his younger brothers admire him.
There are too many rivals!
So I wanna help him now to earn some points!
I know how you feel, Flampe-sama!
We wanna be liked by Katakuri-sama, too!
I don't care about you guys!
When we got here,
he didn't seem like himself.
But now he's as cool as always!
I can't stand to see him having a hard time
against his enemy in the first place!
Every moment should be total perfection!
Or I'll be disappointed!
You're right.
But he's not having a hard time now.
It's just that the enemy's persistent!
He must've received mortal wounds
dozens of times but he keeps getting up.
What a fool!
Laughable.
How many times will you get up?
Until I...
...beat your ass!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Stamp!
Did he try to dodge?
Why aren't they dying?!
Your...
...eyes!
I don't understand.
Falling down itself is already shameful.
I know it's irritating.
You tried to get up so I didn't let you.
You tried to throw a left punch
so I hit your left shoulder.
You tried to throw a right punch
so I hit your right shoulder.
All of this shows you're just an idiot
who can't do anything but feel frustrated...
That's how it is when your every move is
read by someone.
But making you feel
frustrated is not enough...
Left kick or right kick...
I'll hit you before you do anything.
And I'll keep at it until
your heart bursts in half.
Every attack has an intent.
And a hint.
Don't attack blindly, Luffy.
Mama!
That can't be true, Mama!
Zeus got killed!
Mama!
We did it!
We gained some time!
Let's make some headway now!
Hurry up, Brook!
Okay!
Grab this!
I'm back!
Yay! Welcome back!
Brook, well done!
We tried to minimize the damage,
but it's quite bad.
Oh, yeah.
I recovered something.
Oh, Zeus!
I-Isn't it dangerous?!
I don't think he still has that energy...
Oh, where am I?
Nice to see you again, Zeus.
Nice... to... see you... too...
As I recall, you tried to...
...strike me with lightning earlier.
I'm sorry...
If "sorry" were enough,
there would be no need for sheriffs or the Navy.
I bet you got it wrong...
I didn't mean to become your friend
from the start.
What?
Let me ask you again.
Do you wanna be my servant or...
...do you wanna die?
Think about it carefully.
Mama! Mama!
Shut up...
Mama!
Chase them, Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
Every attack has an intent.
Don't attack blindly, Luffy.
Gum-Gum...
...Twin Jet Pistol!
All right!
How's that, Rayleigh?
Don't get carried away.
You've only accomplished the first step.
Next,
I'll be your opponent.
Ouch!
You have no time to rest!
If you can't dodge 100 times, you're not allowed to eat.
What?!
Sounds terrible? Then, focus!
There you are!
Ouch!
Your opponent doesn't always
come from the front.
It's easy to read animals' minds
since they show all of their emotions.
But humans are different...
We can defy expectations and cheat others.
GROWWWL
Ouch!
I'm hungry, Rayleigh!
Will your enemy stop attacking you
because you're hungry?
Every attack has an intent.
Ow!
And a hint.
I smell something delicious.
That's my dinner. Don't pay it any mind.
There you are!
There!
Don't attack blindly, Luffy!
Rayleigh, that hurts!
I feel your anger!
That's Haki, too!
Sharpen your senses!
Ouch!
Feel your enemy's presence!
I feel your anger!
Every attack has an intent.
And a hint.
What is that fool doing?
Sharpen your senses.
Feel your enemy's...
...presence...
Don't...
...attack blindly...
Fall into despair, Straw Hat.
Did he just...
Every attack...
...has an intent!
No way!
Every attack...
...has a hint!
Take this!
Still not so frequently...
But he's beginning to see the future
in the same way I do.
Coming under Mom's fierce attack,
Nami and the others desperately
fight against her
but they are in danger of extermination!
Will Sanji who holds the key to
their fate complete the cake
and make it in time to save his friends from
the greatest crisis they've ever faced?!
The fateful moment approaches!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Finally He Returns!
Sanji, the Man Who'll Stop the Emperor of the Sea!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!