Yes! We've got Super Powers
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Your dream is like a monster
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
will become your one and only treasure
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing in a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
The future gently brings a morning
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
The Sunny was driven to the wall by Big Mom.
However...
It was fun, guys...
Now, give me the cake...
Guys!
Sanji-kun and the others
baked the cake and returned!
Wedding cake!
In the Mirroworld, Luffy's Color of Observation
started working.
Did he see the future again?!
"Lurking in the Darkness!
An Assassin Targeting Luffy!"
It seems like it'll be over soon at last...
That bloodied, disgusting monkey...
Take this.
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Stamp!
Willow Mochi!
Stop getting up. You have no chance!
This fool's Color of Observation is
getting as good as mine!
What?
What the...?
I have to get rid of him soon
or something unexpected could happen!
Mochi...
...Thrust!
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
I can't believe that even the explosion of the chateau
was Straw Hat's plot...
If he's that great a schemer...
something unexpected could happen-soir!
You idiot! I won't let that happen!
To all fleets of Totto Land!
All available ships turn out to Cacao Island
immediately!
And make that place the
Straw Hats' graveyard!
Don't let them get away!
ON THE SEA IN THE TERRITORY
- BEGE AND THE OTHERS
Bege! What are you up to?!
Why's the cake on your ship?!
We'll deal with Mama's Hunger Pangs attack...
We'll let her eat the cake
and take care of her.
Don't lie, you traitor!
What did you put in the cake?!
Nothing. Didn't you know
Pudding made the cake?
Oh, yeah! Where's Pudding?!
You don't have to worry about
Mama or Pudding at all.
Relax and focus on Straw Hat.
--You son of a...
--Clank.
Hey, Bege!
Let's pursue Bege, Bavarois!
What?!
Look at them! I'm one-hundred percent sure
that they're scheming to kill Mama.
Maybe Pudding's already been killed.
But Big Bro Peros!
What about Straw Hat's ship?!
It'll sink at Cacao Island anyway! And...
Ring, ring, ring...
--Who do you think is going after Straw Hat's ship?
--Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Oh, yeah!
--Answer!
--Ring, ring... Clank.
Are you on the trail of Straw Hat's ship,
Smoothie?!
CHARLOTTE SMOOTHIE - 14TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
(ONE OF THE SWEET 3 GENERALS)
Yeah, I am, Big Bro.
You guys keep tracking down Straw Hat's ship!
Bavarois and I are going
to chase Bege and Mama!
Squeeze every last drop of life out of them!
Torment them
and plunge them into an abyss of fear!
Roger that.
Clank.
He should've just let me handle it
from the start...
Big Bro Peros is getting distracted...
CHARLOTTE CITRON - 15TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
It would've been much easier
to stay at Cacao Island,
eating chocolate and drinking tea...
They're so impatient. Men are stupid.
CHARLOTTE CINNAMON - 16TH
DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
Well, don't say that.
Everyone, prepare to fight!
Before they reach Cacao Island,
we'll sink Straw Hat's ship!
Yeah!
Mm-hm!
They know where we'll meet up with Luffy?!
What?!
Then, that means Cacao Island is now...
Yeah, it's probably surrounded by fleets
ambushing us!
Oh, no...
They're considering us tough enemies
which they don't usually do.
Cacao Island will be our last
and biggest challenge here!
We'll rescue Luffy no matter what
and get out of here!
But we have no chance
if we face their fleets directly.
Look at yourself!
I can't believe you slip...
Straw Hat!
My plan is going very well!
Since I can hide my presence so perfectly,
even Big Bro Katakuri hasn't noticed my support!
Big Brother!
Cling!
The thing is, at that time, I...
Oh, I didn't know that, Flampe!
You're such a considerate, good girl!
That's my most-beloved sister.
Oh, I'm so commendable! So cute!
As I thought,
I have to be the king of the little sisters!
Just a moment of carelessness...
and the fight will be decided!
I'm sure that you know that!
Straw Hat!
Why did you lower your guard?!
Mochi Anemone!
What's the matter, Straw Hat?!
Give it to me!
Is this what you wanted, Chiffon?
Yes! Thank you, Bege!
But we took on quite a headache!
To be honest, getting away is more important
than the assassination now!
What are you saying, Bege?!
We decided to let Nami and the others
get away safely!
We can't just give up halfway
because we wanna survive!
That's how you pay your debt!
Mm-hm!
Rero!
Don't worry! Believe in the cake's flavor!
Black-Leg is really an amazing cook!
Man! That's what I love about you, Chiffon!
Ma'am!
Wedding cake!
Let's shake them off, guys!
Yeah!
It's Smoothie-sama's ship!
Smoothie-sama!
Citron-sama! Cinnamon-sama!
Are you ready? Straw Hats...
Another fleet is on our tail!
It's Sweet General Smoothie's ship!
Big Mom left and now it's a Sweet General!
It's that woman who squeezes everything...
Big Sis Smoothie!
How long will it take to Cacao Island?
A little more than three hours!
We'll arrive there at 1 AM
exactly as we promised.
But we have no idea where or when
Luffy will emerge on Cacao Island
and we can't even warn him!
I came up with just one idea
to get through Cacao Island.
Oven-sama! Fleets are arriving one after another
to surround the island!
Do we really need that many?!
I don't think Katakuri-sama will
let Straw Hat get away...
I don't know! Ask Tamago and Montd'Or!
We need them all, Big Bro Oven!
Can you believe this?!
That big explosion of the chateau
was intentional, too!
What?!
Even though he's a Rookie and they're a small group,
don't underestimate them!
If we let them escape, we'll suffer shame!
Don't worry...
We'll get them right here for sure!
Listen! About three hours from now,
at 1 AM,
the separated members of the Straw Hats
will meet up here at Cacao Island.
Think of it as your last chance
to kill them all!
Yes, sir!
If by any chance Straw Hat appears,
he'll come out of a mirror on the island!
Everyone, go home
and break all the mirrors in the town!
Didn't you hear me?! Just do it!
Please! Even precious ones?!
He's a power-user. If you have a mirror
that you don't wanna break, sink it into the sea.
You can salvage later! Anyway...
This is to be the only unbroken
mirror on this island!
No exceptions!
If anyone allows Straw Hat to
get out of their mirror,
I'll execute their whole family!
Hurry up!
Y-Yes, sir!
Don't think you can get away, Straw Hat!
To you, this is no exit...
It's the entrance to hell!
What's the matter, Straw Hat?
What are you doing?
Why did you let up?!
I was just starting to think highly of you...
but you disappointed me!
I think I saw it!
Did I imagine it?
Imagining is fine.
The Color of Observation
is an extension of imagination!
You have to be able to
sense it instinctively!
Instinctively?!
He stands up again!
Look how his feet shake.
All right! Another shot!
This time, I'll give you a Numbing Needle
that's 10-times more effective than the last one!
A monkey who doesn't know when to give up.
Drop dead already!
Numbing Needle!
What? He dodged my silent needle?!
But he fell!
When Katakuri finds out what is up with Luffy,
he stabs his stomach with the Mole
and reveal his secret which he has been hiding
for some time.
Stake everything on this duel!
Against the determined Katakuri,
will Luffy be able to stand up?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"One Man's Determination! Katakuri's Deadly Big Fight!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!