Yes! We've got Super Powers
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Your dream is like a monster
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
will become your one and only treasure
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing in a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
In the Mirroworld,
Luffy and Katakuri's fierce battle continues.
"Finally, It's Over!
The Climax of the Intense Fight against Katakuri!"
Almost...
Yay!
Alright! I'm finally free now!
I know Big Bro Katakuri will never, ever
get defeated by a short-ass like him,
but in any case, it's impossible for Straw Hat
to get out of the Mirroworld without me!
I'm sorry, Straw Hat!
I'll join Big Bro Oven and the others,
and kill every last one of the Straw Hats!
CACAO ISLAND
It's 32 minutes before the appointed time of
12:28 AM
the Straw Hats' rendezvous at Cacao Island.
No one has come out yet.
I guess the battle is dragging on.
Is there any chance of
Big Bro Katakuri losing?
What?! Any chance for Katakuri losing?!
Newji! Are you...
...serious?!
There's no chance!
Ouch!
Why did you hit me?! I'm Newsan!
I didn't say anything!
Katakuri will never be
defeated in his entire life!
He's right, you idiot!
Big Bro Katakuri is simply a perfect man!
Ouch! I'm Newshi!
I'm sorry, Newsan, Newshi...
Ouch!
You owed us!
What?!
You fool! You fool!
But we haven't heard from him for a while...
It's weird.
This is what I'd do if I were Straw Hat.
His rendezvous with his crew
is at 1 AM here on Cacao Island...
In other words, his crew won't get here
until 1 AM...
In that case, I'd capture Big Sis Brulee,
the only key to the Mirroworld,
and wait out the clock
in the Mirroworld or on other islands!
Yeah! Big Sis Brulee has
actually gone missing!
That's right!
It's highly likely that Straw Hat Luffy
will run from the fight against Katakuri
and come out of this mirror at 1 AM sharp.
Yeah, I see.
Big Sis Brulee's a bit dense
so she gets caught easily.
Akimeg, she might be listening
through the mirror.
Oh, oops!
There's 30 minutes to go...
We need to stay alert.
Come on out, Straw Hat!
I'll chop you in half with my sickle!
Are they all soldiers?
Seems like that's the only mirror
that they kept intact...
When Luffy comes out,
we gotta get out of here instantly...
Or both of us will get killed...
When Luffy comes out,
that'll be our farewell then...
Pudding-cha...
Too far!
Do you hear me, Pudding-chan?
D-D-D... Don't look at me!
I-I-I am listening to you!
Sanji...
...san!
Looking back, we met in such an odd way...
This is your fiancée.
Charlotte Pudding-sama!
Let's get married tomorrow.
DAY OF THE WEDDING
Here, Pudding-chan...
Thank you!
Tsk!
Shortly...
Shortly, Pudding-chan and I will...
Bring me egg whites!
They're ready!
Here!
Thank you, Pudding-chan!
--Ah!
--Oops!
L-Let me mix it this time!
Okay, thank you!
Of course, the flavor is important
but so is the presentation!
Okay!
I had so much fun being with you,
but I have to say goodbye soon...
Thanks for everything!
I fooled you and tried to kill you...
So don't thank me, Sanji-san!
I wanna apologize!
I really have to apologize!
Shut up!
No! No! I did it again!
You're right! We're enemies!
To you, our marriage was just a trap.
The whole thing was staged
by the Big Mom Pirates...
But...
...maybe it was unpleasant for you...
...but I'm glad that you played my fiancée!
Oh, I mean...
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to insult you!
No! Stop crying!
Stop, tears!
I-I'm sorry!
I didn't mean that, Pudding-chan!
H-Hey, Sanji...
...san...
Could you do me a favor?!
Just one, for the last time...
I wanna ask you a favor!
12:37 AM
I'll...
...never...
...lose!
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
They've survived until this point!
12:40 AM
The Straw Hats!
If you let them escape
despite your preparations for an all-out attack,
it's gonna be headline news!
Shut up, Morgans! You won't get the scoop!
In order to avoid that at all costs,
we swallowed our pride
and sent tons of soldiers to Cacao Island!
Even if Gold Roger, the former King of the Pirates,
comes out of the mirror,
we won't let him get away!
Once we catch them all,
we'll chop their heads off and line them up,
so put it on the front page tomorrow!
To set an example!
You have bad taste...
That's so unnecessary...
No way! In fact, it's too kind!
We'll get good news soon!
There's no way that one ship can
run through the grand fleet!
12:43 AM
Stop!
ON THE SEA - BEGE'S SHIP
Give me the cake!
The sails are on fire!
Put it out now! We're gonna sink!
We can't go on-rero, Father! This is it-rero!
We're gonna die before we
get to the island-rero!
Let's trash the cake and flee, Father!
Don't get flustered now!
Rero?
We've all come from different places...
Let's at least
die together!
Father!
I see it!
It's Fluffy Island!
Rero!
We're almost there!
Show your manliness, guys!
Yeah!
12:45 AM
ON THE SEA - THE SUNNY
Seems like they stopped attacking.
But we still can't lose them!
There is an ambush at Cacao Island.
They'll probably start attacking again there
to sandwich us!
What?! What should we do?!
I have no choice.
I'll negotiate with that big woman!
Excuse me! Could I see your panties...
Cut it out, you silly skeleton!
Okay... The negotiation failed.
We can make it there by 1 AM as we promised!
But my concern is Brulee,
the key to escaping the Mirroworld.
Even if Luffy wins, he can't get out of there
without Brulee!
Luffy is not the kind of person
to carefully calculate something like that.
That's right! He can't!
He definitely can't! What should we do?!
First of all, we're not sure
if he knows what time it is...
He might not?!
So much could go wrong...
...but we believe in you, Luffy!
12:47 AM
Even when he falls, he falls forward...
But I won...
Listen carefully, Luffy!
We'll get there in 10 hours at the earliest!
Around 1 AM!
So as soon as you kick that guy's ass,
look for a mirror that leads to Cacao Island!
And we'll see you there!
What time is it now?
Are you gonna come back...
...to take down Big Mom someday?
Of course I am! Because I'll...
...become the King of the Pirates!
You're seeing quite far into the future!
Branch... Let's go...
What? Branch?
She escaped!
Oh, no! I can't get out
of here without her...
W-What should I do?
I don't have time...
Big Brother!
Big Bro Katakuri!
Branch!
It's Brulee, Straw Hat!
What kind of a dirty trick did you use
to take him down?!
So you brought down Katakuri!
I can't believe it! Grr!
You are...
My name is Mystoms!
MYSTOMS - A MYSTERY SAVIOR
In order to get you out of here,
I've captured Brulee and have been waiting for you!
So you're okay...
MYSTOMS - A MYSTERY SAVIOR
Pekoms!
PEKOMS
Yeah! Big Bro Pedro sacrificed himself
to save your lives!
I won't let you lose it here!
Come on, Straw Hat!
Let's go to Cacao Island where your friends are!
--Okay!
--Let go of me!
12:50 AM
There it is! Cacao Island!
How many are there?!
That's a massive fleet!
Sanji-kun! How is it over there?
Luffy's not here yet.
Don't get close to the fleet at the shore.
I'll bring Luffy to the ship somehow!
12:55 AM
Guys, are your weapons ready?!
Yeah!
If he's gonna come out,
it'll be in five minutes!
You fools! I'll make you pay for this!
Come on now!
Straw Hat Luffy!
A huge watertight encirclement
is waiting for Luffy!
The Sunny enduring a barrage of bombs
is already reaching its limits!
The time of the rendezvous has finally come!
Facing imminent danger,
Luffy and Pekoms take their chances at the risk of their lives!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Desperate Situation! The
Iron-tight Entrapment of Luffy!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!