Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
The duel between Luffy and Katakuri
finally came to an end.
Meanwhile, for Sanji and Pudding who are sneaking onto
Cacao Island to meet up with Luffy,
it's time to say goodbye.
Could you do me a favor?!
Just one, for the last time...
I wanna ask you a favor!
Are you gonna come back...
...to take down Big Mom someday?
Of course I am! Because I'll...
...become the King of the Pirates!
You're seeing quite far into the future!
If he's gonna come out, it'll be in five minutes!
Come on now!
Straw Hat Luffy!
"A Desperate Situation!
The Iron-tight Entrapment of Luffy!"
ON THE CACAO ISLAND
Four minutes to go...
That's...
I'm sure it is!
The Straw Hats' ship!
Here they are.
What daredevils!
I think they see us!
How could they assemble that many ships?
There's only one ship on our side!
Doesn't it seem like overkill?!
You can say it's logical.
Even though it was unintended,
it's like we declared
that we were going to be there.
So they had to throw away their pride...
Even if they are the mighty Big Mom Pirates.
Tart ships, go!
Sink Straw Hat's ship!
Here they come!
No! We're gonna die!
Luffy, hurry up!
Keep our distance from the island!
All right!
We must avoid being pinned down...
What should we do, Smoothie?!
We'll keep supporting from their aft!
They have nowhere to run.
The Totto Land Grand Fleet led by Snack is ahead of them
SQUARE WITH THE MIRROR IS                       THE SUNNY
OVEN'S ARMY
SMOOTHIE'S FLEET
and our fleet is behind them.
Even if they make it to Cacao Island by any chance,
Big Bro Oven's army is waiting for them.
They're already trapped like rats.
This is the end of the line for them!
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Keep all the Transponder Snails connected!
We need intelligence from all angles.
Certainly, Montd'Or-sama.
Their ship came. Which means...
It means Straw Hat will show up soon.
I wanna slice him up already.
I'll get him!
--What?!
--Who said you can go first?!
Let's decide by rock-paper-scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
I wanna squash him already-yu!
Prepare yourself, you stupid brat!
Come on out, Straw Hat!
Come on!
Hurry up, Luffy!
Help!!
Sulong?
That's right! Grr!
We Minks can transform into our primal form
by looking at the full moon!
But I've always been bad at it...
I can transform into my Sulong form
but I'll become nothing but a beast.
A beast?
I'll run wild and destroy everything around me!
No one's voice will reach me but...
...there was one exception!
That was Big Bro Pedro!
Stop, Pekoms!
Pekoms...
Everything's gonna be all right!
For some reason, his voice alone could calm me down when I was out of my mind!
Pedro...
So there's no one left in this world
who can stop my rampage!
Listen, Straw Hat. It's the full moon tonight!
When I go out to Cacao Island
through the mirror,
I'll transform into my Sulong form!
When I go out of control, that'll be your chance to escape from Cacao Island!
You idiot! It's no use, Pekoms!
You damn traitor!
There is a force at Cacao Island
large enough to launch a war!
Even if you transform,
they'll take you down instantly and it'll be over!
I'm gonna fall!
Shut up, Brulee!
We're almost there, Straw Hat!
Big Bro Pedro sacrificed himself!
No matter what, don't let it be in vain!
Grr!
Okay!
Thanks!
Now, do your work for us!
What?
Let's go!!
It's coming from inside the mirror!
Help!!
Isn't that Big Sis Brulee?!
Just as we thought,
she was captured by Straw Hat.
That bastard!
He's coming! Aim and shoot!
What?!
Is that...?!
Pekoms!
What?!
I'm Mystoms!
Pekoms! Why did you come out?!
What?
D-Don't move, Big Mom Pirates!
I-If you do something stupid,
I'll blow your precious sister
Brulee's brains out! Grr!
--Brulee!
--Big Sis Brulee!
Don't do it, Pekoms!
Pekoms, what are you thinking?!
Why don't you calm down?!
Let go of Big Sis Brulee!
Help! Everyone!
My identity was going to be revealed
by transforming anyway...
It doesn't matter now!
I'll keep Straw Hat alive!
He's the guy who Big Bro Pedro bet on!
No way!
He's trying to become a Sulong!
--Don't do it, Pekoms!
--You'll be out of control!
No!!
Hold him down!
It's too late...
Prepare yourself!
Hey!
You bastard!
Gee, what's this all about?
Coming out of the mirror was
neither Katakuri nor Straw Hat!
How dare you point a gun at my sister...
...for no reason?!
--Ouch!
--Big Bro!
Heat...
...Beating!
Ouch!
No!
Yay!
That's Straw Hat!
Luffy!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
This is Sanji!
Oh, Sanji!
Luffy...
...made it!
Yes!
It's Straw Hat!
--Pekoms was hiding him!
--Get him!
He threw dust in Big Bro Katakuri's eyes
and came out...
That's pretty impressive!
I'm gonna go first!
Ya-hoo!
Look up!
It wasn't smart to jump...
You're an easy target!
Just surrender!
Big Bro Raisin!
Who is that?!
Sanji!
Did you win?!
Yeah!
I knew it!
--They're trying to get away through the air!
--That's Black-Leg!
How simple...
That's to be expected.
We can use Geppo, too!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Straw Hat... Black-Leg...
I've got more in me!
Isn't that right,
Big Bro Pedro?!
To let them get away...
Is that Pekoms?
Pekoms!
Don't get in our way!
You should've been dead!
How's that?
He's unbelievably strong but
seems out of control!
He's just a wild beast!
Stop, Pekoms!
Pekoms...
Everything's gonna be all right!
Big Bro...
Take... Straw Hat...
Get clear away... at any cost...
Okay!
Don't push your luck!
Make it so he'll never see the full moon again!
Pekoms!!
Everything went all right...
Big Bro...
Not paying attention....
...is disrespectful-yu!
When you're vastly outnumbered,
it's meaningless...
...no matter how hard you struggle.
It's over.
Dammit!
What?!
There's an explosion at the harbor!
What's that?!
Hey, what happened-nie?!
Those ships at the shore are burning!
What's going on?!
Is it a bombing?!
It's a fleet, Snack-sama!
Who are they?!
I-It's...
...Germa's fleet!
Why are they here?!
I thought they were fully destroyed several hours ago!
Next! Prepare to fire!
Germa 66!
Why are they here?!
Dammit!
You bastards!
Thank you for what you did for us at the Tea Party,
Big Mom Pirates!
Germa 66!
Why are you here?!
What a coincidence, Sanji.
We wanted to give these fools...
...a crushing blow, too!
Ichiji's sparking techniques, Niji's electric attacks,
and Yonji's monstrous power.
The furious members of Germa 66 show their true strength!
And just like that unforgettable day, Reiju says goodbye.
Will Sanji be able to reach the Sunny,
dashing
through the air in the middle of the combat?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Pulling Back from the Brink!
The Formidable Reinforcements - Germa!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!