Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Luffy finally defeated Katakuri
and with the help of Pekoms,
he escaped from the Mirroworld to Cacao Island.
Sanji!
Did you win?!
Yeah!
Sanji headed for the Sunny carrying Luffy,
but the Big Mom Pirates attacked him.
Just when he was stuck in a critical situation,
those who came to save him were...
You bastards!
Germa 66!
"Pulling Back from the Brink!
The Formidable Reinforcements - Germa!"
Damn Germa! Why are you here?!
If you stand in our way,
we'll take you out along with Straw Hat!
Shoot!
There's not even a scratch on them!
What's wrong with them?!
There'll be another pile
of scum when we're done.
Sanji.
Take the injured and
get off of the island already.
We don't need you here!
They set us up.
We'll make them pay!
This whole island is our target, Sanji!
You guys!
Are they really modified humans
with iron skins?!
Bring me a bazooka!
Germa!
I thought that you were all dead!
How did you survive?!
What do you mean?
Ten thousand soldiers led by Nusstorte
took over your kingdom!
Yeah, the flies swarmed all over us
but we swatted them and dumped them into the sea.
What?!
They dumped our Big Brothers and the others
into the sea?!
What's going on here-soir?!
I definitely got a call saying that
Germa's been destroyed!
We crushed them with ten thousand soldiers.
Their kingdom is devastated!
Who was that, then?!
Contact them-bon!
Th-This is Montd'Or! Come in!
Big Bro Nusstorte! Please come in!
Big Bro Bassquarte! Big Bro Dosmarche!
Whoever is there! Just come in!
Just as I thought, unexpected things keep
happening including Pekoms'
betrayal-vous plaît!
How come Germa's fleet
appeared at Cacao Island-noir?!
What were you fools gonna do
with our scientific technology?
You could do nothing!
You bastards!
Sanji! Just go now!
Okay!
We won't let you get away!
Black-Leg!
Sky Walk!
Shoot him down!
Bazookas! Ready to fire!
Target - Black-Leg Sanji!
--One!
--Two!
--Three!
--Four!
Go!
Don't stop, Sanji!
Black Bug!
What?!
Damn! Germa!
Prepare to fire!
Shoot!
Don't hold back! Shoot back!
Snack and the others are
under fierce attack by Germa!
Shouldn't we go help them?!
Don't get distracted by that!
We've gotta focus on Straw Hat's ship!
Tell it to all ships around the island!
Yes, ma'am!
Montd'Or and the others!
They must've been outsmarted by Germa!
You were outsmarted too, Big Bro Daifuku.
Tsk! But I fought hard to catch up to you!
Why are you letting their ship go?!
Corner them already!
Hey, Jimbei!
What do you think of Germa?
Are they enemies or allies to us?
They could've gotten away.
Why bother coming to get us now?
But they stood up for us just for the time being, right?
How can we trust them?!
Oh! Maybe Reiju-san came
to show me her panties...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Hey, can you hear me?!
Sanji! We can't get any closer
to the island than this!
I know! Sail by the harbor at full speed!
I'll make it there while you're doing that!
Sanji-kun! How's Luffy?!
I got him! I don't have time now!
I'm counting on you, Nami-san!
Okay!
Let's go, Jimbei! Starboard!
Starboard!
Sanji!
You can do it!
Crush Germa!
Where did Black-Leg go?!
I can't see because of the dust!
There he is!
Shoot him!
Don't let him get away!
That's right...
Don't let him get away at any price!
Straw Hat Luffy is the last
person we wanna forgive!
He didn't flee from Big Bro Katakuri
by throwing dust in his eyes...
Big Sis Brulee?!
Do you wanna know
what really happened in the Mirroworld?
The perfect one,
and the world's strongest and greatest...
...our Big Bro Katakuri...
He...
...has been defeated by Straw Hat Luffy!!
What?!
Katakuri...
Your legendary undefeated record...
...has been broken by that squirt?!
No way!!
Big Bro won't lose!
Katakuri-sama will never be defeated!
He must've used some kind of dirty trick!
I can't forgive him!
Shoot him dead!
Cut him up!
Pulverize him completely until
not a single bone is left!
Yeah!
We won't let you flee, Straw Hat!
Damn you!
Straw Hat!!
I won't forgive you!
Kill him, Big Bro Oven!
It's over, Straw Hat!
Sparking...
...Valkyrie!
SPARKING VALKYRIE
Ichiji?!
You're a failure who deserves
to die, right, Sanji?!
In that case, if he really dies,
will it make Father happy?
You are...
a failure.
Take off, Sanji!
Big Bro Oven! Are you okay?!
Hand him over!
Black-Leg!
I'm gonna take you down again-yu!
Germa!
Winch Guillotine!
WINCH GUILLOTINE
Yonji?!
Go, Sanji!
You're such an eyesore!
Shoot! He's above the roofs!
I'll avenge Katakuri-sama!
You're too slow. You'll
be filled with bullets!
Niji!
Germa!
Let's go!
This is a lightspeed sword!
Henry Blazer!
HENRY BLAZER
Oh, no! Oven-sama!
Those two will make it out of town!
Out of town?!
Are you alive, failure?
Damn you!
You give us nothing but trouble.
I didn't ask you to help me!
Idiot.
Goodbye, failure!
Snack! Brownie! Joconde!
Shoot them down at the harbor!
They're coming towards you!
Hey! Isn't someone talking to us
through the Transponder Snail?!
Brownie-sama.
Who cares about that right now?
Shoot Straw Hat Down!
I think I can make it!
Don't let him go any farther!
Prepare tear-gas canisters!
We should just shear him
of his strength to fly!
What's the matter?!
Stay with us!
Hey! Hey!
Germa!
Those who hurt my little brother...
I won't forgive them!
If I can... run away...
...here in the East Blue...
I'll never...
...have to see...
...Dad's face again, right?
Pink Hornet!
That's Straw Hat! Shoot!
You're really a high-maintenance brother.
Reiju!
Don't ever let him go!
Step back!
You have only one chance!
Don't ruin it!
Sanji! You're a boy! Stop crying already!
Listen! Don't ever come back here!
Uh-huh!
The sea is broad! You'll...
You'll definitely meet kind people someday!!
There's no way that you're a failure.
Our mother protected her child
at the risk of her own life and
he was born with the spark of humanity.
That child is you, Sanji.
Run!!
Don't look back!!
Sanji... My little brother
who is the kindest person in the world!
Reiju!
Goodbye!
Straw Hat and Sanji got off of the island!
Fleet, come in!
Hurry up, Sanji!
Sanji-kun...
It's Sanji!
Here he comes, guys!
Sanji is carrying Luffy!
Yay!
I knew he could do it!
Luffy!
There it is, Luffy! The Sunny!
Isn't dinner ready yet, Sanji?
How will Bege's last big gamble end up?!
All eyes throughout the country
are on Mom and the cake!
Meanwhile, the Sunny is in a
joyous mood having Luffy back!
However, Smoothie's cunning strategy puts them
in the greatest no-way-out danger ever!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Last Hope! The Sun Pirates Emerge!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!