Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
"The Parting Time!
Pudding's Last Wish!"
We're in the clear. I see no pursuers.
Do you think that
Jimbei-san and the others are okay?
Well...
In any case,
we have to get out of Big Mom's territory.
You're right.
I see. So Pedro...
...died.
My name is Pedro! Please help me...
Get them treated now...
Or they're gonna die!
The world is waiting for them!
We can't...
...ever let...
...those two die!
It's because he came to rescue me...
I don't think that this is
where you were supposed to die...
It's okay. It's okay, Sanji!
Pedro made his own choice!
Don't blame yourself! Sanji!
You-teia guys saved the Mokomo Dukedom
so we wanted to repay our debt!
If it weren't for Pedro,
we'd all have died at that moment!
So...
...do you think you could just offer thanks?!
Because this is how it's supposed to be!
I know what kind of man he was.
Soul Pocus
The words of soul
With deep reluctance
The ship is pulling away
on the tide with the wind
From the sea of the battle
It's Cotton Candy Flurry!
That means we're close to
the edge of the territory!
We'll make it out of Big
Mom's territory soon!
Mama came back!
Flower
I know it's not so easy to be them
But the flowers and the trees sing cheerfully
And they seduce us sweetly
Soul Pocus
It's a plot that the greedy Mama contrived
The fairy-tale prince and
The beautiful princess
They're manipulated in a puppet show
where they're not attracted to each other
Even sweet nectar that draws us
with its flavor has a slyness
Nothing in this world is
more fearful than sweetness
Hidden motives and misunderstandings
A poorly performed play
at the risk of your life
On our way there was candy
On our way back is a guillotine
Who won the big fight?
Fish-Man Karate Hidden Technique!
Vagabond Drill!
Hang in there!
Once Luffy and the others get out
of the territory, we can go, too!
Hey, what happened to the Straw Hats?
No words from our pursuit unit!
I think they've lost them!
Idiot! Once they cross the border,
we won't be able to catch up!
Pudding, like always, make him love
you madly with your acting skills.
That's easily done, Mama!
You're like a doll, Pudding.
A doll that I control.
Mama... I'm not a doll...
Let's get married tomorrow.
No way...  Like all the others,
once you find out who I really am, you'll...
You're my daughter but that creeps me out...
She's a monster!
"Let's get married!"
You sound exactly like him!
So creepy!
Look! She's a freak!
Please stop!
No one will love me.
Because I'm an ugly freak.
Like all the others,
once you find out who I really am...
Take a good look, Sanji...
at my creepy...
...third eye!
What a beautiful eye!
What?
All right! Let's start baking!
I'm glad that you played my fiancée!
Pudding-chan!
H-Hey, Sanji...
...san...
Could you do me a favor?!
"JUST ONE, FOR THE LAST TIME...
I WANNA ASK YOU A FAVOR!"
"THANK YOU."
"GOODBYE..."
Oh? Pudding-chan?!
You said that you wanted to ask me a favor...
What is it?
Ring, ring, ring...
Big Bro Peros, come in!
Where's Mama now?!
Damn!
Montd'Or-sama!
We got a call from Cacao Island!
Seems like there's a Territory Slug
at the border of the territory!
It's too late!
There was a signal of a passing ship.
The Straw Hats' ship got out of the territory!
What did you say?!
We can't track them anymore!
The Straw Hats' ship sailed out of
the Totto Land territory!
Did they get out?!
Go back to your ships, Germa 66!
Mission accomplished!
Roger that!
Roger!
Germa is withdrawing!
Don't let them do that!
Catch them!
I didn't wanna see you
lying down on your back, defeated.
Brulee.
Why did you purposefully get up and fall on your back?
You were on your stomach first.
I wonder why...
But Brulee...
They say that I never lie down on my back
in my daily life...
That's not true...
Yeah, I know.
I've been watching you through mirrors.
You've pretended to be...
...some sort of perfect man
that no one'll mess with...
...for us...
Katakuri, if you hide that mouth,
you'll have friends.
I don't want any! This is me!
I'll just beat up those who laugh!
A pelican eel!
There is a pelican eel!
I'll kick your asses!
--Oh, no!
--Hurry up!
--How did it happen?
--What is it?
What's the matter?
--This is serious! Brulee is badly hurt!
--What?!
Brulee!
What... happened?
It's nothing...
No, it's not nothing! Tell me!
What happened?!
Those who got beat by you
came for revenge, Katakuri!
Revenge?! On my sister?!
Why?! Why did she have to get hurt?!
Big Bro...
It doesn't... hurt at all...
You're fine just the way you are.
No, fool! I...
Brulee got hurt because of me...
I was too soft!
Here you come, Katakuri!
We've been expecting you.
Huh? What's that thing around your neck?!
How could you cut my sister's face?!
I'll never lower my guard again!
I'll teach them what true fear is!
Brulee...
How's Straw Hat doing?
No doubt you'll think "That's good"
when you hear it.
Can you see ahead into the future, too?
He just made it out of the territory...
I won't forgive him!
He gave you a hard time like this!
I was right.
Luffy and the others left the territory.
Let's retreat!
Retreat! Help the injured!
Germa 66! We'll withdraw!
Shoot, shoot!
Don't let them get away-nie!
Damn Germa!
Their defense on the south side is poor.
Let's get through there!
Yes, sir!
Here she comes...
It's Mama!
Mama is here...
Mama is here!
Jimbei...
I guess they won't just let us go.
Of course, we're ready for it!
I promised Luffy that I'd return alive.
Let's all survive at any cost!
We're at a critical stage!
Yeah!
Soul Pocus
Self-centered words
When you're lured by a sweet cake
You must ask what they
want in exchange for it
There is no gain on our side
Give them a treat or they'll
play a trick on you
Nothing in this world is
more dreadful than sweetness
Soul Pocus
The selfish...
...Mama
--Would you give me your lifespan?
--Or die?
Soul Pocus
It's the queen's...
...song
Life or dead?
Shouldering the hopes of the Sun Pirates, Germa 66,
and those who lost their lives,
the Straw Hats finally made it out of
Emperor of the Sea Big Mom's territory.
Hey...
Can I make you a meal?
A meal?
Food!
Sanji's cooking!
I'm actually famished!
I'm starving!
It's safe, free, and delicious!
Sanji's cooking!
Did something happen while I was gone?
At the same time, in the East Blue...
Isn't my meal ready yet?!
Hey, come on!
BARATIE, THE SEA RESTAURANT
Owner Zeff! Let's kick them out!
Why do we have to serve them food?
They're our enemies!
I'll cook for them so just clam up!
Bring it to me already!
They're pushing their luck!
Food! Food! Food! Food!
Alright, alright.
People always become hungry.
If they're your enemies or not,
everyone gets hungry.
Now, dig in!
If there's someone who's
hungry, I'll feed them.
Then we'll talk!
Luffy took on the Emperor
of the Sea - Big Mom.
The news instantly spreads across the world
and surprises people in a big way.
Luffy who once wanted to be like Shanks
and sailed out to sea now
takes a new title as a pirate!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The World is Stunned! The Fifth
Emperor of the Sea Emerges!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!