Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era...
...is experiencing a groundswell
beyond the World Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it
is now about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"To the Reverie!
The Straw Hats' Sworn Allies Come Together!"
Damn.
My bounty has increased
because of Germa's name...
It doesn't make me happy at all...
Hey, are you alright?
Do your wounds hurt?
N-No...
This...
My bounty has decreased!
Look... It's 150 million berries...
What?!
Really?! I thought it had increased
to 500 million not so long ago!
150 million is lower than
your bounty two years ago!
Is that possible?! Did you do something bad?!
--Wouldn't that have increased it?
--Oh, that's right.
It's not so bad.
People won't come after you.
Nami-san, Luffy is our captain!
It could harm our prestige!
Dammit! Why?!
How are all the royal families?!
NAVY
No problems reported!
What about pirates?!
NEW MARINEFORD
So far, 13 pirate groups
have attempted to kidnap...
...royal family members, but we repelled them
before they approached the ships!
Tell the patrol units to
stay alert at all times!
SAKAZUKI - ADMIRAL OF THE FLEET
NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Yes, sir!
I'm here to report, Fleet Admiral Sakazuki!
The Kingdom of Lulucia ship that was en route
to the Reverie has been attacked by pirates!
The king was unharmed
but Princess Comane has been kidnapped...
What did I just tell you?!
What are guards for?!
Check.
RIKU DOLDO III - THE KING OF DRESSROSA
ELIZABELLO II - THE KING
OF THE PRODENCE KINGDOM
It's no use thinking.
Grandfather-sama!
--Hm? What's wrong, Rebecca?
--Look!
ATTEMPTED ASSASSINATION OF BIG MOM
Have you read about Lucy?!
REBECCA - LADY-IN-WAITING OF DRESSROSA
Yes, I have.
Oh, okay.
Luffyland is doing great!
That's our boss!
The newspaper mentions us, too...
LEO - LEADER OF THE TONTA
CORPS, TONTATTA TRIBE
Folks, once we enter the Holyland,
don't talk about such things.
What? Why?
We're hugely indebted to him but
the World Government and the
Navy see him differently.
You're right! He's a pirate!
Not only that but he's also coming to be considered
a very dangerous man now.
He's really something...
Oh yeah! I'll go show this to Viola-san!
Let's do that!
It's going smoothly...
VIOLA - PRINCESS OF DRESSROSA
I hope we can reach Mariejois
without a problem.
Yes.
Viola-san!
Have you read about Lucy?!
Yes.
Oh, okay...
It hasn't even been a month since he left Dressrosa
but he is becoming quite a figure.
Uh-huh.
It's no mistake... Those are ships of
Dressrosa and Prodence Kingdom!
No Navy guards!
Oh! I-I see Princess Viola!
She is as gorgeous as they say.
The girl she's with is also
a royal family member?
If we kidnap them,
I wonder how much they'll pay us!
What do you think, Princess Comane?
Contact my daddy already!
He'll pay you as much as you want!
This is why I like royal families!
But you gotta wait a little.
We're greedy.
They'll never notice us because...
...we're hiding underwater!
--Sink them!
--Roger!
It's impossible to guard against a torpedo!
What happened?!
An enemy attack?!
--Get the cannons ready!
--Yes, sir!
No! Don't worry!
I'm glad that I made it. You're safe now!
A-Are you a Navy soldier?
JUSTICE
KOBY - CAPTAIN OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
I'm Koby, a captain of the Navy Headquarters!
--Did it miss the target?!
--No way!
We're gonna sink!
You're not hurt, are you?
You're parties from Dressrosa and Prodence.
You must be tired from your long journey.
What just happened?
How did you get here?
I got here from a distant Navy ship.
This ship was just targeted
from under the sea.
Under the sea... You mean by a torpedo?!
I'm glad they missed...
Yeah.
Helmeppo-san, how's it over there?
We caught the pirates!
Look!
HELMEPPO
LIEUTENANT COMMANDER OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Princess Comane from Lulucia is okay, too!
You little...! Roast these jerks on a skewer!
I won't forgive them!
Of course, they'll get the
harshest punishment, princess!
Anyway, what's wrong with your Color of Observation,
Koby?!
I didn't feel a torpedo anywhere at all.
A submarine...
You have to be careful with pirates these days...
That was close.
You!
So you're the famous Captain Koby!
What? From the Rocky Port Incident?!
The incident was masterminded by Trafalgar Law,
one of the Worst Generation...
You're the hero who protected the citizens
at that time.
N-No, I'm not a hero!
You're not just a daring guy
but also a fine young man!
Wow... This man must be strong...
He doesn't even hold saving us
from the torpedo over our heads...
Thank you!
Oh, no...
Oh! Luffy-san!
I mean, it's Straw Hat Luffy!
The front-page article caught my eye.
Do you wanna read it, Koby-san?
No, no. Well, I mean, you know...
"A great captain with 5,000 subordinates"...
"Destroyed Big Mom's castle"...
"Took down the top officer
who is worth a billion"...
"The fifth Emperor of the Sea"...
Luffy-san's as cool as always!
He keeps moving forward!
Koby-san?
Every time I see you in the newspaper,
I think of that day...
I slept great!
Are you toying with us
even when you know we're pirates?!
Man, I'm hungry! You got any food?
Listen when people are talking!
You damn kid!
Die!
What's the big idea?
--W-Who are you?!
--Me?
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
That day, I got in a boat
on the outskirts of town to go fishing...
But it turned out the boat was
actually headed for a pirate ship.
It's been two years since...
In exchange for my life, I've
been forced to be a chore boy.
Man, you're dumb and stupid!
You're brutally honest...
If you don't like it, then run away!
I-I can't! No way! No way!
Just the thought of Alvida-sama finding me
frightens me and
makes my knees knock together!
Oh, you're a wimp, too?
Man, I hate you!
Yeah... That's right...
If only I had the courage
to drift the ocean in a barrel,
there's actually something
I want to do, too...
Yeah?
Umm... What compelled you
to set out onto the sea, Luffy-san?
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
K-K-King of the Pirates?!
K... K...
K-King of the Pirates is the title given to the person
who obtains everything in this world!
That means seeking the great treasure of wealth,
fame, and power... the One Piece!
--Yup!
--Yup?!
Pirates all over the world
are after that treasure!
Me, too!
No way! No way, no way, no way!
Absolutely no way!
There's no way you can stand at
the apex of this Great Pirate Era! No way! No way!
Why did you hit me?
Just because.
It's not about whether I can or not.
What?
I'm gonna do it because I want to.
I've decided to be the King of the Pirates,
so if I die fighting for that,
that's fine with me!
Do you suppose I can do it, too?
--If I'm prepared to die for it?
--Do what?
Do you think even I could join the Navy?
The Navy?
Yes! Catching bad guys is my dream!
Do you think I can do it?!
How should I know?
No! I'll do it! If I'm gonna be a chore boy
for the rest of my life,
then I'll break out of here
and catch even Alvida-sama... no, Alvida!
--L-Luffy-san! Let's get out of here!
--Why?
You saw how powerful her club is!
In these waters, she's the most...
I'm the most what?!
Th-Th-The...
The most ugly, cragged old hag ever!
What did you say?!
I... I'm going to join the Navy!
And then I'm gonna beat up pirates!
Do you even know what you're saying?!
I do! I'm gonna do what I want to do!
I'm gonna... I'm gonna join the Navy...
And catch your lousy ass!
You damn pipsqueak!
That's how Luffy-san and
I went out on a journey.
I can't stand to watch the
Navy like this anymore! I...
...want to be an honorable Navy soldier!
Is that so wrong?!
Luffy-san and I haven't known each
other long, but we are friends!
Right?
Yeah! We're gonna part ways,
but we'll always be friends!
Pardon me!
Is it true that you are pirates?!
Yeah. We gained a member
and became a pirate group just now!
We appreciate that you saved our base
and this town from that tyrant!
However,
now that we know you are pirates,
in the name of the Navy,
we cannot stand by quietly!
You will leave this town at once!
Out of obligation,
we will refrain from contacting headquarters.
Well, guess we should go!
Thanks for the food, lady!
Aren't you part of their crew?
Eh? I...
I'm...
Hold it!
Well? Is he?!
I know what he's done until now.
Luffy-san! You wouldn't!
There was this reaaally fat pirate lady,
I think her name was Ahiruda.
Luffy-san!
If they find out I was on a pirate ship,
I'll never get to join the Navy!
Man, she was an ugly hag!
And for two whole years, this guy was her--
Please don't! Please don't!
Now you've done it, you bastard!
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
Ouch!
Hey! You've gone too far. That's enough.
It's very clear that you
guys aren't crewmates!
Now leave this town at once!
On purpose...
He did that on purpose...
For me...
He purposely got me riled up
to make me hit him...
Please! Please!
Let me join the Navy!
I'll gladly do chores or anything else!
If it means I can be a Navy soldier!
Commander! I'm against the idea!
I still don't fully trust this kid!
There have been cases of Navy
soldiers being pirate spies!
We'll first need to conduct
a background check...
I'm a man who will become a Navy officer!
Thank you!
I'll never forget all you've done for me!
I've never heard of
a pirate being thanked by a Navy soldier.
Let's meet again sometime, Koby!
Luffy-san...
All hands, salute!
What?
Hey, Captain Koby! What are you doing?
Come back!
Yes, sir!
Thank you!
Uh-huh.
Now, you'll soon arrive at New Marineford,
so we'll escort you from here!
Thank you.
Hey.
What is it?
Do you like Lucy, Koby-kun?
You like Luffyland, right?
No! H-He's our enemy!
Yeah, right!
We won't tell anyone...
Let's have a chat.
L-Let go of me! I-I'm from the Navy!
But you looked happy
when you were reading the paper.
--Th-That's because...
--Come on. Let's talk!
P-Please stop!
Oh, Luffyland is in this article here, too!
What?!
So you like him as we thought!
What's going on?!
Why was this fool who screwed
up my important SMILE trade...
KAIDO, KING OF THE BEASTS
ONE OF THE FOUR EMPERORS OF THE SEA
...at that old bag's place?!
He won?!
Huh?! When did I lose?! To who?!
I'm sure he wrote this article, Mama!
Yeah... I'll teach you
a lesson, Morgans... No!
I'll pay you back...
CHARLOTTE LINLIN
BIG MOM, ONE OF THE FOUR EMPERORS OF THE SEA
Straw Hat!
Emperor?
MARSHALL D. TEECH
BLACKBEARD, ONE OF THE FOUR EMPERORS OF THE SEA
It's too soon for you to be called that...
RED-HAIRED SHANKS
ONE OF THE FOUR EMPERORS OF THE SEA
I think... I'll see you soon...
Luffy!
So it got lower.
We can't do anything about it...
Cheer up, Luffy... I'll help you.
Let's work hard again.
Do you want me to make you something?
Uh-huh...
Wait a minute...
Look...
100 thousand, 1 million, 10 million...
100 million...
Your bounty...
...is 1.5 billion berries!
Whaaat?!
The rest of the world is heading
for the Reverie and the Straw Hats
are on their way to the Land of Wano.
The mysterious individuals who appear
when cries echo across the ocean.
They're the formidable captains of
the Revolutionary Army that escaped death!
Led by Dragon and Sabo,
they finally start to act to
bring down the Celestial Dragons!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sabo Goes into Action!
All the Captains of the Revolutionary Army Appear!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!