Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era is experiencing
a groundswell beyond the World
Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"Sabo Goes into Action!
All the Captains of the Revolutionary Army Appear!"
A PORT TOWN OF THE KINGDOM OF LULUCIA
GRAND LINE
Prepare to fire!
Shoot them up!
Let's go!
Grab all their money and goods!
What's the Navy doing?!
I thought they came to help!
How dare they destroy our ship...
Damn!
To hell with the Navy!
Their king's gone to the Reverie.
All their able soldiers are accompanying him!
An unguarded country is an
easy target for pirates!
Listen carefully!
I'm one of the Emperor of the
Sea Blackbeard's affiliates,
upon whom was bestowed the name "Peachbeard"!
PEACHBEARD - CAPTAIN OF THE PEACHBEARD PIRATES
BOUNTY: 52 MILLION BERRIES
Remember my name!
Fear Blackbeard!
Now, you guys, rip everything off of them
in Blackbeard's name!
Okay, give me your money!
S-Stop...
It's no use hiding!
We'll burn the whole town down!
Hey, come on! Let's get out of here!
Hey, catch that girl!
Stop right there!
What do you have in your arms?
Show me what you're holding so tightly!
This is...
Huh? Just milk?!
Psh! I thought that it was money...
Oh well, I'll take it anyway.
No... This is for the
children of the village...
Shut up!
Why can't you just give this thing up?
Please give it back to me...
I really need that milk...
Bring us your money, too!
What? I don't have any...
I bet you have your Heavenly Tribute funds.
Th-The Heavenly Tribute is what we have to pay
to the king and the Celestial Dragons...
We're scrimping and saving every day...
If I can't pay the Heavenly
Tribute, I'll be killed!
What?! Your king sounds terrible!
All right!
Hey, guys, search!
They're hiding the Heavenly Tribute!
They have money! Take all they've got!
Come on! Tell me where's your Tribute!
Leave us alone... This town is poor...
P-Please don't take this money!
Let it go!
Somebody...
You didn't have to get hurt
if you'd just given it up!
Kill everyone who disobeys!
I'm begging you!
Please leave us alone!
Shut up!
Go, Morley...
Who are you?
Why is it shaking?
Is there something underground?!
What the?!
A giant trident?!
Is it a Giant?
One, two! One, two!
One, two!
One, two!!
A Giant emerged from the ground!
In a strange outfit!
What? Why is he wearing a miniskirt?
Come on! Where are you looking?!
Why are you staring at me?!
Are you that attracted to me?!
Why am I suddenly accused of something?!
What's this old man talking about?!
Just shoot! Shoot him to death!
What?!
Stop it, boys!
Th-The Giants live underground?!
I've never seen one before...
Who is he?
Don't be so mean!
Come on!
How is it possible?!
He's pushing the ground around like clay!
Don't be intimidated!
He must be a power-user!
He's so strong...
Now, what do you wanna do?
You passive...
...pieces of trash.
What? Trash?
What should we do?
Excuse me!
Who are you... Who are you people?
Oh, my!
Come on, wait a minute, Morley!
What do you want?
I have a newly-invented weapon
but you went ahead!
Who are these people?!
A murder of crows?!
Captain!
S-Someone is on the roof!
What?!
The crows are gathering together...
How dare you harm the people
who don't fight back...
Captain Peachbeard... Those four are...
...supposed to be scattered
around the world...
They're the captains...
...of the Revolutionary Army!
W... W...
What?!
MORLEY - CAPTAIN OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
WESTERN FORCES
Hey, they're still staring at me.
BELO BETTY - CAPTAIN OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
EASTERN FORCES
Don't get panicky, scum!
LINDBERGH - CAPTAIN OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
SOUTHERN FORCES
Let me use my new weapon!
KARASU - CAPTAIN OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
NORTHERN FORCES
We're here to put a stop to you.
The captains of...
...the Revolutionary Army...
ON THE SEA OF THE NEW WORLD
Oh, don't move, Luffy!
I'll have to wrap it all over again!
Sorry, sorry...
Oh, yeah, Nami.
What?
Isn't there anything about
the Revolutionary Army?
Let's see...
The Revolutionary Army...
...is a mysterious organization
that works secretly to
take down the World Government.
Their goal is to free the
people who are suffering...
...under the World Government
headed by the Celestial Dragons.
The leader of the Revolutionary Army...
...is Straw Hat Luffy's father,
Monkey D. Dragon.
And...
...one of Luffy's two brothers,
Sabo, is working as the Chief of Staff
of the Revolutionary Army.
When they were kids, Sabo
died in an incident...
That's what Luffy thought,
but appearing in front of
him at Dressrosa was...
Sabo!!
Thank you, Luffy!
I'm glad that you're alive!
It seems like there isn't any article
about the Revolutionary Army.
Okay...
According to the last issue,
their general headquarters that was veiled in mystery
for decades was destroyed...
Sabo...
I guess we can start our top officers' meeting
without a problem,
Dragon-san.
Yeah...
It was the right decision
to relocate our general headquarters here.
I was worried what would happen
when we lost Baltigo...
Oh, there they are.
You're finally here!
Heehaw!
Now, this is my country!
KAMABAKKA KINGDOM, PEACHY ISLAND
No restraint is necessary, guys!
You can do as you like!
Ivan-sama is right!
Where's our Chief of Staff?
What? This is a crucial
time. Where did he go?
Don't worry.
He's there...
His bounty has increased so much.
Hey, what are you reading?
Let me see!
Luffy...
Heehaw!
EMPORIO IVANKOV
A TOP OFFICER OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
Straw boy is something!
He sure is your son...
MONKEY D. DRAGON
LEADER OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
And...
...I didn't know that Sanji
boy was Germa 66's prince!
He didn't mention it at all! How insolent!
Germa has been expelled from the World Government
because of that incident.
Straw boy and Sanji boy...
Just as I expected,
they're becoming the center of
attention in the Great Pirate Era!
INAZUMA - A TOP OFFICER
OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
HACK - A SOLDIER OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
The Straw Hats... I'm excited!
Anyway, the top officers are late.
KOALA - FISH-MAN KARATE ASSISTANT INSTRUCTOR
OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
I'm sure they're somewhere near by now...
You're right...
By the way, Sabo,
what have you been doing there?
You kept looking and smiling at
Luffy-kun's article too much and
got a cramp in your face, right?
Are you stupid?!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
This is Lindbergh!
What's wrong? Everyone's waiting.
Is this Sabo? We're almost there.
But there is trouble!
Mind if we're a bit late?
No. As long as you're okay.
Clank.
Oh, I'm so excited... All the top officers of
the Revolutionary Army will be here!
I get to see Morley-sama!
I love Betty-sama by far the most!
Sabo, we don't wanna waste any time.
Let's assemble now.
We better solidify our plan before they come.
You're up, Chief of Staff.
Yeah...
At the upcoming Reverie, we'll finally...
Declare war....
SABO - CHIEF OF STAFF OF
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
...against the Celestial Dragons.
So they're...
...the captains of...
...the Revolutionary Army!
Why are their four top officers here?!
Gee, boys are so violent!
That's because they like you, dorky Giant.
No way. That's gross!
I checked in with Sabo
so can we do it now, Betty?!
You can't stop me...
No one's answering my question
and what is he mumbling about?!
I won't forgive them!
I don't know why but he got pissed!
What are you gonna do, you pieces of trash?!
Get killed or fight?!
Choose your own destiny!
Being a hero is someone else's problem?!
Maybe you can be a hero!
The townspeople picked up sticks!
Come on, that's hilarious!
Are you gonna fight us?!
I don't know why but I'm inspired
and feel a surge of power!
Let's drive the pirates out of here!
We should fight and protect our country!
That's right!
That's Betty's Pump-Pump Fruit power!
By waving her flag,
she can bring forth people's power from within!
Betty is a flag-bearer of freedom!
Now, advance!
Ha! I guess they don't know
it hurts when they get shot!
Don't get carried away!
Lind! Karasu! Back them up!
Got it!
Take this!
Cool Shooter!
--It's cold!
--My gun got frozen!
You bastards! Get out of here, pirates!
Don't back down! Cut them up!
Take their weapons away!
The crows took our swords!
Give them back!
Don't stop!
Fight against your fate!
Go away!
What happened to them all of a sudden?
You...!
The milk!
Give it back to me!
--Let's get away!
--We'll make you pay for this!
Peachbeard... His bounty is 52 million...
That's like nothing.
He's just a crappy pirate who could
only target a country that was weak.
Blackbeard-sama will come after you...
I'm sorry but he doesn't
care about his subordinates.
Come on, boy! Shut up already!
Hey, you cowardly, weak and foolish people!
If you turn him in to the World Government,
you'll get the bounty.
That'll be 52 million berries.
And that's...
...all yours!
I want you to have this, too.
The Revolutionary Army's contact information.
You did great...
What?
Call us any time...
We'll never turn our back on
the weak who stand up.
B-Belo Betty-sama!
Th-Thank you very much,
everyone of the Revolutionary Army!
Hey, what are we meeting up for this time?
We'll pick a fight with
the Celestial Dragons.
Oh, that's great! I can't wait!
Oh, and Karasu!
Turn on your loudspeaker switch.
I forgot...
It's two days to go until the Reverie.
All the different intentions across the world
start swirling around...
Okay, roger.
Clank.
I got a call, Sabo-kun.
Everyone will be here soon.
Okay...
Let's go...
...to drag down the Celestial Dragons.
His exploits at Impel Down
and during the Paramount War,
have earned Monkey D. Luffy
quite a name in the world!
Inheriting the will of Whitebeard
and his brother Ace,
Luffy has now become a hero of the age and
the Navy's new Admiral of the Fleet, Sakazuki,
finally shows his teeth!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Going into Action!
The Implacable New Admiral of the Fleet - Sakazuki!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!