Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era
is experiencing a groundswell
beyond the World Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"The Paramount War!
The Inherited Will of the King of the Pirates!"
They say he's the fifth Emperor of the Sea!
I'm amazed!
I told you to get out...
This is going to be another problem for us.
I'll sink every last one of these pirates.
My goal hasn't changed a bit after two years!
The public execution of Ace
two years ago...
That day, from the moment
Straw Hat fell out of the sky,
the times started to change in a big way.
Ace!
From the era of Whitebeard...
....to something totally new!
Luffy!!
Ace, we're coming to rescue you!
We're here for you!
Garp! It's your family again!
Luffy!
You came here to rescue your brother?
Yeah.
A squirt like you will be dead meat!
Shut up! That's not up to you to decide!
I'm gonna rescue Ace!
--H-He's competing...
--...With Whitebeard!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
Get outta my way!
Stay away, Luffy!
I beg you, Luffy!
I don't want you to share my fate!
This is all my fault!
I'm...
...your brother!
I'm gonna save you even if it means death!
Marco, we can't let that kid die.
Alright.
Luffy!
Straw Hat Luffy who dealt an
immense blow to Impel Down,
came face-to-face with Whitebeard.
At that moment, he became an enemy
who we should have never let loose...
Should I be the last voice you hear
before you die?
Pops!
Do it!
Don't do it!
Don't do it!!
I'm on my way!
Haki of the Color of the... Supreme King!
That brat...
He uses it, too!
--Straw Hat will make it!
--Yeah! Keep going!
Finally... finally...
I made it!
Luffy!
You're so...!
Ace!
You can't get away from me!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Balloon!
Ace is still alive!
Fire! Blow them away!
Straw boy!
No way!
You've always been like this!
Luffy!
You've never even listened to me...
...and always done such crazy things!
--Good!
--Oh my!
Ace!
Ace!!
Everyone, survive at any cost
and go back to the New World safely!
As soon as you rescue
"Fire Fist" Ace, you run!
The Whitebeards must be a group of cowards!
Well your captain is that guy
so you can't help it, can you?
Because after all, Whitebeard is just a...
...loser from the old times!
Take back what you just said!
Whitebeard will die as a loser!
It's fitting for a big
fish in a little barrel!
Whitebeard is a great pirate
who shaped this era!
The name of this era should be "Whitebeard"!
Both Whitebeard and you guys who call him Pops
are the same after all - losers!
Ace...
Ace's Vivre Card!
Gold Roger - the King of the Pirates,
Dragon - the revolutionary.
I was amazed to hear that
sons of those two are step brothers.
You two have bad blood in your veins.
I don't care if the others get away
as long as I get you two!
Watch what I do.
Wait!
Luffy!
Ace...
Ace!
Hey, are you all right? Hey.
I'm sorry, Luffy...
Huh?
Could you tell them...
...what I'm about to say now?
Pops!
Everybody!
And you Luffy.
Thank you...
...for loving someone like me
who is good for nothing...
...and who has such bad blood in his veins...
...up to today.
Thank you!
Ace...
Ace's death...
And Whitebeard met his end as well...
...with the sudden appearance
of his former subordinate
Marshall D. Teech, also known as Blackbeard.
Luffy and his allies were cornered
by the Navy's persistent attacks.
Showing up on the scene in the chaos at Marineford
to end the war was...
"Red-Haired" Shanks!
"Red-Haired"! He is the one who
motivated Luffy to become a pirate!
Everybody.
For now,
you need to do as I say!
Whitebeard, Ace...
Let us handle the burial of those two.
The war was broadcast to the world.
I won't let you dishonor their death
in public any longer!
That's ridiculous!
We raise a shout of victory by exposing
their dead bodies to public view!
I agree!
Only because it's you, I allow it,
"Red-Haired"!
Thanks.
This war is...
...over!
After that war,
pirates became active again...
Straw Hat Luffy...
I didn't expect him to play such a big role
in this era!
On top of that, there were
Whitebeard's last words...
The One Piece...
...is real!!
It's just a dead man's bullshit!
Damn Whitebeard...
I can't believe everyone's been manipulated!
They don't know what it means to
rebel against us...
I'll teach them!
NAVY
Even though it has been relocated,
New Marineford is still guarding the
gate of the Holyland of Mariejois
where the Celestial Dragons reside.
The place where the Paramount War took place
is now Branch G-1.
HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS
FORMER MARINEFORD
The two Navy bases are situated
on both sides of the Red Line...
...to protect Mariejois against invasion.
This is Red Port.
RED PORT
Two huge ports like this are
on each side of the Red Line,
and it's the Government's official means
of getting to the other side of the wall.
Bondola 1, now departing.
Oh, Dad! It's going up!
Bondolas, bubble-based gondolas,
make their way up to the Holyland of Mariejois.
Look! Ships are arriving one after another!
Yeah!
Clear the way for the royals!
Oh! Beer VI of the Roshwan Kingdom!
There are the Matryoshesses!
How cute!
Queen Morollon of the Tajine Kingdom!
She's so beautiful!
Cheers to all the lovely eyes in the world!
It's better to die standing
than live on your knees!
King Taco of the Kingdom of the Dead!
King Ham Burger of the Ballywood Kingdom
has arrived as well!
Why does he walk so slowly?
I may walk slowly, but...
I'll never turn around!
That ship is...
...Vice Admiral Garp's Navy ship!
Oh, that's...
...the Great Knight of
the Sea - King Neptune!
And the three strongest of the Neptune Army!
The Ryugu Kingdom is attending the Reverie!
Prince Fukaboshi!
Moonfish! Moonfish!
I wanna have fun on land!
It's so bright on land-do-re-mi-fa-so!
Let's go, guys.
Moonfish!
Garp-sama!
I thought I was gonna die in the deep sea!
RYUGU PALACE
Hey, Princess-san! Come out!
Okay, Shirahoshi.
Let's go to Mariejois!
Yes...
So this is the surface!
It's Mermaid Princess-sama!
It has been 200 years
since the Ryugu Kingdom began
affiliating with the World Government,
but they have attended the Reverie
only once before.
So this is indeed a big deal.
HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS
Clank.
Sakazuki-san told me to find you
and kick you out...
You wanna fight me?
Give me a break! I don't want to!
It's not like you wanna destroy
the conference, right?
No, I don't...
What I want to destroy is...
...the system.
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious!
You had a long journey.
How is the old man Vegapunk doing?
Well, of course I couldn't lay eyes on it
but he has completed something incredible.
Oh, what is it like?
We no longer need the
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
You're crazy! Really!
By the way, the food here is delicious,
just as I thought!
Why don't you eat something?
Are you still fasting?
RYOKUGYU - AN ADMIRAL
OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
If some young lady helps me, I would eat!
I'm so lazy. I haven't eaten
anything for three years!
The Revolutionary Army led by Sabo commences
their operation to infiltrate Mariejois for
the purpose of changing history forever!
Meanwhile, the dazzling view of
the beautiful surface world brings
tears to Shirahoshi's eyes
and gives her a wish that marks a new chapter
in the Fish-Men's history!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"One Step Forward for Her Dream!
Shirahoshi Goes Out in the Sun!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!