Yes! We've got Super Powers
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Your dream is like a monster
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
will become your one and only treasure
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing in a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
The future gently brings a morning
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era
is experiencing a groundswell
beyond the World Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"One Step Forward for Her Dream!
Shirahoshi Goes Out in the Sun!"
How beautiful she is!
Fire! More than I imagined...
Should we do a feature story on her,
President Morgans?!
Princess Shirahoshi!
President Morgans?
Oh, no! He's totally captivated by her!
Mermaid Princess-sama!
Garp, Shirahoshi is very popular-jamon!
Even on land, word is spreading that
The Fish-Man Island's Mermaid Princess...
...is as beautiful as
Pirate Empress Hancock!
She's so pretty. I'm sure she surpasses
everyone's expectations!
And she's huge!
L-Luffy-sama's grandfather-sama!
Is that what they call a forest on land?!
No, that's a tree.
Hey, Garp the hero!
You know who I am, don't you?
No, you stupid brat! Get out of my way!
"Stupid brat"?! I must've heard wrong!
Yes, Stelly!
Maybe that's not not-it!
How rude!
I'm Stelly, king of the Goa
Kingdom where you come from!
KING STELLY OF THE GOA KINGDOM IN THE EAST BLUE
(SABO'S ADOPTED BROTHER)
And since you're a citizen,
you're one of my subjects!
Remember that!
If I'm correct, Stelly is your
adopted brother, right, Sabo?
Stelly was adopted by Sabo's noble parents.
With that as his first foothold,
he looked enviously to connect with royalty
and married Princess Isntoinette.
Later, the king and prince of the Goa Kingdom
mysteriously died
and several months ago,
Stelly became the king.
The Goa Kingdom...
The Gray Terminal in that country is
the place we first met, right, Luffy?
GOA KINGDOM
GRAY TERMINAL
At once!
Whoa! You got a lot!
Way more than I did!
That's a lot of money!
How'd you get that?
I robbed some thugs near the main gate!
Damn! You won again!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
It's been five years since we started
to put money in our "pirate savings."
I wonder how much we need
to get a pirate ship.
I don't know.
10 million or 100 million maybe?
Long way to go.
"A pirate ship"?!
You guys! Are you gonna become pirates?!
I'm gonna become one, too!
Hey!
At first, Ace and I didn't accept him,
but later, we got close enough to
exchange a cup of sake to become brothers.
So from now on,
we're brothers!
Yeah!!
Ace, Luffy and I did as we liked
and the old man Garp would beat us.
We were gonna become pirates...
So I forfeited my noble heritage
and I planned to carry on living with the two.
But one day, my father came
and forced me to come back with him.
I'll leave the rest up to you,
pirates.
Of course, mister.
You've already paid us for this.
We will take care of these two
so they won't bother your boy again.
Wait a minute, Bluejam!
Dad, that's enough! I understand!
What do you understand?
Don't do it, Sabo!
I'll do as you say.
I'll live as you want so...
...please don't hurt these two!
I'm begging you.
They're very important to
me, they're my brothers.
Sabo...
Then go home right now.
You should stop playing pirate -
it's just a waste of time.
Hey! Don't go!
Be quiet!
Sabo, run!
You don't have to worry about us!
You said you wanna live freely with us!
Sabo, don't go!
Are you gonna put an end to your dream?!
Sabo!
Sabo!!
At that time, all I could do was
turn my back and scream in my mind...
"Spread your wings and
fly away freely for me."
I'm glad that you're safe,
young master.
Oh, Sabo! You're back.
You got bigger.
Mom.
Now Stelly,
say "hi" to your older brother.
Nice to meet you, brother!
My name is Stelly and I'm eight.
A fire?!
Yeah. You don't know about it
because you weren't here.
But they decided it months ago.
They decided to burn down the Gray Terminal.
Then this country will be clean!
What are you talking about?!
That's impossible!
They're gonna burn up
all the shame of this country.
What are you doing?!
You have to evacuate!
Ace! Luffy!
Run!
What happened to you, boy?
This town smells worse
than the Gray Terminal.
It smells like rotten people!
If I stay here... I'll never be free!
I'm...
...ashamed of being born a noble!
They finally made a kid say this!
Goa Kingdom!
What a nice day!
It's perfect for setting sail!
I set off.
I left my noble heritage, parents,
and country behind...
...to live as the freest pirate ever!
How rude is that!
Saint Jalmack!
There is a child on the ship!
When someone flies a black flag,
he's a pirate regardless of who he is-eh.
But most importantly...
A commoner shouldn't cross
the path of my ship!!
Ace... Luffy...
Help me... Somebody...
I met Dragon-san there
and it changed my destiny...
So the damn Celestial Dragons are up there...
I'm ready. Let's do it already.
Chief of Staff.
Yeah!
They sank his ship so you must've
thought that Sabo guy was dead.
Yeah, I thought so at that time.
I cried a lot when Pedro died.
I know how you felt!
A-Ace... I...
I wanna become stronger!
Then I can protect anything or anyone!
I don't have to lose anybody!
I beg you!
Ace,
please don't die!
Cut it out!
Worry about yourself first!
You're far weaker than me!
Listen carefully, Luffy!
I'll never die!
Uh-huh.
Sabo told me to take care of you, too.
I promise that I'll never die!
How can I leave a wimpy
brother like you behind?
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
I'm not smart so I don't quite know
what really killed Sabo yet.
But it must be something opposed to freedom.
Sabo died before he knew freedom.
We exchanged that same cup of sake
and we're alive!
So listen, Luffy.
We have to live without leaving any regrets.
Uh-huh.
We gotta go out to sea someday...
...and live as we like.
Freer than anyone else.
Uh-huh!
That means we'll make enemies of many people.
Even the old man will become our enemy.
You gotta be willing to risk everything.
Let's go out to sea at 17!
And we will become... pirates!
Let's start with finding a crew!
I want at least 10 of them.
And the black flag!
Alright! Let's go!
I'm gonna become...
...the King of the Pirates!
So Sabo-san and Ace-san had an
impact on Luffy-san's sailing-out.
Isn't that nice?! He sailed out for
a never-ending adventure!
And your brother Sabo
who you thought was dead
is now the No.2 of the Revolutionary Army!
The Revolutionary Army's leader
is your father, Dragon.
The other brother, Portgas D. Ace
was the Whitebeard Pirates'
2nd division commander
and the King of the Pirates
- Gol D. Roger's son...
What kind of family is that?!
Too many badasses!
Doesn't it make you feel strange
when you think that your sworn
brother is with your father?
Hmmm...  I don't know
because I've never met my dad before...
But,
wherever I am,
it feels like I'm always connected to Sabo.
The king of the Goa Kingdom?!
The king of the Goa Kingdom, huh?
It's a peaceful rural kingdom
but it's home to a number of outlaws.
Garp is an exception.
The leader of the Revolutionary Army - Dragon,
the Chief of Staff - Sabo,
and the pirates - "Fire Fist" and Straw Hat.
How interesting!
Now, kneel at my feet, Garp!
Get out of my way. Your face irritates me.
His rudeness leaves me speechless!
I'll cut to the chase, Garp.
Give me some pull with the World Nobles!
I wanna eventually become a Celestial Dragon.
You wanna be a scumbag like them?
What?!
Oh, please! Did anyone hear that?!
That could get us the death penalty!
Oh! I shouldn't say that. I take it back.
He scares me!
Are you okay-jamon, young man?
What?
He moved?! I thought he was a building!
Is he a Giant? I heard they eat humans
and can melt rocks with their saliva...
No, wait. Who are they?!
Fangs?!
Scales?!
Look at the colors of their skin.
Are they Fish-Men who are
half-human and half-fish?!
They're classified as fish and you'll
get a rare disease by touching them...
Don't touch me!
Bondola 2, now departing.
All right, take care of yourself!
Luffy-sama's grandfather-sama,
thank you very much.
It was fun to travel with you.
It's so high...
Unbelievable...
What's the matter-jamon, Shirahoshi?
Father-sama... It's the sun...
Brother-sama! The sun is shining so brightly!
Yeah...
The sky goes on forever!
The sea is also endless
and sparkling in the sun!
Yeah, it's really amazing! Mambo!
I didn't know that the
surface was so dazzling!
What a beautiful world!
Mm-hm.
The Sun Tree that lights up the sea floor
can't compare-jamon.
Father-sama, I...
If possible, I want to live on land!
I want to show this world in the sun
to the people of our kingdom!
I'll ask them.
That's what the Reverie is all about-jamon.
KAMABAKKA KINGDOM
Since you're fighting against the
World Government for the Fish-Men,
do you have mixed feelings, Koala?
About the Ryugu Kingdom
attending the Reverie?
No, I don't, Betty-san.
It's not the World Government
that we really wanna bring down.
It's the Celestial Dragons who rule it.
RED LINE
It's really high! I'm scared!
It's very windy! And it's shaking!
Be quiet.
D-D-Did you just see that?!
What did you see?
There was a G-Giant in the wall,
staring at us!
H-H-He had a trident!
You must be hallucinating...
Can't you see how high we're at now?
It was really there!
--Look over there! They're crows!
--They don't usually come up this high.
Those are the birds that
everyone was talking about?
They're flying!
If they peck at the bubble, we're gonna fall!
Hey, guard! Pull out your gun!
Shoot down the crows!
They're gonna pop the bubble!
Don't worry.
You'll be fine. King Stelly.
Vivi from Alabasta. Rebecca from Dressrosa.
And Shirahoshi from the Fish-Man Island.
The three heroines who once stood up
to save their countries
from crises along with the Straw Hats,
meet each other with memories
of Luffy in their mind!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Miss Him! Vivi and Rebecca's Sentiments!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!