Yes! We've got Super Powers
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Your dream is like a monster
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
will become your one and only treasure
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing in a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
The future gently brings a morning
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era is experiencing
a groundswell beyond the World
Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"I Miss Him!
Vivi and Rebecca's Sentiments!"
Shirahoshi and the others
who are headed to Mariejois
where the World Conference
Reverie will take place,
are riding the Bondola
which smoothly ascends the Red Line.
Eventually, the Bondola arrives
at the top of the Red Line.
Thank you for riding with us.
Please watch your step.
Merfolk!
You've left the suitable climate for those bubbles
so use these reinforced ones...
Thanks!
Wow, it's huge!
Guests will climb the large,
long staircase from there
until they reach the world's highest and biggest continent
located at the center of the world.
Somebody, carry me on their back!
We're almost there, King Stelly.
This is where the descendants of
the creators of the world reside.
The name of this magnificent place is...
The Holyland of Mariejois.
This is where the Celestial Dragons are...
I wanna live here!
What a beautiful place!
Is that green area a forest?
It's man-made but yes.
So this is... Mariejois!
The castle's still quite far away...
Please come this way.
Shirahoshi-sama and family,
please use these handles!
Is it an earthquake?!
It's started moving!
I'm gonna die! Save me!
This is a Travelator.
It allows the ground to move.
Father, shall we take a normal walkway?
Shirahoshi, you wanna see the forest, right?
Fukaboshi...
The scenery is beautiful!
Let's take our time!
Oh, that sounds good, Brother-sama!
Father-sama, let's do so!
No problem, of course!
We'll escort you!
I bet they're afraid of modern conveniences!
Stupid fish!
Let's procure one for our kingdom!
The Troublator! It's so useful!
--It's a "Travelator."
--You can call it that, too!
What's this?
I feel something isn't right...
Move at a nice, slow and comfortable speed!
Maintain the same pace, slaves!
Don't stop! Keep moving!
Save me... Or just kill me...
SOME CELESTIAL DRAGON'S PALACE
F-Father-sama! Father-sama!
What's wrong, Charlos?
It's a mermaid-eh!
A very big one...
Open the gate!
A MINGLING PLAZA INSIDE THE CASTLE
Seems like royal families and their bodyguards
from across the world are here...
Their bodyguards look very tough.
I guess we'll be safe...
The food looks fancy, too!
If it's joyous like this every day,
during the seven-day conference from tomorrow,
accompanying family members
won't be bored-fa-mi-re-do!
We love samba more than anything!
Would you like to dance with us?! Samba!
I'd be happy to! King of Samba! Mambo!
--Mambo, mambo! Shake, shake!
--Samba, samba! Shake, shake!
Father is having a good time, too,
so I'm relieved.
U-Um...
E-Everyone?
Oh, Princess from under the sea!
You're breathtakingly beautiful as I heard!
Would you like to meet my son?
He's royalty and single!
Papan! She's not bad! Not bad!
U-Um...
Princess-sama,
we have an only son who is royalty, too!
P-Pappy! I like her!
Um... Uh...
No, Mermaid Princess!
Please meet my royal son!
We have three handsome royal princes!
Now, which royal do you like?!
Oh, um... uh...
Um... I...
None of you are my type!
What?! Even though they're royal?!
Shirahoshi!
Damn you! You humiliated me!
No, she was saying "I'm not married, either"
in an undersea dialect...
Brother Ryuboshi?!
When this happens,
just say "How lovely" or "Let's have dinner sometime"
and turn them down softly, Shirahoshi!
What?! I can't lie...
It's just dodging not lying!
If you hurt someone, it could become
a diplomatic issue-fa-mi-re-do! Let's go!
How cute!
VIVI - PRINCESS OF THE ALABASTA KINGDOM
(AND KAROO)
You're so cute! You're like a fairy!
LEO - LEADER OF THE TONTA
CORPS, TONTATTA TRIBE
That's not a compliment to a warrior!
BIAN     CUB     MANSHERRY
Are you okay, Leo?!
Oh, I'm sorry! I didn't mean it!
What?!
Then, that's okay!
Great! It seems like she's a good person!
So you can move rapidly.
I didn't notice until Karoo found you.
I showed myself because
I heard you said you knew Luffyland.
We're Luffyland and his crew's subordinates!
We're pirates!
Pirates?!
So cute!
So Luffy-san and his crew have
such a lovely subordinate!
Nice to meet you, Leo-san!
Nice to meet you, too!
I never thought I'd be able to talk
so much about Lucy at the Reverie.
It's no wonder. They're
traveling across the world.
REBECCA - LADY-IN-WAITING OF DRESSROSA
Did Lucy visit Vivi-san's country...
No, I mean, Luffy?
That's right! Luffyland!
He did...
My home country Alabasta
still exists today...
...thanks to them.
Princess Vivi of Alabasta,
the sand kingdom in the Grand Line...
...is the Straw Hats' friend who once
traveled with them on their ship.
All right! At any rate, no matter what happens,
this thing on our left arm...
...is the sign of our friendship!
Because of a plot by the
then Warlord of the Sea,
Sir Crocodile who looked to
take control of the country,
a civil war broke out between
the royal army and a rebel army...
At last the time has come for the
Alabasta Kingdom to disappear.
While the Straw Hats were trying to
stop the clash between the two armies,
Luffy noticed Vivi was shouldering
everything by herself.
And what's wrong with thinking that?
What's wrong with not wanting people to die?!
People die.
The rebel army, the royal army, and the
people of this kingdom haven't done anything wrong!
So why do people have to die
when it's all Crocodile's fault?!
Then why are you putting
your life on the line?!
--Whoa, Luffy! You're going too far!
--Damn it, Luffy!
Just one look at this kingdom and even I can tell
what most needs to be done!
What is it?!
As if putting your single
life on the line is enough!
Then what should I be putting on the line?!
I don't have anything else
that I can put on the line...
At least try putting all of our
lives on the line together!
Aren't we friends?!
The Straw Hats and Vivi headed for Alubarna,
the capital city, to stop the civil war,
but Crocodile appeared in front of them.
Sables!!
Who do you think I am?
There are any number of rookies like you,
who are nothing but talk,
Straw Hat Luffy,
here in the Grand Line.
Taken in by Crocodile's plot,
the rebel army and the
royal army got into a fierce battle.
Meanwhile, the Straw Hats fought the members
of Baroque Works, the secret crime
syndicate, on Vivi's behalf.
Take this! Special Attack...
Here it comes! Moletown...
Smoke Star!!
The rest... is up to you, Chopper!
Stop! Mr. 4!
It's me!
Stop...
Special Attack: Hammer Shooting Star!!
Veau Vengeance!!
Swan Bombardier Dive!!
Take this...
Tornado Tempo!
What?!
One-Sword Style Iai Draw and
Resheath Technique: Lion Song!
Atomic Dash!
Let me tell you something...
You can't save this country.
Goodbye, Princess...
Crocodile!!
Luffy-san!
Just in time.
Vivi...
She tells others not to die...
but she's the first to lay down her own life
to save others.
If we don't help her, she'll die.
You guys will kill her.
You're so dense.
That's why I'm telling you
that you can just ditch that burden...!
We don't want her to die!
That's how friends are!
Please... stop fighting!
Who the hell do you think I am?!
I don't care who you are...
I'll surpass you!
Gum-Gum...!
Desert...
Storm!
La Spada!
Luffy-san...
Please stop fighting!
Please don't fight... any more...!!
Since our nightmares are... all over...
Crocodile's plot was thwarted
by Luffy and the others and
the Alabasta Kingdom was saved.
However, the Straw Hats
didn't get credit for it,
because the Government reported that
it was the Navy's achievement.
Say, everyone...
What... should I do...?
We'll draw the ship near the eastern harbor
just once at exactly noon tomorrow.
If you want to continue traveling with us,
that moment is the
only chance to come aboard.
If that happens, we'll welcome you...
though you'll become a pirate.
Come, Vivi! Definitely come! Come now!
If I go, you'll go too, right?
Say... Karoo...
What would you like to do?
Everyone!
Vivi!
Karoo!
Vivi-chan!
Let's go back! Better hurry!
The Navy is right there, too!
I came to say goodbye!
What did she just...?
I can't... go with you!
Thank you so much for everything!
I'd like to go on more adventures,
but there's no ignoring...
that I love this country!
So I can't go!
I see!
I...
If we ever meet again someday...
will you call me your friend again?!
All right! At any rate, no matter what happens,
this thing on our left arm...
...is the sign of our friendship!
They don't like to be seen as heroes...
And because of their bounties and people's talk,
they keep gaining notoriety,
but I'm sure they haven't changed.
When I read about Dressrosa,
I knew that Luffy-san and the others decided to
save somebody again!
That's right!
To us, Luffy is...
The Straw Hats are very special!
I miss him... Lucy...
Um...
Were you talking about Luffy-sama just now?
Oh, the Mermaid Princess!
Shirahoshi!
Talking about him doesn't always mean
they know him!
Luffy-kun is a pirate!
If someone finds out you're his friend-ti-do!
The Mermaid Princess knows Luffy-san?
Hey, did you just say Luffy-sama?
Wait, Rebecca! If we heard wrong...
Yes!
I did say so! Do you know him?!
Stop! Everyone knows his name!
I'm indebted to Luffy-sama...
So are we!
Your voice is heard by us.
Let's go for a walk!
I bet you're happy, Rebecca,
to see your dad!
In front of Vivi and the others,
the Sakura Kingdom's Dalton, Dr. Kureha,
and their arch-enemy Wapol appear
and tensions rise in the Holyland!
Meanwhile, a lone figure goes deep inside
the Pangaea Castle
and a great hidden secret is unveiled!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"In the Dark Recesses of the Holyland!
A Mysterious Giant Straw Hat!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!