Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era
is experiencing a groundswell beyond
the World Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"In the Dark Recesses of the Holyland!
A Mysterious Giant Straw Hat!"
Hey, Luffy-san ate a lot, didn't he?
Uh-huh!
He had an unbelievable appetite in Dressrosa!
He did in the Ryugu Palace, too.
--They're having fun.
--They really are...
It's a good thing that those who will lead
their countries
in the future get along.
Anyway, it's a strange connection.
Yes, we have to thank
Straw Hat and the others.
Hey! Aren't you Rebecca from Dressrosa?!
Oh, I know him!
It's me - Sai!
SAI - 13TH LEADER OF THE HAPPOSUI ARMY
I didn't expect to see you again so soon!
--How've you been?!
--I've been doing fine!
He's a member of the Happosui Army of Kano...
I heard that Chin Jao
stepped down as leader...
He is the new leader.
Sai!
Oh, brother! You're here, too, Leo!
I'm a secret bodyguard!
You're so reliable!
He is, isn't he?
Is he your friend?
We exchanged cups of sake
with Luffyland together!
We're both his underlings!
Well well, Princess Vivi!
Wapol!
WAPOL - KING OF THE EVIL BLACK DRUM KINGDOM
You fool!
KINDERELLA - QUEEN OF THE
EVIL BLACK DRUM KINGDOM
Why are you here?!
It's strange, right?
Yes, I was sent flying!
By Straw Hat Luffy, to a far off distant sea!
But I'm back!
Do you wanna know how my darling came back?
Is he Luffy-sama's friend, too?
No, he's our enemy, Shirahoshi!
Is the humorless King Cobra doing okay?
Well, I saw him looking not so well earlier
so that's just a bit of sarcasm!
Oh, honey!
You're as entertaining as the universe!
My golddigging self laughs!
Wapol!
Cut the crap!
I can't believe you became a king again...
DALTON - KING OF THE SAKURA KINGDOM
So there's another poor country.
The Government must be in decline!
DR. KUREHA - A DOCTOR OF THE SAKURA KINGDOM
Why do they wanna affiliate
with this fool again?!
Dalton! The old witch hag!
You're still alive?!
--Hm? Indeed - how do I stay so young?
--I didn't ask that!
Dalton-san! Dr. Kureha!
It's nice to see you again!
Hi, Vivi-chan.
You became even more dignified.
Are you happy?
If I knew that you were
a princess at that time,
I would've charged you a higher medical fee.
Who are these people?
I met them when I was traveling
with Luffy-san and the others.
Nami became ill on our way to Alabasta
so to find her a doctor,
we stopped by at a Winter Island...
Attention, pirates! Leave this place at once!
This instant!
Vivi!
Why, you--!
Aim!
No! Stop!
Fighting won't help anything!
I'm fine! It only grazed my arm!
In that case, we won't land here!
But could we ask for a doctor?
Our friend is suffering from a grave illness.
Please help! I beg you!
Vivi!
If you start a fight here,
what will happen to Nami-san?
Please call a doctor!
Please help our friend!
I will show you to the village.
Follow me.
At that time, the Winter Island was
under the oppressive rule
of the then king - Wapol,
but one day, when it came
under attack by pirates,
he abandoned the country instead of fighting.
Dalton-san who served under him
protected the citizens.
But Wapol, who waited out the invasion
disguised as a pirate,
came back to the island with his underlings.
Hm?
What's that strange flag?
The flag...
...belonged to Dr. Hiriluk
who raised Tony-kun with Dr. Kureha
and loved his country dearly
until the very moment of his death!
This castle is no longer yours!
This isn't a place for rotten brats like you!
Leave this country!
The Drum Kingdom has already died out!
Of all the flags, don't fly that quack's flag!
It will ruin the castle!
Doctor... tried to save even you!
Chopper...
Don't hold a grudge against humans.
This country is sick right now.
The king also suffers from a sickness of the heart.
Why? Doctor, a guy like
him isn't worth saving!
Hm?
I...
I won't hit you... so leave this country!
What're you saying, Chopper?!
You think he'll just listen to you?!
But... after all...
Humph!
You were a fake pirate, right?
You don't know what this pirate
flag means because you were
fake pirates who didn't even risk your lives!
Dodge it! Watch out!
You can't break this flag!
He must've been blown away! Such an idiot!
See? It didn't break...
You'd better be prepared if you're
gonna meddle with someone else's skull flag!
Gum-Gum...
Hold on a sec!
I'll give you status and a medal!
Doctor...
The kingdom is...
The Drum Kingdom is...
Then... I'll make you vice-king...!
...about to fall!
...Bazooka!!
Thank you. Drum will definitely...
...be reborn...
Dalton-san helped Luffy-san get rid of Wapol,
and by the wish of all the citizens,
became the king of the renamed
country, Sakura Kingdom.
I see.
Hey, hey, hey!
Dalton! You told me to cut the crap earlier,
even though you're merely my subordinate!
That was long ago...
Now...
I'm on even terms with you!
Honey!
Dalton-san!
You have the kingly attitude down pat!
What? No...
Listen, Dalton! You bastard in shining armor!
You can't be naive when running a country!
I'm living proof since I came back by making
a fortune with my Munch-Munch Fruit power!
The higher you climb,
the more you'll see how dirty this world is!
I'll teach you! And pay you back...
By the way, did you read
the article on Luffy-kun?
Yes, thoroughly.
Say, maybe... Dalton-san...
You like Lucy?
You like Luffyland, don't you?
I like him very much.
This is gonna be fun!
Are you guys listening?!
You, old witch hag,
how much longer are you gonna live?!
You're way over 150!
I'm still a spry 141!
By the way, ladies...
Did you see that blue-nosed reindeer?
Yes, I saw him!
In the Ryugu Kingdom, he saved Luffy-sama
who was critically injured as
well as the kingdom itself.
I see.
Please... teach me to be a doctor!
I'll become the all-purpose medicine!
I'll become a doctor who can cure anything!
I'll cure even a country!
Because...
there's no disease in this world that can't be cured!
Hey, let's be pirates together!
Okay?!
It's not possible.
Because...
Because I'm a reindeer! I
have antlers and hooves!
I even have a blue nose!
I'm not even a human! I'm a monster!
I can't become your friend! So...!
So I just came to say thank you...
I do appreciate you guys.
Thank you for asking me to join you.
I'll stay here, but...
one day... if you feel
like it, stop by agai...
Shut up! Let's go!
I have something to talk with you!
Listen, Doctorine! I'm gonna be a pirate.
I'm going with them!
Don't be ridiculous!
I've never heard of a mere reindeer
going out to sea.
That's right. I'm a reindeer! But...
I'm a man, too!
What do you think someone like you
can do at sea?!
Are you gonna live in a fantasy
just like that quack did?!
You're wrong! It wasn't a fantasy!
Doctor's research had
actually been completed!
Was it okay to bid farewell like that?
A pet I was taking care of is being taken in
by someone else. That's all.
I don't like... tears...
Are you ready, young men?!
I will make cherry blossoms bloom.
Once my invention is completed,
this country will be saved!
Doctor...! Doctorine...!
Now, have a safe trip, my stupid son...
Ouch!
What happened?!
I tried to help Sanji cook
and I cut my finger...
Let me see.
You're fine. It won't take long to heal!
It'll sting a bit.
Chobro, you're great!
What?
Because there's no injury
you can't treat.
Luffy was all cut up
but now he's totally fine!
That's because I was taught
by the greatest doctor in the world!
It's a nice day.
Leo.
I've been working for the Kano
Kingdom, but I'll cut ties
with them after this bodyguard duty.
This will be my last service for them.
I'm deeply indebted to Straw Hat and the others
for saving us in Dressrosa.
We're seven representatives of the Straw Hat Fleet
with over 5,600 troops in total.
We have to be ready to help him at all times.
Uh-huh.
I heard the other members
started preparing, too.
What did you say?!
RESIGNATION
You're suddenly leaving
the Standing Kingdom?!
Give me a reason!
I have to pay back a great debt!
Barrier!
Barrier Crush!
Just by crossing fingers,
anyone can put up a barrier!
Even children know that!
W-We surrender!
We lose! We'll serve under you
so give us a break!
Well then...
Put this on.
Wh-What is it?
Let's support the Straw Hats together!
Let's!
Two unidentified ships are approaching!
Are they remnants of Doflamingo's troops?
Cavendish.
As you may know,
I was formerly the prince of
the Bourgeois Kingdom.
Cavendish-sama!
But all the women in the country
were crazy about me
and not one of them was
willing to marry other men...
I was expelled from the country
for being too popular.
So...
It's not necessary to attack them
since they're not our enemies.
I know that Straw Hat
will face those who are
more dangerous than Doflamingo hereafter.
We have to become stronger.
Yes! I'm training myself with my crew, too!
I hope we can fight for
Luffyland together again!
Yep!
The Underwater Prison Impel Down...
THE UNDERWATER PRISON IMPEL DOWN
The lowest level...
Level 6 holds the criminals
who are considered extremely dangerous.
The Infinite Hell.
What's this solitary cell?
Am I all alone here? I feel so lonely.
Don't tell me you're trying
to protect me, Magellan!
Did an assassin from on high come to kill me?
In order to prevent me from telling someone
about the secret of Mariejois,
did they send an assassin to silence me?!
Why does it matter if it's revealed now?
Power doesn't last long.
It'll rot faster than anyone thinks!
MARIEJOIS
The threat of a Celestial Dragon who
suddenly strikes falls on Shirahoshi.
He has Rob Lucci from Cipher Pol on his side
and no one can stop him
nevertheless Neptune moves to make
an attack much to his chagrin!
However, it comes to a stunning end!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Holyland in Tumult! The
Targeted Princess Shirahoshi!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!