Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era is experiencing
a groundswell beyond the World
Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"The Holyland in Tumult!
The Targeted Princess Shirahoshi!"
HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS
On this day, King Neptune
of the Ryugu Kingdom...
...arrived at the Holyland of Mariejois,
site of the Reverie.
This was the fervent wish
of the late Queen Otohime.
We shall live under the sun!
The day that humans and we
understand each other will come!
Otohime...
I wish I could bring you with me here!
PANGAEA CASTLE
King Stelly of the Goa Kingdom, come in.
So that is the center of the world!
--Now, make a pledge...
--What?
Can I sit on it?!
Don't even joke about such things!
Tsk!
No one's allowed to sit on the throne.
It's the Empty Throne.
It symbolizes the pledge that
royals of all countries are
equal and no one desires a dictatorship.
The 20 weapons that protect the throne...
...represent the 800-year-old
pledge that was made by the
First Twenty who created the world system.
It's located at the center of the world
and its vacancy is a visible
demonstration of peace...
Just as the most powerful in the world
divide their power amongst five,
as the Five Elders,
the highest-ranking Celestial Dragons,
no one rules the world single-handedly.
Now, make a pledge, King Stelly.
If I can sit there, I'll
be the king of the world!
King Stelly?
I wanna sit there!
MINGLING PLAZA, PANGAEA CASTLE
Come on!
What are you...?!
Please stop!
I found one-eh! I found a giant Mermaid-eh!
SAINT CHARLOS - A WORLD
NOBLE (CELESTIAL DRAGON)
Shirahoshi!
Father-sama...
Should that unruly behavior be forgiven,
Father-sama?!
Come on! Stop fighting!
What are you doing?! Please stop!
Yeah! Chain her up!
Shirahoshi!
Wait! What are you trying to do,
Princess of Alabasta?!
Shirahoshi-chan!
Stop, Rebecca! He's a Celestial Dragon!
So what?! Let go of me!
They have no moral qualms!
If you make them mad, they'll destroy Dressrosa!
That bastard...!
Don't do it, Leo!
Shirahoshi...!
Whoa, come on!
No one interfere!
Come on!
Go, Slave-3!
I'll make her my pet-eh!
I can't hold myself back!
How dare he do that to our Boss's friend!
Leo!
Damn! I have no choice!
I'm coming for you, Mermaid Princess!
--Don't do it, soldier of Kano!
--Somebody, stop him!
Let me go!
Leo!
Who are you bastards?!
ROB LUCCI - CIPHER POL "AIGIS" 0
You should be thanking me.
Cipher Pol 0...
Yes, since we stopped you,
several countries have been saved.
KAKU
Don't stand against the Celestial Dragons.
Even children know that.
STUSSY
Cipher Pol is a secret organization
under the direct control of the World Government.
Among them, "Aigis" 0 is the greatest
and the most powerful unit.
And when this man, Rob Lucci...
and Kaku were members of CP9,
another unit of Cipher Pol,
they got in trouble with the Straw Hats.
CP9 caught Nico Robin
who they considered a threat and were pursuing,
and took her to Enies Lobby,
the Island of Justice.
Look at that symbol, you damn pirates!
That logo indicates the unity
of over 170 member countries
spanning the four seas and the Grand Line!
This is the world!
Do you now realize how completely
powerless you guys are to fight against it?!
Do you realize how huge of an organization
this woman has been pursued by?!
I now understand well the
identity of Robin's enemy.
Sogeking.
Hm?
Shoot through that flag.
Roger.
Huh?
This is my new weapon,
a Giant Slingshot... named Kabuto!
Have a good look at its power!
Special Attack... Firebird Star!
Oh, no...!
Robin!
We still haven't heard you say it!
Say you want to live!
I want to live!
Take me to the sea with you!
In order to save Robin,
the Straw Hats picked a fight with CP9.
KAKU - CP9
A ZOAN-TYPE DEVIL FRUIT - COW-COW FRUIT
MODEL: GIRAFFE
I'll use my strongest
Tempest Kick, Sky Slicer,
the one that slashed this tower...
...and end this battle by
splitting you into two!
So give it up. You have nowhere to escape.
You're the one who has to give up.
Demon Aura... Nine-Sword Style...
...Asura!
Splendid! But it's too late!
You're the one who's too late.
Wait until you dodge this
Tempest Kick to make such a boast.
Sky Slicer!
My slash attack...
...was turned into mist?!
Hardships are fine by me!
I choose to walk the path of Asura!
Asura... Silver Mist!
During this battle against CP9,
Luffy's power evolved drastically.
You'll now...
no longer be
able to keep up with me.
What?
All my techniques will
evolve one step further.
Gear... Two!
Gum-Gum...
--Shave!
--...Jet Pistol!
ROB LUCCI - CP9
A ZOAN-TYPE DEVIL FRUIT - CAT-CAT FRUIT
MODEL: LEOPARD
Jet Whip!
Did you forget, Straw Hat Luffy?
You went down with a single
thrust I gave you in this form.
Oh, that... I got better after I ate meat.
Shave!
Finger Pistol!
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body!
...Jet Bazooka!
Gear Three!
Bone Balloon!
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body!
...Giant Pistol!
In the midst of the deadly fight against Lucci,
Luffy's power evolved even more.
Gear Two to Gear Three.
However, the evolution was associated
with a great risk.
You guys won't be able to
get past Enies Lobby after all!
That's just reality!
Gum-Gum... Jet Axe!
Even if this island gets
destroyed in the process...
...I'll pursue that woman who
threatens the World Government's plans...
...to the very ends of the
earth and eliminate her...
...in the name of dark justice!
We came to take Robin away from all that!
Jet Stamp!
Six King Gun!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
It's over...
We'll be okay now.
We're gonna go back together!
Robin!
After being defeated by Luffy,
Rob Lucci disappeared once,
but he returned to Cipher Pol at some point
and became a member of
their greatest unit - "Aigis" 0.
Sai!
The Celestial Dragons are gods
who created this world.
And all we have here are
merely royals of the lower world.
Of course, you have to give a god
whatever he wants.
He's right-eh, you idiots!
That's not fair and it
doesn't make any sense!
A god doesn't need to make sense.
Vivi-chan-sama...
Otohime...
The world that you dreamed
to live in side-by-side with humans is...
The world under the sun is...
Give me back Shirahoshi! She's my friend!
Wait, Princess of Alabasta!
King Neptune!
Thank you! I won't forget your kindness!
I'm afraid I must let it go now-jamon!
What?!
I'll kick their butts
and go back to the sea bottom-jamon!
No! Don't hit him!
If this is how life on the surface would be,
I can't bring my people anyway!
No! This isn't how it'd be!
King Neptune! They don't represent humans!
I'm sorry, Otohime...
Let's face them together!
Then maybe we can make a difference
for the future of the children on this island,
even just a small one!
Even if we give them our
love, humans won't change!
I have to save Shirahoshi... Forgive me!
Do you dare to defy me?
Kill him, Cipher Pol 0!
Yes, sir.
Get out of my way!
Stop, Neptune the Great Night!
Don't jump the gun!
Father-sama... no!
We should not hate anyone!
Ugh...
Who punched a Celestial Dragon?!
I-I have nothing to do with this!
Okay, you fools?!
I'm sorry...
As a fellow Celestial Dragon, I feel ashamed!
Please forgive us!
Is he a Celestial Dragon?!
Let go of the Princess, you idiot!
My apologies to everyone!
This fool brought panic to a place meant for socializing!
I assume you don't remember me, Neptune...
But I was indebted to the Ryugu Kingdom
and have been waiting for this day!
The day that you all would come here...
Don't tell me you're...
I'm a silly Celestial Dragon...
...who drifted down to the
Ryugu Kingdom a decade ago...
Hurry up and save my life, you fools!
Don't do it, fools! Know your place!
Who do you think I am?!
--Kill him!
--Make him suffer!
Show him no mercy!
Don't do it!
You stupid fish!
Queen Otohime!!
The Queen has been shot!
Queen Otohime...
Everybody, drop your gun!
Children are watching!
Otohime-sama...
It's just a scratch.
Why do you protect him?
You don't know what he did to us in the past!
I can feel your anguish - it's very painful.
I know it's hard but...
...you can't plant your anger and resentment
toward humans in children's mind!
They need a chance to meet humans
and figure them out on their own.
SAINT DONQUIXOTE MJOSGARD
A WORLD NOBLE (CELESTIAL DRAGON)
I was admonished by the late Queen Otohime
and became a decent human!
I would do anything to help your people!
King Neptune! It's my honor to see you again!
Cipher Pol! Retreat from here!
Kaido and Big Mom talk to each other about going after Luffy!
The two angry Emperors of
the Sea are on the move!
While the Navy raises the level of caution
to deal with the unprecedented situation,
an even more unimaginable thing is about
to happen in Mariejois!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Explosive Situation! Two Emperors
of the Sea Going After Luffy!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!