Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era is experiencing a groundswell
beyond the World Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"Finally, It Starts!
The Conspiracy-filled Reverie!"
Okay, let's go home-eh.
They left.
Let's start a strategy meeting.
We understand the geography of Mariejois
and the structure of the castle.
But the problem is their security...
I heard even the Navy Admirals are here.
That's what we expected!
No matter who gets in our way,
we'll save Kuma!
Of course, we will.
That's what we're here for...
Your brother and his crew were saved by him, too,
right?
Yeah, while I was suffering memory loss
and couldn't do anything...
At the Sabaody Archipelago,
he helped my brother and his crew
escape Admiral Kizaru!
Everyone focus on escaping!
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
Run! Run!
Damn you!
Stop! Sanji!
No!
Luffy... Help m--
Nami!
Stop it! That's enough!
Robin!
Luffy!
What is this? What is this?!
I'm...!
I couldn't save even one of my friends...!
We will never meet again.
Farewell...
They've developed their skills quite a bit
during the two years they were away.
I met some of them in Dressrosa.
They were very strong.
I guess they had to become stronger.
Damn!
I'm too weak!
I can't save anybody!
Damn! Damn!
Dammit!!
Luffy-kun.
Go away!
Leave me alone!
I can't!
I can't just watch you hurt yourself anymore.
It's my own body!
It's none of your business!
Can't you see things clearly now?!
You believed that you could overcome anything!
And you've never doubted your strength!
But all those formidable enemies
took away your confidence!
And your brother was your guide on the sea!
I know that you have lost a lot!
And the toughest enemies in the world
blocked your way time after time!
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
You can't get back what you've lost!
What is it that you still have?!
I still have...
I still have my friends!
Zoro! Nami! Usopp! Sanji!
Chopper! Robin! Franky! Brook!
They are my friends!
I wanna see them now...
I wanna see them!!
What's the matter with you,
Usopp'n?
I...
...have no time to waste here now!
Luffy lost his brother in the war!
He must be having a very hard time now!
When your friend is having a hard time,
you should be there for him!
Luffy! I know that you're okay!
I'm sorry!
You've always supported us!
It's our chance to return the favor!
Oh yeah! I got it, Luffy!
I got it now! Okay! Okay!
I got it, Luffy!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
The meeting will be two years later
instead of three days later.
And everything else was done
just to get all the publicity.
This is a message exclusively to us.
Luffy made a decision.
Even if we rush now,
we're not good enough to get far in the New World.
We have to stop once and get stronger.
And meet again no matter what!
Luffy-san has made up his mind.
Well, then I have to do something, too.
He always does ridiculous things.
If I left him alone...
If I left him alone,
he'd probably end up dead.
He's not-so-bright
and high-maintenance!
Uh-huh.
That's why I wanna help him.
Like he helped me.
I never thought that I'd want to get stronger...
...for somebody else.
See you at the Sabaody Archipelago
in two years!
They must've had unimaginably hard training days...
And two years later,
they reappeared in the limelight.
Alright...
Let's go!
Waiting for someone?
He must be a wimp who'll apologize in tears
once he hears Captain Luffy's name anyway!
So come here now!
I'll only say it once!
You're no match for me
so I'm not gonna drink with you!
I'm sorry but I no longer belong to the weak trio
with you and Chopper.
I became a warrior
who isn't fazed by anything!
Did I shake them off?
Brook's concert?
URGENT CREW NEEDED
The Straw Hats' recruitment?
What is going on?
Hey, Zoro! Sanji! Robin!
We finally see each other
but you're acting weird!
Zoro and Sanji,
you guys got along in these two years.
Oh, you're being shy, you bastards!
Women! Real ones!
Ah, there's no doubt!
There are actual ladies in front of me!
These are the real ladies that I've longed for
every single day, on this island!
Viva Sabaody!
What an attractive woman before me!
You're our super archaeologist -
Robin, aren't you?!
I got on...
...the wrong ship.
People think Straw Hat Luffy is dead?
That's nonsense!
Tell this to the whole world!
The pirate - Straw Hat Luffy is alive!
He will become the King of the Pirates someday!
His departure shouldn't be a quiet one!
Oh baby!
Everybody!
I brought them!
Hey!
Luffy-san! I missed you so much!
You guys sure do look stronger!
We all got together again!
You guys!
I've got a lot of things that I want to share with you
but in any case,
thank you for going along with
my selfish decision for two years!
That wasn't the first time.
He's right!
You've always been selfish!
Set sail!!
Yeah!
And now, the Straw Hats...
...have become the most prominent pirate group
in the sea world...
They're a huge success.
Yeah, if it weren't for Kuma,
they would've never made it.
But as a consequence, he became...
He's our special comrade.
I have to return the favor
for what he did for my brother!
Let's save Kuma-chan - our dear friend!
Why are you laughing?
The wanted poster?
Well, his bounty tripled,
from 500 million to 1.5 billion...
That's the bounty of a great pirate.
Oh, it's News Coo.
WORLD CONFERENCE CONVENES TODAY
It finally starts.
What does?
The Reverie.
And...
HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS
...it's finally time for the Reverie!
PANGAEA CASTLE
The sea world is divided in four...
...by the high wall - the Red Line...
and the dangerous sea - the Grand Line...
EAST BLUE          NORTH BLUE
MARIEJOIS                       NEW WORLD
SOUTH BLUE         WEST BLUE
...in which Luffy and the others are traveling.
And the World Government
is a huge organization...
...which is affiliated with 170 countries,
the majority of the world.
Among them, 50 representative kings and queens
assemble at this Holyland every four years.
W-Where's my seat?!
--Finally.
--Yeah.
How's your country been?
You said it was ravaged by pirates four years ago...
Thanks to Fleet Admiral Sakazuki,
they've been sent to Impel Down.
Speaking of pirates, I often hear one name lately.
I think it's...
Straw Hat Luffy, right?
He attempted to kill Big Mom and rumor has it that
he's going after Kaido next.
Kaido?! Does that mean the Land of Wano
will be in turmoil next?
The Land of Wano is not affiliated with the World Government
so it's lawless.
We don't know if it's even proper
to call it a country.
Is there anything we can do?!
Sending the Navy costs money.
How could he cause problem after problem,
that Straw Hat Luffy.
Can't believe it, huh?
What's so funny, Prodence?
Luffy-kun...
The chairman is chosen in turn.
Who is it this time?
It's me!
Thank you very much.
It's Ballywood.
Sounds good.
I think you'll run everything efficiently.
Even if we have a full seven days,
we have so many things to discuss.
The big conference where they decide
the direction of the world.
It is called...
All right. Let's have a good debate as always.
For the sake of this beautiful world!
Kings and queens of various countries!
...The Reverie!
It seems like the conference has begun...
During this congress, Cobra, the king of Alabasta,
is requesting to see us, too.
The Nefeltari Family...
...was the only family of the First Twenty,
who stayed in the lower world 800 years ago.
In a sense, they're betrayers.
Has he noticed something?
Let's hope things don't become complicated.
You can say the same about
Big Mom and Kaido's problem.
It's been two years since the Paramount War...
The swell is unstoppable now.
The balance of the world can't be maintained forever.
We need to clean it up thoroughly soon.
INSIDE PANGAEA CASTLE
CHAMBER OF FLOWERS
Imu-sama.
They are all here.
Have you decided which "light"
needs to be extinguished...
...From history this time?
If so, share the name with us!
Cat Viper and his clan meet Marco at Whitebeard's homeland.
Will Marco stand up again?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Marco! The Keeper of Whitebeard's Last Memento!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna kick the Emperor of the Sea, Kaido's butt!
Tough enemies are waiting for him!
Samurai, shogun, and ninja!
One Piece! The Land of Wano Arc will finally begin!
LAND OF WANO ARC STARTS SUNDAY, JULY 7TH! (JST)