kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Led by Luffy, the Straw Hats entered
the sea around the Land of Wano.
There's no turning back!
It's a strong wind!
Carrot, furl the sail!
--Okay!
--I'll help!
Oh no! It's coming!
Why are carp in the sea?!
Oh! Look at that!
Climbing up the large waterfall
that was in their way,
they thought that
they had finally reached the Land of Wano...
Luffy! Let go of those carp!
No! They're my dinner!
They have been drawn into a massive whirlpool
along with the Sunny.
"The Land of Wano!
To the Samurai Country where Cherry Blossoms Flutter!"
LAND OF WANO
Want some freshwater clams?!
Move outta my way!
UDON
Come in! Come in!
Try our special Flower Udon!
We're short-handed here.
Could you help me a little bit?
Hey! Carry the other end!
--Come on. Carry that end.
--We don't have enough joists!
Hey, hey, hey!
New guy!
Is it you who did this part?!
Yes, Boss!
Is there something wrong?
It's more than just something wrong,
you fool!
What kind of idiot are you?!
It's perr-fect!
Good job!
You damn fool!
Of course, it's perfect because I...
That is your role!
Oh...
That's good... Thank you, sir!
You asshole!
FRANOSUKE - A CARPENTER
Everyone!
Gather 'round! Gather 'round!
Those of you who are not in rush,
please stop and listen!
This is a noted sword...
...which Sandai Kitetsu
gave ample time to forging.
It's totally different from blunt swords...
...that have tips and middle parts that can be
easily cut themselves but can't cut anything!
Gather 'round!
Hi-yah! Once you draw it,
it won't be sheathed
until first slicing something!
Here's a sheet of paper
- no gimmicks or setup!
One sheet becomes two!
Two sheets become four!
Four sheets become eight!
Eight to sixteen,
then thirty-two to sixty-four!
Hi-yah! Hi-yah! Hi-yah!
I give you the fluttering dance of...
...a springtime cherry blossom shower...
and the snowfall of Wano's early evening!
Now you see how sharp this great sword is.
Just by grazing it a bit...
See how easily you get cut.
But, watch this!
What I have here is toad oil!
If you apply it to the wound...!
Ta-dah!
Look! You see?!
It works like this!
The blood's stopped, too!
The East Blue's special toad oil!
Come and get some!
--I'll have some!
--Me too!
You folks have a good eye!
Now, gather 'round! Gather 'round!
USOHACHI - A TOAD OIL SALESMAN
You're doing great! That's it! That's it!
So irresistible!
Your hand is too low!
Lower your hips more!
Yes, ma'am...
What you're trying to achieve is nigh on impossible!
So push yourself!
You're not gonna be called by the Shogun
in a short time like that!
Keep it up, baby!
Yes, ma'am...
OROBI - A GEISHA
It's delicious sake.
ZOROJURO - A RONIN
--I'll come back soon.
--Thank you very much!
The moon's beautiful...
I should drink and take in the view later.
No!
Move!
The smell of blood...
Wait!
You smell pretty good, buddy.
It's like a blood-scented perfume...
It's quite pungent...
And it makes me sick.
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
ARREST
Yeah, the slasher went that way.
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
--You slasher!
--Don't resist!
Just hold still!
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
I have to defend myself...
...from the trouble that I'm getting into!
That is your role!
Listen, guys. You're in the Land of Wano.
The Shogun's name is...
...Kurozumi Orochi!
Officials who follow him are
all under the control of Kaido.
That's why those officials
are so high-handed.
But if you touch them,
Kaido will hear about it!
Until all of our allies get here
and we're ready to fight,
we can't let them know who we are!
So pretend that you're citizens for now
and quietly and peacefully,
play your roles!
I guess I have no choice...
I got it-de-gozaru...
Hey, tie him up!
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
That's amazing!
Swords become stronger
by absorbing human blood...
It's the same no matter
how many straw dummies you cut.
What do you want?
We caught the slasher!
Oh...
That arch-villain who was
stoking fear in the town recently!
Magistrate-sama has finally,
finally caught him!
The criminal will be sentenced to seppuku!
More details are in here!
I hate him! He sliced up my husband, too!
What a relief! Just this month, as many as three people
were slashed on the streets at night...
Hey, can I have one, too?!
Thank you!
Excuse me.
ZOROJURO THE SLASHER
Z-Zorojuro...
I knew he would do something like this.
ZOROJURO THE SLASHER
So your name is Zorojuro...
Everyone was afraid of the slasher...
If you slash your belly,
the town will become peaceful again.
I can't believe you're...
...also a grave-robber.
23 years ago...
Amid the confusion of
the pirate trouble,
the legendary swordsman
Ryuma's corpse and...
......his great sword, Shusui, went missing!
Legend has it that Ryuma chopped off
a giant savage dragon's head...
...with this sword, Shusui.
But now, you slasher...
That grave-robbery took place 23 years ago.
You don't look that old.
Did you steal it from the robber?
Oh, well...
The famous Shusui is now in my hands!
Yes, sir.
Now, Zorojuro, it's time.
Hey.
This blade has no grip...
...de-gozaru.
A seppuku blade is usually short
and has no grip.
You won't fight with it
so it doesn't matter.
Do you know the proper etiquette of seppuku?
If you call yourself a samurai,
admit your guilt and kill yourself honorably!
Before you start suffering...
I'll assist you in dying!
Well then...
Farewell.
Don't cry like a baby...
A proper death is a samurai's honor.
We have witnesses! And enough evidence!
It's an honorable death
that you don't deserve!
Be happy that you can perform seppuku.
I smell blood.
You...
...are the slasher!
I'm sorry, Kin'emon.
Ouch!
Is this... the Land of Wano?
Where did they go?
Let's see...
What happened to us?
Everyone! Fight him!
What the?!
Surrounded by samurai, Zoro
is in a desperate situation!
Will he be able to use his
technique without his swords?!
Meanwhile, Luffy meets a mysterious
girl Otama and clashes
with the Emperor of the Sea Kaido's army!
The battle in the Land
of Wano finally begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Otama Appears! Luffy vs. Kaido's Army!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!