kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Separated from Sanji and the others,
Luffy arrived on the Land of Wano alone
and saved Otama from Kaido's soldiers.
I'll kill you!
Now...
I need to know if this is
the Land of Wano or not.
This country?
Yes, this is the Land of Wano!
You're in a region called Kuri
in the Land of Wano!
Big Bro!
Big Bro! Big Bro! Big Bro!
Big Bro! Big Bro!
Big Bro? Why do you call me "Big Bro"?
Well...!
Because you saved my life,
you're my Big Bro!
Oh, I see!
"He'll Come!
The Legend of Ace in the Land of Wano!"
Now...
Why were you being chased?
Well...
I went to the town for shopping...
But on my way home,
that evil one's men with the baboon found me.
To protect me, Komachiyo
attacked the baboon...
Uh, that's why you guys were in a fight.
Meanwhile...
They stole everything I bought!
Out of anger,
I said something that goes against the law.
When the Kozuki Clan comes back,
they'll teach you a lesson!
What?!
Let go of me!
I thought I'd never be able to go home again,
but thanks to you, I got away!
So let me return the favor!
Oh, that'll help me out.
I just arrived here so I
have a lot of questions.
Okay! You need to eat!
--Is this okay?
--Yes.
The enemy won't find it here.
Damn! As I thought,
there's nothing to eat!
Big Bro!
Let's go now!
What?
I'd like to invite you over for a treat!
KOMACHIYO - A LION-DOG
Big Bro! Hihimaru! This way!
HIHIMARU - A NEW FRIEND
His name is Hihimaru?
I just came up with it!
I see. I'm counting on you, Hihimaru!
There are pirates that I like
and that I don't like!
That makes no difference to me.
You're strong and kind.
My house is over there.
There's a village in the mountains?
No, it's gone, now!
Now, my Master-sama and I live by ourselves.
In the future, I'm gonna be a bewitching...
...female ninja!
"Bewitching"?
Yes, "bewitching"!
That's "bewitching"!
It's dirty, small, and stinky here.
Big Bro, that's a little impolite.
Oh, smells delicious!
It's gonna be ready soon!
Isn't it ready yet, Tama?!
It's ready!
Here you go.
Go ahead and dig in!
Big Bro!
Freshly-cooked rice!
Thank you for the food!
It's delicious!
Aren't you gonna eat?
No, not now.
I can't become a ninja if I'm not agile!
Seconds, please!
How quick!
But that was all I cooked.
What?
There are no more pickles, either...
Okay.
I was just joking when I asked for seconds.
What?!
You're bad at lying!
I gotta go to the bathroom.
I haven't had enough yet
but she's kind enough to cook for me.
She's so nice! Tama...
Who the hell are you?!
What?! Usopp...
No, it's not!
Why are you lying down here?!
Don't tell me you ate the rice.
I did. Who are you...
You fool!
Stop making noise, stomach!
This isn't becoming of a samurai!
Wait!
Who are you?!
I'm just here because Tama cooked for me.
Why did she cook for you?
How many days do you think it's been
since she ate?!
What?
Even if she busily weaves hats every day
and sells them,
we can only earn barely enough for
one person to live!
Sometimes we get to eat barnyard grass
and that's it.
But at least, twice a year,
on her birthday and New Year's,
I want her to eat rice!
RICE
So I gave her money today
and sent her to the town
to buy rice for her eighth birthday!
How could you eat that?!
Master-sama!
Please stop!
Forgive me for cooking it
without asking!
But...!
He saved my life!
Don't bring disgrace on me!
I'll weave many hats!
Please forgive me!
Let me return the favor to
Big Bro Luffy properly...
Please...
Otama!
Tama!
Hey, Tama!
She must've done a foolish thing!
I suppose she drank the river water
to ease her hunger.
Water?
River waters in this country...
...are polluted by liquid wastes
from Kaido's factory!
For a small girl like her,
it's like drinking poison.
Then, why are you living here?!
There are places that would be
a bit better.
But she's waiting here.
For someone who promised to come back...
He is a pirate named Ace!
Ace?!
Tama...
The Ace that you're waiting for is...
...Portgas D. Ace, right?
Do you know him?
Big Bro...
Uh-huh.
Ace died.
That's a lie...
That's a lie!
That's a lie!!
Big Bro, you're a liar!
Tama!
Otama!
Pull yourself together, Tama!
She fainted.
So Ace visited the Land of Wano, too...
Are you a devil or something?!
How could you tell Otama
that Ace died so casually?!
But it's true.
Even if it's true,
that wasn't the right time!
But no matter how long she waits,
Ace won't come back!
But still...
you should've considered
when and how to say it!
You have no delicacy!
Who are you?!
I'm Luffy.
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
What?! You're a pirate?!
I generally don't like pirates!
Who are you?!
I'm Hitetsu.
TENGUYAMA HITETSU - A SWORDSMITH
I'm a swordsmith.
(A BEAUTIFUL GIRL KOKESHI DOLL COLLECTOR)
Ace is now gone!
Take Tama and move to a better place!
I truly want to do so.
But I've been waiting...
...for someone here for a long time myself.
There are only the two of us here now,
but there was a village
called Amigasa before.
But around a year ago,
a man who joined Kaido's army as a Headliner
came here.
He was a pirate named X. Drake.
The village's five key samurai
were taken down
and everything was destroyed.
In the Land of Wano,
there is only one place that's thriving now
and that is the Flower Capital
where the Shogun Orochi lives.
The other places...
...were turned into lawless wilderness areas
by Kaido and his clan.
That man came here four years ago.
This village was always poor
and no one had enough to live on
so people often died of hunger.
Just when we thought that
the village was doomed...
Ace was tossed up on the beach.
The villagers stole all the food and water...
...from those weak pirates
then ate it up and stayed alive.
Ace watched them finish everything,
then, surprisingly,
he easily untied himself.
Everyone thought he was gonna retaliate
and prepared themselves.
Did you eat enough?
What?
Uh... Uh-huh.
Then you want something sweet now!
What?!
Where can I find something for dessert?
Okay, I'm gonna go pick it!
Everyone was stunned.
Ace stayed at the village
for several weeks.
Otama was especially attached to him.
I can't believe our lives were saved
by the shipwrecked pirates.
Yeah...
I see.
The communication was
probably cut at Kuri Beach.
It's possible that they
were beaten by someone.
We don't know how many there are.
And there is no ship, but it's definite
that they came from the outside world.
What should we do, Boss?
Don't tell Kaido-san.
I'll handle it!
Luffy and Hancock get in
a fierce fight against
the army of the world's
strongest bounty hunter!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Side Story! The World's
Greatest Bounty Hunter, Cidre!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
It's the Pirates Fest!
The King of the Pirates challenges you!
TO GET THE KING OF THE PIRATES' TREASURE
Come on and seize the treasure!
ALL THE PIRATES AND MARINES COME TOGETHER!
The movie ONE PIECE STAMPEDE!
AND... A DARK PLOT IS LAUNCHED
Your ambition...
...is ignited!