If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Luffy arrived at the Land of Wano
and met Otama.
Why did she cook for you?
How could you eat that?!
Don't bring disgrace on me!
Otama!
Tama!
Luffy learned that Otama is waiting to
see Ace again in her village but...
Ace died.
Big Bro, you're a liar!
The communication was
probably cut at Kuri Beach.
What should we do, Boss?
Don't tell Kaido-san.
I'll handle it!
Otama!
Ace!
"Save Otama!
Straw Hat, Bounding through the Wasteland!"
Hey!
Where can I get water and food?
And is there a doctor around here?
Don't tell me...
I'm gonna take Tama!
In return for giving me food!
If you cross the wasteland to the north,
you'll find a town with a doctor...
Okay.
Wait!
Kaido's subordinates could be on patrol
along the way!
Besides, carrying Otama there is too much...
Don't worry! I'm quite strong!
I can't risk Otama's life for my cause...
Isn't this a golden opportunity?
Wait, you fool!
Your outlandish outfit is too conspicuous!
Put this on!
Oh, it's a kimono!
--Stay still!
--I like samurai armor, too!
No one wears that every day!
You're good to go!
There's a reason I can't go to the town...
Take care of Otama!
I'll reimburse the doctor's fee later!
If I can meet my friends before that,
we'll get food and medical care for free!
They'll help us!
Look what you got there!
Let me borrow this sword, too!
It's very samurai-ish!
Okay, see you!
Tama! I'll take you to a doctor now!
No, wait!
You fool! You can't take that!
It's a well-known sword!
It's a sin to handle it so casually!
My ancestor, Kotetsu,
forged that world-famous sword!
It's one of only 21 Excellent Grade Swords!
It's called Kitetsu II!
Listen!
Out of the numerous swords in the world,
the ones that were made by the great swordsmiths
are called Grade Swords.
And the finest among them are called...
50 FINE GRADE SWORDS
...the 50 Fine Grade Swords,
21 EXCELLENT GRADE SWORDS
the 21 Excellent Grade Swords,
12 SUPREME GRADE SWORDS
and the 12 Supreme Grade Swords.
There's a story behind Kitetsu in particular...
Huh?!
He's gone!
See you! I'm gonna take the sword!
Hey! Listen to me!
Wait! Wait!
I said no!
Then, let me borrow your sword instead!
This one is a famous sword, too!
The one you took is cursed!
It's quite scary.
I don't wanna carry it!
You're gonna become cursed!
I'm leaving now, Grandpa Nose!
I won't forgive you
if anything happens to Otama!
Yeah, I'll save her at any cost!
And don't forget to return the sword!
Answer me!
Why aren't you responding?!
Oh, Dog! Are you gonna carry us?!
This is much easier!
Please make a beeline to the town!
What?!
Oh, Tama! You're up!
Big Bro, where are we going
riding Komachiyo?
To the doctor.
Does this dog know the way?
Ace died.
Whoa-whoa, stop! You're gonna fall!
You're a liar!
Ace can't come back!
Everyone knows about the Paramount War!
But...
...we made a promise.
Ace will come back!
Ace! Take me to the sea with you!
I'm old enough!
But you're only five.
I'm already five!
--You're good at that.
--Yeah, I am!
You're gonna leave here soon, right?
Yeah! I have to finish this before that...
I... don't wanna say goodbye to...
Ace and everyone else...
Tama...
We'll come back!
After we become a greater pirate group!
Then, will you let me join your crew?
I wanna go on an adventures with you!
Ace! Let me join your crew!
To be a pirate, you must be strong!
When I come back,
if you become a bewitching female ninja or something,
I'll take you along!
Ace! Is it the "bewitching" thing required?!
Ace!
I got it! That's a promise, okay?!
We were very close...
He said he'd come back...
You don't know how nice he is!
That's why you don't understand my pain!
Stop hitting me...
Although it doesn't hurt...
How could you say he died that casually?!
You... dummy!
We're almost out of the bamboo forest!
The Grandpa Nose was right...
It's really a wasteland!
THE SLASHER
They still haven't caught the slasher yet?!
It's dangerous...
I can't sleep at night!
What are the authorities doing?!
That bastard! Where did he go?!
This place is great!
I can eat as much meat and fish as I want!
If I could just get sake, it'd be perfect...
Hey! Woman, stop!
It's a tiger!
And a boar!
What is that?!
--Th-That's a Sharkodile!
--It's pretty wild!
If you're ever hungry,
you can just eat them!
That's impossible.
Those samurai who were strong enough to catch them have
either been arrested or became bandits...
Besides...
Animals drink the polluted river water, too...
So they are poisonous for humans to eat...
But they look so delicious!
That's unforgivable!
Is that the factory where the smoke is coming from?!
Yes!
They have a mine and a weapon factory...
So there are a lot of
Kaido's subordinates there.
What do they eat?
The Shogun and Kaido have an untainted farm...
...just for themselves.
That's why they have clean water and rice...
...and fish...
...and meat... lots of them...
Man! So it's not like
there isn't any on this island!
Hey! Tama! Are you alright?!
Ouch!
I think your temperature is rising!
Hang on!
I'll get you to a doctor soon!
If the enemy has water and food,
that serves my interest just fine!
Hurry up, Dog!
Please forgive me!
Wait, woman!
Leave everything you have!
Help! Somebody!
Damn! I'll make you pay for this!
Lady, step back...
ZOROJURO - A SERIOUS CRIMINAL
MURDERING THE MAGISTRATE
You're that serious criminal, Zorojuro!
You fool.
That sake...
Give it to me!
Samurai-sama!
I don't know who you are,
but thank you for saving my life!
Oh, don't mention it.
I just wanted their sake...
...de-gozaru.
But I wanna return you a favor.
Then, sake, please!
Oh, I don't have any.
That's Zoro!
Hey, Zoro! It's me, it's me!
Hey!
Luffy!
You were here after all!
I finally get to see you!
Zoro!
Ya-hoo!
It's been a long...
It's been a long time-de-gozaru!
Is everyone with you?
Yeah, I lost them, but...
...I guess they're okay!
You have meat! Gimme some!
There are a bunch of fish and animals to hunt
in this area, Luffy!
You'll never be short of food!
No, be careful!
The water around here is poisonous!
So I heard the meat and fish
are poisonous, too!
I see.
That's why I have a stomachache.
Anyway, Zoro, come with us!
One thing led to another,
and I'm on my way to take her to a doctor.
A sick brat!
You shouldn't be stopping to eat!
Don't worry! I'll eat fast!
--Just eat already!
--Okay!
Are you...
...the ronin who is wanted
across the country, Zorojuro,
and members of his clan?
Oh?! He's...
That's right...
Seems like he's working for Kaido.
Straw Hat!
I was on my way to Kuri Beach...
But you're the one who caused the trouble there, aren't you?
Two of my subordinates
and one baboon went missing...
BASIL HAWKINS
ONE OF THE BEAST PIRATES' HEADLINERS
The possibility that you guys have something to do with it...
...is 98 percent.
But...
...that doesn't matter.
In this Land of Wano, you either follow the strong
or become their prey...
You have no other option!
This is the warning Kin'emon gave us, Luffy!
"Don't make a scene!"
Well, then I'll have to just...
...apologize to him later!
Luffy and Zoro demonstrate their intense
sword skills!
Will they be able to defeat the invincible Hawkins?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Headliner! Hawkins the Magician Appears!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Let's go!
UNEXPECTED ALLIANCE
It finally begins!
I'm gonna kill
all the marines and pirates!
Pave the way for Luffy!
--Luffy!
--Straw Hat-ya!
In this sea world, no one lives alone!!
The movie ONE PIECE STAMPEDE!
THEATERS GET ALL HEAT UP!!