If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Let me borrow this sword, too!
It's very samurai-ish!
You fool! You can't take that!
It's a well-known sword!
It's a sin to handle it so casually!
My ancestor, Kotetsu,
forged that world-famous sword!
It's called Kitetsu II!
In order to take Otama to a doctor,
Luffy borrowed Hitetsu's sword
and left Amigasa Village.
That's Zoro!
Hey, Zoro! It's me, it's me!
Hey!
Luffy!
You were here after all!
I finally got to see you!
Thus, Luffy met Zoro again.
However, there came...
In this Land of Wano, you either follow the strong
or become their prey...
You have no other option!
"The Headliner!
Hawkins the Magician Appears!"
The probability of you two living another month...
19 percent...
If you're here for sightseeing,
get lost.
Do you know who reigns over this country
behind the scenes?
I don't know!
It's Kaido, right?!
We're here to...
...beat the Emperor of the Sea!
Hey, Luffy!
Kin'emon said
we shouldn't say things like that, either...
Uh, that was a lie!
I don't know!
By the way, where did you get that sword?
It's a famous sword, isn't it?
Well, it really seems like a famous sword to me.
Let me see it for a sec.
No way!
Come on! Let me just hold it!
--No-de-gozaru!
--Just let me see it!
--I said no-de-gozaru!
--Why?!
--No-de-gozaru!
--Hey, cut it out!
A sword is a samurai's soul-de-gozaru!
You're a pirate!
Is it okay for you to have a samurai's soul?!
You can't use a sword anyway
so just give it to me!
No, no, no!
I'm gonna cut them up-de-gozaru!
Zorojuro, handle those in the back-de-gozaru!
Okay... But listen!
Once we take care of them,
let me see your "soul"!
Charge.
This is a sword fight-de-gozaru!
Don't throw the scabbard!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
That's not a sword technique!
This is my chance!
You're not using it the right way!
I'm a samurai!
I'm gonna dice it up more and more-de-gozaru!
Ace...
We made a promise...
Gum-Gum...
...Battle-Axe!
Hawkins-san! We're no match for them!
Boss! Please fight for us!
Boss!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Even the lizard's attacking me!
Damn you!
Straw Sword.
What kind of sword is that?!
I feel bad for the lizard!
That was fast!
That's impressive.
What just happened?!
Why's he still alive?!
Minus One Life.
These Strawmen represent my subordinates.
I can store them within my body
with my Straw-Straw Fruit power,
so I won't be harmed.
If I store ten of them,
I can die ten times.
Now, let's play a game.
A game?!
That's right... With these Strawman Cards...
I'm not a straightforward person
who'd fight two pirates from the Worst Generation squarely.
He's a bigger pain in the ass than I thought...
What else would you expect?
Let's begin.
The Reversed Fool!
Oops... It signifies an internal discord.
Sorry... I'll draw a better card next...
You must take the risks,
because there are cards that will grant you power
which exceeds your limits.
Hey! What are you doing, Dog?!
Hawkins-san!
Fear not.
Tama! Stay with me, Tama!
She's burning up!
That's why this dog is rushing.
--You bastards!
--We won't let you get away!
Chase them!
Stop!
We gotta hurry up!
Yeah, I'm gonna finish them off!
Hawkins-san! They're getting away!
Boss!
I drew a good card.
The Reversed Hierophant...
The card of pursuit!
When Otama and Luffy end up in a deadly crisis,
Zoro's avenging slash howls!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Defeat is Inevitable! The Strawman's Fierce Attack!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Everybody! Let's go!
THEATERS ARE PACKED!!
BIGGEST OPENING DAY OF 2019
You need friends because you're weak!
In this sea world, no one lives alone!!
The movie ONE PIECE STAMPEDE!
A BLOCKBUSTER NOW PLAYING!