If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
In order to take Otama to a doctor,
Luffy left Amigasa Village and ran into Zoro on the way.
However, Hawkins who became Kaido's subordinate
stood in their way!
Nigiri...
Tower Climb...
...Ripple!
After losing Hawkins, Luffy and the others
headed for a teahouse following Otsuru's directions.
At the teahouse, the waitress, Okiku, was hit on
by Urashima, the No.1 wrestler in the Land of Wano...
Hey... I'm sorry but your fat-ass is in my way.
Move aside.
Meanwhile, a group spies on
Luffy and the others' movements.
"The Greatest Day of My Life!
Otama and Her Sweet Red-bean Soup!"
Tama! Stay with us!
Tama!
This is a decoction of Evil-Purging Herbs.
It's bitter but it works well.
Let her drink it.
Uh-huh.
Tama. Here's the medicine.
Drink it!
Yww!
Bear with it and drink!
Drink!
You're bleeding from your arm...
Oh, it's just a scratch.
--It's gotta be treated now...
--It'll heal on its own.
No!
Here...
Oh, are you awake?!
Big Bro! Ma'am!
Where am I?
This is my teahouse.
Komachiyo!
Sorry to make you worry.
Otama-chan!
How's your stomach?
Does it hurt, Otama-chan?
I feel better!
It worked so fast!
The Evil-Purging Herb is
an incredible wonder drug.
Thank you all!
Nin-nin!
But...
...the poison in your body
can't be removed completely.
So don't ever drink the river water again,
Otama-chan.
Okay, I got it!
Stop making noise, stomach!
This isn't becoming of a samurai!
Water!
River!
Otama-chan! Stop!
The river water...!
Huh?
What?!
The river water...
Don't ever drink it!
There, it's done.
This is only a field dressing though...
Yeah. Thank you.
You're so huge.
But Big Mom was an even huger woman.
Thank you for saving me earlier
when the sumo wrestler was hitting on me.
I didn't do anything.
I forgot to introduce myself.
I (sessha) am Okiku.
Sessha?!
What?!
I can't... I can't... No, no!
You shouldn't do that!
Go ahead and eat.
Please! Take it away! Ma'am!
I don't even have money for the herbs!
How could I pay for
some sweet red-bean soup?!
You don't have to pay for it.
No!
I can't have it!
I know both you and Okiku-san
haven't eaten much!
That's okay. Don't be shy.
You've already saved my life
and now you're trying to give me food!
How can I accept this?!
That's okay.
No!
I said that's okay!
I'll pay you back for the herbs
no matter what...
That's enough!
What?!
Once a woman serves food...
"I don't want it."
"Okay."
Do you think she'll just put it away so easily?!
If you're not gonna eat it...
I'll spill it in the street!
No!
Otama-chan, eat it!
Otsuru-san won't take no for an answer.
How long will you sit like that?
You should be happy!
Today's your birthday!
Is that true?
That's what I heard.
Then, take it as a birthday present from me
and eat up.
It's so yummy!
This soup is so delicious!
What?
Is this your first time having it?!
Yes!
How many days do you think it's been
since she ate?!
Even if she busily weaves hats every day
and sells them,
we can only earn barely enough for
one person to live!
There are some rice cakes in it!
What a sumptuous treat!
You can make them out of your cheek.
You can't fill your stomach with those.
Yum-yum!
Ma'am! Thank you very much!
I don't think I could top
a wonderful birthday like this!
I feel bad for Master-sama though!
Otsuru-san...
This is the greatest day of my life!
Children like her are not uncommon...
...in the Land of Wano...
Such a small child not being able to get enough food
is unbelievable!
Well, if you're a grown-up,
you can eat poison.
No, you can't!
As long as we have the sea, mountains, and forests,
getting food shouldn't be a problem.
Right.
If we humans hadn't ruined them ourselves...
Damn Kaido!
Yeah...
You're such sweet young men.
Oh, yeah! What are your names?
My name is Zorojuro.
I'm a ronin.
I'm Monkey D...
His name is...
Luffytaro.
What?!
R-Right...
I'm Luffytaro!
...Gozaru.
You're from overseas, right?
--It must've been hard to enter the country.
--How could you tell?
--You talk weird.
--What?!
Don't worry. I won't tell anybody.
I'm new to this town, too.
And Okiku-chan has only been working here
for a month.
I heard this town is called Okobore (Leftovers).
What kind of name is that?
Just like the name implies,
those who live here
get leftovers from the town of officials.
Tama said there is
non-poisonous food somewhere.
Look over there.
You see the mountain without chimneys?
On the top of it,
there used to be a castle called Oden.
It's already been 20 years.
Oden... I've heard that word before.
What was it?
Until some 20 years ago,
a clan called Kozuki had governed this Land of Wano
for a very long time.
That vast farm that expands
to the bottom of the mountain...
...was made by the late Oden-sama,
in order to feed everyone in Kuri
delicious food.
It wasn't meant for Orochi and the others
to monopolize the country's food supplies.
That Paradise Farm...
I heard that!
It wasn't meant for Orochi and the others
to monopolize the country's food supplies.
That Paradise Farm...
I heard that!
Is there non-poisonous food at the farm?
There is.
Safe delicious food,
clean water and clothes...
They all belong to...
...the Shogun Orochi!
On the other side of the shrine gate,
there is a town where the officials live.
We beg them to sell us things that they no longer use
and nearly spoiled food to maintain our lives.
That's why it's called Okobore Town...
But we're fine...
At least, we can live.
What do you think you're doing?!
Don't get in my way!
I heard you, woman!
You were speaking ill about the Shogun!
I can hear six times better
than normal humans!
BAT-MAN - A GIFTER WITH THE BAT SMILE FRUIT
I won't miss a foul word spoken
about the Shogun!
I understand that you heard it,
but is that a good reason
to take someone's life?
She would've died if it hit her.
As long as you live quietly,
I'll rarely have cause to hurt you!
But Orochi-sama...
...will never allow people to harbor
a rebellious spirit!
Tsk! How about this?!
I got this!
Arrows!
He blocked all of them!
Who are you?!
For several weeks,
there have been robberies at the farm.
We're looking for the robber now!
Don't tell me it's you guys!
A one-eyed ronin?!
ZOROJURO THE SLASHER
I saw him on the wanted poster!
Let go of me!
Who are you?!
I'm a great runner!
I can run at 200 kilometers per hour!
Big Bro!
Tama!
Otama-chan!
Help!
Big Bro!!
Tama!!
Otama is taken away to Bakura Town where officials and pirates
under the control of Orochi's subordinates thrive!
As danger descends on Otama moment by moment,
will Luffy and his clan be able to reach the enemy's territory?!
On the next episode of One Piece! "Charging into the
Enemy's Territory! Bakura Town - Where Officials Thrive!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!