kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Luffy and Zoro were rushing towards a town to save Otama.
With the help of medicine brewed by Otsuru,
the teahouse owner they met along their way,
Otama made a full recovery.
Luffy learned that the people of Wano
have been forced to live hard lives.
Tama said there is
non-poisonous food somewhere.
There is.
Safe delicious food,
clean water and clothes...
They all belong to...
...the Shogun Orochi!
I heard that!
You were speaking ill about the Shogun!
That's unforgivable!
Luffy and the others
suddenly came under attack.
However, the Gifter's true purpose was...
Let go of me!
Who are you?!
Otama-chan!
Help!
Big Bro!!
Tama!
Tama!!
GAZELLE-MAN - A GIFTER WITH THE GAZELLE SMILE FRUIT
Mission accomplished!
"Charging into the Enemy's Territory!
Bakura Town - Where Officials Thrive!"
Help!
--Otama-chan!
--Damn!
Give us back Tama!
I won't let you go!
Don't get in my way!
Okiku-chan!
A sword?!
He runs so fast!
Let go of me!
Shut up, you little shit!
Give me a lift, Lion-dog-kun!
Dog!
--That woman's holding a sword!
--She said she knew how to use it...
I've never seen her using it though...
Dog!
Take me with you!
Look at his arm!
Wait!
I'll come, too!
Okay!
Those fools!
Luffytaro-san! Zorojuro-san!
What do they want from that brat?!
I don't know!
But we have to get her back now!
Tama!!
I'm gonna save you right now!
Big Bro!!
Not if I have my say!
Dog! Dodge!
Gazelle-man! Just go!
All right!
You can't catch up to him anymore!
Dammit!
How pathetic!
I'm sure they've been planning this!
Some Headliner must've ordered this!
And there is only one place to go
in that direction...
It's definitely the town of officials.
That's the town where those who sell
their leftovers to you guys live.
Right...
A notebook?
Who are you, really?
There are three Headliners in that town.
Hawkins.
Holdem.
Speed.
In addition...
there are about 30 soldiers who've gotten special abilities from strange artificial fruits.
You're not just an ordinary girl.
Who are you?
I (sessha) am...
...a samurai.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Holdem-sama! This is Gazelle-man!
I caught the brat who they said
tamed the baboon!
Let me go!
Well done...
She'll be of use...
Bring her here.
Yes, sir!
Big Bro Luffy!!
This is the flourishing town in Kuri, Land of Wano, called Bakura Town.
RESTAURANT
Damn!
That annoying ronin!
I backed away because of
his strangely strong spirit,
but I wanna take Okiku as my wife
at any cost-pe!
I have high social status, a good name,
and safe food supplies...
She'd be crazy to reject me-pe!
Stop worrying over nothing, you idiot!
She's a girl from Okobore Town, right?
They're so low-class that Orochi-sama
wouldn't even bother to rule over them...
Whether she loves you or not
doesn't matter at all.
You can force her to marry you...
...or burn her house down...
...or kill all of her relatives
so she'll have no place to go.
Take away all her options
and make her dependent on you!
You're of the samurai class!
MOUSE-MAN
A GIFTER WITH THE MOUSE SMILE FRUIT
In the Land of Wano, we have a clear status system.
You're a star of our national sport
so if you give a damn about a lowly person like that,
you're not setting a good example
for others!
You're right!
Yeah! I can do whatever I want with Okiku!
Yokozuna...
Didn't you like the food?
That's a raccoon dog, right?
Yes, it's a pet that we've had
for a long time...
--Cook it!
--What?!
Raccoon dogs are my favorite food!
BUDO
You're finally here...
I see it!
We'll charge in there!
Luffytaro-san and Zorojuro-san!
Beyond that point is Bakura Town!
The town of officials and pirates!
There's no guarantee of our safety!
Are you ready?!
Yeah!
Is this her?
Poor girl...
She's about to cry.
I'm not gonna cry!
Don't try to act strong!
A CERTAIN RESIDENCE, BAKURA TOWN
Ouch...
I have a pain in my side!
Shut up! Gazelle-man!
You can go now!
Your heavy breathing annoys me!
Build up your stamina!
You idiot!
I wasn't talking to you!
Stop staring at my face like that!
HOLDEM - A HEADLINER OF THE BEAST PIRATES
WITH THE LION SMILE FRUIT
I'm so scared!
He has a lion in his stomach!
KAMIJIRO - HOLDEM'S STOMACH
What is that hostile look?!
What happened?
There it goes! The lion's blow to the balls!
But...
...since they share the same body,
that groin also belongs to the lion!
Why doesn't he learn?
Why do some people repeat the same mistake?
Holdem-sama.
What should we do with this brat?
Holdem-sama!
My balls (tama)...
So your name is Otama.
How could a weak little shit like you...
...tame the savage baboon?!
My men saw you do it!
Don't try to pretend that you don't know!
It must be none other than
a real Devil Fruit power.
Come on...
Spit it out!
Otama!
Your ability is enticing even to your enemies.
Don't ever use it in front of others!
I-It's just...
...animals...
...tend to love me...
Oh!
I see!
That's what it's all about!
Yes, it is.
Do you think I'm a fool?!
You damn brat!
I believe they said you tore
part of your cheek off.
If you're not gonna tell me...
Let's give that a try.
Hey, bring me some pincers!
Yes, sir!
Not that one! The bigger one!
Big Bro Luffy...
Help! Big Bro Luffy!
Tama!
Stop! Stop! Don't you wanna live?!
Invaders!
Bakura Town is just past them!
Luffy! We don't have time
to fight those weaklings!
I know!
Charge, dog!
What?!
Captain!
We have a problem!
What? Why are you so upset?
It's Straw Hat and Roronoa!
Straw Hat-ya is in the Land of Wano?!
So he's finally here...
Straw Hat and Roronoa plunged themselves
into Bakura Town!
Hey, wait!
All we can expect from this is trouble!
That's right...
Captain?
Captain?!
Let's go stop those idiots!
Aye-aye, Captain!
Don't do it...!
If you don't want me to, show your ability!
Tama!
As the undefeated yokozuna, Urashima,
doggedly makes advances on her,
the samurai, Okiku, says something which will lead to further turmoil!
Seeing Okiku in danger, Luffy finally goes into action!
Will he be able to help Okiku, targeted by Urashima,
out from the tight spot?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Yokozuna Appears! The Invincible Urashima Goes After Okiku!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!