kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Don't do it...!
If you don't want me to, show your ability!
Tama!
To save Otama,
Luffy and the others infiltrated Bakura Town.
On their way,
they stumbled across a sumo event
and Urashima, the yokozuna
who was pursuing Okiku, was there.
You guys!
We're looking for someone!
She's a little girl named Tama!
Tell me where this town's boss is!
However, Urashima and his clan didn't listen
and came to take Okiku away.
Don't get in our way!
Shut up, you commoners!
To us samurai-class, you fools are all
the same, vulgar, lowly bastards-pe!
I (sessha) don't know anyone
who is called...
...a lowly bastard!
So cool!
Kiku is so daring!
Okiku!
I knew you were the kind of man
who would hit a woman...
Die!
Urashima's deadly slap
is about to be unleased on Okiku!
"A Climactic Sumo Battle!
Straw Hat vs. the Strongest Ever Yokozuna!"
Gum-Gum...
...Sumo Slap!
Oops, oops, oops, oops...
Oh no, oh no... No, no, no...!
Whoa-whoa-whoa...
No, no, no, no, no...!
Oh no, whoa-whoa-whoa, no, no...!
Whoa! Oh no, oh no!
Oh no, oh no...!
Whoa-whoa-whoa...
Hang on, Luffytaro-san!
Oh! Oh no, no, no... Whoa-whoa...
Oh no, no, no!
No, no, no!
Oh no, oh no!
Damn!
What did you do to my slap?!
Damn you...
Who are you to Okiku-pe?!
Move out of my way!
I have to tear Okiku into bits...
Otherwise I'll lose face!
Okay! No problem!
Well then...!
Dosukoi!
If you can beat me!
What?!
I'm...
...good at sumo!
LUFFY-NO-UMI - SUMO-WANNABE PIRATE
RECORD: UNDEFEATED VS. USOPP
Let's have a sumo match!
Ready...
Move...
...out of my way!
Go!
Go! Go! Whoa!
Bodhisattva Slap!
He's dodging Urashima's slaps!
He's so agile!
--Keep it up, little guy!
--You can't win if you're just running around!
Oh no!
You little shit...
You're like a rat!
Ear-Splitter!
Hey!
Eye-Splitter!
Hey! Those are all illegal moves!
Shut up!
I'm...
...a yokozuna!!
Well, whatever!
Holdem-sama! We have a problem!
Huh? The yokozuna got his topknot
chopped off by a woman?
Everyone's upset!
And we don't know what to do!
I don't care!
What do you want me to do?!
I'm busy tearing her cheek off!
Have mercy on me!
You can have your baboon back!
Please stop!
I won't!
I heard that you mentioned the name "Kozuki."
When the Kozuki Clan comes back,
they'll teach you a lesson!
I bet you know...
...that saying the name "Kozuki"...
...is a serious offense!
So this is also a punishment
for your crime...
Stop chasing after ghosts forever...
The Kozuki were an evil clan...
...that tried to destroy the Land of Wano
two decades ago!
Get out of my way, you little shit!
What Okiku did is irreparable-pe!
She turned down the honor of marrying
and serving the samurai-class me,
and even muddied my good name!
I'll smash her brains in
and set an example!
Just shut up!
Like I said, do as you like once you beat me!
You can't beat me though!
What do you mean?!
I'm...
...the greatest yokozuna in the Land of Wano!
Far Bank Slap!
What's this?
I don't know... What is it?
You're a yokozuna...
And I'm...
...the man who's gonna be
the King of the Pirates!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Please stop!
Let go of me!
Help me...
Big Bro Luffy!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant...
...Sumo Slap!
Dosukoi!
No...!
What the...?
A-Am I safe now?
Th-The yokozuna...
He was sent flying!
Yokozuna!
No way!
He can't be beaten by a little guy like him!
I'm a yokozuna!
I don't care who you are,
just bring it on!
I guess we did enough to
get the attention of their boss.
I think so!
Th-That guy...
I remember!
He killed the magistrate!
WANTED - ZOROJURO
Zorojuro?!
So what?
Don't tell me he's that guy's ally!
Alright! Let's go now, guys!
What's the matter, Bepo?
Bepo, you...
Room!
Scan!
I knew it.
Sorry.... I couldn't control myself
and...
A-Am I gonna die, Captain?
No way! You've just got the runs.
That's why I told you
not to eat fish from the river.
Boy, the timing couldn't be any worse!
I-I'm sorry...
Stop acting cute!
Man! Why's everyone causing trouble?
I hope they're laying low...
Those fools...
Hey!
Bring the boss of this town!
We're here to take back Tama!
Luffy, Zoro, and Okiku's swords swing
and cut up Kaido's men one after another!
Then, Bakura Town's boss and a Headliner
who has a lion head
in his stomach, Holdem springs into action!
The big sword fight in Bakura Town heats up!
Will Luffy and the others
be able to rescue Otama?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy Rages! Rescue Otama from Danger!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!