kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Big Bro!
Luffy was furious at Holdem, a Headliner,
who was holding Otama hostage, but...
If you make Holdem mad now
and Jack who is known as a Disaster
comes to retaliate,
this town will be in ruins.
That's not fair!
It's like they're holding
the whole town hostage!
TREASURE
While Luffy and the others were at it,
another Headliner, Speed,
showed up leading a treasure ship
filled with provisions.
What's going on, Holdem?!
It's Speed-sama's food treasure ship!
It's our grub for today!
That's a lot of food!
That's food from the Paradise Farm...
After seeing the excess amount of food,
Luffy asked...
Zoro! Could you handle that?!
Okay...
--I'll save Tama!
--What?
Kiku! I'm sorry but
we've decided to steal it and run.
What? When did you...?
Look what you've done!
Oh, I see now!
You don't need the brat back, right?!
Go ahead, Kamijiro!
Kamijiro! What the hell are you doing?!
Get us out of town!
What happened to your cheek?
It's nothing.
It was just pulled by some pincers.
Kibi Dango...
You won't be able to pull it out like that...
Pincers?!
Give me a minute!
Red Hawk!
"Duel!
The Magician and the Surgeon of Death!"
Big Bro!
Holdem-sama!
Tama!
Big Bro!
Hold on tight!
Okay!
Alright! Let's run!
Holdem-sama!
You're a Headliner
but you got knocked out by a single blow?!
Who did it?!
Luffy, that fool!
He shouldn't have done that...
Luffytaro-san!
Otama-chan!
Don't worry!
Leave the brat to Luffytaro!
Don't stop!
Keep making for the entrance of the town!
Win back the treasure ship!
Or we'll lose our food!
Hold on tight!
Yes, Big Bro!
I'm not gonna let go of you!
You can't go any farther!
How could you do that to Holdem-sama?!
You bastard...
Don't think you can get away!
B-Big Bro...
Chop him up!
Big Bro!
Big Bro!!
Get out of my way!
I've got to catch up to Zoro and the others
or they'll eat all the delicious stuff!
--Great! Let's hitch a ride! I'm gonna jump!
--What?
Who is it?!
Who's holding me in his arms?!
Giddy up, horse!
Okay!
Wait, what're you doing?!
What?! She's a human?!
Neigh-neigh!
No, she's a horse!
--How dare you get on Speed-sama like that?!
--Yank them down!
Get off of me, you rude bastards!
Hey, Tama, bring out the dango!
--What?!
--Just do it!
Kibi Dango!
Now, tame the horse!
What? That's impossible!
It won't work on humans!
You don't know until you try!
Get off, you little...
This is Kibi Dango. It's delicious.
Screw that!
I'm not gonna eat a
suspicious dango like that!
I'm not gonna...
I'm... not...
Neigh-neigh! It looks delicious!
S-Speed-sama?
As I thought, it won't work on humans...
Neigh-neigh! Where should I take you,
Master-sama?!
Yay!
It worked!
But why?
I guess it's because she's half horse.
S-Speed-sama...
Let's go after her!
She's too fast!
Alright, Horselina! Chase the treasure ship!
I'm not your servant!
My name is Speed!
Don't call me Horselina as if I'm your friend!
I want you to do as he says,
Horselina-chan.
Certainly, Master-sama!
I can't believe the Headliner Speed-sama
became obedient like that!
Do they have something on her?
Big Bro...
Red Hawk!
Fire Fist!
Big Bro, you were like...
...Ace earlier...
Hm? What?
Did you say something?
No!
Never mind.
AT THE ENTRANCE OF BAKURA TOWN
Who are you?
I'm gonna take your life.
What did you say?!
Damn you!
Don't mess around with us!
--Let's take him out!
--Yeah!
Room!
That ability...
That tattoo...
Is he...?!
That's possible!
They formed an alliance!
Roronoa-ya is with them
and he knows our plan.
Even as reckless as they are,
they wouldn't do a foolish thing like taking down Holdem.
Holdem-sama!
Oh no!
We've got to report this to Jack-sama now!
If they do something to him,
our plan will...
...no longer...
Go away, Hawkins!
Chambres!
Help me!
What?! I'm alive?!
What the hell?!
His lower body's moving by itself!
Injection!
Shot!
It's no use...
Now... What kind of ability was that?
Straw Sword!
Take off your mask!
Trafalgar Law!
There it is! The treasure ship!
Hey!
Zoro!
Luffy!
Horselina, jump!
I'm not your servant!
Please! Horselina-chan!
Whoa! It looks delicious!
There is so much food!
I've never seen this much at once before!
It's unbelievable!
Big Bro, are you okay?!
Oh, yeah! The most important
thing isn't here!
--What?
--I'll be back!
Big Bro, where are you going?!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
What is the most important thing?
I knew it wasn't gonna be that easy,
Basil Hawkins!
But...
Stop talking!
I'm gonna shut you up!
Attack!
Wait!
Amputation!
Takt!
Chambres!
You cut up all my proxies...
You catch on to things quickly.
It's just a threat though.
I'd rather not kill anyone
seeing as how I'm a doctor.
Welcome to the Land of Wano.
It's been a while since the fateful Sabaody.
I assume you're not here for vacation
since your allies are also here...
You didn't expect that I knew?
I ran across Straw Hat
and the others earlier.
I bet you wanted to silence me
before it's too late...
Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Holdem-sama was taken down by thieves
and they're on the run now!
We've already reported to Jack-sama!
They crushed Holdem
and now Jack has been notified?!
As you just heard,
all your effort was for nothing.
And of course, Kaido-san will know
what you and Straw Hat's group are doing.
Those fools...
Because of them, we have the worst possible outcome!
Hey, you guys! Clear the way!
Roronoa-ya?!
Excuse us! Let us pass through!
We're in a hurry!
Chase! They stole our food!
Roronoa-ya!
Hey, Tra-guy!
You idiot!
This is the origin of One Piece,
written by Eiichiro Oda!
A grand romantic adventure! A
mighty dream across the sea!
The freest man in the sea world!
He is the King of the Pirates!
The beginning of another Luffy's epic journey!
One Piece 20th anniversary special program!
"Romance Dawn"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!