If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Romance Dawn means the dawn of an adventure.
This is the story of a Luffy slightly different from the one
in One Piece...
I had a good sleep! I feel great!
What was that noise?
Is my boat broken?!
It's fine. Weird!
What? W-What? What is it?!
Is this a bird? An ostrich?
No, a panda?
There!
Stay right there!
I'm filling the hole with your butt!
If I don't, the boat'll sink!
A wound?!
Then the gunshot earlier was...
Balloon!
N-No!
Stay still! M-My boat... Oh, no!
That's a huge ship!
Balloon! Fly away as far as you can!
Young man with a straw hat.
Could you bring that bird up to this ship?
Okay.
How dare you?!
Why did you bring Balloon?!
He got caught because of you!
NAME: ANNE
Is Balloon that panda?
He's not a panda!
He was shot.
Yes, Six Hones Spiel shot him.
Who's that?
The captain of this pirate ship...
Oh, is this a pirate ship?
That's right. Spiel is
an infamous and cruel sorcerer.
When my village was raided,
everyone tried to fight back with their weapons,
but they couldn't even get near him.
Hmmm, a pirate who attacks villages, huh?
The Captain's here!
There! That's him!
Look at that.
Even his crewmembers are afraid of him!
He destroyed my village and stole our treasure!
All who defy him will be killed!
Well done. So you managed to catch
a Ruku - monster bird.
Yes!
Good. And you're the kid
who helped us catch it, right?
Come down!
What do you want for a reward?
What's the matter, boy?
I'm asking what you want.
Your head's weird.
M-M... M-My head's weird?
NICKNAME: SIX HONES SPIEL
You fool! Were you listening to me?!
Well, look at his head! It's weird!
Lock these idiots up!
All right. Keep quiet.
What a view! Big ships sure are nice!
I really wish I could kill you...
Don't.
Hey, is that ostrich yours?
He's not an ostrich either!
He's a so-called Ruku, a type of monster bird!
His name is Balloon!
We've been together for
as long as I can remember...
We've played and napped together,
and never left each other's side even for a moment
He may look like just a bird to others...
But to me, he's a more trustworthy,
important friend than anybody else.
I see...
Then why have you been kidnapped?
A good question!
That's because...
...I'm cute!
Y-Yeah? You sure?
What were you doing in that small boat
in the middle of the sea?
I was seeking out the Peace-mains
so we can become friends.
Peace-mains?
They're a type of pirates.
The pirates who just lawlessly plunder
like the ones on this ship are Morganeers.
And the Peace-mains go on adventures
ripping them off.
I wanna become a Peace-main!
My grandpa was a Peace-main pirate!
Grandpa!
Hey, Luffy! It's good to be a pirate!
If you're a man, set out to the sea!
Grandpa...
I'm not gonna become a pirate!
Let's divide the spoils we gained this time!
I'll take this!
Oh, Captain! That's not fair!
Cut it out! Thank me for not losing our way
on that island!
But...
Shut up! If I can have this one,
it's enough for me this time!
Hey, Luffy! Come here!
Here! Take a look!
It's the best part of our haul.
It's a mystic fruit, a Gum-Gum Fruit!
An enemy ship had it by chance
and we stripped them of it thanks to me!
We can sell it for 5 billion berries...
Yuck!
You fool!
That's a diabolical fruit!
If you eat it,
you'll never be able to swim again!
What?! No way!
It's true!
I'll never be able to swim again?
Yeah...
No...
W-Well, but that's okay.
I wasn't gonna become a pirate anyway...
O-Okay... So you don't mind.
Yeah...
It could've been worse
if you wanted to become a pirate!
It's all right!
There are tons of people
who enjoy their lives without being involved with water!
Grandpa... I was lying...
Because I wasn't sure if I could become one...
But the truth is...
I wanna become a pirate like you
and travel to all kinds of places!
I can't stand the fact
that I won't be able to swim again!
Luffy, you...
I see. So you wanna become a pirate...
Don't underestimate the sea!
Listen! The sea is nothing like ponds or rivers!
It's a monster!
What would you do if your ship sank
in the middle of the sea?!
A man shouldn't cry over such a little thing...
You brutal geezer!
Damn you!
How could you kick your grandfather?!
You started it!
What did you say?!
No violence!
It's your fault, Grandpa!
--Stop it! Ouch!
--You'll become a good-for-nothing...
--Oh, so you can't swim.
--For the rest of my life.
That brutal geezer wore this hat all the time.
This is my treasure.
Your treasure, huh?!
Yep...
What's your treasure?
In that case, Balloon is mine!
Look at that! A pod of whales!
I'm talking!
Gee!
I can't just stay here like this!
I'm gonna get out of here!
Don't be silly. That's impossible!
You're right. My boat was wrecked.
No, I mean you won't be able to
get out of here.
You're driving me crazy...
You'd better stop being ridiculous
and save your energy, too.
Alright!
How did you get out?!
The key was hanging there.
What I'm asking is how you could get it
from behind bars!
--Can you use sorcery or something?
--No.
But it's kinda close.
Hey, help me with rescuing Balloon.
No. I'm gonna look for a boat.
--Help me!
--No. It's a pain.
Okay, you jerk!
Balloon! I'll get you out of there now!
I'm so lucky! Everyone's having a nap!
When did you get here?!
Hey, girl!
It's showtime!
Have a one-on-one fight with him!
If you win, I'll release the Ruku.
Do you promise?!
Yes, I keep my word.
A good haul!
I found food while looking for a ship!
There it is! That boat looks good!
Did you underestimate me
because I am a woman?
Now, release Balloon as promised!
Wait! Oh, don't do it, Captain!
What a piece of crap...
How could he lose to a little girl like her...
You won.
You can let it out.
Great!
Balloon! I'll get you out of there!
How naive.
Pirates don't keep their promises.
I won't release it.
I took a lot of trouble to catch it!
Idiot!
Hi.
It's a lovely day, isn't it?
Where are you going?
Your friend is in a mess.
What are you gonna do?
Your hair looks like a water bug.
Is he a fool?!
He shouldn't say that!
Hey!
Why are you lying down bleeding?
Isn't it obvious?!
I got shot and collapsed!
It missed my vital organs
so I was waiting for the right moment.
Oh, okay.
You insolent brat...
Why don't you show more concern?!
So you're fine, right?
Know your place!
Oh, that was surprising!
Why did you do that all of a sudden?!
What just happened?
Come on, Hammer!
Go to hell!
Idiot! He shouldn't have pushed his luck!
N-No...
Why do you keep attacking me?!
Don't make me mad!
No way!
Hey, guys! Don't just stand there!
Your Captain is in trouble!
Y-Yes, sir!
I just saw your limbs stretch!
What's wrong with you?!
It's a riot, right?
Remember when I told you
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit?
And...
...my entire body turned to rubber
in exchange for my swimming ability!
So that was a true story!
H-He's a monster...
Only you can beat him, Captain!
You don't have to call me Captain!
This pirate group is breaking up!
Because I got what I wanted!
Balloon!
Rubber Man, just keep expanding
and contracting right there forever!
Goodbye!
Balloon!
Why are you doing this to us?!
--Balloon!
--He turned his back on his crew!
Oh, no!
I'm gonna drown!
I'm still alive!
Th-Thank you! Thank you so much!
You saved my life!
Hey...
Balloon...! Balloon...!
Balloon is said to be the last Ruku...
They believe there is magical power in Ruku's blood...
That's why I got kidnapped.
As long as they have me here,
Balloon will come back again and again...
I wish he wasn't so rare
and didn't have magical power!
Even if he wasn't special,
he'd still be my most important friend for me!
Not yet!
Don't give up!
He's your best friend, right?!
Don't worry!
Leave it to a Peace-main!
What are you gonna do?!
I'm gonna fly!
I'm proud of myself.
I know when to quit!
Even if I fight that monster,
I would've earned nothing.
All I need is this bird's blood.
I can form another pirate group anytime.
Hey, Ruku!
Don't try to escape death now.
Just give up!
What?!
Hi! I wish I could fly like you!
How the hell did you get here?!
Hey, you fool! Don't get on!
This broomstick is for one person!
Get off!
Hey!
Don't touch my hat!
O-O-Okay!
Oh, no! The Ruku!
The Ruku...
Don't worry! It'll be here any minute!
What will?!
My right hand.
No... Don't... Don't... Don't...
Don't do it!
Look, I know you saved me...
But isn't there a better way to carry me?
Forget it. Let's go back!
Hey, Luffy.
Remember! Real treasure is not
a huge diamond, gold, silver, pearls, nor coral.
It's not all the things that only sparkle.
Oh, it's not?
Right, you'll see
once you set out to the sea!
The sea is great, Luffy!
Uh-huh!
There!
I hope you can become a Peace-main!
I'll become one at any cost!
See you again!
Yeah, see you!
All right!
This is the beginning of a new journey!
Several years later, a pirate named Straw Hat Luffy
makes his name in the world of the sea!
The treasure ship filled with food gives a rays of hope
to the people of Okobore Town!
"I will make the country a place where
everyone can eat as much as they want!"
Otama sees in Luffy, as he looks to the future,
the shadow of Ace who she misses!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Coming of the Treasure Ship! Luffytaro Returns the Favor!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!