If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Where are they?
Those shitty brats...
So the only ones he's coming after are...
...me and Straw Hat-ya!
Kaido is coming after us, right?!
Then, I'll stop him!
They're hiding in the ruins of Oden Castle!
That brings back memories...
It is indeed a good place to hide.
So that's where they are...
They took SMILE away from me.
LAW AND STRAW HAT'S PIRATE ALLIANCE
Those hateful punks!
I won't let them get away!
Ow, ow, ow...
--We're in trouble, Nami-san...
--What?
Blast Breath!
"Finally Clashing!
The Ferocious Luffy vs. Kaido!"
ODEN
Guys, go back to the mountain without me!
Shutenmaru-sama!
I have a bad feeling.
He's crazy...
It was finished in a flash.
Not long enough for him to sober up...
Straw Hat-ya!
Kaido-sama!
Oh, no!
Mother!
Damn! My house...! My house!
Father!
Gear Three!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Kaido-san!
Kaido-sama is falling from the sky!
Who's that?!
Oh! He's the guy who beat Yokozuna Urashima
and Holdem-sama!
Kiku!
Where are you, Kiku?!
I'm here!
I'm here, Kin-sama!
Kiku! Are you all right?!
Yes.
But...
Oden Castle!
Momonosuke-sama!
Please wait!
Why?! I must hurry to make sure
he is all right!
If something happens to him...!
I feel the same way!
But don't you have something else
to worry about now?!
Tsuru...
He can wake up and rampage again
at any moment!
If that happens, even Okobore Town will...
I see.
I am going to go to Okobore Town.
Kiku, take care of Momonosuke-sama!
Of course!
You're okay!
You somehow got away!
Right, guys?!
Speed-sama!
Stay with us! What happened?!
I thought she went out of town!
She's just fallen from Kaido-sama's body!
Speed-sama! Speed-sama!
Who the hell are you?!
Hey, it's you, Horselina!
Horselina!
Speed-sama!
You're...
Why are you here?!
Where's Tama?!
You took her home, right?!
Answer, Horselina!
On our way, we were spotted by Kaido-sama...
...and I fought...
...but I couldn't protect...
...Master-sama...!
What's the matter?
Where are you going, Speed?!
Horselina-chan!
I received a strange report...
It's so yummy!
This soup is so delicious!
This is the greatest day of my life!
It's an apple!
Tama...
I'm paying you back for feeding me.
I'll never forget...
I'll never forget the taste
of the sweet red-bean soup
and the apple that I had today
for the rest of my life!
See you again!
Damn!
I should've...
...escorted her!
Straw Hat-ya!
What are you doing?! Let's run!
Since he's so gigantic,
he probably doesn't know what's happened!
It's not too late yet.
He got Tama.
Kin'emon and the others...
...and your crew and mine...
We don't know if they're alright!
If I kick his ass now,
it's all over, right?
Kaido!
I'm here!
You are...
Luffy.
The man who'll become
the King of the Pirates!
Luffy...?!
Did you say Luffy?!
Blast Breath!
So you've come...
...to the Land of Wano!
Gear Three!
He did it!
Now he screwed up everything!
It's unforgivable...
I swear, I'll make you pay!
Gum-Gum...
I'll never forget the taste
of the sweet red-bean soup
and the apple that I had today
for the rest of my life!
Elephant Gatling!
Luffy mounts ferocious attacks on the
invincible Kaido at a breathless speed!
Is the moment he finally takes down an
Emperor of the Sea just around the corner?!
However, Kaido's anger which is strong
enough to shake the sky strikes Luffy!
What will happen to Luffy
who gives it all he has?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Destructive! One Shot, One Kill - Thunder Bagua!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!