If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
In order to take down Emperor of the Sea
Kaido who reigns over the Land of Wano,
Luffy and the others
decided to launch a raid!
Will they be able to avenge the late Oden
and open up the Land of Wano?
The plan is set for Onigashima
on the night of the Fire Festival.
Blast Breath!
ODEN
You're okay!
You somehow got away!
Right, guys?!
Horselina!
Why are you here?!
Where's Tama?!
You took her home, right?!
Answer, Horselina!
On our way, we were spotted by Kaido-sama...
...and I fought...
...but I couldn't protect...
...Master-sama...!
Kaido!
I'm here!
You are...
Luffy.
The man who'll become
the King of the Pirates!
Luffy...?!
Did you say Luffy?!
"Destructive!
One Shot, One Kill - Thunder Bagua!"
Gum-Gum...
Elephant Gatling!
Straw Hat-ya!
Kaido!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Giant Stamp!
I'll send you flying, Kaido!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly...
...Magnum!
Supreme Commander Kaido...
Straw Hat-ya!
That's enough! Come back!
Come to your senses!
Kaido!
Gear Four!
Bounce-Man!
How dare you...
...mess with my friends, you bastard!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Gun!
...Double Culverin!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Organ Gun!
Who is that guy?
Gum-Gum...
...King Kong Gun!
Thunder Bagua!
That fool!
I should grab him and run!
I think I have enough stamina for that...
Room!
Shamble...!
I lost my energy...!
Don't do it, Trafalgar.
It's you again! Not now!
The Sea Prism Stone used across the world
originated in the Land of Wano.
It's a Sea Prism Stone... nail?!
Only the Land of Wano has artisans
who can refine it into something that small.
Straw Sword!
Damn! This is the worst...
Room!
Shambles!
What an annoying ability...
He can't go that far.
He must be around. Look for him!
Yes, sir!
I can't believe this.
He's still breathing.
I bet so.
What?
I don't know whether it's out of his
indomitable spirit or bravado...
but he's glaring at me.
To me, he just looks unconscious...
What kind of king did you say you'd be?
You little punk!
Taken down by Kaido, Luffy is sent to a
mine where hellish forced labor awaits him!
However, he unexpectedly
reunites with someone there!
Are Otama and the Straw Hats alive?!
And what will happen to the desperate Luffy?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Living Hell! Luffy, Humiliated in the Great Mine!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!