kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
LAND OF WANO - ACT TWO
The Land of Wano Arc - Act Two now begins!
After being defeated by Kaido,
Luffy got caught
and at the Excavation Labor
Camp in the Udon region,
he was forced to do heavy labor.
I won't give in!
Wait for me, Kaido!
And his friends started
preparing for the raid.
Meanwhile, Nami snuck into a residence
with a kunoichi Shinobu
to spy on the enemies.
This is the order sheet for arms and weapons.
Somebody's there!
Get them, get them!
There are suspicious figures!
There are intruders in the building!
Oh, no!
Shinobu-chan!
"Rampage!
The Prisoners - Luffy and Kid!"
Who are they?!
Go up in the attic, too!
Catch them at any cost!
Calm down, Shinobu-chan!
You're not getting away!
Be quiet!
Where did they go?!
Oh, is it just a cat?
What's the matter with you, Shinobu-chan?!
Are you okay?
Onami...
There is something I haven't told you...
What?
Find them! Catch them!
Don't let the intruders get away!
I...
...have a fear of sharp objects!
You're not cut out for any kind of fight!
But Onami...
A mature woman...
...is as deadly as...
...a weapon.
Let's catch this wind.
What?
Ninpo: Great Kite!
GREAT KITE
NIN
Shinobu-chan! This is awesome!
Haven't you found them yet?!
What did you see in the residence, Onami?
Um...
Oh! I saw the name of the port
and the shipment day!
Good job!
Now we know when and where
they're stockpiling their arms!
Let's steal them!
Uh-huh!
Smells good! I'll have some.
Me, too!
Yes! Thank you!
Oh? Something is going on in the town.
What's that line for?
Is it a sale?!
There are so many young girls.
Welcome! Welcome!
Come on and try it, ladies!
That voice... It must be...
It's sweet when it melts in the mouth.
It sure is al dente!
Sangoro's...
...nihachi soba!
SANGORO'S NIHACHI SOBA
San, go, ni, hachi!
3 5 2 8
The sum is 18!
NUMBER 18 (OHAKO)
OHAKO (SPECIAL) SOBA
It's my Special Soba!
The noodles are glimmering!
Slightly chewy!
It's delicious!
There's no samurai!
Thank you!
I'll take one, too!
Yes, thanks!
He doesn't look familiar...
But it's really popular.
That squirt...
Does he know who's turf he muscled in on?!
We've got to teach him...
Strike the iron!
Haul the stone!
If you can't work,
why don't you at least die
and get out of the way?!
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP AND WEAPONS FACTORY
UDON, LAND OF WANO
I-Is this it?
By hauling five big blocks of rock,
you get one millet dumpling!
You got too old to earn your own food,
Old Man Hyo?!
You're finally close to death!
I worked all day and...
Huh?! What did you just say?!
Talking back to a guard...
...will be punished by dismemberment!
Next!
Old Man Hyo!
Don't fight. Save your energy!
Or you're gonna die!
Oh, four exchange tickets!
Well done!
Move! Move! Move! Move! Move!
Outta my way!
You guys are in my way!
Do you wanna get run over?!
Watch it, Jaggy!
I'll run you over, too!
Wait, wait! It's already full!
This is it for today!
Then, bring out another ship!
You slowpokes!
I-I'm sorry!
How many stones did they haul?
I was counting up to 500...
--Huh?! What about the Sea Prism Stone?!
--They're wearing it.
Even weakened they can still pull that off?
How strong will they be uncuffed?
I finished my work! Give me food!
What?!
Whaaat?!
How much did they haul
to get that much food?!
--What's your problem?!
--What are you looking at?!
I made one more round-trip than you!
You fool! I outpaced you!
Screw you!
No, you didn't, Jaggy!
Can't you even count, you stupid monkey?!
You bastard!
Damn you!
I thought they were both badly injured...
They work, eat, and sleep...
After a few days, they're fully recovered.
How do their bodies work?!
What can we do to break their spirits?!
Say something to them!
What?!
C-Chew well!
Are you their mother?!
My dumplings...
Dammit!
Hippo!
It's Dobon-sama!
This is unforgivable! Come out!
Whoever did it!
DOBON - A VICE WARDEN (A HEADLINER)
HIPPO SMILE FRUIT
Which prisoner ate all
the food in the storage?!
It's Dobon-sama!
Hippo!
Perpetrator, come forward!
Help...
Oh! Old Man Hyo is trapped!
Crawl out, Old Man!
--Dobon-sama!
--The perpetrators are behind bars!
What?! What about the dumplings?!
They ate them all...
You guys just stood there and watched?!
They worked hard and got the
proper amount of food in exchange,
so we couldn't say anything...
How could you ignore a vice warden...
I can't really hear
because the hippo closed its mouth...
Can it shut him up like that?
Hippo?
It's unforgivable!
Dobon-sama...
Bring the perpetrators here!
Dobon-sama! We brought them!
These are the perpetrators!
They're stuffed!
I've never seen someone
with a full belly here before!
Lucky them!
You fools!
Damn you!
I'm a big eater but there are
only three dumplings left for me
because of you guys!
Look at this mouth!
Do you think that's enough?!
No way!
Wait a minute...
Let me digest...
Who do you think I am?!
What?
What?!
What?!!
How do your bodies work?!
Everyone eats, digests,
and takes a dump, right?!
I don't wanna see a prisoner
with such a satisfied look!
My...
...food!
Hey! Don't push your luck, you fools!
Listen carefully!
If you mess with the guards...!
The first offense, your arms will be cut off!
For the second, your legs!
And for the third...
you're sentenced to death!
Be careful!
He's right!
You guys have no right to fight back!
Hey... We're only weaklings
since our powers
have been drained by the Sea Prism Stone.
All we did was work hard.
You guys should be punished because...
...you ate all of my food!
Son of a...!
Jaggy!
Hippo!
I will...
...discipline you!
Whoa! They got eaten!
Poor boys!
Inside of the mouth is
Dobon-sama's slaughter room!
Now, it's time for punishment!
What happened?!
I've never seen the hippo go down like this!
Vice Warden Dobon?!
Look what you did!
Now you can't escape the death penalty!
Do you have any proof?
What?!
I said, "Do you have any proof?"
Good job, guys!
You guys are the heroes of the prisoners!
As the Straw Hats secretly
proceed with the preparations,
Sanji's soba shop gains a growing reputation and
becomes extremely popular!
When the Kyoshiro Family that comes to make an accusation
infuriates Sanji,
a melee between the Straw Hats and
the Kyoshiro Family blows up a storm in the capital!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Great Sensation! Sanji's Special Soba!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!