kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
At the castle,
the Shogun Orochi's banquet has started.
Everyone, the Fire Festival is coming up!
Let's have a pre-party!
Around the same time,
Big Mom and her children
were trying to reach the
shore of the Land of Wano.
They were close,
but due to the Lead Performer King's attack,
Big Mom was thrown into the sea.
Dammit!
Mama!
Meanwhile, at the Flower Capital,
Page One was rampaging
looking for Sanji.
Sangoro!
Maybe it's no use.
If he's a coward, he'll never show himself!
They're using trickery!
Our top priority should be on running!
Sanji!
How...
...could I do that?!
Stop! We have nothing to do with him, either!
Then, call out for him!
Everybody!
For Sangoro the soba cook!
I'm...
...here!
Diable Jambe!
Concasser Crush!
Stop it!
If Drake and Hawkins come, it'll be all over!
He doesn't know who I really am.
So no one will find it out
and I won't get hurt!
I can beat this fool in an instant.
Guys, move ahead!
What?
It's fine as long as...
...I keep my identity secret, right?
"Dashing!
The Righteous Soba Mask!"
The soba cook really showed up?!
Is he stupid?! Does he wanna die?!
This is the perfect time to transform.
What's that? Is it a can of something?
He should've forgotten about the town.
What is he gonna do?!
I think that's Germa's...
Even I put this on,
I won't allow myself to become like Germa!
I'll at least try it on!
If you don't start,
I'm gonna attack you!
Soba cook!
We're about to fight an Emperor of the Sea...
Perhaps my stubbornness will
get in the way of saving someone.
Maybe I can save someone
if I swallow my pride...
Stop talking gibberish!
If this thing gives me that much power!
Here I go!
What are you doing?
You just changed in the air?
Black-Leg-ya...
Oh, he transformed?! It's just super!
Cool! How did it work?!
Wait. I know that costume from somewhere...
Oh, yeah... But...
...why does he have that suit?!
Without doubt, it belongs to
the enemy of Sora, Warrior of the Sea!
The No.3 member of the evil army, Germa 66!
Stealth Black!
Hey, why do you know so much?!
Of course I do!
Everyone from the North Blue knows!
Whatever!
Listen! Don't ever call me Germa!
Understood?!
I was a legitimate fan
who supported Sora, Warrior of the Sea!
I hated Germa, those despicable villains.
SORA, WARRIOR OF THE SEA
I hated them, too!
Hey, you!
You're not an ordinary soba cook...
Identify yourself!
I... am...
You're a member of Germa 66...
Stealth Black...
I... am...
A member of Germa 66!
I am...
Identifying himself is a big moment for a hero!
Come on, Sangoro!
Problems hearing, soba cook?
Let me repeat myself.
Identify yourself!
I... am...
I am...
SOBA MASK
...Soba Mask!
Soba Mask...
No... He's definitely Germa...
That's awful! Change your name!
Give us the rights to name you!
Did you say Soba Mask?!
Don't mess with me!
Where did he go?
What?!
He's floating in midair!
How is that possible?!
I have no doubt...
That's Germa's scientific technology...
The power of the devices on their feet
to float...
After all, he's...
That's awesome!
That's just child's play!
Way to go, Soba Mask!
What kind of feature was that?!
In the heels of Germa 66's special suits,
there are acceleration devices...
Your attacks are so annoying
and they piss me off!
What the hell is this?!
--Wow!
--It's shutting out his punch!
Germa 66's capes can...
...turn into solid shields...
I know your moves!
You can't attack me like you did before!
Oh, no!
If he's the real Stealth Black,
he'll use that!
I won't let you get away now!
Disappeared?!
No way!
People can't just disappear!
Where is he?! Where did he go?!
Come out!
I thought so.
--So strong! Huh? Where is he?!
--He's moving too fast to see!
No, that's a special ability of
Germa 66's Stealth Black...
He became invisible
by projecting the background over his body!
Even Sora, Warrior of the Sea,
had quite a hard time with him...
Damn Germa...
Which side are you on?!
I mean, how do you know so much?!
Everyone from the North Blue knows!
What's this suit?! Did I disappear?!
It's the same as the Clear-Clear Fruit?!
DEVIL FRUITS
It's the Devil Fruit that
I dreamed of having...
With the Clear-Clear Fruit,
I can become invisible.
My dream that once crumbled...
Yes. You stole a dream from me!
I don't recall doing that.
It must be a mistake.
I wanted to become the invisible man!!
So you, who ate the Clear-Clear Fruit,
crushed one of my dreams, all right?!
W-What?!
It's not his fault!!
My dream that once crumbled...
...came true by the technology
of Germa that I reviled?
How ironic...
But this ability is very useful...
This'd be handy in the women's bath...
No, no!
I can use it to protect my friends!
What a dilemma!
An invisible man?
There's something fishy about you...
Who the hell are you?!
It should be easier for
me to fight in this form
against someone who moves around so much...
I was gonna work you over,
but I guess I'd better just kill you.
An invisible man?
There's something fishy about you...
Who the hell are you?!
I am...
...Soba Mask!
That's exactly who I am!
So you can't reveal your true identity...
I'll kill you and tear off that mask!
Give yourself away!
Stealth Black!
I told you not to call me that!
I'm neither evil nor righteous!
I'm nothing more than Soba Mask...
Don't worry about me. Just go ahead!
He's...
...just perfect for testing
how powerful this Raid Suit is!
Hey, Jaggy!
I bet you still have some dumplings!
Jaggy!
Jaggy! Don't pretend to be sleeping!
I'll repay you so give me your dumplings!
I know you're hearing me, Jaggy!
Good! Good!
All right!
This is an old and mysterious room...
This country has been
isolated for centuries...
And the Ponegliff was invented here...
I'm sure they have one.
There must be a hidden door somewhere...
Are you looking for something?
No way! How could I have missed it?!
Good!
Good, good, good, good...
Komurasaki.
I want you to play that one now!
As you wish...
You shouldn't have done anything suspicious
since ninja were here...
How ridiculous!
Don't you know who ninja are?
She could be from overseas.
OROCHI'S ONIWABANSHU
SHOGUN OF WANO PERSONAL NINJA FORCE
Oh, hello.
You're a troublesome geisha...
I give you a chance to explain.
FUKUROKUJU - CAPTAIN OF THE ONIWABANSHU
But...
...you get only one.
You okay, Sangoro?!
The Ancient Type power users are so powerful!
But...
...it's not enough to beat Stealth Black...
It hurts a bit, but this thing is durable.
But the capital can't take it too long...
Hey! Why are we leaving Sangoro behind?!
He told us to go ahead.
Yes, he did, but...
All right... Let's deliver his dead body
to Boss Kyoshiro.
But who was he after all?
There'll be more pursuers
and it's gonna get messier.
We shouldn't stay in the capital for the time being.
Let's go to Ebisu Town!
Shooting Star! Soba Kick!
What?!
Tsk! He's so tough...
Where are you?!
Show yourself, Soba Mask!
Soba Mask, huh?
I should ask Franosuke and Usohachi
to redesign this!
A move at lightning speed! Bizarre weapons!
Orochi's Oniwabanshu, the great ninja force,
launch unexpected attacks!
Robin, Nami, and Brook are cornered!
For the success of their raid operation,
a perilous fight begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Desperate Situation! Orochi's
Menacing Oniwabanshu!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!