If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Six deadly figures among the Headliners -
the Tobi Roppo.
To fight one of them, Page One,
Sanji splendidly transformed himself.
In the Flower Capital,
Sanji and Page One put up an intense fight.
Meanwhile, at Orochi's Castle...
Oh, hello.
You're a troublesome geisha...
I give you a chance to explain.
But you get only one.
FUKUROKUJU - CAPTAIN OF THE ONIWABANSHU
"A Desperate Situation!
Orochi's Menacing Oniwabanshu!"
OFF THE COAST OF THE LAND OF WANO
Lick...
Boy, that was terrible.
I didn't expect King would attack us himself!
Yeah!
I didn't see it coming.
Now we're separated from Mama...
Hey, Brother Peros!
What should we do now?
Well, let's see what we can do. Lick.
I found you, Straw Hat!
Big Mom!
Here I go!
Life or death?!
Death!
That's it! That's it!
That's the music!
I love it!
I wonder why...
Whenever Big Sis Komurasaki plays that music,
she puts on that mask.
Now, I give you one chance to answer my question.
Who are you and what were you doing?
If you speak true,
I'll kill you at once, so you won't suffer.
Otherwise, you'll be subjected to
merciless torture...
My name is...
...Ushimitsu Kozo.
I came here to see how money flows
in the Flower Capital.
I see...
So you're saying that you were doing research on
who should be your next target?
That's a very smart answer...
But we know that you didn't give out your real name!
I won't let you get away!
By seeing how you moved,
I know you're not a common geisha.
To hide your identity, you used Ushimitsu Kozo's name
and tried to blame a crime on the thief.
That's very mean!
Right. Ushimitsu Kozo has
just appeared in the capital.
Let me ask one more time.
Who are you?
And what have you been doing?
I guess you really want to be tortured...
Well then...
Do it!
BEACH OF KURI, KURI
Otama! Let's have a fair fight!
I could ask for nothing better, Chopperemon!
Ninpo: Leaves Jutsu!
Ninpo!
Zigzag Run!
Take this!
It's a long way to go
to become a bewitching kunoichi...
I somehow dodged all of it...
Both of you, good job!
I'm still worried about Big Bro Luffy...
Don't worry! He'll be alright!
But we haven't heard from Raizo yet, either.
It's hard not to be anxious...
Master-sama said that no one has ever
left the prison in Udon...
I said he'll be fine! Nin-nin!
All we can do now is train ourselves!
Ninpo: Tree-climbing Jutsu!
If I were strong enough,
I would go to save him now...
Oh?
What is that?
Huh?!
What?!
She's gone?!
Where did she go?
I would've died if I didn't use
the Shadow Clone Jutsu...
This is Orobi!
Onami! Shinobu-san! Bonekichi!
I'm sorry, but I was discovered
by the enemies!
What? They found Robin?
Oh no! That's a big deal!
I can't believe they found Orobi-san!
There are some ninja in the castle!
11 of them at least!
11 ninja?!
Fukurokuju!
Fukurokuju is the leader of the ninja force!
Orochi's Oniwabanshu led by him is
a group of capable ninja!
I'm sure they'll go after Orobi!
Let's protect her, Onami!
Uh-huh! Robin, where are you?!
Oh! You're a geisha!
Oh, yes!
What are you doing here? Oops...
Whoa-whoa, watch your step.
I'm so drunk.
I gotta go to the bathroom...
Now, I'll take a leak so I can drink more!
Disconnected...
We have to find her ourselves.
Brook, did you hear that?
Find Robin and protect her.
Okay, okay! I got it.
Clank.
And here I finally got to do something
other than gathering food...
A curse on you!
Was she a ninja?
Or a specter?
Whether it's ninjutsu or magic,
the main body should be around here.
Listen!
Orochi-sama is having a banquet!
Don't make trouble over a rat!
Yes, sir!
Now, let's drink more!
Oh no, you're drinking too much.
Oh, how pleasant!
Oh, Orobi the new girl!
Where have you been?!
Come closer!
Oh, yes!
"A wise man would hide a leaf in the forest."
It's impossible to get out of here now.
Plus, I still have things to do.
I'm sorry...
I've taken too much time!
My Lord!
This way!
What is it, Chopperemon?
What's that?! A person?!
What a huge person...
Still smaller than the Giants though!
K-Kaido or this person - which one is bigger?
Is that person a woman?
What?! No way!
You lovely one. I'm feeling good!
Here you go, my Lord!
That's right!
It's delicious! Sake tastes better
when you pour it!
Oh... Thank you very much!
--By the way...
--What?
This banquet is really enchanting.
I'm so honored to be invited to something like this.
I'm happy, too!
To have you...
I want to drink the night away with you!
Eh?!
Those words...
Even if you're joking, they make me happy...
No no. I'm not joking. I'm serious!
Oh... I'm so grateful!
Now, my Lord...
I heard you would have a big banquet
at Onigashima on the day of the Fire Festival...
Oh yes, I will!
Every official of the Land of Wano
and all of the Animal Kingdom Pirates will be there!
That many people?!
I cannot believe how powerful you are...
How amazing!
It's an annual festival!
We must do it in a lavish manner!
I want to attend...
...that banquet...
Please summon me.
All right! All right! Count on me!
Are you sure?! I'm so happy!
So cute!
Orobi-san!
Where are you?
I have to look for her until I get bone-tired
because I'm basically made of bones.
Is she here?
Or here?
Oh! No!
--Who are you?!
--Stop!
What are you doing over there?!
--Oh?
--Where did that person go?!
You saw me!
S-S-Something is here!
It's a specter!
Must have imagined it...
Whoa! Such treasures will be
taken to Onigashima?
Indeed!
Do you want to hear more about
the Fire Festival, Orobi?
Yes, I want to become acquainted with you
more and more...
Then would you like to compete
to become my primary consort?
Komurasaki!
You're so mean...
Don't pout, don't pout, Komurasaki!
How cute! You're very, very cute!
Orochi-sama...
Doesn't he know the other side of her?
Even if he learns about it,
she will evade reproach with that prettiness.
So cute!
Hm? What's the matter, Orobi?
Oh, nothing...
Here you go, my Lord!
Komurasaki's sake sinks into the marrow!
Komurasaki the top Oiran!
Oh, she's beautiful!
I wish I were Orochi-sama...
But I'm scared of her darker side!
Don't worry!
She won't fall in love with you!
Right?!
She is more tamed
than any woman from your pleasure hall.
Boss Kyoshiro.
Don't talk about the courtesans
like they are dogs or something...
People are flowers.
If you are not clean water,
your ladies won't bloom elegantly.
You got us there!
But I heard that you brought out the Tobi Roppo
just to take down one soba cook!
You're relentless as always!
We yakuza become parents
to any underling once we exchange cups of sake.
If your child came home beaten up,
what would you do?
I'm always impressed by your chivalrous spirit...
You're right, Kyoshiro!
You must always crush your enemy
with overwhelming force!
To make sure they'll never stand against you!
Even if it's...
...a ghost!
Ghost, huh? Here we go again.
Orochi-sama will talk about the Akazaya Nine again...
He is still afraid of Kozuki Oden's retainers
who were wiped out two decades ago.
How ridiculous...
No way!
Big M...
BIG MOM (CHARLOTTE LINLIN)
CAPTAIN OF THE BIG MOM PIRATES
What is wrong?
Don't speak! It'll wake her up!
We've got to run!
It's all over once she wakes up!
No... It's no good!
Even if we run...
If she came after us...
What are you talking about?
Do you know who she is?
Everyone knows her! She's...
Whaaat?!
She is the infamous Big Mom?!
You're too loud!
Who is Big Mom?
I'll tell you later!
I'm gonna kill her right now!
That's right! Think of her as Kaido!
She's the same as Kaido!
T-Too late!
Anyway, just run!
Where...
Where... am I?
Who...
...am I?!
Being laughed at by a girl, Otoko,
Orochi is infuriated by his humiliation!
The banquet turns into hell! Orochi loses his senses and changes
into something ghoulish in order to destroy everything!
Who is the surprising figure who stands in Orochi's way
to save the girl's life?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Pandemonium! The Monster Snake, Shogun Orochi!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!