The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Well, we're finally here.
I'd tell you not to be too eager,
but I guess that's asking too much.
But do you have a plan
for stopping the rebellion?
I do have a plan, but there's no
guarantee it will make things stop.
So hungry...
So hot...
Please! Don't make a hasty decision!
"Nanohana, Alabasta Kingdom"
"Off to the Desert Kingdom! The Rain-
Summoning Powder and the Rebel Army"
So this is an Alabasta city?
Food!
Listen, guys! Use self-control and
try not to act on instinct too much!
Yes, Nami-san!
The guy who needs to hear
that the most is already gone.
Food place!
Get back here!
He's all-instinct.
What should we do?
Don't worry.
Find where the most commotion is,
and he'll be there.
You got that right.
Ugh! I wish he'd at least realize
he has a bounty on his head!
Especially in a big country like this!
Forget about him.
Let him do whatever.
Let's just eat first.
We can think after that.
They're all the same...
Karoo and I can't go with you.
--Eh?
--Huh? Are you not feeling good?
I'm too recognizable here...
That's for sure.
Don't worry! I'll go shopping
for you too, Vivi-chan!
What is it?
Mr. 3's ship!
That creep didn't kick
the bucket after all?!
There's no doubt about it!
His ship runs on the power
of his Wax-Wax Fruit!
The bastard's here?
This is bad. He's seen our faces.
It's alright! I have an idea!
There's no telling where he is,
so we hafta move without standing out.
I think we're standing out quite a bit...
Alright! You can come out, guys!
We've been long out.
Looks like nobody noticed us!
If so, it's a miracle.
Vivi-chan. We're safe from
view for a little while now.
Vivi-chan?
Yes?! Yes? You were saying?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry. I just felt
a little relieved, so...
At the very least,
from what I've seen of this town,
things still seem all right...
I probably can't rest easy...
...but I think I'll make it in time.
Yeah. It does seem like a peaceful town.
Hey, Vivi.
You said you had a plan for
stopping the rebel army, right?
What will you do now?
What should we do?
Eh?
If you think you're gonna make it in
time, it'd be better to act quick.
Th-That's true, but the agreement
was only to bring me to Alabasta--
Come on, now!
Are you still saying that?
Nami-san?!
We traveled this far together.
We can't just leave you now.
Yeah, Vivi! Don't act so distant!
Plus, I'm interested in this
Warlord of the Sea!
You don't have to mention that!
Anyways, stop thinking that way!
Not to mention people are
out to kill all of us but me.
Sanji-san...
So there you have it!
And besides, if this
country gets destroyed,
we won't get our reward
for bringing you here.
--Understand?
--Y-Yes.
Very good, then!
Go to hell.
Thank you, Zoro! I haven't forgotten
about your debt to me, either!
Wh-Why, you--!
Even if I'm a ghost I'll
still come for my money!
You lousy--!
You'd better pay the
400,000 Berries you owe!
It's gone up!
It'll go even higher if
you're not quick to repay!
--Hey, Usopp! Say something!
--Thank you.
--Forget it!
--Nami-san is in the right!
Say what?!
Northwest of this city
is an oasis called Yuba.
That's where the rebel army is based.
I'd like to go there
first to stop the uprising.
But to get to Yuba,
we'll have to cross the desert.
For that, we'll need to stock up on
the necessary food and water here...
...but if Mr. 3 is in town...
Oh. In that case, it's no problem.
He hasn't seen my face.
That's right! You've met
almost none of them so far!
And one other!
Oh, yeah! Chopper, too!
That'll be perfect. We'll have a
lot to carry. I'm counting on you!
Right! Got it!
Hey, now. You gonna be okay?
I'll be okay! I wanna do what I can!
There's no problem like this, right?
Alright! Now that's a human reindeer!
In that case, your help is appreciated.
Leave it to us!
I've listed everything we need.
Oh, and we'll need some clothes, too.
Clothes?
Ordinary clothes so we won't stand out.
--Ah.
--And perfume!
Yes, Nami-san!
--Food and water!
--Tabasco!
Who cares about you!
--Food and water!
--Tabasco!
Still...
...where could that idiot be,
and what is he doing?!
Hmm... It doesn't look like there'd
be a food place here at all...
But, actually...
...where am I?!
"Nanohana"
No choice. I'll just have
to go back the way I came.
Smoke?
If there's smoke, that means...
Food place!
Says it's deer meat!
That's what's great
about historical lands!
Got all kinds of ingredients!
What is it, Chopper?
There's something strange mixed
in with the smell of the food...
Strange?
Oh! That's the scent of perfume!
Perfume?
Yeah. That shop there sells some.
I don't really like this smell... Hey!
That's a wonderful outfit, Miss!
But it and your exotic fragrance
are put to shame by your raw charm!
What do you say?
Would you like to have some tea--?
What was that, Chopper?!
That was just getting good!
What are you doing?
Shopping comes first!
Yeah, I know!
Oh, it's too much!
This smell is making me sick...
Oh, that's okay. Don't push yourself.
I'll do the shopping.
You go wait over there.
Later!
Miss!
Is he really gonna be okay?
This is bad. I'm starting to
have symptoms of heat stroke.
I need to go somewhere where it's cool...
Ah! That feels nice!
I think I'll take a nap until
Sanji comes back.
Is that okay? Is it? I guess it is...
Is it closed?
Yeah. Let's go.
We don't want anyone finding it.
Now where'd he go?
"Katorea"
Nanohana is famous for its perfume,
but the perfume is actually
made at an oasis called Katorea.
It's a city west of here.
I dunno, this doesn't seem like
a food place at all, but...
Anyone here?!
Huh? No one's even here?
Oh! Water!
Come on! Just a little would be good!
What're these?
What's this green powder?
Is it food? It doesn't look very tasty...
Yuck! Yuck! What is this stuff?! Blech, yuck!
Oh! Perfect!
This stuff is obviously poison!
Now you burn!
What a waste of time that was.
Now to find me a food place...
What is that?!
Rain...
Oh! This is perfect! Water!
Wh-What is this?!
Aah! All the bags are gone!
What the hell did you do?!
--Who are you?
--Shut up!
I'm asking what you did with that powder!
Powder?
I burned it all!
You burned it?!
My Dance Powder! My treasure!
What's with you, old guy?
Why're you so sad?
Shut up! How dare you
waste my prized powder!
Do you know how much I spent for it?!
I don't care! Why would you
want that poison anyway?!
That's none of your business, you bastard!
Give me my dream back!
That stuff was your dream?!
That's right! It was a step
toward achieving my big ambition!
I'm very sorry!
Apologizing won't fix things!
Pay me for it!
I can't. I don't have money.
Don't say that proudly!
I even built a cabin out here and
finally managed to get this far...
C'mon, don't be so down!
You can just buy some more!
It's not that easy to buy!
The World Government outlawed
it from being made or sold!
Come again?
Hey, old man.
Are you a really bad guy?
You found me out?
Then die!
Huh?! Where am I?!
Huh? Huh? Who're they? Where am I?
Rifles!
What's wrong?
Thought I heard a voice. It's nothing.
I dunno what's going on,
but they seem dangerous!
I should probably get out of here, quick!
Oww!
--Good work. That took a while.
--Yeah.
The weapon store guy really raised
his prices, that greedy bastard...
It can't be helped. They're in huge
trouble if they get found out, too.
--Where's Koza?
--Inside.
We got a bit of food, too.
It's in the back.
Got it.
What is this?
They went and bought a whole deer?
Koza. We got some weapons.
Just a few, anyway...
Yeah. Sorry for giving you
such a dangerous job.
It's nothing at all.
Why're you in such a daze?
This country is screwed...
It'll either collapse from the inside, or...
Whatever the case, it won't stay at peace.
We have enough men now after
300,000 of the Royal Army
switched to our side, but we
don't have enough weapons...
Or food.
And our strength is at its limit.
There's no point in shedding
any more unnecessary blood.
We're going to finish everything
for good with our next attack!
We, the rebel army,
must change this country!
Hey! Wasn't there deer meat here?
Huh? Are you sure someone
didn't haul it out already?
C'mon, do better checks, will ya?
What?!
Water? There's some in
that trough! Drink that!
Hey! Let's get the rest
out of here! Gimme a hand!
Right!
A-Am I safe now?
Whew! Thank you!
But why did you help me?
"I got no reason. I'm cool, ain't I?"
You're so strange!
Thank you so much!
He's a little strange,
but he's a nice guy!
I feel like I'm going to see him again!
Still, who were those people?
Oh, well. Now which way is Nanohana?
This way.
Oh! You certainly are strong!
No one can beat me!
Yeah, I would think not!
Not with your strength! My apologies!
No, no! I apologize for
burning your important stuff!
Oh, uhh, no, let's just
call it a mutual apology!
In any case, please keep
this powder thing a secret!
Hey.
What was that powder?
Y-You don't know?
No. It was yucky.
That was stuff known as Dance Powder!
Dance Powder?
It's also called
"Rain-Summoning Powder."
It's what caused that
sudden downpour just now!
Umm, shall I explain in more detail?
I wouldn't understand anyways!
You look like you wouldn't.
You're a rude guy!
I-In any case, this powder can
artificially produce rain, yes.
Dance Powder, when released into
the air, forms the cores for rain!
When moisture collects around them,
clouds form and precipitate!
Understand?
So it's mystery powder, basically?
Well done!
You really are a rude guy!
Why would you wanna use
that powder to make it rain?
You don't seem to know
anything about this country.
No. I just landed here by boat.
This land of Alabasta has always
been battling with drought.
Drought?
It's when it never rains
and the land dries up!
I know that much!
So anyway, this land has
always been low on water.
And rain's been especially
scarce these past few years.
That's really something!
Most oases have dried up now!
Huh? Then just use the mystery powder!
Exactly! But the World Government
has outlawed Dance Powder!
They'll execute you if
they catch you using it!
It's also said to be what
started this country's rebellion.
Really?
--I don't know much myself, though.
--Oh.
Oh! Was your dream to use that
mystery powder to save this country?
Huh?!
You said it was important powder earlier.
No, uhh, that wasn't quite
what I had in mind...
What, then?
Well, I thought I could
make a bunch of money
by selling water in these hard times...
Yeah, you could! You're smart!
But, whatever. That has
nothing to do with me.
Guess I'll keep looking
for a food place again.
U-Umm! Please, don't
tell anyone about this!
I won't. I don't care.
I beg you! I'll give you whatever I can!
--For reals?!
--For real! For real!
Oh! Thanks for this lunch, old guy!
Not at all! I hope it's to your liking!
It's more than enough! Later, old guy!
Please remember not to tell anyone!
Don't worry! Don't worry!
I couldn't turn you in,
even if I wanted to!
Huh?
After all, I'm a pirate!
See ya! Thanks for the food!
That isn't fair!
Wow!
This is wonderful!
I love these kinds of clothes!
I know I asked you to
shop for us Sanji-san,
but aren't these outfits
for dancer girls?
Come, now! It looks marvelous on you!
--I asked for commoner clothing...
--Dancers are commoners, too!
--But we're going to cross a desert...
--Don't worry!
If you get tired, I'll carry you!
There's no getting through to him...
But, compared to them,
you two clearly look like bandits.
How're you any different?!
Chopper! What're you doing?
The smell is killing me...
--That reminds me, where did you go?
--Various places!
--Is he not feeling good?
--Oh, the perfume's gotten to him.
Perfume?
Oh, right! Tony-kun
has a sensitive nose!
--Oh, this...
--Some of it can be rather strong.
Like this?
--Stop!
--Mellorine love into the abyss!
What are you, an idiot?
In any case, we've accomplished our
first goal of gathering supplies!
Yes...
We're going to a place
called Yuba, was it?
Yes, but first is a
trek through the desert.
It will likely be much more difficult
than you imagine right now.
There's no telling what might happen.
One wrong step in this burning land,
and there's no guarantee you'll survive.
I'm still a little uneasy and unsure
about taking you to such a place,
but I want to return peace to this kingdom!
So I... So I ask you again!
Everyone! Please lend me your help!
I beg of you...
You finally said it.
We've been waiting for it!
There's no telling what happens on
the sea, either. Right, Vivi-chan?
Yeah! It'll be no different from before!
I can't wait to see the desert!
Alright, guys! Whadya say
we get going to Yuba now?!
Yeah!
Everyone...
Don't we seem to be missing someone?
Luffy!
This won't be enough at all!
That moron!
Even this sleepless town
has dozed off for now
From today forth,
something's going to change
I'm sure I can start fresh,
since I'm not alone
Just by having you by my side,
I feel I can become strong
I wonder how far I can go,
towards the place that leads to the future
Off in the distance it shines,
encompassing the world
Before dawn
Where in the world could Luffy have gone?
Uh oh! Hide! It's the Navy!
What's all the commotion?
Did something happen in town?!
Some idiot pirate must
be running around town.
Heya, guys!
It's you?!
Yikes! It's that copycat girl!
Crap! I'm outta here!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Heroes' Reunion!
His Name is Fire Fist Ace!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!