The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Yuba"              "Nanohana"   "Katorea"
Three years have passed since
a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
and a mighty swell.
Having returned to the
Alabasta Kingdom at long last,
Princess Vivi and Luffy's party
landed at the port town of Nanohana.
While hiding from
Baroque Works' assassins,
the group prepares for a trek across
the desert to stop the rebel army.
However, Luffy had rushed
ahead of everyone else
and found himself
lost outside of town.
"The Heroes' Reunion!
His Name is Fire Fist Ace!"
Oh, youngster!
I haven't seen you before!
Is this your first time in Alabasta?
Whadya say? Check out
this solid-gold apple!
Hold on!
Don't tell anyone,
but this is an incredible treasure
I found in some ancient ruins!
It's said one bite of this magic gold
apple will let you live 1000 years!
Sorry. I'm not interested
in living a thousand years.
I just need to live today.
--A solid-gold apple?!
--1000 years of life?!
For real?! For real?! You found
it in some ancient ruins?!
Yep, sure did! It's a legendary
artifact of an ancient civilization!
One bite and we can live 1000 years?!
Yep! It's the truth! I give you my word!
Awesome!
I see you have very sharp eyes!
In that case, I'll part with it for
the one-time price of 1000 Berries!
1000 Berries?! You got yourself a deal!
Honestly, now! What are you thinking?!
I wouldn't take him seriously if I were you.
Hey! Let go!
I was just about to live 1000
years for only 1000 Berries!
Quit wasting time and look for Luffy!
We're done shopping,
so we leave for the next town
the minute we find him!
Where did Luffy run off to, anyway?
Shut up, you two!
He's...
Just a quick question.
Have you seen this guy?
Huh?
Monkey D. Luffy?
He might be here in town. I've been
looking for him for a while now.
Hmm. Never seen him.
Oh, but if you're looking for someone,
ask at the restaurant up ahead.
The owner there knows a lot of people.
Much appreciated.
The restaurant, huh? I was
just feeling hungry, anyways.
Who's that? He looks incredibly strong.
Why's he looking for Luffy?
Maybe he's a bounty hunter?
No. He's not.
That mark...
As a former pirate-hunter,
there's no way I wouldn't recognize it.
No... It couldn't be!
It's wrong!
Selling a sword like this for 200,000
Berries is as good as swindling!
Do you even have a permit?!
It is her!
I didn't realize you were
Roronoa Zoro, and a pirate.
You... You lied to me!
A rogue like you can't be
allowed to own a renowned sword!
I'll collect your sword,
the legendary Wado Ichimonji!
What is that woman doing here?!
Never try this again!
Do you understand?!
What're you doing, Zoro?
Why're you hiding?
That woman spells nothing
but trouble! Dammit!
Hey. Tashigi.
Captain Smoker!
Small fry pirates.
They thought they could act
like big-shots around me,
so I took care of 'em.
Even in such a distant land, your
distaste for pirates is unfaltering!
If you got time for pointless chit-chat,
have the royal army take 'em!
Y-Yes, sir!
There doesn't seem to be any word yet
of Straw Hat Luffy having
come to this country.
But don't let your guard down.
They will show up. I'm sure of it.
Smoker? That's the Navy
captain from Loguetown!
Are you saying he followed us
all the way here from Loguetown?!
It would seem so.
And then there's that man...
Things could get ugly quick.
Where is that idiot?!
I'm hungry...
Oh! Thanks for this lunch, old guy!
That wasn't enough at all one bit...
Where's the town?!
Where in the world is the food place?!
Food!
Hey! What's going on? What happened?
Oh. It seems someone suddenly
died in the restaurant.
Suddenly died?!
He supposedly died in the middle
of a conversation with the owner!
He's a traveler.
We think he unwittingly ate a
Desert Strawberry while traveling...
A Desert Strawberry?
They're poisonous spiders that
look like red strawberries.
Eat one by accident, and you'll
suddenly keel over a few days later.
Contagious poison spreads through
your corpse a few hours after that,
so nobody can get close.
In the desert, what you
don't know can kill ya.
Just look! The way he's
still stuck holding the meat
is proof of just how powerful
the Desert Strawberry's poison is!
He came back to life!
A-Are you all right?
Oh, whoops.
I fell asleep.
You were asleep?!
Th-That's absurd! You were in the
middle of a conversation and a meal!
And now he's eating again!
What's all this commotion, anyway?
We were worried about you!
Does this restaurant do
comedy skits or something?
No, it's not like that.
But it's good you're alright.
Hey, now! Don't sleep again!
Aw, so he wasn't dead after all?
Just a false alarm...
That hit the spot!
Say, Mister.
Yeah?!
Has this guy been in town?
He's a pirate who wears a straw hat...
I'm impressed you're bold
enough to eat out in public...
...Second Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates...
...Portgas D. Ace.
Wh-Whitebeard?! The Whitebeard Pirates?!
That dimwit is one of the
Whitebeard Pirates?!
Come to think of it, I have seen
the mark on his back before!
That's the mark of
the Whitebeard Pirates!
What's he doing here?!
What is a famous, big-shot
pirate doing in this country?
I'm searching...
for my little brother!
Food place!
What is that?! There's a
weird smell in the way!
Oh! There's one! There's a food place!
So? What do you want from me?
To let me capture you quietly.
Nope. I think I'll pass.
Yeah, I figured.
I'm busy trying to find
another pirate at the moment.
To be honest, I have no
interest in taking you in.
Then just look the other way.
Can't.
Not as long as I'm a marine...
and you're a pirate.
That's a bland reason.
Let's have some fun.
Gum-Gum...
Rocket!
A food place! I finally found one!
Now I can eat! I'm starving!
Old guy! Food! Food! Food!
On the double!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Food! Food! Food!
Yum! This is such a yum food place!
Y-Yeah. Thanks. But...
Uhh, you should probably
run away while you can...
How come?
That guy that got sent flying
just now... Do you know who he is?
Huh? Who sent someone flying?
You did!
I did? Who went flying?
What's with these holes?
What a weird shop!
Is this your hobby, old guy?
You caused it!
I did? When?
Why, you--!
Who the hell did this?!
What the hell?!
What's the big idea?!
Oh! Sorry for disturbing your meal!
What idiot would do
something this crazy?!
Lu--!
Hey! Luf--!
Straw Hat!
I've been looking for you, Straw Hat!
So you did come to Alabasta!
Quit eating!
Isn't he...
You're finally here, Straw Hat Luffy...
Didn't I tell you you can't enter
the Grand Line unless you beat me?
What?! What?! What's going on?!
I ate the Plume-Plume Fruit.
So my body becomes smoke at will.
Gum-Gum Pistol!
You get it? You can't even
enter the Grand Line.
Didn't I tell you that?!
You're that smoke!
What're you doing here?!
Bastard...
Hold it!
Thank you for the meal!
Huh?
Halt!
Wait, Luffy! It's me!
Hey! Wait up! Hey! Luffy!
They ran off without paying...
This is bad! My Gum-Gum moves
don't work on that guy at all!
All I can do for now is run!
Tashigi!
Y-Yes, Captain Smoker?!
Do you want a towel?
This kingdom certainly is hot!
Catch that guy! It's Straw Hat!
Straw Hat?!
I'll stop him!
Tashigi! Gather the marines at once!
Search every square inch of
this town for Straw Hat's crew!
Yes, sir!
People with powers are fighting!
Whoa!
Straw Hat's crew! That means...
Roronoa Zoro is in this city!
White Snake!
Straw Hat! Why did you
come to this kingdom?!
What are you after?!
What am I after? I'm here to
beat up a guy named Crocodile!
What?! Crocodile?!
How are you and Crocodile connected?!
He disappeared!
Bastard thinks he's crafty!
Straw Hat!
Where could Luffy-san have gone?
Geez! He's always such
a high-maintenance captain!
Oh! Nami-san!
Hey, now! This is bad!
It feels like we'll be in big trouble
if we don't get moving quick!
Big trouble?
The Navy is here.
The Navy?!
And a strange man!
Let's just find Luffy as quickly
as possible and leave town!
Hey! Hide!
--What for?!
--What is it?!
Get back here!
The Navy!
There seems to be a big commotion!
Don't let him escape! After him!
Some idiot pirate must be
running around town or something.
Idiot pirate?!
Get back here, Straw Hat!
It's you?!
Heya! Zoro!
Oh! Is that where you guys are?!
You idiot! Go get rid of them first!
There's the Straw Hat crew! Over there!
So, what should we do now?!
--We have to run, obviously!
--Hurry! To the ship!
What're you doing?! Let's get back!
Hey, you!
--Stop!
--Don't let them escape!
Fall back!
Captain!
Straw Hat is mine!
Yikes! Yikes! Here he comes!
White Blow!
Uh oh!
There's no escape!
Heat Haze!
You, huh?
Give it up.
You may be smoke, but I'm fire.
A fight between your power
and mine would never end.
He had Devil Fruit powers?!
Who is he, anyways?!
Why is he helping us?!
Ace?!
You haven't changed a bit, Luffy.
Ace?! Is that you, Ace?!
You ate a Devil Fruit?!
Yep! The Flare-Flare Fruit!
Captain Smoker!
We're securing the perimeter!
Anyways, we can't chat like this!
I'll catch up! You guys run!
I'll hold these guys off!
--Go!
--Let's go!
Yeah!
But, Luffy!
Who is that guy?!
I don't get it.
Why are you helping Straw Hat?
It's natural for a big brother to
worry about his bungling kid brother.
What? Brother? You mean to say--?
Move, Portgas D. Ace!
I'm afraid that's a no-can-do.
Wait, Luffy! Who is he?!
Is he an acquaintance of yours?!
Yeah!
He's my brother!
Brother?!
Even this sleepless town
has dozed off for now
From today forth,
something's going to change
I'm sure I can start fresh,
since I'm not alone
Just by having you by my side,
I feel I can become strong
I wonder how far I can go,
towards the place that leads to the future
Off in the distance it shines,
encompassing the world
Before dawn
Guys! This is my brother, Ace! Say hi!
This sensible man can't
possibly be your brother!
I would've expected him to
be as reckless as Luffy!
He's a nice guy who
cares about his brother!
Brothers can be so wonderful!
The sea is just full of surprises.
Come now, everyone!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Ace and Luffy!
Hot Emotions and Brotherly Bonds"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!